<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>You can't cancel her; She quits!</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/music/story/2021-03-18/lana-del-rey-chemtrails-over-the-country-club-album</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following some headline-making media flubs, Lana Del Rey asserts herself as a once-in-a-generation songwriter on "Chemtrails Over the Country Club."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic pummels privacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pandemics-unexpected-privacy-pitfalls-be10b55e-1a60-4ea1-a469-4cfd5e1df69b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving our entire lives online has been a lifesaver in some ways but a privacy nightmare in others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POST-COVID HOLLYWOOD FOREVER CHANGED...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/entertainment-industry/working-in-hollywood-after-covid-19-1234932406/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working in entertainment may never look the same again. To hear numerous executives tell it, the past 12 months have shifted the paradigm for modern office life. Gone are the days of staying tether…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herschel Walker Scrutinized Ahead of Senate Decision; Wild Conspiracy Theories...</title>
      <link>https://thebulwark.com/get-ready-for-the-herschel-walker-experience/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia Republicans get ready for the next phase of the Trump Wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentaries changing public opinion about celebs -- with consequences even filmmakers didn't expect...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Documentaries-are-changing-public-opinion-about-16038326.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmakers Kirby Dick and Amy Ziering knew their documentary series</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio closes beaches...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-rio-janeiro-closes-beaches-132211756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beaches of Brazilian city Rio de Janeiro will be closed this weekend, according to a municipal decree enacted on Friday, as the local government seeks to stem the spread of the COVID-19 pandemic. Even with a rising number of infections and deaths in Brazil's second-largest city, residents have flocked to the breaches, especially on sunny weekends. Rio de Janeiro's hospitals reached 95% capacity on Thursday, as patients' admissions to intensive care units soared over the past few days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem introduces resolution to expel Marjorie Taylor Greene...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/544009-democrat-introduces-resolution-to-expel-greene</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Jimmy Gomez (D-Calif.) on Friday formally introduced a resolution to expel Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) from Congress over her past indications of support for violence against prominent Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-wife of Trump Org executive has spoken to investigators 'multiple times'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/ex-wife-trump-org-executive-has-spoken-investigators-multiple-times-n1261459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Weisselberg said it appears investigators have been seeking information about her former father-in-law, Allen Weisselberg, the company’s CFO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cramer Rages at Young Bankers Complaining About Work Conditions: 'SHAME is What Makes Good Associate!'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/cnbcs-jim-cramer-rages-at-young-bankers-complaining-about-work-conditions-shame-is-what-makes-a-good-goldman-sachs-associate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young Goldman Sachs associates are complaining about grueling work conditions, but one prominent alum of the financial behemoth has little sympathy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Caliphate' or not, Islamic State expands its reach...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210319-caliphate-or-not-islamic-state-expands-its-reach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Caliphate' or not, Islamic State expands its reach</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Magic Mushrooms Heal? Oregon Blazing Psychedelic Trail...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/18/oregon-is-blazing-a-psychedelic-trail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Kate Brown of Oregon announced the members of the state’s newly formed Psilocybin Advisory Board this week. Why does</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: TX Customer Who Refused To Wear Mask Stabs Fast Food Restaurant Manager...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/19/texas-customer-refused-wear-mask-stabs-fast-food-manager/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hunt is on in Texas for a man who allegedly stabbed a restaurant manager several times after he was told to wear a mask inside a Jack in the Box restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission to clean up space debris set for launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/19/business/space-junk-mission-astroscale-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A demonstration mission to test new technology developed by the company Astroscale to clean up space debris is set to launch in the early hours of Saturday from the Baikonur Cosmodrome in Kazakhstan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Cuomo joked he wanted to 'mount' female staffer like a dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/new-york-elections-government/ny-new-yorker-ronan-farrow-lindsey-boylan-cuomo-20210319-oaxbupmmnfa3vehdgfh52rdgzy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindsey Boylan — whose claims about the governor in a Medium post in February was the first of a series of allegations about his inappropriate behavior — told New Yorker writer Ronan Farrow that the incident happened in February 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest who presided over inauguration mass under investigation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/543983-priest-who-presided-over-biden-inauguration-mass-under-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A priest who presided over an inaugural mass for President Biden in January is currently under investigation regarding inappropriate behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Sandbags Staffers, Sidelines Dozens for Pot Use...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-white-house-sandbags-staffers-024922667.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast/ Photos GettyDozens of young White House staffers have been suspended, asked to resign or placed in a remote work program due to past marijuana use, frustrating staffers who were pleased by initial indications from the Biden administration that recreational use of cannabis would not be immediately disqualifying for would-be personnel, according to three people familiar with the situation.The policy has even affected staffers whose marijuana use was exclusive to one of the 14 states—and the District of Columbia—where cannabis is legal. Sources familiar with the matter also said a number of young staffers were either put on probation or canned because they revealed past marijuana use in an official document they filled out as part of the lengthy background check for a position in the Biden White House.In some cases, staffers were informally told by transition higher-ups ahead of formally joining the administration that they would likely overlook some past marijuana use, only to be asked later to resign.“There were one-on-one calls with individual affected staffers—rather, ex-staffers,” one former White House staffer affected by the policy told The Daily Beast. “I was asked to resign.”“Nothing was ever explained” on the calls, they added, which were led by White House director of management and administration Anne Filipic. “The policies were never explained, the threshold for what was excusable and what was inexcusable was never explained.”In February, NBC News reported the White House intended—for some candidates—to waive the requirement that all potential appointees in the Executive Office of the President be able to obtain a “Top Secret” clearance. The rules about past marijuana use and eligibility for the clearance vary, depending on the agency: for the FBI, an applicant can’t have used marijuana in the past three years; at the NSA, it’s only one. The White House, however, largely calls its own shots, and officials at the time told NBC News that as long as past use was “limited” and the candidate wasn’t pursuing a position that required a security clearance, past use may be excused.Asked about the policy and its effect on the administration’s staffing, a White House spokesperson disputed the number of affected staff, but said the Biden administration is “committed to bringing the best people into government—especially the young people whose commitment to public service can deepen in these positions,” and noted that the White House’s approach to past marijuana use is much more flexible than previous administrations.“The White House’s policy will maintain the absolute highest standards for service in government that the president expects from his administration, while acknowledging the reality that state and local marijuana laws have changed significantly across the country in recent years,” the spokesperson added. “This decision was made following intensive consultation with career security officials and will effectively protect our national security while modernizing policies to ensure that talented and otherwise well-qualified applicants with limited marijuana use will not be barred from serving the American people.”A candidate’s personal drug history, barring past convictions for possession, is largely based on the honor system, as well as supplemental interviews with family and friends by the FBI—although lying on the 136-page SF-86 form is a felony, and effectively bars a candidate from ever working for a federal agency. Over the years, some rules have been relaxed or altogether eliminated (the existence of nude photos of a candidate are no longer automatically disqualifying, for example).Some of these dismissals, probations and remote work appointments could have potentially been a result of inconsistencies that came up during the background check process, where a staffer could have, for example, misstated the last time they used marijuana. The effect of the policy, however, would be the same: the Biden White House would be punishing various staffers for violating thresholds of past cannabis use that would-be staffers didn’t know about.Previous drug use can pose problems for obtaining a security clearance. While practices across the federal government vary, in general agencies may consider the type, frequency, and recency of drug use as mitigating factors when granting a clearance.Past Pot Smoking Won’t Bar Some Applicants From White House RolesThe Biden administration has attempted to modernize the White House’s personnel policy as it relates to past marijuana use, which has disproportionately affected younger appointees and those from states where marijuana has been decriminalized or legalized. (Marijuana, of course, remains illegal in the eyes of the federal government.) The number of allowable instances of past marijuana use was increased from the Trump and Obama administrations—a reflection of the drug’s widespread use—and the White House approved limited exemptions for candidates whose positions don’t require security clearances. Those employees, like all those at the White House, must commit to not using marijuana while serving in the federal government and must submit to random drug testing.The president, however, remains the final authority on who can receive a clearance, and the chief executive can overrule agency judgments on eligibility, as President Donald Trump did when he granted his son-in-law Jared Kushner a top secret clearance over the objections of the intelligence community and his own counsel.“I find it absurd that, in 2021, marijuana use is still part of a security clearance background check,” Tommy Vietor, a veteran of the 2008 Obama team who subsequently worked as a National Security Council spokesperson, said on Thursday. “To me, marijuana use is completely irrelevant when you’re trying to decide whether an individual should be trusted with national security information.”In past administrations, White House staff have also had their applications denied, or the jobs they’d started abruptly yanked, because of marijuana use. In the earliest days of the Trump era, multiple people—some mid-tier, some more senior-level—had jobs they had already accepted pulled by White House brass after flunking urine tests that showed signs of recent marijuana use, according to a person with knowledge of the matter.The marijuana policy has tripped up the appointments of even senior White House officials in past administrations. Ben Rhodes, a former deputy national security adviser in the Obama White House, wrote in his memoir that his interim security clearance was initially denied because of past marijuana use. Alyssa Mastromonaco, who served as deputy chief of staff for operations in the Obama administration and has a self-described “love of the ganj,” wrote in Vice in 2017 that, after filling out her SF-86, she “went home and flushed all the pot I had stashed in my underwear drawer.”In the end, Mastromonaco was allowed to join the administration, she wrote, “but I was randomly drug-tested pretty much once a month for the first year, and regularly after that.”But would-be staffers in the Biden administration whose dream jobs were derailed by an opaque system now feel their own truthfulness has been used against them.“It’s exclusively targeting younger staff and staff who came from states where it was legal,” the former staffer said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You better know who's behind the curtain': The man who guided Josh Hawley's rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/govt-and-politics/you-better-know-who-s-behind-the-curtain-the-man-who-guided-josh-hawley-s/article_5df53e0c-9bdc-59cc-b927-e3cc8f1a5770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawley’s critics see the influence of Timmy Teepell and other consultants in the senator’s defiant approach following the Jan. 6 Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiery Start to U.S.-China Talks Shows Acrimony Here to Stay...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/fiery-start-to-us-china-talks-shows-acrimony-is-here-to-stay/ar-BB1eKRDO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first face-to-face meeting between the U.S. and China since President Joe Biden took office was bound to be confrontational. The question now is whether the two sides can find a way cooperate after unloading so many grievances in public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-woman watchdog torments far right in deep-red Northern California...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/a-one-woman-watchdog-torments-the-far-right-in-deep-red-northern-california/article_d603d672-a6ef-5349-b734-6b5305db4db4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. — Only halfway into the endless plague year, the most outspoken journalist in one of California’s most conservative counties had already tangled with the sheriff, the local megachurch,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland 'World's Happiest Country' Despite Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/finland-world-s-happiest-country-despite-pandemic-report-01616150104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 has done little to alter the ranking of the world's happiest countries, with Finland at the top for a fourth year running, an annual UN-sponsored report said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist behind vaccine says next target is cancer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-world-news-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-d6fd143e9fd9b4bd50d0c1cb697b6dab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The scientist who won the race to deliver the first widely used coronavirus vaccine says people can rest assured the shots are safe, and the technology behind it will soon be used to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Final Polls Show Another Election Night Stalemate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israels-final-polls-show-another-election-night-stalemate/ar-BB1eKiRz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last polls before Israel’s March 23 national vote point to another inconclusive outcome on election night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces onslaught of legal problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Legal-woes-trail-Trump-beyond-the-White-House-16034848.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The district attorney is sifting through millions of pages of his tax records. The state...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selling Art to Pay Bills Divides Nation's Museum Directors...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/19/selling-art-to-pay-the-bills-divides-the-nations-museum-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It started as a stopgap measure to respond to the pandemic, a temporary two-year loosening of an Association of Art</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Illegal Rave Scene Thrives During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/19/how-the-illegal-rave-scene-thrives-during-the-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On New Year’s Eve, Sam Adeelmirza, the event organizer known as Sam Black, still felt cagey about attending a dance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears considering tell-all Oprah interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/entertainment/news/britney-spears-is-considering-a-tell-all-oprah-interview/ar-BB1eKxeq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Off the back of the success of the Britney documentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Erupts in Fury Over Biden 'Putin Killer' Comment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/18/europe/biden-putin-killer-comment-russia-reaction-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin has reacted angrily to US President Joe Biden's remarks that Russian leader Vladimir Putin is "a killer," calling the comment unprecedented and describing the relationship between the two countries as "very bad."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal defendants still cite 'gene for violence.' It doesn't exist...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-criminal-defendants-still-cite-a-e2-80-98gene-for-violence-e2-80-99-it-doesn-e2-80-99t-exist/ar-BB1eJcLd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Mexico Supreme Court missed a chance last month to end the controversy — and affirm scientific consensus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog FINALLY adopted after 450 days in shelter...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/sweet-dog-named-max-finds-a-new-home-after-year-and-half-in-shelters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Max, a 5-year-old pit bull mix, is finally living The Good Life with a kind-hearted man named Ed near a lake in central New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gave newspaper her Social Security number, phone numbers, addresses...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/private-investigator-says-sun-paid-215018915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sun hired a famous private investigator to get information on Meghan Markle. He says he accessed her phone and Social Security numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry suing SUN and MIRROR over separate hacking claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/04/media/prince-harry-suing-sun-daily-mirror-gbr-intl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tabloid PI Tells of Shady Hunt for Meghan Markle Scoops...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/amp/uk-56444635</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An LA-based investigator tells BBC News he unlawfully obtained her social security number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danno Digs The Dirt!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/private-investigator-admits-illegally-spying-221500290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A private investigator is revealing that a British tabloid paid him large sums of money to spy on Meghan Markle at the onset of her relationship with Prince Harry. Daniel Portley-Hanks, who is now a retired private investigator out of Los Angeles, was hired by The Sun to obtain private information about Markle, now the Duchess of Sussex, The New York Times reported on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers clash during emotional hearing:  'I am not a virus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/I-am-not-a-virus-Lawmakers-clash-during-16037119.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Two days after an Atlanta-area shooting left eight dead, including six Asian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man With Gun And Ammo Arrested Outside VP Kamala Harris's Residence Told Police He Was 'looking for help'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Texas-man-arrested-outside-vice-president-s-16037030.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A Texas man arrested outside the vice president's residence on Wednesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Poverty-violence-and-fresh-hope-under-Biden-16036943.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - Omliver doesn't know who Joe Biden is. Nor does he know anything about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of 'digital dictatorship' as Myanmar deploys AI...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210318130045-zsgja</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters fear they are being tracked by cameras armed with facial recognition technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted NEW YORK TIMES reporter slams newsroom's culture: 'Mean, spiteful, vengeful place'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/mar/18/ousted-new-york-times-reporter-slams-newsrooms-cul/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Times reporter Donald McNeil, who was forced out earlier this year for using the n-word in a conversation, describes the paper’s newsroom atmosphere as a tense and accusatory one that he compares to the communist dictatorship in North Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEEN VOGUE Editor Out After Old Racist Tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/teen-vogues-new-eic-alexi-mccammond-out-after-backlash-over-old-racist-tweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Condé-owned outlet’s new editor has exited the job just days before she was set to take on the gig.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIRD WAVE WRECKS SPRING</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2538922/paris-covid-lockdown-month-16-regions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS will be plunged into a four-week lockdown from midnight tomorrow as a third wave of Covid hits France’s capital. The country’s prime minister Jean Castex announced a month-long lo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANA DEL REY 'MASTERPIECE' WITH 'CHEMTRAILS OVER COUNTRY CLUB'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/03/18/lana-del-rey-delivers-a-pop-masterpiece-with-hit-laden-hypnotic-new-chemtrails-over-the-country-club</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know you’re in for something unusual in 2021 when an album’s title track starts with this couplet: “I’m on the run with you, my sweet love There’s nothing wrong co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Post-Trump Slowdown, Old Gray Lady Eyes Games Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/facing-post-trump-slowdown-new-york-times-eyes-24100-billion-games-market/ar-BB1eIBtG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran of FarmVille and Words With Friends looks to entice more subscribers with non-news diversions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem sheriff on border: 'It's basically open'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/18/texas-sheriff-at-us-mexico-border-says-its-basically-open/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HIDALGO COUNTY, Texas — A sheriff whose county sits on the Mexican border said the new surge of migrants essentially has an open door into the United States — and he believes the “crisis” will only…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAGES OF ZOOM SCHOOL: LONELY KIDS, STRESSED PARENTS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/children-are-lonely-parents-are-stressed-cdc-study-finds-remote-learning-taking-a-devastating-toll-194106405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings confirm previous research into the deleterious emotional and physical effects of keeping children out of school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS LOCKED FOR MONTH</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210318191921-tnox7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Paris goes into lockdown as COVID-19 variant rampages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building INSTAGRAM For Kids -- Under 13...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/facebook-instagram-for-children-under-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We have identified youth work as a priority for Instagram and have added it to our H1 priority list,” reads an internal Instagram post obtained by BuzzFeed News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Prosecutor Demoted for Delivering Food for DOORDASH -- During Business Hours!</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/03/18/bucks-county-first-assistant-district-attorney-demoted-for-delivering-food-for-doordash-during-business-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gregg Shore was the county's first assistant district attorney, but the DA recently found out Shore was delivering food for DoorDash too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Face Is Not Your Own...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2021/03/18/magazine/facial-recognition-clearview-ai.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a secretive start-up scraped the internet to build a facial-recognition tool, it tested a legal and ethical limit — and blew the future of privacy in America wide open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff's office sorry for 'bad day' comment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/sheriff-s-office-regret-any-heartache-bad-day-comment-after-n1261447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Capt. Jay Baker drew widespread criticism for saying the suspect in shootings that left eight dead "was fed up, at the end of his rope" and "had a bad day."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of talks, Shanghai cops beat up American students...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/ahead-of-talks-chinese-police-beat-up-u-s-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese authorities’ harassment of Americans in China has started to take a similarly disturbing turn this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George W. Bush:  'I was sick to my stomach'...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/24/texas-tribune-george-w-bush/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president's comments came during an interview that was part of this year's virtual SXSW programming and kicked off Bush's promotional tour of his new book, "Out of Many, One: Portraits of America's Immigrants."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel may have left pandemic behind for good!</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/coronavirus-disease-recedes-as-ministers-discuss-fate-of-the-airport-662389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;*Daily cases, serious patients and R rate at the lowest in months. *More restrictions to be lifted on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia proposes app to document sexual consent...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/australia-proposes-app-to-document-sexual-consent-but-experts-say-it-misinterprets-the-circumstances-of-sexual-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL finalizes new 11-year media rights deal: Worth over $100 billion!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/18/nfl-media-rights-deal-2023-2033-amazon-gets-exclusive-thursday-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new agreement runs through 2033 and will feature two Super Bowls returning to Disney's ABC network channel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasty drought worsens for much of USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/water-use-weather-california-agriculture-united-states-b24a2a60ae320df2fb245e4f215aeb5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With nearly two-thirds of the United States abnormally dry or worse, the government’s spring forecast offers little hope for relief, especially in the West where a devastating megadrought has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE SHUT FOR MONTH</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/paris-month-coronavirus-lockdown-e6fab602-eb13-4ce1-a14c-9a74d704dca0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the third lockdown for France's capital city since the start of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sells fart for $85, cashing in on NFT craze...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/18/nyc-man-sells-fart-for-85-cashing-in-on-nft-craze/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’re darn tootin’ you read that correctly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun sales to Asian Americans surge...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/18/gun-sales-to-asian-americans-surge-amid-spate-of-hate-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian Americans are stocking up on guns amid the surge in hate crimes targeting them since the onset of the coronavirus pandemic, a report said Thursday. Though police have stepped up patrols in As…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan 6 Capitol Siege TV Series Planned From Anti-Trump Director...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/capitol-assault-showtime-series-january-6-the-comey-rule-billy-ray-shane-salerno-1234717205/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime is set to develop an untitled limited series from The Comey Rule cohorts Billy Ray and Shane Salerno that will trace the events that led to the January 6 assault on the U.S. Capitol. Whipp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Star QB Watson faces 3 sex misconduct suits...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/houston-texans-quarterback-deshaun-watson-faces-three-sexual-misconduct-suits-n1261411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I have never treated any woman with anything other than the utmost respect," he said in a tweet after the first civil suit was filed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE:  Some Ghislaine Maxwell Details Too 'Sensational,' 'Impure' to Be Made Public...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/judge-rules-some-ghislaine-maxwell-details-are-too-sensational-and-impure-to-be-revealed-to-the-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge in Manhattan on Thursday ruled on a series of redactions proposed by Ghislaine Maxwell and prosecutors in regards to a compilation of transcripts submitted under seal by the Government last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone tablet marking First Amendment leaves DC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/constitutions-philadelphia-museums-freedom-of-speech-united-states-d86ac3b25a1bafe0becc48f5baad5d97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — A four-story, 50-ton marble tablet engraved with the text of the First Amendment, previously displayed on the facade of the now-shuttered Newseum in Washington, will find a new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN Flight Delayed 8 Hours After Crew Robbed At Gunpoint...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/17/costa-rica-miami-american-airlines-robbery-flight-delayed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Costa Rica to Miami American Airlines flight was delayed seven and a half hours on Tuesday after the Miami-based crew van to the airport was stopped on the road, and the crew was robbed at gunpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Bullets to Back: Striking silence around cop killing in small-town CO...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/crime/3-bullets-to-the-back-part-one-zach-gifford/73-65208a42-6113-4b8c-9a61-92242635c68d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a 3-part story about a police killing in rural Kiowa County and the reluctance of a pro-law community to hold law enforcement accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly more likely to catch virus a 2nd time...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/18/elderly-more-likely-to-catch-covid-second-time-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People over 65 who have recovered from COVID-19 have a 50-50 chance of a second attack within six months of their first illness, a new study has found. The odds are much better for younger, healthi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child dies after PELOTON treadmill accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2537523/peloton-warning-tread-accident-child-died/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PELOTON has issued a warning after a child allegedly died in a Tread+ accident as parents are told to keep kids away from the exercise equipment. The company has told parents to keep children and p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruises Coming Back -- With or Without CDC Blessing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/cruises-for-americans-are-coming-back%E2%80%94with-or-without-cdc-blessing/ar-BB1eIFGZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crystal is tweaking the “cruise to nowhere” formula with Bahamas-only itineraries and on-ship Covid-testing labs. But first, you’ll need to get vaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why bands are disappearing: 'Young people arent excited by them'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/mar/18/why-bands-are-disappearing-young-people-arent-excited-by-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maroon 5’s Adam Levine was scoffed at for suggesting there ‘aren’t any bands any more’ – but if you look at the numbers, he’s right. Wolf Alice, Maximo Park and industry insiders ask why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  THREE new lifeforms 'unknown to science' have been found on the ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2537213/three-lifeforms-unknown-science-discovered-iss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THREE entirely new lifeforms have been discovered at different locations onboard the International Space Station. A team of US and Indian scientists studied four strains of bacteria found on the or…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect isn't first to blame 'sex addiction' for heinous crimes. But scientists are dubious...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-atlanta-suspect-isnt-the-first-to-blame-sex-addiction-for-heinous-crimes-but-scientists-are-dubious/ar-BB1eIs3G?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Aaron Long, 21, isn't the first high-profile defendant to blame a "sex addiction," but some researchers say the type of treatment he reportedly sought can actually make psychological problems worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asians organize in wake of Atlanta attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asian-americans-wake-of-atlanta-attacks-1731404048730b467d2b45944ad2c661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian Americans were already worn down by a year of pandemic-fueled racist attacks when a white gunman was charged with killing eight people, most of them Asian women, at three Atlanta-area...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man missing since tsunami 16 years ago 'found in psychiatric hospital'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/policeman-missing-boxing-day-tsunami-23751131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police believe they have found Zainal Abidin, known as Asep, who was one of tens of thousands of people missing after the 2004 Boxing Day tsunami that hit Aceh, Indonesia killing a staggering 230,000 people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahomans Say 'Liberal' Donald Won't Convince Them to Get Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/oklahoma-diner-customers-tell-cnn-they-wont-get-vaccinated-even-if-trump-told-them-to-why-listen-to-a-liberal-new-yorker-like-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oklahoma diner customers unanimously tell CNN they won't get vaccinated, some refuse even if Trump told them to get the shot: Why listen to a ‘liberal New Yorker?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angelina Jolie Claims 'Proof' of Alleged Domestic Violence Against Brad Pitt...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/angelina-jolie-claims-she-has-proof-of-alleged-domestic-violence-against-brad-pitt-in-new-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to court records, the actress also filed a document regarding testimony of their minor children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly Woman Who Clobbered Attacker Talks About Assault In San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/18/elderly-asian-woman-beats-up-man-attacking-her-in-san-francisco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elderly woman being attacked on Market St. in San Francisco Wednesday - the latest victim in a wave of attacks on Asians in the Bay Area - turned the tables on her assailant, leaving him with injuries that required a trip to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
