<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DOUBTS ON EXPLANATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Circumstances-of-Jamal-Khashoggi-s-death-will-not-13322985.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL - A spokesman for President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's ruling party vowed Saturday that Turkey would "uncover what has happened" to Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi, hours after Saudi authorities said that the Washington Post contributing columnist had been killed earlier this month during a fistfight inside the Saudi Consulate in Istanbul. The Saudi explanation - that an argument in the consulate led to a fatal brawl - is at odds with the conclusions of Turkish investigators, who believe that Khashoggi was deliberately killed by a team of Saudi agents who were dispatched to Istanbul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Half million' rally in London for new Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tens-thousands-rally-london-brexit-vote-004938246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU flag waving Britons rejecting a future outside Europe packed the heart of London on Saturday for an anti-Brexit protest organisers said drew more than half a million people. The police gave no figures for how many showed up for the massive march and rally outside parliament aimed at pressing the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Reno, boomtown resurgence leads to housing crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/reno-boomtown-resurgence-leads-housing-154217675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. (AP) — They were the toast of Reno in the 1950s, when the growing casino industry sparked a boom that for a time turned northern Nevada into the West's top gambling destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Indicts Woman Who Tried to Block Afghan Man's Deportation on Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/20/world/europe/sweden-elin-ersson-deportation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors said Elin Ersson had violated the Swedish aviation act by remaining standing on takeoff. But she vowed to continue her campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Candidates Struggling in Key Battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/20/us/politics/republican-governors-congress-midterms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Party leaders worry that candidates for governor and Senate are in trouble in Michigan, Illinois, Minnesota, Pennsylvania and possibly Wisconsin, and that difficulties could spill into House races.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnitude 4.0 earthquake shakes Texas, Oklahoma panhandles...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/texas/article/Magnitude-4-0-earthquake-shakes-Texas-Oklahoma-13323017.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMARILLO, Texas (AP) - An earthquake has shaken parts of the Texas and Oklahoma panhandles. The U.S. Geological Survey says the 4.0 magnitude earthquake was recorded at 8:04 a.m. Saturday about 9 miles (15 kilometers) north-northeast of Amarillo. The temblor was recorded at a depth of 3 miles (5 kilometers). There were no immediate reports of damage or injuries. Geologists say damage isn't likely in quakes of magnitude 4.0. Thousands of earthquakes have been recorded in Oklahoma in recent years, with many linked to the underground injection of wastewater from oil and natural gas production. Scientists have also linked earthquakes in Kansas, Texas and other states to wastewater injection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL THEY TURN BACK?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181020165252-ccbx7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CARAVAN (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-U.S.-bound migrant caravan stuck on Guatemalan border with Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big numbers of illegals arriving at AZ border...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/arizona-news/big-numbers-of-central-americans-arriving-at-arizona-border-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large groups of Central American migrants continue to surrender to Border Patrol agents in Arizona with the arrival of one recent group numbering 108 captured in dramatic video images, authorities said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside notorious 'serpent church' where devotees die from grabbing rattlesnakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7512634/inside-snake-church-kentucky/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the nail-biting moment a pastor drinks fatal poison while holding up a deadly rattlesnake with his bare hands – and miraculously survives.  As the deadly strychnine, which can cause m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob Assaults Gay Journalist at Gillum Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/10/angry-democrat-mob-assaults-gay-journalist-at-andrew-gillum-rally-jobsnotmobs-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot gets 92 TINDER matches in 2 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/usa/441792-sex-robot-tinder-harmony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people go on dating apps for some human warmth now and then – for some, though, 'human' isn’t necessarily part of the equation. A realistic sex robot has garnered almost a hundred matches on Tinder in just two hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California growing shadow looms over Nevada races...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/californias-growing-shadow-looms-over-nevadas-midterms-152851133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — The Republicans running in Nevada's hotly contested races for governor and U.S. Senate are taking aim at a common target as they try to maintain GOP control of the seats: California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lioness kills father of her 3 cubs at Indianapolis Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/20/us/indianapolis-zoo-lion-dead/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lioness killed the father of her three cubs at the Indianapolis Zoo this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN host invites congressman to body slam him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/412377-cnns-chris-cuomo-invites-gianforte-to-bodyslam-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN host Chris Cuomo on Friday invited Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto campaign sued for spam texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/election/article220344070.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politics: Campaign of Beto O’Rourke, who is running for Senate against Ted Cruz, is facing a class action lawsuit by a Collin County resident who says the organization sent him text messages without permission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign mode revives fiery immigration talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/138443b2ba4646ad8f2b3abf4837bf00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. (AP) — Donald Trump fueled his 2016 campaign with fiery immigration rhetoric, visions of hordes flowing across the border to assault Americans and steal their jobs. Now, in the final weeks before midterm elections, he's back at it as he looks to stave off Democratic gains in Congress. It's an approach that offers both risks and rewards. He could energize Democratic foes as well as the Republicans he wants to rouse to the polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/19/tulsi-gabbard-2020-presidential-bid-917418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gabbard became a darling of the left in 2016 when she resigned as a DNC vice chair after fighting against the primary debate schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie, Kamala set to criss-cross Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412334-sanders-harris-set-to-criss-cross-iowa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego No. 1 booziest city...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/business/tourism/sd-fi-sandiego-booziest-cities-20181020-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on an analysis of average annual expenditures on booze, San Diego tops the list of metro areas of tipsiest cities in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing broadens propaganda drive to heartland America...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinese-broadens-propaganda-drive-heartland-132238597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — China's propaganda machine has taken aim at American soybean farmers as part of its high-stakes trade war with the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks on public figures growing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/412273-attacks-on-public-figures-are-growing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of protection, there is no room for error and in today’s threat matrix. There is little lack of imagination concerning what a threat could be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasive 'Spotted Lanternfly' Threatening Christmas Tree Crop...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/10/19/spotted-lanternfly-christmas-trees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With wings coated in black and red spots and a body of bold yellow, the spotted lanternfly could soon be hitching a ride home with you from the farm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Confronted at Restaurant by Angry Customers...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/10/20/senator-mitch-mcconnell-confronted-restaurant-protesters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Mitch McConnell was confronted at restaurant by protesters who threw his doggie bag out the door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi cursed out by protesters in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/20/nancy-pelosi-cursed-out-by-protesters-in-florida/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi was hounded by a group of protesters in Florida — with some cursing and calling her a “communist.” Video of the confrontation shows the small gr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 DAYS LATER: Candles, flashlights, no AC in Florida's hurricane zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/candles-flashlights-no-ac-floridas-hurricane-zone-123055049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PANAMA CITY, Fla. (AP) — More than 100,000 Florida customers are still without power due to Hurricane Michael, which tore into the Florida Panhandle more than a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors blast CDC...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/as-afm-illness-strikes-dozens-of-children-doctors-say-cdc/article_4debc074-5f93-5d4b-9d61-1750bf88729d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — LaMay Axton watched in horror as her granddaughter Cambria stumbled and toppled over as she ran into the kitchen of their house. The 2-year-old tried to stand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey won't allow 'cover-up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/086a03cd1b4d44b0a1d06263e353c092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey will "never allow a cover-up" of the killing of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi in Saudi Arabia's consulate in Istanbul, a senior official in Turkey's ruling party said Saturday after Saudi Arabia announced hours earlier that the writer died during a "fistfight" in its consulate. The critical reaction by Numan Kurtulmus, deputy head of the Justice and Development Party, suggested that Turkey, which started its own investigation amid pro-government media reports that a Saudi hit squad killed Khashoggi, was not prepared to go along with the Saudi version of what happened to the writer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudist beach surfer punches shark to escape attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nudist-beach-surfer-punches-shark-escape-attack-070339086.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surfer who got bitten by a shark at an Australian nudist beach managed to make his break for freedom after punching the creature until it let him go, he said Saturday. Paul Kenny was riding the waves off Samurai Beach, a naturist spot 200 kilometres (125 miles) north of Sydney, when he accidentally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: 63 Remains of Fetuses Found at Second Detroit Funeral Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2018/10/19/fetuses-perry-funeral-home-detroit/1702594002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the grisly total, there were 36 fetuses stored in boxes and another 27 found in freezers, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Drowning in Chinese Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/vancouver-is-drowning-in-chinese-money#gs.72Padkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vancouver was the first place to experience the tidal wave of Chinese cash. Now the city is leading efforts to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands turn out for anti-Brexit protest in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8ce2135b264e49e59614ff87d1ea0014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thousands of protesters were gathering in central London on Saturday to call for a second referendum on Britain's exit from the European Union. London Mayor Sadiq Khan was among those set to address the People's Vote March, which culminates at a rally in Parliament Square. Organizers expect the protest to be the biggest of its kind, with about 150 buses ferrying thousands of activists from across the country to the capital. Britons voted to leave the trade bloc by a narrow margin in the 2016 EU membership referendum. Prime Minister Theresa May has ruled out another public vote on the subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b913157e71ec4730b414b357758a450c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MESA, Ariz. (AP) — President Donald Trump, seeking to frame the choices for voters in the midterm elections, said Friday that Democrats are "too extreme and too dangerous" to take control of Congress. On a three-day swing out West to make his closing arguments for Republican candidates, Trump sought to hone in on immigration as one of the defining election issues this fall by falsely accusing Democrats of wanting "open borders" and encouraging illegal immigration. "Anybody who votes for a Democrat now is crazy," Trump said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL THEY TURN BACK?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181020015542-5zzjs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CARAVAN (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Migrant caravan halted on Mexico-Guatemala border, pressure to turn back mounts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil election battle rages over FACEBOOK's WhatsApp...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181019225559-3eodi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Brazil election battle rages over Facebook's WhatsApp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORMS MEXICO BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/honduran-migrants-gather-mexico-border-despite-trump-threats-164133863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of migrants forced their way through Guatemala's northwestern border Friday and flooded onto a bridge leading to Mexico, where riot police battled them back, halting their trek toward the United States -- at least temporarily. The caravan of mainly Honduran migrants, whose journey has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crown prince had 'no knowledge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-investigation/saudi-crown-prince-had-no-knowledge-of-specific-khashoggi-operation-source-idUSKCN1MU00F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia's crown prince had no knowledge of the specific operation that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zirinsky close to clinching top '60 MINUTES' job...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/19/susan-zirinsky-close-to-clinching-top-60-minutes-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“48 Hours” producer Susan Zirinsky has emerged as the front-runner to become the new executive producer of “60 Minutes” at CBS News, sources told The Post. Zirinsky is now the favorite to fill the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAUDI ADMITS: KHASHOGGI KILLED IN CONSULATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/saudi-arabia-acknowledges-jamal-khashoggi-died-consulate-says-18-detained-n922336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamal Khashoggi disappeared on Oct. 2 after visiting the Saudi consulate in Istanbul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER CEO complains about 'unfairness' in San Fran homeless tax on corporations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/412335-jack-dorsey-complains-about-unfairness-if-san-francisco-homeless-tax-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dorsey and Salesforce CEO Marc Benioff, who strongly supports the proposition, have butted heads on the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 DETAINED...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/saudi-arabia-detains-18-people-in-connection-with-journalists-death-1539987519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Saudi Arabia prosecutor says a dispute inside the consulate in Turkey led to the death of journalist Jamal Khashoggi as the kingdom issues the preliminary findings of its investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King asserts authority...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-politics-king-insight/as-khashoggi-crisis-grows-saudi-king-asserts-authority-checks-sons-power-sources-idUSKCN1MT1LF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So grave is the fallout from the disappearance of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashog...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Songwriter wins $44,000,000 in suit over Usher song...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/entertainment/celebrities/usher-lawsuit-44-million-bad-girl-stairway-to-heaven-20181019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usher is off the hook, though</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEOs Avoid Riyadh Conference, But Not Kingdom Cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/19/business/ceos-saudi-money.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though American and European executives are staying away, companies are unlikely to sever ties or avert future deals after the killing of Jamal Khashoggi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insects invading VA, PA could be 'most destructive' in 150 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/spotted-lanternfly-invading-virginia-and-pennsylvania-could-be-most-destructive-species-in-150-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An invasive insect species native to China, India, and Vietnam is posing a problem in at least two states in the northeastern and southeastern part of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sedentary worse than smoking, diabetes, heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/health/study-not-exercising-worse-than-smoking/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being unfit should be treated as a disease that has a prescription, called exercise, the study's author said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albatrosses to spy out illegal fishing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/albatrosses-spy-illegal-fishing-192539540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chizé (France) (AFP) - Fishermen illegally trawling the Indian Ocean might soon find they have more to worry about than the proverbial albatross around their neck -- real bad luck might now lurk in the form of one of the birds spying on them from the sky. A scientific programme, designed to study the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptojacking: Your computer quietly mining bitcoin -- for someone else?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/your-computer-could-be-quietly-mining-bitcoin-someone-else-n922101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The act, known as cryptojacking, has grown in popularity because it is hard to detect, reasonably passive and lucrative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Lawyer Previews Defense: Police Misconduct, 'Non-Victim' Actresses...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/harvey-weinstein-criminal-lawyer-previews-defense-strategy-police-misconduct-victim-actresses-1153774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a NY Bar Association panel behind closed doors, Ben Brafman addresses Gwyneth Paltrow and Rose McGowan ("quintessential non-victims"), the Brett Kavanaugh hearings ("an embarrassment to watch") and a #MeToo movement he says could undo progress for women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi hints at short-term lease on speakership...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-nancy-pelosi-speaker-20181019-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Without term-limiting herself, the Democratic leader says she "has things to do, books to write, places to go." Without picking a favorite, says she would be delighted to hand speaker's gavel to another woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military members catfished, blackmailed on dating apps by male prisoners posing as women...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2018/10/19/soldiers-are-getting-catfished-blackmailed-on-dating-apps-by-male-prisoners-posing-as-women-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged sextortion scheme began in 2015, with prisoners posing as women in the same age bracket as the targeted soldier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 250 Snakes, Skunks, Ferrets, Gators Inside PA Home...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/10/18/officials-find-more-than-250-snakes-alligators-and-skunks-found-in-montgomery-county-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators believe the home is connected to a similar incident in Macungie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ charges Russian with interference in Midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/19/first-criminal-case-filed-over-russian-interference-in-2018-midterms-916787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russia-based accountant was accused of buying social media ads and web postings intended &amp;quot;to sow division and discord in the U.S. political system.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TESTED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d52af53fc55b49cdbd320df9a19ff626</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECUN UMAN, Guatemala (AP) — Central Americans traveling in a mass caravan broke through a Guatemalan border fence and streamed by the thousands toward Mexican territory Friday, defying Mexican authorities' entreaties for an orderly migration and U.S. President Donald Trump's threats of retaliation. Arriving on the Mexican side of a border bridge, they were met by a phalanx of police with riot shields. About 50 managed to push their way through before officers unleashed pepper spray and the rest retreated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff bans alcohol sales after Hurricane Michael...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article220302375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in Bay and Gulf Counties in Florida have banned alcohol sales while survivors of the hurricane-ravaged area deal with Michael’s aftermath. But Panama City officials have bucked the ban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Reporter Hit With Tear Gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnns-bill-weir-hit-with-tear-gas-during-harrowing-live-report-at-mexico-guatemala-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Controversy-Marred Playoffs, MLB Sees Ratings Decline...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/10/19/mlb-postseason-alcs-nlcs-tv-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ratings have been mostly down year over year, but how much of a concern is that for Major League Baseball?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel Probes WIKILEAKS Contacts...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mueller-probes-wikileaks-contacts-with-conservative-activists-1539978208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Mueller’s probe is scrutinizing how a collection of activists and pundits intersected with WikiLeaks, the website that U.S. officials say was the primary conduit for publishing materials stolen by Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  F-bombs, storm-out among Trump's top staff as tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/f-bombs-storm-out-among-trump-s-top-staff-tensions-n922151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angry exchange between Trump officials over how to curtail rising border crossings points to White House divide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Hip-Hop Music Videos 'Public Health Threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/public-health-threat-hip-hop-videos-tobacco-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are hip-hop music videos a danger to the millions of young fans who enjoy watching them? According to researchers from The Dartmouth Institute and Johns Hopkins University, many very well may be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for threatening Kavanaugh-supporting senators...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/19/man-arrested-for-threatening-kavanaugh-supporting-senators/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long Island man was busted for making death threats against two US senators for their support of newly minted US Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh. Ronald DeRisi, 74, was taken into custody e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO berats analyst on earnings call: 'Embarrassment to your parents'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d55394848697bca59990ab60c20f7f98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — The CEO of a mining company exploded at Wall Street analysts on Friday, saying they can't read financial reports and should resign. Lourenco Goncalves told analysts on a conference call that they didn't understand his company, Cleveland-Cliffs Inc., or even their own businesses. "You guys should resign for your lack of knowledge of things," the CEO said. "You are a disaster. You are an embarrassment to your parents." The rant earned Goncalves an invitation to appear later on CNBC, but Cleveland-Cliffs shares sank nearly 8 percent in afternoon trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort pushed into court in wheelchair, missing shoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/paul-manafort-shows-court-wheelchair-learns-sentencing-date-n921826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort’s lawyer told the judge, "There are significant issues with Mr. Manafort’s health concerning confinement."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses 10 charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/paul-manafort-sentencing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort appeared in a wheelchair in a Virginia courtroom Friday afternoon, where he learned he will be sentenced next February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant galaxy supercluster found lurking in early Universe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/giant-galaxy-supercluster-found-lurking-early-universe-105630607.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have discovered a primitive "supercluster" of galaxies forming in the early Universe, just 2.3 billion years after the Big Bang. The structure, nicknamed Hyperion, is the largest and most massive to be found so early in the formation of the Universe, which sprang into existence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen: Vote out 'craziness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/michael-cohen-vote-craziness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, Donald Trump's former lawyer, pleaded with the American public on Friday to head to the polls and vote against the President and the Republican Party, predicting that if they did not, there would be two or six more years of "craziness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones Really Wants Bezos to Buy SEAHAWKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/2018/10/19/-jerry-jones-jeff-bezos-seattle-seahawks-ownership-paul-allen-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jones told the MMQB's Jenny Vrentas that he'd "carry [Bezos] piggyback to get him to the NFL."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Plans to Launch 'Artificial Moon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/china-plans-to-launch-an-artificial-moon-to-light-up-the-night-skies/ar-BBOAHOu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Economy SLOWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/finance/city/1033779/China-news-China-economy-US-trade-war-Shanghai-Composite-Index-Beijing-growth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA’S economy has felt the brunt from an escalating trade war with the US as latest figures show growth is at its slowest for almost a decade. The Asian stock market has been rattled on consumer fears of a slowdown in economic growth, with stocks plunging to an almost four-year low this week.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
