<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CALLS FOR JAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/sports/nfl-world-stunned-by-myles-garrett-attack-on-mason-rudolph-calls-for-season-ban-jail-050946065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former NFL players were stunned by the Myles Garrett attack on Mason Rudolph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kissinger warns of 'catastrophic' conflicts between China, USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3037870/kissinger-warns-us-and-china-their-conflicts-will-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘It will be worse than the world wars that ruined European civilisation,’ says former secretary of state and adviser to Richard Nixon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, in 3rd Visit in Month, Tries to Boost Republican in Louisiana Governor's Race... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/trump-goes-after-adam-schiff-at-rally-ostensibly-to-boost-louisiana-governor-candidate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump tried to undermine House Intelligence Chairman Adam B. Schiff during a political rally in Louisiana, saying he has a "small neck."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCORSESE URGES ART OVER ALGORITHM; 'IT'S ALL ILLUSION'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/martin-scorsese-urges-commitment-art-algorithms-1255113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honored with the 14th annual Kirk Douglas Award by the Santa Barbara International Film Festival Thursday night, 'The Irishman' filmmaker also opens up on his legendary collaborators and the name on his new trophy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male sex robots to replace men as women leave loveless relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/male-sex-robots-could-see-20841272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The male sex doll market is rapidly growing. Here's how it could impact relationships in the future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He could have killed him'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/nfl-players-react-to-myles-garrett-swinging-helmet-at-steelers-quarterback-mason-rudolph/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL world did not have any sympathy for Myles Garrett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete surges ahead of Iowa caucuses...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/470565-buttigieg-surges-ahead-of-iowa-caucuses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg is surging in the 2020 primary, capitalizing on a Democratic Party wrestling with its political identity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELMET ATTACK SHOCKS NFL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9ba79fa26c6c4c55b10a9405d374e4b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — Myles Garrett swung a helmet. The NFL will soon swing back at the Cleveland Browns star. Garrett could be facing an unprecedented league suspension for his violent outburst...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts claim addiction to shopping is mental illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/experts-claim-addiction-to-shopping-is-a-mental-illness-8zptsggjt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Addiction to shopping fuelled by online retailing should be classed as a mental health condition, psychiatrists claim. Researchers said that about 5 per cent of adults in developed countries — more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge slams feds over indecision on FBI's McCabe...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/14/andrew-mccabe-prosecution-uncertainty-071028</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ongoing uncertainty over the prosecution was unfair to the former deputy FBI director, the federal judge said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Dirt Bike Gang Taunts, Circles Around NYPD Cop At Gas Station... </title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/11/14/nypd-officer-taunted-by-dirt-bike-riders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD has made an arrest in an incident that some say disrespected the badge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOMELAND SECURITY' CONFIRMS NO NEW BORDER WALL YET...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/14/dhs-confirms-no-new-border-wall-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration still has yet to fence in any new miles of border with President Trump’s wall, a top Homeland Security official acknowledged Thursday — though he said that’s not the right way to look at the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: GEORGE SAYS KELLYANNE IN A 'CULT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/11/kellyanne-caught-in-west-wing-cross-fire-as-george-goes-full-resistance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump complains, and Jared wants her out, as George Conway fires fierce salvos at the president and parties with Kathy Griffin and Paul Krugman. But he still loves Kellyanne, sources say. “He’s going through a tough time,” says one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, in 3rd Visit in Month, Tries to Boost Republican in Louisiana Governor's Race... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/going-louisiana-governors-race-trump-tries-thread-needle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is signaling Saturday's Louisiana governor's race is a harbinger of things to come in 2020. So he's going back there. For a fourth time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX TOPS RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/13-1-million-watched-first-impeachment-hearings-with-fox-news-most-viewed-and-cnn-second-in-demo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Day 1 of the impeachment hearings captured the nation's attention — and blanket coverage across the big three broadcast and cable news networks resulted in a massive daytime audience. Overall, 13</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAYLOR SWIFT BANNED FROM PLAYING OLD HITS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/taylor-swift-american-music-awards-scooter-braun-scott-borchetta-1203405629/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift has taken to social media to tell fans that Scott Borchetta, her former label head at Big Machine Records, and his new partner Scooter Braun are trying to nix her plans for a retrospec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish media paints White House visit as Erdogan triumph over Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/470559-turkish-media-paints-white-house-visit-as-erdogan-triumph-over-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish media are seizing on President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan’s comments that President Trump had “no reaction” to his returning the American leader’s notorious letter to him, saying it shows a clear victory over Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg apologizes for sexist remarks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/14/bloomberg-apologizes-for-sexist-remarks-as-he-plots-presidential-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg — who is expected to soon declare his candidacy in the Democratic primary, issued a rare apology through a spokesman in a New York Times piece about his lurid statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State slipping back into drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/california/article237368339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese killer robots sold to Middle East will leave 'every human dead'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/chinese-killer-robots-sold-middle-20882729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears that 'fully autonomous' military drones sold by China to Middle East countries could have dire results with the machines able to decide on who lives and dies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE NEWS struggles to add subscribers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/apple-news-has-struggled-to-add-subscribers-since-march-launch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple signed on 200,000 subscribers to Apple News+ in its first 48 hours in March, but has been stuck in neutral since that time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meds pose global environmental risk, experts warn...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/medicines-pose-global-environmental-risk-experts-warn-170419416.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residues from billions of doses of antibiotics, painkillers and antidepressants pose a significant risk to freshwater ecosystems and the global food chain, a new analysis said Thursday. There are growing fears that the unchecked use of antibiotics in both medicine and agriculture will have adverse effects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy declares state of emergency in Venice after flood...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-declare-state-emergency-venice-flood-132501344.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy on Thursday declared a state of emergency for Venice after an exceptional tide surged through churches, shops and homes, causing millions of euros worth of damage to the UNESCO city. Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte said the cabinet had approved the state of emergency and ordered the immediate release</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PETITIONS SUPREMES TO SHIELD TAX RETURNS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/019be473afbe4cddbc21aff91f4fa611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is asking the Supreme Court to block a subpoena for his tax returns, in a test of the president’s ability to defy investigations. The filing Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key West shatters record with 232 consecutive days of 80 degrees or higher...</title>
      <link>https://accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/this-is-the-land-of-perpetual-summer/627654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone trial jury ends 1st day of deliberations without verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-stone/jury-in-trial-of-trump-adviser-stone-ends-first-day-of-deliberations-without-verdict-idUSKBN1XO2AS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury in the criminal trial of U.S. President Donald Trump's adviser Rog...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Deval could torpedo Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/14/deval-patrick-joe-biden-2020-070915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-Massachusetts governor eyes a path through South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seen Lining Up Military Aircraft For Possible Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/14/779089382/north-korea-seen-lining-up-military-aircraft-for-possible-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images shared exclusively with NPR show North Korean fighters and helicopters massed at a single airbase. It could be another sign of escalating tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton offers advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/14/bill-clinton-offers-donald-trump-impeachment-advic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clinton, America’s most-recent impeached president, on Thursday offered apparently sincere words of advice for President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anonymous' whistleblower: Medical data of millions at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2019/nov/14/im-the-google-whistleblower-the-medical-data-of-millions-of-americans-is-at-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When I learned that Google was acquiring the intimate medical records of 50 million patients, I couldn’t stay silent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds preparing to take over private land in Texas?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/trump-admin-preparing-take-over-private-land-border-wall-n1082316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is preparing court filings to begin taking over private land in Texas to build a border wall as early as this week, say officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PETITIONS SUPREMES TO SHIELD TAX RETURNS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/trump-asks-supreme-court-to-let-him-keep-his-tax-returns-secret.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case could determine whether any president has blanket criminal immunity while in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlottesville suit seeks to link online talk to violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47b79d2805754f77af8083c1a3731ad4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The white nationalist rally that took a deadly turn in Charlottesville, Virginia, during the summer of 2017 shocked Americans with its front-row view of hatred on the rise. But weeks before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why not naming whistleblower bad for mainstream media...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/11/14/whistleblower-nyt-impeachment-070887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times will only partially unmask him. The rest of the news media should finish the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States' massive GOOGLE antitrust probe will expand into search...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/states-google-antitrust-probe-to-expand-into-search-android-businesses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far, the investigation, which is being led by Texas' attorney general, has explicitly focused on Google's advertising business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Student editor in hiding after reporting triggering news...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/daily-northwestern-editor-in-chief-hides-in-office-to-dodge-free-beacon-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daily Northwestern editor in chief Troy Closson hid inside his office on Tuesday rather than answer questions from the Washington Free Beacon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-year-old genius to graduate university...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/14/europe/university-graduate-child-genius-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child prodigy from Belgium is on course to gain a bachelor's degree at the tender age of nine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mo'Nique Sues NETFLIX Over 'Discriminatory Pay Offer' for Stand-up Special...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/monique-sues-netflix-over-discriminatory-pay-offer-for-stand-up-special/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress and comedian Mo'Nique filed a lawsuit accusing Netflix of pay discrimination based on her race and gender Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein's brother: Epstein didn't kill himself, wasn't trafficking women...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article237242984.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX DOMINATES IMPEACHMENT RATINGS</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/impeachment-hearings-tv-ratings-donald-trump-fox-news-cnn-msnbc-1202786141/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was just by a hair, but the debut of the impeachment hearings against Donald Trump yesterday beat Robert Mueller’s testimony before Congress earlier this year …barely. With a grand total o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Tactical edge will shift...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/227149e8403744bf87261f4c9a06f002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It’s been easy for majority Democrats to keep Republicans from shifting the focus of the House impeachment hearings. Yet GOP leverage to do just that will grow should the battle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Dead in California High School Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/shooting-reported-high-school-los-angeles-area/story?id=67010044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting was reported Thursday morning at a high school in Santa Clarita near Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy says Trump will stay loyal to him -- but jokes he has 'insurance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/14/rudy-giuliani-donald-trump-insurance-loyal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President’s lawyer, a key figure in the impeachment inquiry, speaks to Guardian amid speculation Republicans will seek to paint him as a rogue actor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/11/14/shooting-at-saugus-high-school-prompts-lockdown-of-campus-gunman-sought/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspect has been apprehended after a shooting that left one person dead and several other injured at Saugus High School in Santa Clarita, prompting a massive police response and the temporary lockdown of two entire school districts Thursday morning. The incident began around 7:30 a.m. when deputies responded to a report of shots fired on the campus, located at 21900 Centurion Way, the Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department's Santa Clarita station said in a series of tweets. The agency characterized the incident as an "active shooter situation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 70% Of Americans Struggling Financially...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/70-americans-are-struggling-financially/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Income is not keeping pace with expenses," expert says in noting the prevalence of financial hardships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass brawl breaks out at gym as men swing punches, dumbbells, pull-up bars...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/14/gym-goers-clock-each-other-with-exercise-equipment-in-wild-brawl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British dumbbells used workout equipment to attack each other during a terrifying caught-on-camera gym brawl. The wild footage shows one workout warrior screaming obscenities as he swings around th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect in custody...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c0c6610889a24810b44eb760397f74231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Trump pardon?</title>
      <link>https://www.predictit.org/markets/detail/5211/Will-Trump-pardon-Stone-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.predictit.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Heart Attack Injects New Life Into Campaign?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/13/bernie-sanders-heart-attack-070538</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Down Drones With Standard Laser Pointers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/11/how-chilean-protesters-took-down-drone-standard-laser-pointers/161288/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The low-powered presentation tool/dangerous children’s toy is becoming a weapon of choice for protesters around the world trying to take down or disable surveillance tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police hunt 'Asian gunman in dark clothes'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/los-angeles-county-deputies-respond-report-santa-clarita-school-shooting-n1082231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is an active shooter situation," said the Santa Clarita Valley sheriff's office. "If you live in neighborhoods anywhere near Saugus High, PLEASE LOCK DOORS and stay inside."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPSOS:  PRESIDENT'S JOB APPROVAL 39%...</title>
      <link>https://www.ipsos.com/sites/default/files/ct/news/documents/2019-11/2019_reuters_tracking_-_core_political_impeachment_tracker_11_13_2019.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ipsos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple faces jail for living in RV on own property...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/couple-may-be-jailed-for-living-in-rv-after-fire-burns-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Mississippi couple whose home was partially gutted in a fire is now facing fines and jail time for temporarily living in an RV while they dealt with insurance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California high school on lockdown after at least seven people shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7686163/California-high-school-lockdown-six-people-shot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting was reported st 7.45am Pacific Time at Saugus High School on Centurion Way in Santa Clarita, leaving at least six people wounded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County Morgue Overwhelmed with Dead Migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/11/13/exclusive-border-countys-facilities-overwhelmed-with-dead-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A border county medical examiner's office is now packed beyond capacity with the remains of migrants who died after crossing from Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling narratives on Trump's actions collide for shared audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2019/11/14/dueling-narratives-on-trumps-actions-collide-for-shared-audience/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A witness had a moment of speechlessness when pressed on conspiracy theories apparently driving the president’s actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg's path to convention  -- and beyond...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/470231-bloombergs-path-to-the-convention-and-beyond</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Bloomberg runs, he'll open those deep pockets in the presidential primary contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems confront prospect of long primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/470378-the-memo-democrats-confront-prospect-of-long-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no true front-runner in the Democratic presidential race — and that opens up the specter of a long and divisive nomination fight within a party desperate to beat President Trump in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/14/shooting-at-saugus-high-in-santa-clarita/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle lines harden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d7dff9c076d44b0b55ed4d822cf383b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With historic impeachment hearings underway, Democrats and Republicans are hardening their arguments over the actions of President Donald Trump as they set out to win over a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: Kellyanne Blows Up at Blitzer for Saying 'There Are Issues' With Marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kellyanne-conway-blows-up-at-cnns-wolf-blitzer-for-saying-there-are-issues-with-her-marriage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Did you just say there are issues there?” she exclaimed. “You don’t want to talk about—why would you say that?!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE SAYS, SHE SAYS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/kellyanne-conway-rips-msnbc-featuring-george-conways-anti-trump-commentary-where-is-the-shame/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Senior Advisor Kellyanne Conway appeared on CNN Thursday morning for special coverage of the ongoing impeachment inquiry, and things got strange and heated when host Wolf Blitzer asked her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They turn '49 MERCURYS and COBRAS into EVs, one TESLA carcass at a time...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2019-11-14/tesla-electric-vehicles-classic-cars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing army of hot rodders is cannibalizing crashed electric cars and turning them into custom vehicles with electric power trains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye 'Sunday Service' with Joel Osteen to attract record crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/kanye-west-joel-osteen-sunday-service</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The focus of the all-day affair will be Kanye’s journey to finding God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDROID...</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.idrudgereport.iDrudgeReportUniversal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;play.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's all you need to know to use the app to it's fullest: *** NOTIFICATIONS *** On first open, Android will ask you to allow notifications. Tapping allows results in alerts being sent to your phone whenever there is a siren, new banner or a highlighted headline (e.g. colored red.) Review these urgent headlines anytime by tapping on the urgent headlines button (bell with lines under it.) Then to modify which alerts you receive by tapping on the settings (gear) icon. *** SCROLL TO TOP *** Tap on the reload button.  *** COLUMN SWITCHING (phones) *** Tap on the columns icon once to be taken to the top of the first column. Tap again for the top of the second column. Tap for the third column. Tap one more time and you'll be brought to the top. Repeat as desired. A personal response for those who tap on the Notifications Button &gt; Settings Button &gt; Tap "App Support" for comments, bug reports or suggestions for improvement. Posting bugs in the comments may not get the attention they deserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I wish I'd never been born: Rise of the anti-natalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/14/anti-natalists-childfree-population-climate-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adherents view life not as a gift and a miracle, but a harm and an imposition. And their notion that having children may be a bad idea seems to be gaining mainstream popularity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass brawl breaks out at gym as men swing punches, dumbbells, pull-up bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/mass-brawl-breaks-out-gym-20879199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group of gym-goers grabbed exercise equipment to use as weapons during the terrifying scrap at the Ab Salute training facility in Brentwood, Essex</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>468%: Stocks 10-year run becomes best bull market ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/the-markets-10-year-run-became-the-best-bull-market-ever-this-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current bull market, which started March 9, 2009, has enjoyed a whopping 468% gain for the S&amp;P 500 through the first day of November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: Kellyanne goes off after CNN plays clip of husband criticizing president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/470433-kellyanne-conway-after-cnn-plays-george-conway-remarks-im-embarrassed-for-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House counselor Kellyanne Conway confronted CNN's Wolf Blitzer on live television Thursday after he played footage of her husband criticizing President Trump and Republicans as part of MSNBC's coverage of the impeachment hearing the day befo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN MERCH: WAR ON WEALTHY!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elizabeth-warren-billionaire-tears-mugs-145359512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren isn’t backing down from her fight against billionaires — in fact, the Democratic senator from Massachusetts is now selling $25 “billionaire tears” mugs on her campaign website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of city hangs in balance...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10345964/venice-flooding-mayor-barrier-delays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE mayor of Venice says the “future of the city” hangs in the balance after “apocalyptic” floods devastated the iconic lagoon metropolis. More questions have been asked about a multi-b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Falling Asleep, Staying Asleep Increasingly Rare...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-falling-asleep-staying-asleep-growing-more-difficult-for-americans-each-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may not think twice about the occasional sleepless night, but a new study finds that falling asleep and staying asleep is an increasingly rare skill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea threatens military escalation as clock ticks on year-end deadline...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/North-Korea-threatens-military-escalation-as-14834092.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea - North Korea has a message for President Donald Trump and the United States: The clock is ticking, and a bomb is about to explode.  There are seven weeks until North Korea's leader Kim Jong Un is scheduled to deliver a keynote New Year's Day speech. That will come a day after his self-imposed year-end deadline expires for the United States to come up with new proposals to restart nuclear talks.  On Wednesday - with Washington transfixed on the House impeachment inquiry - North Korea significantly raised the stakes, making an implicit threat to resume long-range missile or nuclear tests. In an official statement, the North said it felt "betrayed" by a U.S. decision to continue with joint air drills with South Korea, calling it an "undisguised breach" of an agreement made between Kim and President Trump in Singapore last year.  As a result, North Korea said it no longer felt bound by previous commitments. That could signal plans to resume nuclear or long-range missile tests.  "The U.S. is not accepting with due consideration the year-end time limit that we set out of great patience and magnanimity," the statement from the country's State Affairs Commission said.  "We, without being given anything, gave things the U.S. president can brag about but the U.S. side has not yet taken any corresponding step," it added. "Now, betrayal is only what we feel from the U.S. side."  Trump has repeatedly boasted that North Korea has stopped conducting nuclear or long-range missile tests under his watch, although it has conducted about a dozen shorter-range ballistic missile tests since April. But Pyongyang says Trump has reneged on a promise to end joint military exercises with Seoul.  Relations between the two sides deteriorated sharply after a failed summit in Hanoi in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Paramedic Cut $8K Ring Off Dead Woman's Finger, Sold It For $45...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/11/13/paramedic-accused-of-cutting-diamond-ring-off-dead-patients-finger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arkansas paramedic was arrested Monday for allegedly cutting a 1.7-carat diamond ring from a deceased woman's finger at a hospital and selling it at a pawnshop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Americans struggle to ID true facts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c762f01370ee4bbe8bbd20f5ddf2adbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a sharply divided country, here's something many Americans agree on: It's hard to know what's a true and honest fact. A new poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old dogs, new tricks: 10,000 pets needed for science...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4bee7e617c2b44b397e79f4a16523877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Can old dogs teach us new tricks? Scientists are looking for 10,000 pets for the largest-ever study of aging in canines. They hope to shed light on human longevity too. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite police force spreads terror in the barrios of Venezuela...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114123112-q82ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-VIOLENCE/POLICE (SPECIAL REPORT, PIX, TV):SPECIAL REPORT-Elite police force spreads terror in the barrios of Venezuela</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We are human and want to have sex too, disabled women say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114121711-tjt2p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women with disabilities are often ignored, shunned or mocked when seeking help from medical practitioners or even friends or family, victims said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire threat darkens California dream, residents say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114093153-rsecy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more powerful wildfires threaten more people, the Golden State may be losing its shine, some residents say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America, Friendship, Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/13/ford-v-ferrari-starring-matt-damon-and-christian-bale-races-to-the-screen-with-big-ideas-about-america-friendship-and-cars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Ford v Ferrari,” much buzzed for Oscar nominations, is coming this Friday. Among racing movies, it’s a winner, with a compelling central story about Henry Ford’s team vs. F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Humans Step In After Robots Fumble 777 Jet Assembly...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/boeing-abandons-its-failed-fuselage-robots-on-the-777x-handing-the-job-back-to-machinists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing said Wednesday it is reverting to an older approach that "has proven more reliable, requiring less work by hand and less rework, than what the robots were capable of."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Manly Appeal of 'FORD V FERRARI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/11/movie-review-ford-v-ferrari-manly-appeal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a delightful throwback, an old-school story of hard men solving tough problems, in superbly entertaining fashion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses can expect abuse, death threats, say survivors of past scandals...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114103057-qj0y4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-SPOTLIGHT (PIX):Impeachment witnesses can expect abuse, death threats, say survivors of past political scandals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love him or hate him, voters say hearings will not change views...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191114010359-6qkkm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-DECIDERS (PIX):Love him or hate him, voters say impeachment hearings will not change their views on Trump</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
