<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Horror pics reveal brutality of bare knuckle boxing as it makes comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7140811/bare-knuckle-fighting-fc2-bkfc-drew-lipton-chris-lytle/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE horrifying pictures reveal the sickening reality of bare knuckle boxing – with pulverised fighters getting punched square in the jaw without ANY gloves. The barbaric sport made a comeba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas unveils 24-foot-long, fully functional bong...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-largest-bong-vegas-20180831-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed the world's first marijuana museum and set to open in Las Vegas, Cannibation will feature what it calls the world's longest bong, coming in at 24 feet. How was it made, transported and brought to Vegas? Very carefully, man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURNING MAN: Dirty burners line up for group foam bath...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/life/arts/burning-man/2018/08/30/dirty-burners-line-up-group-foam-bath-dr-bronners-soap-funded-camp/1151270002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not-quite-decommodified camp sponsored by soap company cycles through more than 22,000 gallons of water during three days at Burning Man</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Fitting End To Rap's Underwhelming Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bryanrolli/2018/08/31/eminem-kamikaze-review/#7435196caa20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year’s critical lashing has inspired some of Eminem’s most intricate wordplay and spirited flows in years, but he still flaunts his vile behavior and outdated stylistic choices on 'Kamikaze.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas town scrutinized for blocking Muslim cemetery plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article217576505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials may sue a Texas town over its decision to halt a religious association's plans to build a Muslim cemetery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concern in White House over shortage of lawyers, press aides...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-allies-raise-alarm-team-040849514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasingly convinced that the West Wing is wholly unprepared to handle the expected assault from Democrats if they win the House in November, President Donald Trump's aides and allies are privately raising alarm as his circle of legal and communications advisers continues to shrink. With vacancies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers feed seaweed to dairy cows to 'reduce emissions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/researchers-feed-seaweed-dairy-cows-045848837.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVIS, Calif. (AP) — University of California researchers are feeding seaweed to dairy cows in an attempt to make cattle more climate-friendly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorologist accused of fracturing anchor's skull in fight...</title>
      <link>https://wvva.com/news/west-virginia-news-from-the-associated-press/2018/08/31/meteorologist-accused-of-fracturing-anchors-skull-in-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wvva.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — A meteorologist at a West Virginia TV station is accused of shoving a news anchor and fracturing her skull. The Charleston</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo Industry Booming...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tattoo-industry-wins-over-millennials-1535713200 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tattoos are leaving an indelible mark on society, and it’s shaped like a dollar sign. Over the next decade, the industry is expected to continue to grow at an annualized rate of 7.7%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon to FACEBOOK: Lots of Extreme Political Ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/coming-soon-to-facebook-lots-of-extreme-political-ads-1535707802 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaign strategists are gearing up to flood Facebook with inflammatory and polarizing ads heading into the midterm elections, saying its advertising platform rewards extreme messaging more than other venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishops Reject Reporting Abuse Revealed in Confession...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/australian-bishops-reject-reporting-sexual-abuse-revealed-in-confession-1535703402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic Church leaders in Australia said they oppose laws requiring priests break the “seal of confession” when told of possible sexual abuse, as recommended by a judicial inquiry into abuse in churches and schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy catcher says China using LINKEDIN to recruit Americans...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180831095955-jizcu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINKEDIN-CHINA/ESPIONAGE (EXCLUSIVE, PIX, TV):EXCLUSIVE-Chief U.S. spy catcher says China using LinkedIn to recruit Americans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The secret files...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/robert-mueller-secret-files-russia-investigation-ec344cf7-b875-4b78-a0d9-2b7058e08fcf.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember all the evidence Mueller may have that we haven't seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Brutal summer for Republicans...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/senate/404473-brutal-summer-for-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been a brutal summer for the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE blocking gay pride watch face in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90230803/apple-is-blocking-its-gay-pride-watch-face-in-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An iOS developer found evidence that the pride Apple Watch face is “hardcoded to not show up if the paired iPhone is using the Russian locale.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem wages war on SOUNDCLOUD rappers and Trump in surprise album...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kamikaze-review-eminem-wages-war-085454206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamikaze review: Eminem wages war on Soundcloud rappers and Trump in a furious return to form</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel's Secret Plan to Continue Investigation After Being Fired?</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/even-if-trump-goes-on-a-firing-spree-mueller-has-a-secret-parachute-expert-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrests in courtrooms escalate feud...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-ice-courtroom-arrest-20180829-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Was the arrest of an immigrant in Sacramento the first by ICE in a California courtroom?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone says he expects Mueller to charge him with crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/ex-trump-adviser-roger-stone-says-he-expects-mueller-charge-n905091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mueller team wants "to frame me for some nonexistent crime to silence me and pressure me to testify against the president," says Stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call to boycott IN-N-OUT meets its own resistance...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/business/consumer/article_39be46dc-6ae4-543e-be69-fde631ba765b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Anthony Grigore is a Democrat. But as he waited Thursday at an In-N-Out Burger in El Segundo for his meal, Grigore made it clear party loyalty would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judges side with Mueller, nix Russian joint appeal bid...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/judges-side-mueller-nix-russian-joint-appeal-bid/story?id=57512160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An associate to Roger Stone is challenging Robert Mueller's appointment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's arm amputated after contracting flesh-eating bacteria from sushi...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-arm-amputated-days-contracting-flesh-eating-bacteria-sushi-2-091101854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Korean man developed a flesh-eating bacteria after eating raw sushi. Source: New England Journal of Medicine (left)/File: (right). WARNING, DISTURBING CONTENT: A man has had to have his left arm amputated after he contracted a flesh-eating bacteria from raw sushi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Serial Cat Killer Claims 13th Victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.king5.com/article/news/local/13th-cat-found-dead-linked-to-thurston-county-serial-cat-killer/281-588606180</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.king5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $36,000 reward is being offered for information leading to the person or persons responsible for a series of brutal cat killings in Thurston County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> In Hollywood, politics pushes way into ratings game... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/In-Hollywood-politics-pushes-its-way-into-13195239.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few months after President Donald Trump took office, Lorne Michaels, producer of "The Tonight Show," was in a meeting with fellow television executives when one of them asked him about a threat to the late-night juggernaut. Was he worried that his program could face a ratings swoon because host Jimmy Fallon was much less political than rival Stephen Colbert? Michaels said he wasn't. "He brushed it aside," said a person at the meeting who asked not to be identified because they were not authorized to speak about it. "He didn't seem concerned at all. He just said that the pendulum would swing back, and Fallon would be fine." Michaels turned out to be mistaken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying bugs bring town to standstill; 'Insect APOCALYSE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/726620/Insect-apocalypse-flying-bugs-Russian-town-Taganrog-standstill-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My robot makes me feel like I haven't been forgotten'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-45332710</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How internet-connected robots are helping combat the scourge of isolation and loneliness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE BUILDS ON POPE...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/faith/thousands-of-catholic-women-sign-letter-pleading-with-pope-to-break-silence-on-sex-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our hearts are broken, our faith tested..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acapulco in health emergency over uncollected trash...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/mexicos-acapulco-health-emergency-uncollected-trash-57509551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in southern Mexico declared a health emergency Thursday in the once-glittering resort of Acapulco due to mountainous piles of uncollected trash. The health secretary of the state of Guerrero said city authorities in Acapulco had not acted on previous warnings about the garbage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Xanax abuse surging...</title>
      <link>http://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2018/08/24/teen-xanax-abuse-is-surging</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many teens are taking Xanax combined with opioids and alcohol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN:  The Oil Export Boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-oil-export-boom-1535670283 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houston-Galveston exports exceed imports for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Trump Preps 'Counter-Report' to Question Mueller Legitimacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rudy-giuliani-is-putting-together-a-counter-report-to-question-robert-muellers-legitimacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s being done with the explicit blessing of Trump who is ‘happy’ that this is part of his legal team’s ‘strategy,’ the president’s lawyer says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day gas prices hit 4-year high... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/gas-prices-remain-stuck-at-4-year-highs-for-labor-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national average gasoline price remains stuck around $2.85 a gallon, and analysts don't expect it to drop much this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga does Venice...</title>
      <link> http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6115179/Lady-Gaga-models-80s-bustier-dress-50s-pin-curls-Venice.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Threatened Ronan Farrow If Kept Reporting on Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sources-nbc-threatened-ronan-farrow-if-he-kept-reporting-on-harvey-weinstein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ronan Farrow had already left NBC News. But a top lawyer at the network threatened to smear him if he continued to pursue the Hollywood mogul, multiple knowledgeable sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Passes Nation's Toughest Net Neutrality Law...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/politics/news/california-state-assembly-passes-nations-toughest-net-neutrality-law-1202922693/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A net neutrality bill that would prohibit internet providers from a host of discriminatory practices cleared the California Assembly on Thursday, setting up a potential showdown with the Trump admi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor to fly over London in yellow bikini...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/30/mayor-sadiq-khan-to-fly-over-london-in-bright-yellow-bikini-7897884/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organisers have raised more than £58,000 for the 29ft blimp as part of a campaign seeking to remove Mr Khan from his post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Yellowstone grizzly hunt in 40 years blocked by judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/first-yellowstone-area-grizzly-hunt-40-years-blocked-000526847.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - A federal judge in Montana on Thursday issued a court order temporarily blocking the first Yellowstone-area grizzly bear hunts in more than 40 years, siding with native American groups and environmentalists seeking to restore the animals' protected status. The 14-day restraining order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK's favorite sandwich: Falafel...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6116445/How-Britains-favourite-sandwiches-changed-decades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sandwich never seems to go out of fashion. Even with the advent of alternatives such as takeaway salads or pastas, the average Briton is getting through some five sandwiches a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLEFACEBOOKAMAZON in 'very antitrust situation'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/404472-trump-google-facebook-and-amazon-are-in-a-very-antitrust-situation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He charged the firms with exhibiting a bias against conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF sex worker's wild journey ends in dramatic escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/crime/article/Sex-worker-s-murder-case-testimony-gives-rare-13192240.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman sipped from a can of Mike's Hard Lemonade, feeling carefree as she walked along Leavenworth Street in San Francisco's Tenderloin. She thought she'd been invited out to celebrate her birthday. Instead, she said, her former pimp crept up from behind and dropped her with a roundhouse punch. Two men heaved her into a car trunk and they were off, forcing the woman to claw for her life in the dark as the vehicle careened along crowded city streets. Her life as a sex worker was dangerous, but now it had turned potentially deadly. Soon police were in pursuit across the Bay Bridge. Minutes later the car would slam into a pole in a fiery, fatal wreck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela arrests 131 accused of economic sabotage...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuela-arrests-131-accused-economic-sabotage-224652708.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan authorities have arrested 131 people accused of attempting to sabotage reforms implemented by President Nicolas Maduro to alleviate a crippling economic crisis, the attorney general said on Thursday. Tarek William Saab said the arrests included "several managers of large chains"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Host Says Bombshell 'Tomorrow'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chuck-todd-warns-of-possible-mueller-bombshell-i-wouldnt-miss-work-tomorrow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman: UNITED paid $75 'hush money' after man masturbated next to me for 'hours'...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/travel/2018/08/30/woman-claims-united-airlines-paid-her-75-hush-money-after-man-masturbated-next-to-her-for-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She claims the airline lied about reporting the incident to the local authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick NFL grievance headed to trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/arbitrator-sends-kaepernicks-grievance-against-nfl-trial-210623173--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — An arbitrator is sending Colin Kaepernick's grievance with the NFL to trial, denying the league's request to throw out the quarterback's claims that owners conspired to keep him out of the league because of his protests of social injustice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Monsignor Meth' gets more prison time for failed drug test...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/30/monsignor-meth-gets-more-prison-time-for-failed-drug-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARTFORD, Conn. — A Connecticut Roman Catholic priest who ran a methamphetamine ring has been sent back to prison for nine months for failing another drug test while on supervised release. Kevin Wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAME CHANGE:  Top McCain Aides Shut Out From Funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/30/john-mccain-funeral-campaign-aides-no-invite-804162</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain's 2008 presidential campaign manager Steve Schmidt, senior adviser Nicolle Wallace, and longtime strategist John Weaver were all left off the funeral guest list, as was former running mate Sarah Palin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President threatens World Trade Organization withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/30/trump-says-he-will-pull-u-s-out-of-wto-if-they-don-t-shape-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Says He Will Pull U.S. Out of WTO ‘If They Don't Shape Up’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Gore Message to Pres. Trump: Resign...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxla.com/news/local-news/al-gores-message-to-pres-trump-resign-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fmr. Vice President Al Gore has a message for President Trump: &amp;ldquo;Resign!&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duo dragged out of prison, burned alive by Mexican vigilante mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7136143/child-kidnap-gang-burned-alive-after-150-strong-vigilante-mob-doused-them-in-petrol-outside-police-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MOB in Mexico has burned alive a pair of suspected child kidnappers after dragging them out of a police station. Locals in the village of San Vicente Boquerón, in the Acatlán de Osorio region, in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator asks FTC to examine GOOGLE ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-antitrust-google/republican-senator-asks-ftc-to-examine-google-ads-idUSKCN1LF275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Senator Orrin Hatch on Thursday added to the growing push in Washington to have the Federal Trade Commission rekindle an antitrust investigation of Alphabet Inc's Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Warns: ICE Officers could be prosecuted post-Trump...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/30/dem-rep-warns-immigration-officers-following-illegal-trump-orders-will-not-be-safe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Democratic lawmaker issued a startling warning to government officials involved in “illegal” deportations that they “will not be safe” from future punishment when Donald Trump is no longer president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNMANNED AIRSHIP TO SPY FROM SKY?</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6115199/Zero-emission-unmanned-blimp-like-airships-used-police-spy-people-sky.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed Eon by its designers at Manchester aviation firm Avalon Airships, the vehicle is a fully-autonomous airship that could land on water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMAIL 'smart responses' creep out users...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/useful-creepy-machines-suggest-gmail-replies-182733187--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Google is toeing the line between helping you save time and creeping you out as it turns to machines to suggest email replies on your behalf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO VS HYPE: WIN OR LOSE -- 'NEXT OBAMA?'</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/08/could-beto-orourke-be-the-next-obama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O’Rourke offers not just a path to victory in Texas but an antidote to the entire stupid artifice of American politics in the Trump era. He’s authentic, full of energy, and stripped of consultant-driven sterility. On what planet is Beto O’Rourke not a presidential contender, even if he loses?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Football's Growing Problem: Empty Seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/college-footballs-growing-problem-empty-seats-1535634001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Announced attendance dropped 3.2% in football’s top division last season, but schools’ ticket scans show even fewer fans in stands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life on Jupiter? NASA close to water discovery... </title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1010670/NASA-news-is-there-life-on-Jupiter-water-discovery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA’S scientists are closing in on the discovery of water on Jupiter – but could this be a sign of alien life existing on the gas giant?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunters guard friend's dead body, kill polar bears while waiting days for rescue...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/north/polar-bear-kimmirut-nunavut-death-1.4803481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nunavut hunter who survived a polar bear attack that killed one of his friends last week says the encounter started when a mother bear and her cub approached their camp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President eliminates pay raises for civilian federal employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-cuts-pay-raises-civilian-employees-890c57a1-1d6e-4e39-b8ef-b675101ab110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Undoing their 2.1% pay increase for 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Bans 9/11 'Never Forget' Project...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/red-alert-politics/campus-bans-sept-11-memorial-for-bias-against-muslims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Administrators at Ripon College in Wisconsin have ruled that a Sept. 11 memorial cannot take place on campus because it may offend Muslim students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papal silence tests faith around globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/pope-francis-normally-wont-stop-talking-hes-picked-a-funny-time-to-go-silent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a guy who loves to talk, Pope Francis sure has picked a funny time to be silent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Tells Denmark: 'No Such Thing as True Dane, True Frenchman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/london/2018/08/30/macron-denmark-true-dane-frenchman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French politicians have reacted with anger after Emmanuel Macron claimed that “true” Frenchmen and Danes “do not exist”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gerard Depardieu Accused of Rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/gerard-depardieu-accused-sexual-assault-1138559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French woman, believed to be an actress in her 20s, has reportedly filed a criminal complaint with French police against the 69-year-old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal Leaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/trump-lawyers-hope-emmet-flood-will-focus-on-mueller-not-replace-mcgahn.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's lawyers see Flood as a critical piece in their strategy to combating any attempt by Mueller at issuing a subpoena for the president to appear before a grand jury, a person close to the president's legal team told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Harvard Hurts Asian Americans With 'Personal Rating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/justice-department-says-harvard-hurts-asian-americans-admissions-prospects-with-personal-rating-1535637680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department says Harvard University puts Asian-American applicants at a disadvantage through the school’s use of a subjective “personal rating.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi terrorist-turned-politician says worked with Iran to kill Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/josh-rogin/wp/2018/08/30/iraqi-terrorist-turned-politician-told-u-s-interrogators-he-worked-with-iran-to-kill-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly released interrogation reports shed new light on an old foe of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAPCHAT sorry that map called NYC 'Jewtropolis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7135583/snapchat-jewtropolis-snap-maps-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snapchat has apologised for a major gaffe that labelled New York City “Jewtropolis” on Snap Maps, leading users to blast it as “racist”. But the blunder – which is impacting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper blames tariffs for layoffs -- but reductions likely remain as tariffs overturned..</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/business/Tariffs-on-Canadian-newsprint-are-overturned_171322528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The International Trade Commission on Wednesday overturned a Trump administration decision to impose tariffs on Canadian newsprint, saying that U.S. paper producers are not harmed by new</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETA Pushes Memorial For LOBSTERS Killed In Crash...</title>
      <link>https://wgme.com/news/local/maine-dot-denies-request-from-peta-to-put-up-memorial-for-lobsters-killed-in-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK (WGME) -- The Maine Department of Transportation has denied a request from People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals to build a 5-foot tombstone memorial where lobsters may have died after a crash on Route 1 in Brunswick last week.Brunswick Pol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top search engine sues comedian over joke...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/30/technology/baidu-sues-comedian-china/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baidu is suing a comedian, demanding damages and a public apology, after he mocked the company and its CEO on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>229k+ teens get plastic surgery, fueled by socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/should-you-let-your-teenager-get-plastic-surgery-2018-08-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Society of Plastic Surgeons released new guidance for cosmetic procedures on teens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARGENTINA CURRENCY COLLAPSES; RATES HIKED TO 60%! IMF RESCUE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/argentina-crisis-peso-crashes-to-record-low-amid-imf-plea.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Argentina is struggling to cope with yet another financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Seeks AI to Match Criminals to Biometric Database...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/08/fbi-looking-tech-foil-fingerprint-obliteration/150908/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI wants artificial intelligence tools that can ID people with burnt, cut or otherwise altered fingerprints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA freezing accounts of customers suspected of not being citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article217095125.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bank of America has been accused of asking citizenship questions and for proof of residency, then freezing customers’ accounts after failing to properly recognize their current residency status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKE NEWS... FAKE SEARCH... FAKE SOCIALS... FAKE BOOKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-tweets-fake-everything-nbc-cnn-books-google-news-8ccb6e50-24cf-47dc-b547-34b2aa8e5e9f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, books, social media and Google searches are all in his Twitter sights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO American flag?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/canadian-first-man-actor-defends-omitting-american-flag-planting-on-moon-achievement-transcended-countries-and-borders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The late Neil Armstrong’s 1969 trip to the moon may have been “one small step for man, one giant leap for mankind,” but it was also a massive achievement for the United States. One of Armstrong’s first orders of business was to proudly plant the American flag, after all. But Ryan Gosling, the Canadian actor …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Monster' lizard menacing family in backyard. Even trappers stumped...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/broward/article217507540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A six-foot Nile or Asian monitor lizard has eluded trappers from Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission and Martin County Trappers in the Davie family neighborhood of Zachary and Maria Lieberman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical depression likely to form in Atlantic over weekend...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/weather/hurricane/fl-reg-tropical-weather-aug-28-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patch of storms and clouds near the Cape Verde Islands has a 50 percent chance of becoming a tropical cyclone, say forecasters at the Miami-based National Hurricane Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call for boycott...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/404323-california-dems-call-for-boycott-of-in-n-out-after-donation-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California Democratic Party chairman is calling for a boycott of In-N-Out Burger after it was revealed this week that the fast food chain donated $25,000 to the California Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Dems Outraged As IN-N-OUT BURGER Donates To GOP...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/08/30/in-n-out-burger-republican-donation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cult fast food chain is taking sides in this year's election—or is it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy drag queen serving looks -- and country...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/navy-drag-queen-harpy-daniels-serving-looks-country-n905056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Kelley, 24, performs drag for his fellow Navy sailors while also fulfilling the role of his squadron’s administrative supervisor by day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Jr. says he'd back a new conservative social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-am-6b5b747e-4bab-4d9a-a6da-802524475400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10 stories that will drive the day, from the world’s most wired reporter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON hits $2,000 per share...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/amazon-set-to-open-above-2000-a-share-for-the-first-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a major milestone in the stock's climb to match Apple's $1 trillion market valuation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 48%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/current_events/politics/prez_track_aug30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day gas prices hit 4-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/30/gas-prices-remain-stuck-at-4-year-highs-for-labor-day.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national average gasoline price remains stuck around $2.85 a gallon, and analysts don't expect it to drop much this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space station 'hit by meteorite'; Depressurization...</title>
      <link>https://www.airlive.net/breaking-pressure-sensors-detected-a-depressurization-in-the-international-space-station-possibly-caused-by-a-micrometeorite-impact/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airlive.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
