<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Near-death Experiences Can Scar Animals for Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/08/wild-animals-ptsd/619736/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans may not be the only creatures who get PTSD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin alarmed over 'unprecedented' natural disasters in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/08/14/putin-alarmed-over-unprecedented-natural-disasters-in-russia-a74788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin on Saturday said the scale of natural disasters that have hit Russia this year has been "absolutely unprecedented".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney lockdown fines increased to $3,700, stay-at-home extended...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/567857-sydney-lockdown-fines-increased-to-3700-stay-at-home-extended</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Sydney and its home state of New South Wales will now face fines of up to $3,700 for violating coronavirus stay-at-home orders, which were extended Saturday following a record number of daily COVID-19 i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapon seizures 'massive boon' as cities fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210814-weapon-seizures-massive-boon-for-taliban-as-cities-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weapon seizures 'massive boon' for Taliban as cities fall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Wall St Most Bullish on Stocks in Two Decades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wall-street-most-bullish-stocks-121500623.html#:~:text=(Bloomberg)%20%2D%2D%20It's%20been%20two,buys%2C%20the%20most%20since%202002.</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s been two decades since Wall Street analysts were this upbeat.About 56% of all recommendations on S&amp;P 500 firms are listed as buys, the most since 2002. It’s one more data point that shows the extent of the euphoria sweeping markets after a blockbuster earnings season.While analysts are historically a bullish bunch, they’re turning even more optimistic in the face of relentless stock-market gains and corporate earnings that topped even the highest expectations. For all the con</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Behold Barack Antoinette...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/behold-barack-antoinette/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Jay Gatsby gave big, lavish, new-money parties at his sprawling mansion on the water because he wanted to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska hit by 6.9 mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3473187/alaska-earthquake-news-magnitude-7/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge earthquake struck the Alaska peninsula on Saturday morning, the European-Mediterranean Seismological Centre (EMSC) reported. The quake registered a magnitude of 6.9 on the Richter scale and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens Cash in on NFT Art Boom...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/14/teens-cash-in-on-the-nft-art-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last fall, Randi Hipper decided to, as she put it recently, “go in-depth with the crypto space.” After hearing about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan president appeals for help as Taliban close in on capital...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/567855-afghanistan-president-appeals-for-help-as-taliban-close-in-on-capital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghan President Ashraf Ghani is calling on the international community to aid in the country’s fight against the Taliban, which has closed in on Kabul as fears grow that the capital could soon be overrun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN MARCH ON KABUL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-taliban-f600d6faf28e9c2ccb454ad176987b19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban seized two more provinces on Saturday and approached the outskirts of Afghanistan's capital while also launching a multi-pronged assault on a major northern city defended by former warlords, Afghan officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bkyUv5ih_r0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House discusses vax mandate for interstate travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-08-12/biden-eyes-tougher-vaccine-rules-without-provoking-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as President Joe Biden becomes more aggressive in pressuring Americans to get vaccinated, he has refrained from using all his powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER SENTIMENT LOWEST IN DECADE...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/economy/consumer-sentiment-in-us-plunges-to-lowest-since-2011-2589476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer Sentiment in U.S. Plunges to Lowest Since 2011</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO SPEAKS; FIRST INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/andrew-cuomo-resigns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How he lost the governorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H'wood may require wearable proof...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/covid-hollywood-proof-of-wearing-visible-proof-vaccination-tv-film-sets-1234814461/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Some cast and crew members on films and TV shows soon might be required to wear identification that “clearly and visibly” verifies their Covid vaccination status while workin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi seeks doctors, nurses and ventilators...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/mississippi-seeks-doctors-nurses-and-ventilators-as-covid-patients-pack-icu-beds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi seeks doctors and nurses and has asked federal officials for ventilators as the state hit a record of more than 5,000 new Covid cases in one day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 9/11 anniversary could inspire extremist attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-religion-race-and-ethnicity-bfde115ff5407b2e2042c8108f8ca270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The upcoming 20th anniversary of the Sept. 11 attacks as well as approaching religious holidays could inspire extremist attacks, the Department of Homeland Security said in a terrorism alert issued Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' warns of violence from MAGA fans over reinstatement theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3469741/homeland-security-maga-violence-trump-reinstated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WARNING issued by the Department of Homeland Security is alerting Americans of MAGA supporter violence if Trump isn’t returned to the White House. The threat comes from QAnon conspiracy theorists…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Reeks of shady deal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9891933/New-York-State-Assembly-SUSPENDS-Cuomo-impeachment-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State Assembly has suspended impeachment proceedings in the wake of Cuomo's resignation, leaving the door open for him to seek re-election next November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Jake Paul won't face federal charges after FBI raided his mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jake-paul-won-t-face-federal-charges-after-the-fbi-raided-his-mansion-he-was-being-investigated-for-filming-looting-at-an-arizona-mall-in-2020/ar-AANhS9G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The YouTube star will not face any charges after the FBI raided his home in response to looting at an Arizona mall in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>63 on Martha's Vineyard test positive since Obama's party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9891873/63-people-Marthas-Vineyard-tested-positive-Covid-Obamas-60th-birthday-bash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A total of 63 people on Martha's Vineyard have tested positive for Covid-19 since former President Barack Obama's 60th birthday on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Diplomats Shredding, Burning Docs in Case Taliban Wins...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/u-s-embassy-shredding-burning-documents-in-case-taliban-wins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Embassy Shredding, Burning Documents in Case Taliban Wins</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bulk' of additional troops arriving in days...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210813182349-j5brh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/USA-MILITARY (URGENT):'Bulk' of additional U.S. troops will be in Afghanistan in coming days -Pentagon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In West, Connection Between Covid and Wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-the-west-a-connection-between-covid-and-wildfires/ar-AANi9MP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exposure to wildfire smoke during last summer’s wildfire season could be associated with thousands of additional coronavirus infections as well as hundreds of deaths, potentially causing an even greater challenge to public health officials in Washington, Oregon and California, a new study has found. Wildfire smoke contains high levels of the smallest, most dangerous type of soot known as PM 2.5. Researchers at Harvard University estimated that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Jill Gets a Boot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-joe-biden-health-hawaii-51a60bd0eb961d204e7373eeeec8b275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Jill Biden is wearing a medical boot following a recent foot injury on a Hawaiian beach. The boot was on the first lady's left foot Friday as she and President Joe Biden boarded a helicopter in Delaware to fly to the Camp David presidential retreat in Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Talent Agent Sues NYTIMES, Reporter for Defamation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/tiktok-talent-agent-ariadna-jacob-013737418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ariadna Jacob, an agent who represented TikTok stars like Charli D’Amelio and other online Influencers, filed a defamation lawsuit on Thursday against The New York Times and reporter Taylor Lorenz for an August 2020 article about her business. Jacob says the article contained “numerous false and disparaging statements” about her and her business, including the accusation that she leaked nude images of one of her clients and hiked up the rent on her content house tenants. She said the article als</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Jury Weighing Criminal Charges Against Deshaun Watson...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox26houston.com/news/deshaun-watson-latest-grand-jury-investigation-being-used-for-possible-criminal-charges-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox26houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources tell FOX 26 that Johna Stallings, Human Trafficking Section Chief for the Harris County District Attorney’s Office, is sending out the subpoenas for the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign jihadis flocking to launch new terror war...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3468810/chilling-map-jihadis-flocking-afghanistan-terror-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOREIGN fighters are flocking to Afghanistan to launch a new terror war on the West as the Taliban tears through the country. Jihadis from the UK, Syria, Libya and central Asia have been heading to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago speed cameras now ticket drivers going 6 mph over...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/chicago-speed-cameras-now-ticket-drivers-going-6-mph-over-the-new-rules-resulted-in-about-300000-citations-and-dollar11-million-in-fines-in-the-first-2-months/ar-AANhbY8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across the street from a car wash, next to a fenced-off former lumber yard stands one of Chicago’s most prolific park safety speed cameras. And two blocks west on Lawrence Avenue, on the other side of a railway viaduct, sits the small park the camera is ostensibly protecting from speeding cars. Until last March, that camera and more than 100 like it around the city could ticket drivers going ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian army to end virginity test for female soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/08/13/indonesian-army-to-end-archaic-virginity-test-for-female-soldiers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two-finger test has no scientific value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOAA: July Was Hottest Month Ever Recorded...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/climate-change-july-2021-hottest-month-noaa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's "very likely" that 2021 will be among the world's 10 warmest years on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 photojournalists sue DC police, claim use of illegal chemical irritants...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/08/2-photojournalists-sue-dc-police-claim-use-of-illegal-chemical-irritants-at-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two photojournalists who covered a protest at Black Lives Matter Plaza, in D.C., against police brutality last August are suing the District and eight members of the police, claiming officers used chemical irritants and stun grenades that had been banned by D.C. law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS sets new high for catch-and-release at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/13/dhs-sets-new-high-catch-and-release-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security set a new monthly high in July for illegal immigrants caught and released during the southern border surge with nearly 60,000 people turned loose into communities, according to new numbers the department released Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NY Assembly to suspend Cuomo impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/new-york-state-assembly-will-suspend-cuomo-impeachment-investigation-after-resignation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York state Assembly will suspend its impeachment investigation of Gov. Andrew Cuomo after his resignation takes effect on Aug. 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent Attacks, Bloodies Elementary Instructor Over Mask Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/08/12/amador-counnty-sutter-creek-mask-fight-parent-teacher/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A district dad came back to campus after picking up his daughter and confronted the school principal. He was angry his daughter was forced to wear a mask inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to require air travelers to be vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-canada-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-f504cb07e496c8569529bd5b8f5b2cf5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — The Canadian government will soon require all air travelers and passengers on interprovincial trains to be vaccinated against COVID-19. Transport Minister Omar Alghabra said Friday that includes all commercial air travelers, passengers on trains between provinces and cruise ship passengers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War veterans horrified: 'Why did my friend get blown up?'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98why-did-my-friend-get-blown-up-for-what-e2-80-99-afghanistan-war-veterans-horrified-by-taliban-gains/ar-AANhE8k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veterans across the world are voicing frustration over the Taliban’s faster-than-expected comeback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOPES Co-Founder Caught Writing Plagiarized Articles Under Fake Name...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/deansterlingjones/snopes-cofounder-plagiarism-mikkelson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You can always take an existing article and rewrite it just enough to avoid copyright infringement."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC woman arrested for walking dogs without leash...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-arrested-over-unleashed-dogs-in-nyc-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was handcuffed and arrested over her unleashed dogs in a Manhattan park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fast Carbs' Won't Make You Fat?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fast-carbs-dont-make-you-fat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The theory is that high-GI foods raise glucose levels and insulin secretion, which may lead to health issues through overeating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Lawsuit Could Jeopardize NASA 2024 Moon Landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/08/spacesuits-and-lawsuits-put-2024-moon-landing-jeopardy/184476/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two lunar-exploration spacesuits won’t be ready, a new report says, while bid protests have held up work on the lander.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE staffers in revolt over plan to scan users' iPhones for 'abuse' pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3464672/apple-revolt-tech-scan-customers-iphones-child-abuse-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE staffers are openly revolting over the tech-giant’s plans to scan iPhones for child abuse images – amid fears users’ privacy could be compromised. More than 800 messages on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhDs are most hesitant to take shot...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/the-most-vaccine-hesitant-education-group-of-all-phds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been much debate over how to get the unvaccinated to get their jabs — shame them, bribe them persuade them, or treat them as victims of mis- and disinformation campaigns — but who, exactly, are these people? Most of the coverage would have you believe that the surge in cases is primarily down to [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
