<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Elite NFL prospect discloses epilepsy...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/04/21/justin-fields-told-nfl-teams-he-is-managing-epilepsy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quarterback Justin Fields has shared some medical information with teams ahead of next week’s draft. NFL Media reports that Fields has informed teams that he is managing epilepsy. The neurological condition can cause seizures and is usually treated with medication, although different cases can call for different medical approaches. Per the report, Fields has not [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI ZOOM COURT: Butt injection during virtual hearing...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/DavidOvalle305/status/1384867018508312578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man mulling mandatory jabs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arts-and-entertainment-cultures-lifestyle-government-and-politics-81405fb48db2e911a7f8ebcedce8c1f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. (AP) — Burning Man organizers have said that they are considering requiring attendees to prove they have been vaccinated for COVID-19 if the organizers move forward with plans to hold this year’s counter-culture festival in the Nevada desert. The organizers backed off an earlier statement indicating that they had already decided to make the shots mandatory. They say they won’t decide for sure until the end of the month whether the event that was canceled last year because of the pandemic will take place this summer. Burning Man CEO Marian Goodell said in a video message posted on the group’s web site on April 8 that “vaccines will be required to come to Burning Man.” She erroneously said at that time that the state of Nevada requires that people have proof of vaccination at large gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine commandant reveals new mission preparing for conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/21/marine-commandant-reveals-new-mission-preparing-ch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine Corps Commandant Gen. David H. Berger has revealed new plans for shifting the Corps’ mission to prepare for a future conflict with China: scouting and screening operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New rules allowing small drones to fly over people in U.S. take effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-drones/new-rules-allowing-small-drones-to-fly-over-people-in-u-s-take-effect-idUSKBN2C82FH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said that final rules announced in December took effect on Wednesday allowing for small drones to fly over people and at night, a significant step toward their eventual use for widespread commercial deliveries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service running 'covert operation' to monitor social posts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/the-postal-service-is-running-a-running-a-covert-operations-program-that-monitors-americans-social-media-posts-160022919.html?soc_src=social-sh&amp;soc_trk=tw&amp;tsrc=twtr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The law enforcement arm of the U.S. Postal Service has been quietly running a program that tracks and collects Americans’ social media posts, including those about planned protests, according to a document obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverted cop funding goes to mental health center...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-mental-health-364365482f58133842e2d710f6e71072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANHAM, Md. (AP) — Officials in a Washington suburb marked the groundbreaking this week of a mental health treatment center funded by money diverted from a police training facility. Prince George's County redirected the $20 million for the facility after the police killing of George Floyd , The Washington Post reported . The facility at Doctors Community Medical Center in Lanham will help address a long-standing disparity in access to mental and behavioral health care in the county, County Executive Angela Alsobrooks said at a news conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans, amid medicine scarcity, turn to herbal remedies, bartering...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/cubans-medicine-scarcity-turn-herbal-remedies-bartering-rcna737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba is suffering acute shortages of basic medicines as it grapples with its worst economic crisis in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Black soldiers harassed by IHOP patron...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/04/21/4-black-soldiers-harrased-by-ihop-patron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unnamed patron unloaded racially charged comments at a group of soldiers at IHOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems push $25B to electrify school buses, a Biden priority...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-health-technology-environment-and-nature-business-78082d303d5152c3a0d06eeba53ae7d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic lawmakers on Wednesday unveiled legislation that would invest $25 billion to convert the nation’s fleet of gasoline- and diesel-powered school buses to electric vehicles, aiming at a component of President Joe Biden’s $2.3 trillion infrastructure plan to improve children’s health. The legislation led by Sen. Alex Padilla , D-Calif., seeks to build on the administration’s effort this week to promote the electrification of school buses, which Biden sees as an important step in addressing climate change and economic inequities. School buses make up 90% of the nation’s total bus fleet and typically carry nearly 25 million children each day. Emissions from diesel engines may contribute to respiratory illnesses in children, studies have found, and have been linked to poor academic performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX 'close call' crash suddenly becomes much more mysterious...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/elon-musk-spacex-oneweb-satellite-collision-mystery-b1835045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX claims OneWeb was ‘demonstrably inaccurate’ as satellites passed over 1000 meters - not 60 - from each other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore plant with contaminated J&amp;J jabs had multiple failures, unsanitary conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/baltimore-plant-with-contaminated-johnson-26-johnson-vaccines-had-multiple-failures-unsanitary-conditions-fda-says/ar-BB1fTtnO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan to Stop Prosecuting Prostitution...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/21/manhattan-to-stop-prosecuting-prostitution-part-of-nationwide-shift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney’s office announced Wednesday that it would no longer prosecute prostitution and unlicensed massage, putting the weight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Human being, not political cause': Will death, conviction spur reforms?</title>
      <link>https://www.wenatcheeworld.com/news/human-being-not-a-political-cause-will-floyd-s-death-chauvin-conviction-spur-reforms/article_949932be-a24c-11eb-84e0-d7aec10c2934.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wenatcheeworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — Racial justice advocates and legal experts on Tuesday hailed former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin’s murder conviction in the killing of George Floyd, expressing hopes the case could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christie gears up for 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/chris-christie-2024-presidential-election-4eac5391-8239-4a92-93e1-4f0fb5b367ab.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Absent another run by former President Trump, the field would be wide open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Releasing Long-Awaited Update To Restrict Apps From 'Tracking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iphone-ios-privacy-update/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New mobile platform has privacy controls to limit how advertisers and companies like Facebook can track you online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Mixing Human Body Parts With Robots, Monkeys. What's Next?</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2021/04/21/scientists-are-mixing-human-body-parts-with-robots-and-monkeys-we-dont-want-to-see-whats-next/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent scientific experiments reveal a dangerous desire — and the increasing ability — to alter the fundamental elements of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin crackdown on Navalny allies as he fights for life...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210421121015-yheep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-PUTIN/PROTESTS-DETENTIONS (URGENT):Police detain more than 100 people at protests in support of Navalny - protest monitor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUILTY, GUILTY, GUILTY</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/04/20/derek-chauvin-jury-reaches-verdict-george-floyd-death-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following nearly a year of protest, introspection and raw emotion, former Minneapolis officer Derek Chauvin has been found guilty of second-degree murder and two other charges in Floyd's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ TO PROBE POLICE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/george-floyd-verdict-police-reform-doj-e24dd1a390a781af3495fa1e0271f492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General Merrick Garland is expected to announce that the Justice Department is opening a sweeping investigation into policing practices in Minneapolis after the guilty verdict in George Floyd's death, a person familiar with the matter told The Associated Press on Wednesday. The announcement comes a day after former officer Derek Chauvin was found guilty of murder and manslaughter in Floyd's death last May, setting off a wave of relief but also sadness across the country. The Black man's death prompted months of mass protests against policing in the U.S.  The Justice Department is already investigating whether the officers involved in Floyd's death violated Floyd's civil rights. The investigation announced Wednesday is known as a “pattern or practice" and will be a more sweeping probe of the entire department and may result in major changes to policing there, the official said. The official had direct knowledge of the matter but was not authorized to speak publicly about the upcoming announcement, planned for Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER-MUTANT COULD PROLONG PANDEMIC?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14667687/scientists-world-most-mutated-covid-strain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have detected what is believed to be the world’s mutated Covid strain as fears grow new super variants may prolong the pandemic. The team of experts revealed their findings in a pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Who Drink 3-5 Cups Of Coffee Daily Have Better Memory?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drink-coffee-more-alert-memory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coffee drinkers had a more "efficient" brain, with quicker connectivity in the cerebellum, the right precuneus, and the right insular.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran celebrates 'explosion' at 'sensitive Israel missile factory'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-media-celebrates-explosion-at-sensitive-israel-missile-factory-665875</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports indicate the explosion happened near Ramle at a routine test at the Tomer factory for advanced weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry over TV show that has 'ISIS' kidnap celebs, tell them they'll be executed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9495115/Outcry-Iraq-TV-fake-ISIS-fighters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TV show in Iraq has sparked outcry over fake ISIS fighters 'kidnapping' celebrities, strapping fake suicide vests to them and telling them they will be executed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research finds new variant potentially resistant to antibodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/research-finds-new-coronavirus-variant-potentially-resistant-to-antibodies-665836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During lab tests, research showed that "several neutralizing antibodies are ineffective in controlling other variants with the same genetic markers as BV-1," the university said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang Wins Endorsement from Left-Wing Rival...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/21/andrew-yang-wins-endorsement-from-left-wing-rival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang may be leading early polls in the New York City mayor’s race, but he has nonetheless faced skepticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES crisis deepens as former president expelled, advisers resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/apr/21/golden-globes-crisis-philip-berk-former-president-expelled-and-advisors-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Foreign Press Association expels Philip Berk after he shared article calling Black Lives Matter a ‘racist hate group’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian sub missing after torpedo test...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/indonesia-submarine-missing-53-on-board-after-expected-torpedo-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say they lost contact with the 40-year-old submarine's crew north of Bali, and they've asked Singapore and Australia for help finding it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests erupt after Ohio police release video of fatal shooting of Black teen girl...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/officer-involved-shooting-columbus-ohio-1-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio police officer shot and killed a teenage girl Tuesday as she attacked two other people with what appeared to be a knife in east Columbus, body camera footage released just hours after the fatal shooting shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Byron Bay to Bali, tourist hot spots wary of INSTAGRAM influencers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210421065017-2swxa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a perception that social media influencers and digital nomads are indifferent to local communities and bring few gains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India's second Covid wave hits like 'tsunami'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/21/india/india-covid-hospital-shortage-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Healthcare and other essential services across India are close to collapse as a second coronavirus wave that started in mid-March tears through the country with devastating speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns against crossing Russia's 'red lines'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/21/putin-warns-against-crossing-russias-red-lines-talks-up-military.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin warned against provoking his country in his annual State of the Union speech Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fatal TESLA crash highlights company's shaky history with safety investigators...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tesla-crash-that-killed-two-shines-spotlight-on-company-s-shaky-history-with-us-safety-investigators/ar-BB1fRUr9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials said Tesla is not party to a probe into a weekend Model S crash that killed two — a departure from typical protocol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRATIONS IN STREETS</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Cities-brace-for-post-trial-unrest-get-16116261.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across America, communities had prepared for the worst. They had put up barriers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's first long weekend of vaccination era is coming. Here's where travelers are headed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/america-e2-80-99s-first-long-weekend-of-the-vaccination-era-is-coming-here-e2-80-99s-where-travelers-are-headed/ar-BB1fRwAT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Memorial Day weekend, Americans are heading to Vegas, beaches and national parks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudin now 'stepping back' from films in wake of allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Scott-Rudin-one-of-Hollywood-s-most-powerful-16115511.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Rudin, one of the most powerful and decorated film producers of the past...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Requires Burial of Aborted Babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/tennessee-house-passes-bill-requiring-burial-or-cremation-of-aborted-babies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abortion advocates oppose fetal-remains laws because they expose the reality of what happens in an abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu gives up on forming a govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/netanyahu-gives-up-on-arab-backed-coalition-665777</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He said he would instead seek a direct election for prime minister, which he said would pass if Yamina supported it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX SUBS HIT WALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/20/netflix-correction-quarter-streaming-giant-stumbles.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix prepares for post-pandemic life with conservative second-quarter guidance of just 1 million adds, but longer-term trends remain bullish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Naval Base in Africa Expanded...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/04/20/africom-chinese-naval-base-in-africa-set-to-support-aircraft-carriers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recently completed pier at the Chinese naval base near the entrance to the Red Sea is large enough to support an aircraft carrier, the top U.S. commander for Africa told lawmakers on Tuesday. Referring to the Chines naval base in Djibouti, U.S. Africa Commander Army Gen. Stephen Townsend told the House Armed Services Committee …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOWS TO SPEND $17 BILLION ON PRODUCTIONS!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/netflix-to-spend-17b-on-content-in-2021-1234740528/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has revealed that it will spend $17B on content in 2021 – on par with its 2020 spend. The streamer noted the figure in its first quarter financial results. “While the roll out of vaccines i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female passenger takes bite out of UBER driver's neck...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/uber-bloody-attack-395821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 20--A passenger sunk her teeth into the neck of an Uber driver and choked the victim from behind in a bloody, unprovoked assault, according to court records. Police say that Michele Stilwell, 5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  WE CAN'T STOP HERE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-derek-chauvin-trial-verdict-414655f26ad6be79b43e3fd28869ec3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said Tuesday the conviction of former Minneapolis Police Officer Derek Chauvin in the killing of George Floyd “can be a giant step forward" for the nation in the fight against systemic racism. Biden spoke from the White House hours after the verdict alongside Vice President Kamala Harris, with the pair calling for Congress to act swiftly to address policing reform. “It’s not enough," Biden said of the verdict. "We can’t stop here.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  'Thank you for sacrificing your life for justice'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/live/2021/apr/20/washington-us-politics-live-derek-chauvin-trial?page=with:block-607f477a8f08505668d96105#block-607f477a8f08505668d96105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waters has made clear she will not allow Republicans to pressure her into silence about police killing of George Floyd and Daunte Wright</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Biden, Harris call Floyd family...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/attorneycrump/status/1384623880900419584?s=21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeks closer 'strategic partnership' with Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210420-russia-cuba-seek-closer-strategic-partnership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia, Cuba seek closer 'strategic partnership'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VP Harris: Verdict 'will not heal pain that existed for generations'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/20/politics/kamala-harris-chauvin-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even a verdict finding former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin guilty of George Floyd's murder will not erase generations of trauma caused by systemic racism, Vice President Kamala Harris said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COP IN CUFFS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/2738008/jury-delivers-verdict-derek-chauvin-george-floyd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEREK Chauvin has been found guilty of second-degree murder, third-degree murder, and second-degree manslaughter in the death of George Floyd. The 45-year-old former cop was found guilty of all cou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Old-School Democrat...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/04/20/vice-president-walter-mondale-obituary-1984-democratic-campaign-483448</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His 1984 campaign was a political obituary for a party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada death row inmate asks to be killed by firing squad...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/zane-floyd-nevada-killer-death-penalty-firing-squad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zane Michael Floyd says it would be more humane. His lawyers say it's not a delaying tactic. He shot four people to death in 1999.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINUTES' #1 TV SHOW IN NATION -- AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.viacomcbspressexpress.com/cbs-news/releases/view?id=57393</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.viacomcbspressexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX reports dramatic slowdown in subscribers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/20/netflix-nflx-q1-2021-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix reported earnings for the first quarter of 2021 after the bell on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire breaks out at DOMINO Sugar factory in Baltimore...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-domino-fire-20210420-wzv6h7qzuffqvlgso256plwzyi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire broke out at the Domino Sugar facility in Baltimore’s Inner Harbor Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll rants about despicable human race...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/20/this-sex-doll-rants-about-how-despicable-the-human-race-is/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not exactly typical bedroom talk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of babies born with syphilis quadrupled...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-number-of-us-babies-born-with-syphilis-has-nearly-quadrupled-in-5-years/ar-BB1fRGqA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An STD report from the CDC found that 1,870 babies were born with congenital syphilis in 2019, a 291% increase from 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of young gay people have attempted suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nbc-out/out-health-and-wellness/nearly-third-gay-youths-attempted-suicide-study-finds-rcna724</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicide rates among young people &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/nvsr/nvsr69/NVSR-69-11-508.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;have been on the rise&lt;/a&gt; in recent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINUTES' #1 TV SHOW IN NATION -- AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/tv-ratings-sunday-april-18-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS' broadcast of the ACM Awards hit an all-time low in total viewers and adults 18-49 on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Median home price in Boston-area hits record of $725K...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boston-health-business-coronavirus-6efa6312e3d661f2d92ee797c2e73004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Housing prices in the Boston-area have reached record levels. The median price for a single-family home in the region was nearly $725,000 last month, setting a new record, according to the Greater Boston Association of Realtors. The $723,750 price for a typical home in the area was 14 % higher than last March's figure. The number of properties for sale, meanwhile, fell by one-third in the same period.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
