<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>800 dogs getting cancer vaccine. Humans may be next...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/21/health/cancer-vaccine-dog-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cancer vaccine is being tested in 800 pet dogs. If it works, researchers say it could one day be tested in humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate protesters storm coal mine in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-48734321</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The activists broke through police lines during a weekend of protests against fossil fuel use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns against uncontrollable scope of war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f5871d3a11444fb0a1e11fa2b8d0274d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA strikes Iranian military computers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f01492c3dbd14856bce41d776248921f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakes high as candidates prepare to debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-2020-presidential-debate-high-stakes-20190621-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first debate gives members of the huge Democratic field a chance to attract badly needed attention. For some, it could be a final opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant Spotted Shooting at AZ Wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/06/22/migrant-spotted-shooting-at-az-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yuma Sector Border Patrol camera operators observed a group of migrants cross the primary barrier near San Luis, Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Brush With Police Puts Leadership Bid in Turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-48731774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr Johnson tells a Tory hustings "people did not want to hear" about the reported argument.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GHOSTS OF 2016 PRIMARY HAUNT DEMS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/449812-ghosts-of-2016-primary-haunt-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are feeling a sense of déjà vu as infighting among presidential candidates intensifies.And with less than a week until the first 2020 primary debate, the sniping is only expected to worsen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAHER: Oprah Only 'Sure-Thing Winner' In 2020...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/06/donald-trump-bill-maher-oprah-winfrey-is-the-only-sure-thing-winner-for-democrats-in-2020-1202636487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Maher closed out the 500th episode of his HBO series Real Time with Bill Maher with a bruising appraisal of the Democratic Party’s feckless options for 2020 and a point-by-point explanat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCAL OFFICIALS DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7169923/Trump-says-ICE-deporting-illegal-immigrants-ordered-leave-courts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The people that Ice will apprehend have already been ordered to be deported. This means that they have run from the law and run from the courts,' Trump tweeted on Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared unveils economic portion of Middle East peace plan...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190622151754-01165</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/PLAN (UPDATE 1, EXCLUSIVE, PIX, TV):EXCLUSIVE-White House's Kushner unveils economic portion of Middle East peace plan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOY STORY 4' Opens Below Box Office Expectations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/toy-story-4-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woody and Bo Peep won't match "Incredibles 2," but will still double the opening of any other 2019 animated film</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran executes 'CIA spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9352702/iran-spy-executed-cia-drone/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN has executed a former Ministry of Defence employee after intelligence officials reportedly caught him spying for the CIA. Aerospace contractor Jalal Hajizavar was killed at the infamous Rajai …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese sign up for DNA matchmaking as country heads for demographic crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/06/22/japanese-sign-dna-matchmaking-country-faces-generation-singletons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scene resembles a typical blind speed-dating event:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How trip on magic mushrooms helped decriminalize psychedelic plants...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-oakland-decriminalize-mushrooms-psychedelic-plants-20190622-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man's psychedelic "trip" helps lead to the decriminalization of magic mushrooms in Oakland, making it the first such California city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON CREEPY DRONE TECH TO SPY ON HOME...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/amazon-patents-creepy-drone-technology-to-spy-on-your-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A disturbing reminder that corporate America not only wants to monitor your search trends and social media posts but now wants to monitor the outside of your home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden camera found in studio toilets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/22/uk/uk-james-bond-pinewood-camera-scli-gbr-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was arrested Friday after the camera was found in the women's toilets at Pinewood Studios, where the next James Bond film is being filmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers wage cyber campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f01492c3dbd14856bce41d776248921f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WEATHERS STORM</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/22/joe-biden-south-carolina-fish-fry-1376705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For nearly 90 minutes on a sweat-soaked stage in South Carolina on Friday night, it was almost as if Joe Biden had put the uproar surrounding his comments about segregationists behind him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Rover on Mars Detects Puff of Gas That Hints at Possibility of Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/22/science/mars-curiosity-rover-methane.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Curiosity mission’s scientists picked up the signal this week, and are seeking additional readings from the red planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACK:  Extensive details of border security online...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Hacked-documents-reveal-sensitive-details-of-14028128.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent cyberattack on a U.S. Customs and Border Protection subcontractor didn't expose just the faces and license plates of thousands of U.S. travelers. It also revealed the inner workings of a complex surveillance network that border authorities have long sought to keep secret.  CBP officials have downplayed the significance of the material taken in the hack, saying only that fewer than 100,000 photos of travelers had been compromised and that none of those had been posted to the "dark Web," the corner of the Internet where stolen documents are often traded and displayed.  That assessment, however, woefully understates the number of sensitive documents that are now freely available on the Web - so much material, totaling hundreds of gigabytes, that The Washington Post required several days of computer time to capture it all.  The documents offer an unusually intimate glimpse of the machinery that U.S. officials depend on for the constant monitoring of legal immigration through the border. They also illuminate the government's plans for expanding its use of license plate readers and facial-recognition cameras, including such details as how many cameras are focused on which traffic lanes at some of the busiest border crossings in the world.  The hoard of hacked documents includes detailed schematics, confidential agreements, equipment lists, budget spreadsheets, internal photos and hardware blueprints for security systems.  Among potentially sensitive government material are internal Department of Homeland Security handbooks, border surveillance diagrams and dozens of signed nondisclosure agreements between the subcontractor and government authorities, as well as companies such as Microsoft and the defense-contracting giant Northrop Grumman. Microsoft and Northrop Grumman did not respond to requests for comment.  The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete confronted by protesters after fatal police shooting...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/449839-buttigieg-confronted-by-protesters-after-fatal-police-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg (D) was confronted by protesters Friday night as the presidential hopeful and his city continue to grapple with the fallout from a fatal police shooting of a black man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel to remove liquor dispensers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/22/dominican-republics-hard-rock-hotel-to-remove-liquor-dispensers-after-tourist-deaths/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino in Punta Cana is removing all liquor dispensers in guestroom minibars after a string of suspicious deaths and illnesses in the past year at the Dominican Republic r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem presidential hopefuls seek black support at SCarolina fish fry...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-south-carolina/democratic-presidential-hopefuls-seek-black-support-at-south-carolina-fish-fry-idUSKCN1TM15M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fish fry in South Carolina on Friday drew the largest crowd of Democratic pres...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIDS START SUNDAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ice-raids-targeting-migrant-families-slated-to-start-sunday-in-major-us-cities/ar-AADegXN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion world shaken by cultural appropriation claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190622-fashion-world-shaken-cultural-appropriation-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion world shaken by cultural appropriation claims</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCAL OFFICIALS WON'T COOPERATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/officials-agents-in-impending-ice-raids-shouldnt-expect-cooperation-from-local-authorities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal immigration agents can expect pushback from some public officials when they begin a mass roundup of migrant families with deportation orders, an operation slated to begin Sunday at the direction of President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Brush With Police Puts Leadership Bid in Turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/boris-johnson-s-brush-with-police-puts-leadership-bid-in-turmoil-1.1277059</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO MAYOR DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/chicago-mayor-vows-shield-migrants-001052489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot condemned the Trump administration over planned raids of migrant communities and said she had ordered police to cut federal agents’ access to databases related to immigration enforcement activities.“We are all aware of the threat from President Trump regarding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police called to loud altercation at Boris Johnson home...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/jun/21/police-called-to-loud-altercation-at-boris-johnsons-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Neighbour records shouting and banging at flat MP shares with Carrie Symonds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road to 'BOND 25' full of potholes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/The-road-to-Bond-25-is-full-of-potholes-14028959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh off his Oscar win for a film plagued by drama, Rami Malek has again found himself working on a rather chaotic production. He's been shooting scenes in Norway as the villain of "Bond 25," a working title for the 25th installment in the spy film franchise, but has yet to do so with James Bond himself.  That's because star Daniel Craig had to undergo ankle surgery last month after hurting himself on set in Jamaica, the latest injury to afflict an actor who famously once said he would rather kill himself than play Bond again. While filming a fight scene for 2006′s "Casino Royale," his first outing as the iconic character, Craig reportedly lost a couple teeth after getting hit in the face. With 2008′s "Quantum of Solace," he both tore his shoulder and sliced off the tip of his finger. Production on 2015′s "Spectre" halted for a few days so Craig could undergo a minor procedure after injuring his knee on set. (This guy commits.)  It's not unusual for production issues to set back a film - not even for Bond movies, given the mess that occurred with "Quantum of Solace" script revisions in 2007, when Craig himself stepped in to help after the Writers Guild of America went on strike for a few months. But everything has played out quite publicly with "Bond 25," to the point where actors have even addressed the issues on the record. Malek insisted in an interview with the British news website Digital Spy this week that Craig's latest injury doesn't spell doom for the film, which Cary Joji Fukunaga (TV's "True Detective," "Maniac") is directing.  "Daniel was injured, so they are shooting what they can," Malek said. "I talked to Cary yesterday and the schedule has been altered. I know that. But with a franchise like this, I think they have it together."  Perhaps, as Malek suggested, drama present since the very start of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/immigration/article231823753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor says won't cooperate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/449819-chicago-mayor-says-city-wont-cooperate-over-reported-ice-raids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot (D) said she would take “concrete steps” to support immigrant communities after reports emerged that Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Iran reversal, did Trump break pledge to never 'telegraph' military ops?</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/with-iran-reversal-did-trump-break-pledge-to-never-telegraph-military-ops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said he would never signal U.S. military operations. Then he canceled strikes on Iran after an attack was in motion.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
