<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Opens dramatic court battle to stay in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220109-djokovic-opens-dramatic-court-battle-to-stay-in-australia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennis world number one Novak Djokovic launches a make-or-break court battle on Monday to stay in Melbourne and defend his Australian Open title, arguing he has an all-clear because of a positive cor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial killer describes himself as 'good person who did some bad things'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10382673/BTK-killer-Dennis-Rader-thinks-monster-good-person-did-bad-things.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dennis Rader, the church leader and  family man later identified as Wichita's BTK killer, thinks of himself as both a 'monster' and a 'good person who did some bad things.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama wades back into politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/09/politics/michelle-obama-2022-elections-fight-for-vote/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Michelle Obama has a message for Americans ahead of the 2022 midterm elections: "We've got to vote like the future of our democracy depends on it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US troops' movement limited in Japan to prevent spread...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/588904-japan-announces-us-troops-will-stay-on-base-except-when-absolutely-necessary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. troops in Japan will be required to stay on base “except when absolutely necessary” starting Monday, as both countries look to curb the spread of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guantanamo rankles as prison turns 20...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-cuba-prisons-congress-01da0f22b22c0a56b91c146ba2d2f4fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Advocates for closing the Guantanamo Bay detention center were optimistic when President Joe Biden took office. And they were relieved this summer after the U.S. released a prisoner for the first time in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archive amassed by Nazis sheds light on Masonic history...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220109-archive-amassed-by-nazis-sheds-light-on-masonic-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Curators combing through a vast historic archive of Freemasonry in Europe amassed by the Nazis in their wartime anti-Masonic purge say they believe there are still secrets to be unearthed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard steps in to alleviate pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/09/politics/national-guard-hospitals-omicron-covid-massachusetts/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An incoming tide of patients is slowly drowning UMass Memorial Medical Center, and the US military's National Guard is working to plug the gaps. In wave after daily wave, the emergency crews pull up to the ambulance bay, dropping off patients for which there is no room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Port Hustles to Cut Logjam Amid Labor Woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/new-york-port-hustles-to-cut-rare-logjam-amid-covid-labor-woes-1.1704736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Port of New York and New Jersey is working to clear a small but rare bottleneck of container ships anchored off the coast of Long Island as Covid-19 cases among dockworkers collide with a pandemic-fueled surge in cargo volumes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watershed moment: New law allows noncitizens to vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/voting-rights-new-york-new-york-city-voting-united-states-64edb2ed4de261156f5e717b61101247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — More than 800,000 noncitizens and “Dreamers” in New York City will have access to the ballot box — and could vote in municipal elections as early as next year — after Mayor Eric Adams allowed legislation to automatically become law Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why was there less lightning during lockdowns?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/lightning-covid-lockdowns/story?id=82143368</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have determined that COVID-19 lockdowns resulted in less lightning because aerosol emissions also declined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN trans swimmer loses to YALE trans swimmer in women's Ivy League race...</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/penn-transgender-swimmer-lia-thomas-beaten-by-yale-transgender-swimmer-iszac-henig/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Penn transgender swimmer Lia Thomas, who had been crushing her competition since joining the women's swim team after three years swimming as a biological</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Colombian with non-terminal illness dies legally by euthanasia...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/man-dies-euthanasia-colombia-first-non-terminal-illness-rcna11506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombian Victor Escobar became the first person in the Andean country with a non-terminal illness to die by legally regulated euthanasia late on Friday, his lawyer confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder suspects allegedly had sex in victim's bed while she died in next room...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/08/murder-suspects-allegedly-had-sex-in-victims-bed-as-she-died/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people accused in the murder of an Oklahoma woman allegedly had sex in the victim’s bed while they heard her “struggling to live” in the next room, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cows given VR headsets to reduce anxiety, increase milk...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/01/07/farmer-gives-cooped-up-cows-vr-headsets-to-increase-milk-production-15880604/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They're cooped up in a cow shed but think they're outside in the pasture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside landmark push for reparations for Black Californians...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/09/california-reparations-slavery-african-americans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taskforce including civil rights leaders and attorneys scrutinizes legacy of centuries of injustice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escapees pay bribes, cross rivers, risk lives -- to return to NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/escapees-pay-bribes-cross-rivers-110039277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While tens of thousands risk everything to flee North Korea, a few, having failed to adjust to the capitalist South, make a desperate journey back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man makes bomb threat to jump line for DOJA CAT concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/news/local/2022/01/08/doja-cat-indianapolis-2022-free-concert-bomb-threat-monument-circle/9145396002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doja Cat is performing in Indianapolis at Monument Circle for the College Football Playoff national championship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Tianjin testing all residents after omicron found...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-winter-olympics-sports-health-beijing-84d7be3e7dfb2da4cce5b6e87d321a46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Tianjin, a major Chinese port city near the capital Beijing, began mass testing of its 14 million residents on Sunday after a cluster of 20 children and adults tested positive for COVID-19, including at least two with the omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Backer of 'Anti-Smoking' Vape Group? Big Tobacco...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/secret-backer-anti-smoking-vape-020030856.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyA pro-vaping group says it wants to save your life. Cigarettes, they remind us, can kill you. But smokers may be surprised who’s behind that message.“The World Vapers’ Alliance amplifies the voice of passionate vapers around the world and empowers them to make a difference for their communities,” reads the homepage for the WVA, whose logo is revolutionary pastiche—a left fist clenching a vape pen. “Back vaping. Beat smoking,” the page</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic pictured smiling with kids day AFTER testing Covid positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/17258987/novak-djokovic-anti-vaxxer-tennis-charity-kids-test-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-VAX tennis star Novak Djokovic was snapped smiling while handing out awards to a group of young tennis fans AFTER testing positive for Covid. The World No 1 tested positive on December 16, but…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA really heading for second civil war?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/09/is-the-us-really-heading-for-a-second-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the country polarised and Republicans embracing authoritarianism, some experts fear a Northern Ireland-style insurgency but others say armed conflict remains improbable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL cases, hospitalizations surging, but has 2nd-lowest death rate. What's going on?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/florida-e2-80-99s-covid-cases-and-hospitalizations-are-surging-but-the-state-has-the-second-lowest-death-rate-in-the-nation-what-e2-80-99s-going-on/ar-AASyQKx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 MILLION OUT SICK NEXT WEEK?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10381669/Five-million-people-call-sick-week-hits-second-highest-daily-case-count.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has posted its second-highest daily total for new COVID-19 cases, as one expert predicts some 5 million Americans could call in sick in the coming week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals struggle to match WALMART pay as staff flees omicron...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2617292-p2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. hospitals are struggling to get the workers they need to treat patients through the winter’s COVID-19 surge as the virus collides with a historically tight labor market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant Telescope Grows in Space...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/08/a-giant-telescope-grows-in-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers are starting to breathe again. Two weeks ago, the most powerful space observatory ever built roared into the sky,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duchess of Cambridge, the reliable royal, turns 40...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-prince-philip-london-europe-a1668accc67638478e993b10e7824840</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — At least there’s Kate. The Duchess of Cambridge, who turns 40 on Sunday, has emerged as Britain’s reliable royal. After Prince Harry and Meghan’s stormy departure to California in 2020, the death of Prince Philip last year, and now sex abuse allegations against Prince Andrew, the former Kate Middleton remains in the public eye as the smiling mother of three who can comfort grieving parents at a children's hospice or wow the nation by playing piano during a televised Christmas concert.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
