<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Colombia to give employees paid leave off work to mourn dead PETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3712407/employees-2-days-paid-leave-mourn-dead-pets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORKERS in Columbia are to be given two days’ paid leave if their pets die as part of new laws being planned in Colombia. Politician Alejandro Carlos Chacon brought forward a bill that would …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough cases expected to become more common...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/09/22/breakthrough-covid-19-cases-expected-to-become-more-common-in-coming-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts blame the rise of the delta variant and declining efficacy of coronavirus vaccines but say there is no need for alarm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crackdown Gathers Steam...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/crypto-risks-existential-threat-as-us-crackdown-gathers-steam/ar-AAOGPfQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrency firms are fighting for lobbyists and fielding subpoenas in what could be an existential fight over how the multitrillion-dollar industry should be regulated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEPP SPEAKS:  No one is safe from cancel culture...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/johnny-depp-says-cancel-culture-is-so-far-out-of-hand-no-one-is-safe-asks-people-to-stand-up-against-injustice-san-sebastian-1234842145/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp went on the record today saying that he is a victim of cancel culture and that “no one is safe” from the movement, calling on people to “stand up” for people facing “injustice”. “It can…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters Slams: 'Worse Than What We Witnessed In Slavery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/maxine-waters-haitian-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What the hell are we doing here?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police slammed for creating 'surveillance state' using AI software...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10018111/Police-creating-surveillance-state-software-scans-social-media-critics-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Massachusetts and Michigan are licensing SocialNet, a program from ShadowDragon that scours platforms from Facebook to Pornhub to help cops identify persons of interest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>747-sized asteroid skimmed by Earth. Scientists didn't see it coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/science/747-sized-asteroid-skimmed-by-earth-and-scientists-didnt-see-it-coming-680052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed 2021 SG, the asteroid flew close to the planet on September 16, but because it came from the direction of the Sun, scientists didn't see it coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 soldiers arrested after shooting in Louisiana...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/09/22/four-soldiers-arrested-after-drive-by-shooting-in-louisiana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All four soldiers are assigned to 3rd Brigade, 10th Mountain Division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Intermittent Fasting Improves Sleep Quality...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/intermittent-fasting-diabetes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Eating at random times breaks the synchrony of our internal program and make us prone to diseases,” researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicolle Wallace Favorite to Replace Maddow?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/nicolle-wallace-replace-rachel-maddow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Dylan Byers, "several high-level MSNBC insiders" regard Chris Hayes and Ari Melber as nonstarters to replace Rachel Maddow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapy from llamas shows promise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-58628689</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An immune therapy derived from llama blood shows "exciting potential" in early coronavirus trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's Prostate Removed -- After Mistaken Cancer Diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/09/21/man-prostate-removed-after-mistaken-cancer-diagnosis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of being relieved with the mistaken cancer diagnosis, the couple was crushed because Eric had already had his prostate removed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder Up 30%...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/murder-rose-almost-30-2020-182032147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States in 2020 experienced the biggest rise in murder since the start of national record-keeping in 1960, according to data gathered by the FBI for its annual report on crime. The Uniform Crime Report will stand as the official word on an unusually grim year, detailing a rise in murder of around 29%. The previous largest one-year change was a 12.7% increase in 1968. The national rate — murders per 100,000 — still remains about one-third below the rate in the early 1990s. Sign up for T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  'Domestic Terror' Fears Will Be Used To Justify Increased Snooping, Harassment...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/22/domestic-terrorism-fears-will-be-used-to-justify-increased-snooping-and-harassment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is greatly increasing FBI caseloads and agents. That's bad news for anybody who is worried about federal overreach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother, daughter accused of 'outlaw' buttocks augmentations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arrests-california-los-angeles-riverside-59d0b8874bdcde1a20b9e563c3a7aae5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A mother and daughter have been arrested in Southern California on suspicion of performing “outlaw” buttocks augmentation procedures on women, including one who died, police said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sanctuary City' Supporter To Oversee ICE Prosecutions...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/biden-taps-sanctuary-city-supporter-to-oversee-ice-prosecutions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration appointed a left-wing attorney who has publicly endorsed sanctuary laws for illegal aliens to serve as Immigration and Customs Enforcement's top prosecutor, according to an internal memo obtained by the Washington Free Beacon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kicked In Ribs. Harassed. Health Care Workers' New Normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.gpb.org/news/2021/09/22/kicked-in-the-ribs-harassed-at-vaccine-sites-health-care-workers-are-tired-of-new</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gpb.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across Georgia, hospitals are raising the alarm on a startling increase in violent outbursts by patients against their staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Ribbon Reefer: CA State Fair to Award Best State-Grown Marijuana!</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/09/22/california-cannabis-state-fair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's state fair has struggled with two years of COVID cancellations. But planning is already underway for next year's event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle keeps buying new buildings to house homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/politics/2021/09/the-fastest-we-have-ever-brought-housing-online-seattle-to-buy-3-new-buildings-to-house-homeless.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;165 studio apartments that were going to be rented at market rates will instead house people leaving homelessness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States Rationing Liquor As Alcohol Shortages Get Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/22/1039600464/liquor-shortages-covid-19-pennsylvania-virginia-ration-alcohol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some producers can't source glass bottles, the cost to import liquor has gone up, and there is a shortage of truck drivers. Also, it just takes a long time to make some types of booze.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uma Thurman Reveals She Had Abortion at 15...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/uma-thurman-reveals-she-had-an-abortion-at-15-in-emotional-column-against-texas-law-my-darkest-secret-until-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uma Thurman has penned a powerful and deeply personal essay in protest to Texas' restrictive abortion law, which bans the procedure after six weeks of pregnancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Emerging Artistry of Hunter Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-emerging-artistry-of-hunter-biden/ar-AAOHeLQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His upcoming solo show is a headache for the White House—and a window into the murky finances of the international art market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantined LA Schoolkids Have Lower Covid Rates Than Dosed Teachers...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/21/quarantined-l-a-schoolkids-have-lower-covid-rates-than-vaccinated-teachers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media persists in pediatric scare stories even while the country's largest dataset shows tiny yet still-declining rates, including among the needlessly quarantined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mafia Pivoting to Cybercrime...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epne4j/how-the-mafia-is-pivoting-to-cybercrime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators from Spanish and Italian police explain how organized crime is going online and expanding into cybercrime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO BITE BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/haitian-migrants-bite-ice-officers-deportation-flight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas — Federal assault charges will be brought against two Haitian migrants after they bit federal law enforcement officials on board a deportation flight when the plane was taxiing to the runway, the Washington Examiner has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD CALLING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10016997/Billy-Eichner-Matt-Drudges-double-Impeachment-American-Crime-Story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday night's episode of Impeachment: American Crime Story opened with a scene portraying Drudge's real-life 'origin story' as a clerk in a gift shop at CBS Studios in Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUG COMPANIE$ HYPE VAX 'RESULTS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/sep/21/experts-bemoan-science-press-release-covid-19-era/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drugmakers are hailing great results with COVID-19 boosters and shots for school-age children, enthusing a pandemic-weary public and markets but flustering scientists who say it is important to look at real data before getting too optimistic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former treasury secretaries tried defusing debt ceiling bomb with McConnell, Yellen...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Former-GOP-treasury-secretaries-tried-defusing-16478519.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Two former GOP treasury secretaries held private discussions this month with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX launches autonomous truck routes...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fedex-aurora-to-launch-autonomous-truck-routes-in-texas-11632322936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FedEx Corp. and self-driving vehicle startup Aurora Innovation Inc. are launching a pilot of autonomous truck shipments between Dallas and Houston in an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief slams space joy rides...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/un-chief-tells-musk-bezos-25045505</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The likes of spacefaring billionaires Jeff Bezos, Richard Branson and Elon Musk were heavily criticised by the U.N. Secretary-General, who emphasised the major problems here on Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID REVOLT GROWS IN OZ</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10016021/Police-fire-rubber-bullets-anti-vaxxer-tradies-took-Melbournes-war-memorial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have fired rubber bullets at anti-vaccination protesters who set up camp atop Melbourne's war memorial in the hopes police wouldn't fire on them out of respect for fallen Anzacs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson taking aim at his own book publisher...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Tucker-Carlson-is-taking-aim-at-his-own-book-16478536.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acknowledgment section at the beginning of a book is an opportunity for the author to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas border patrol round up Haitians with whips...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/opinion/op-ed/elviadiaz/2021/09/20/border-patrol-using-whips-del-rio-round-up-haitian-immigrants/5789596001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Border Patrol agents are using reins like whips to round up Haitian immigrants in Del Rio, Texas. What happened to Biden's more humane approach?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Sues NYT, Niece Over Tax Story...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-courts-lawsuits-business-newspapers-da4689bcce1e58c15fc909377fa3a450</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Former President Donald Trump on Tuesday sued his estranged niece and The New York Times over a 2018 story about his family’s wealth and tax practices that was partly based on confidential documents she provided to the newspaper’s reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stalkerware Firm Leaking Real-Time Screenshots of Phones Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7ezj8/stalkerware-leaking-phone-screenshots-pctattletale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pcTattleTale, which markets itself for monitoring spouses without their consent, lets anyone view screenshots of infected devices by just visiting specific URLs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge mysterious 'void' in space spotted by astronomers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/huge-mysterious-void-space-spotted-25046162</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The huge 'bubble' in space some three thousand trillion miles across should be home to billions of stars, but it's virtually empty, and scientists are struggling to find an explanation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio high school locked down after 100-person brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10017253/Multiple-people-stabbed-massive-brawl-breaks-Ohio-high-school.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 100 people are believed to have been involved in several brawls inside a Columbus, Ohio high school that required pepper spray to be used and led to the fire alarm being pulled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: BIDEN APPROVAL RECORD LOW</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/354872/biden-approval-rating-hits-new-low-harris.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's job approval rating has reached another low point in his presidency. The overall drop in approval is driven largely by political independents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clowns lurked outside schools to promote speech academy. Horrified parents called police...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Clowns-lurked-outside-schools-to-promote-a-speech-16478765.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple clowns have been spotted loitering outside schools in Singapore - staring...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel in Canada is prize for vaxxed and vigilant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-canada-environment-and-nature-coronavirus-pandemic-d00a3ac04df825881223c372899ffd58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KAMOURASKA, Quebec (AP) — When the pandemic descended, the boundless vistas and insane sunsets of Kamouraska became a distant, unattainable dream for this bicyclist from Virginia. This is one of Quebec's most beautiful places and, for me, a yearly touchstone I could no longer touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Sanctions First Exchange...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cybersecurity/2021/09/treasury-sanctions-first-cryptocurrency-exchange-combat-ransomware/185512/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The department also emphasized guidance for victim organizations who risk running afoul of enforcers by paying attackers and failing to report incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Pins Hopes on 'BOND' Director...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/bond-director-cary-fukunaga-no-time-to-die-1235017724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'No Time to Die' helmer on the last-minute decision to move the film, being the first American to steer the franchise and ushering 007 into a post-MeToo era: "You can’t change Bond overnight, but you can change the world around him."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former treasury secretaries tried defusing debt ceiling bomb with McConnell, Yellen...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/09/22/debt-ceiling-yellen-mnuchin-paulson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet freedom on decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/sep/21/internet-freedom-decline-free-speech-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study cited a lack of regulation in the domestic tech industry, and the rise of authoritarian agencies abroad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Woman with no memory found alone on island inhabited by bears...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-with-memory-loss-found-alone-on-island-inhabited-by-bears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Croatian police said Wednesday they have established the identity of a woman who was found in a remote area on a northern Adriatic island with no recollection of who she was or where she came from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man murdered while feeding homeless in Oakland...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/victim-of-east-oakland-homicide-killed-while-feeding-the-homeless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lisa Chavez says Robert Herron found a way to help others despite his own struggles. In her words, he was a success story with a sad ending. He was one of 100 people killed in Oakland this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of organic food market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/22/organic-food-sales-surged-in-2020-higher-demand-and-cheaper-costs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organic food industry is a booming business. U.S. organic sales surged in 2020 by 12.4% to $61.9 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health director says woman tried to run him off road after backed mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/county-health-director-says-woman-tried-to-run-him-off-the-road-after-he-backed-mask-mandate/ar-AAOGdGL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan’s Kent County Health Department Adam London is one of the many health officials who has reported threats and abuse since the start of the covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you 'own' goal? Collectible NFTs rolling into elite soccer...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210922125917-4kjfl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINTECH-NFT/DAPPERLABS:Can you 'own' a goal? Collectible NFTs rolling into elite soccer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided Swiss to vote on same-sex marriage...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210922125616-a1aw7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SWISS-LGBT/MARRIAGE (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Divided Swiss to vote on same-sex marriage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Man Fed Up With Speed Bump Smashes It To Pieces!</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/09/21/brighton-park-speed-bump-smashed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We've all grown frustrated with speed bumps at one time or another, but a Brighton Park man was so fed up with the one behind his house that he removed it piece by piece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRE MOOD AT UN MEETING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-general-assembly-health-china-climate-business-ce8a39b4001eb05e572093cd3b6459a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Racism, the climate crisis and the world’s worsening divisions will take center stage at the United Nations on Wednesday, a day after the U.N. chief issued a grim warning that “we are on the edge of an abyss.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra Butter? Consuming More Dairy Fat May PREVENT Heart Attack, Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dairy-fat-prevent-heart-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An international team finds people who consume higher levels of these fats are less likely to develop cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen target Ukraine president aide in 'assassination attempt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210922-gunmen-target-ukraine-president-aide-in-assassination-attempt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunmen target Ukraine president aide in 'assassination attempt'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain tells food industry to prepare for CO2 price shock...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210922080748-6vlvb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWER-PRICES/BRITAIN-CARBONDIOXIDE (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Britain tells its food industry to prepare for CO2 price shock</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My whole life in van': Islanders flee Spanish volcano...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-africa-environment-and-nature-canary-islands-acid-rain-d60ce64a9d3df03aefa358013415f728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TODOQUE, Canary Islands (AP) — A wall of lava up to 12 meters (40 feet) high bore down on a Spanish village Wednesday as islanders scrambled to save what they could before the molten rock swallowed up their homes following a volcanic eruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS AT WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/22/biden-warring-democratic-factions-513564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many party lawmakers have waited weeks for their president, after a summer largely focused on off-Hill crises, to turn his attention to the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden slips into political quicksand...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/22/biden-haitian-migrant-513561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is bucking calls to stop deportations of Haitians even as his team expresses outrage over images or aggressive treatment by border agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Bush to hold fundraiser for Cheney...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/573331-bush-to-hold-fundraiser-for-cheney</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President George W. Bush is reportedly scheduled to hold a fundraiser for Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Online Betting Boom Carving Up Century-Old U.K. Bookies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/u-s-online-betting-boom-is-carving-up-century-old-u-k-bookies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Online Betting Boom Is Carving Up Century-Old U.K. Bookies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The press ever-so-politely turns on Biden, as troubles mount...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/573322-the-press-ever-so-politely-turns-on-biden-a-troubles-mount</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden is finally getting criticism from the political press, at least as it pertains to the stories they actually cover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States, cities grapple with critical school bus driver shortage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/573288-states-cities-grapple-with-critical-school-bus-driver-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;School districts around the country are struggling to fill thousands of bus driver positions as students return to in-person classes this fall while worker shortages lead to late arrivals and last-minute scrambles to bring retired workers back onto payrolls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Gandolfini and Riddle of Tony Soprano...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/22/michael-gandolfini-and-the-riddle-of-tony-soprano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Michael Gandolfini was filming his role in “The Many Saints of Newark,” a period crime drama that casts him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERGRANDE veers toward default -- and $300 billion global shock...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/china-evergrande-debt-markets/2021/09/22/eeb80fd4-19cc-11ec-bea8-308ea134594f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a pledge to pay some debts due this week, the massive property developer is teetering on the brink of collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel makes late push to secure legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/germany-e2-80-99s-merkel-makes-final-campaign-push-for-stumbling-political-heir/ar-AAOGZBA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armin Laschet has campaigned poorly, threatening Merkel’s legacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil health minister tests positive at UN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-health-minister-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-at-un-general-assembly/ar-AAOGB0w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marcelo Queiroga was accompanying a defiantly unvaccinated President Jair Bolsonaro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Abbott sends miles of cars to deter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/21/us/del-rio-texas-border-crisis/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 8,600 migrants remaining under the Del Rio International Bridge, Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said Tuesday officials are using "unprecedented" methods to deter migrants from crossing into the state, including parking Texas National Guard and Texas Department of Public Safety vehicles for miles along the border to create a "steel barrier."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: Stronger mortgage demand points to surge in home sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/22/stronger-mortgage-demand-points-to-september-surge-in-home-sales.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage demand rose last week as more buyers came into the housing market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, GOOGLE raise new concerns by yanking Russian app...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-europe-business-russia-vladimir-putin-b811d32132c41840e1eb32c024235452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERKELEY, Calif. (AP) — Big Tech companies that operate around the globe have long promised to obey local laws and to protect civil rights while doing business. But when Apple and Google capitulated to Russian demands and removed a political-opposition app from their local app stores, it raised worries that two of the world's most successful companies are more comfortable bowing to undemocratic edicts — and maintaining a steady flow of profits — than upholding the rights of their users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Haitian migrants being released in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-united-states-texas-el-paso-del-rio-3a8146cbcb47b9df7a31a19594df3ec6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas (AP) — Many Haitian migrants camped in a small Texas border town are being released in the United States, two U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S HIS 'IMPEACHMENT' NOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/09/impeachment-american-crime-story-drudge-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After fleshing out Monica Lewinsky and Linda Tripp’s story lines, the series switches focus to Matt Drudge, the controversial figure who outed Bill Clinton’s affair to the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLINTON VICTIMS:  MATT WAS OUR HERO!</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2016/11/02/exclusive-video-broaddrick-willey-jones-praise-hero-drudge-breitbart-slam-mainstream-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victims of Bill Clinton’s alleged sexual assault - Juanita Broaddrick, Kathleen Willey, and Paula Jones - have blasted mainstream news media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insidious new Covid variant found in Kentucky nursing home... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3707195/new-covid-variant-kentucky-nursing-home-mutations-virus-antibodies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW variant of COVID-19 with deadly mutations that give it “increased resistance to antibodies” was discovered in a Kentucky nursing home. The variant, called R.1, infected 45 residen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Sues NEW YORK TIMES and His Niece Over Tax Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/donald-trump-sues-new-york-times-and-his-niece-mary-trump-over-tax-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president claims there was an “insidious plot to obtain confidential and highly-sensitive records.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE HEALTH DRAMA STRIKES WENDY WILLIAMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3705485/wendy-williams-hospitalized-evaluation-weeks-premiere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WENDY Williams is expected to remain under medical evaluation for weeks and her show’s premiere will likely be pushed back yet again after she was hospitalized for psychiatric issues ear…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates Awkwardly Addresses Ties to Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/bill-gates-gives-a-super-cringe-answer-when-confronted-about-his-ties-to-jeffrey-epstein-well-hes-dead-so/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a Tuesday with Judy Woodruff on PBS, Gates appeared to be caught off-guard by a series of questions relating to Epstein.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
