<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rival blasts 'undertone of racism in caucus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/marcia-fudge-speaker_us_5bed9033e4b03af89267a979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fudge, a congresswoman from Ohio, suggests African-Americans in Congress are getting a raw deal from Pelosi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'firmly rejects' diplomatic request to visit internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/china-will-firmly-reject-diplomatic-request-to-visit-uighur-camps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China will “firmly reject” a request from a group of western diplomats seeking to visit a region reportedly suffering under widespread repression, a top diplomat said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Algorithm flips another seat for Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.centralmaine.com/2018/11/15/final-ranked-choice-vote-count-slated-for-noon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.centralmaine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marine Corps veteran wins 50.5 percent of the vote versus 49.5 for incumbent Republican Rep. Bruce Poliquin after the elections results are run through the ranked-choice tabulation software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi taunts rebels...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/pelosi-taunts-critics-support-elected-speaker/story?id=59222261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democratic Leader Nancy Pelosi taunted critics Thursday, saying she still has support to be elected speaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planned to use altered forms to fix mail ballots...</title>
      <link>https://www.naplesnews.com/story/news/politics/2018/11/15/florida-recount-democrats-launch-plan-altered-state-form-fix-ballots/2009178002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.naplesnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Democrats launched plan to give voters altered forms to fix absentee ballots after state deadline in hopes a judge would allow them to count.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT:  Bernie rolls out 'Stop WALMART Act'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bernie-sanders-rolls-out-stop-walmart-act-that-would-block-stock-buybacks-until-retailer-raises-pay-2018-11-15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After his Stop BEZOS Act helped push Amazon to raise pay for its workers, Sen. Bernie Sanders launches a similar effort Thursday that targets Walmart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First lady Melania Trump speaks about civility and good online habits...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/specials/live-video-1?adkey=bn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to employees: 'AMAZON will fail' -- our job to delay...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/bezos-tells-employees-one-day-amazon-will-fail-and-to-stay-hungry.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At an all-hands meeting, Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos was asked what he's learned from the failures of big retailers. Bezos told employees that "Amazon is not too big to fail," and that the company must stay hungry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate confesses to 90 deaths!</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article221716090.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas prosecutor says a man convicted in three California murders but long suspected in dozens of deaths now claims he was involved in about 90 killings nationwide _ about a third of which investigators have corroborated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate accused of killing alleged child molester; Said God 'told me to do it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article221659165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate with schizophrenia at Tarrant County jail charged with killing a notoriously accused child molester said he hears voices, “God and his mother” spoke to him before the killing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach misses election recount deadline after machines stop working...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/palm-beach-likely-to-miss-recount-deadline-after-machines-stop-working-supervisor-sends-technical-manager-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's already farcical recount was dealt yet another blow Thursday when Palm Beach County failed to meet a 3 p.m. deadline, with the election supervisor blaming faulty equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG:  'Tremendous Respect for George Soros'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/digital/news/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-crisis-pr-denial-1203029724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg claimed during a press call Thursday that he wasn’t aware of the company’s relationship with Defenders, a Washington D.C.-based consulting and PR company that was doing…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK says getting better at removing 'hate speech'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e3dbb9561734b4da9b4d3a9ec5c509a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Facebook says it's making progress on deleting hate speech, graphic violence and other violations of its rules and detecting problems before users see them. The company released its second report Thursday detailing how it enforces community standards on hate, nudity and other posts. Compared with its May report, Facebook says it has doubled the amount of hate speech it detects proactively, before users report violations. The new report covers April to September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative outlet files brief in support of White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/416954-conservative-outlet-one-america-news-files-brief-in-support-of-white-house-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of conservative outlet One America News Network (OANN) said Thursday that the organization will file an amicus brief in support of the White House as it faces a lawsuit from CNN over the revocation of reporter Jim Acosta's press pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMY SCHUMER HOSPITALIZED...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/15/amy-schumer-hospitalized-for-pregnancy-issue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details emerging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman injured in SPAGHETTIOs assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtae.com/article/spaghettios-assault-one-woman-injured-another-facing-charges-following-incident-in-pittsburgh/25119804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtae.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other people may face charges as investigation continues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surviving An Active Shooter -- Now A College Course...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/11/14/surviving-an-active-shooter-now-part-of-college-coursework/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say mass shootings are now so frequent, everyone should be prepared for how to react and get to safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War-zone DNA specialists called in...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dna-firm-schooled-war-zones-helps-id-california-110526283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With many of them likely burned beyond recognition, traditional DNA analysis techniques are inadequate, as they require samples to be shipped to a laboratory and take weeks to produce a DNA match. In addition, traditional tools sometimes fail when extreme heat damages tissue samples. As a consequence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump visits Marine Barracks and speaks about supporting military families...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-visits-marines-responded-recent-dc-fire-171350940--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump paid a visit Thursday to the Marine Barracks and met with Marines who responded to a fire at a local public housing complex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon fails first ever audit...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pentagon-fails-first-ever-audit-official-says-182503527--business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon has failed what is being called its first-ever comprehensive audit, a senior official said on Thursday, finding U.S. Defense Department accounting discrepancies that could take years to resolve. Results of the inspection - conducted by some 1,200 auditors and examining financial accounting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents charged with using kids' identities to rack up debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/parents-charged-using-kids-identities-rack-debt-175542057.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATH, N.Y. (AP) — New York State Police say a couple racked up nearly $10,000 in unpaid utility bills and credit card debts using the man's son name, destroying his credit rating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD's Worker Charged In Bacon Attack On Manager...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/mcdonalds-bacon-assault-902851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOVEMBER 15--A McDonald’s cook tried to “shove hot crispy bacon” in the face of her manager during a confrontation Friday that resulted in an assault and battery charge being filed against the worker,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music legend Roy Clark dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/roy-clark-country-music-legend-and-hee-haw-star-dead-at-85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country star Roy Clark, the legendary singer and guitar player who headlined the cornpone TV show "Hee Haw" for nearly a quarter century has died. He was 85.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost DISNEY film showing Mickey Mouse predecessor found in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/lost-disney-film-showing-mickey-mouses-predecessor-found-080617483.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Yasushi Watanabe bought a cartoon film decades ago as a high school student in the Japanese city of Osaka, he had no idea he was purchasing animation history. The discovery was reported by Japan's Asahi Shimbun daily, which Watanabe contacted after reading a book about the history of "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First woman makes it through Army Special Forces selection...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2018/11/14/a-female-soldier-has-made-it-through-the-armys-special-forces-selection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since the Army opened its special operations jobs to women in 2016, a female soldier has completed the initial Special Forces Assessment and Selection process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy SEALs, Marines Charged With Green Beret's Murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/seals-marines-charged-with-green-beret-logan-melgars-murder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim allegedly discovered SEALs in Mali were stealing money from an informant fund and soliciting prostitutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House weighs booting Erdogan foe from USA to appease Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/white-house-weighs-booting-erdogan-foe-u-s-appease-turkey-n933996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Once they realized it was a serious request, the career guys were furious," a U.S. official said of request tied to Khashoggi killing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT CHAOS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181115164414-jv8tx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (UPDATE 11, PIX, TV):UPDATE 11-British PM May fights to save Brexit deal and her job</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu faces snap election calls after defense minister quits...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181115163311-2570b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/ (PIX):Netanyahu faces snap election calls after defence minister quits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA orders restriction on e-cigarette sales; youth use surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-orders-restriction-e-cigarette-sales-youth-surges-163625321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US regulators Thursday ordered sharp restrictions on sales of e-cigarettes, as national data showed a 78 percent single-year surge in vaping among young people, with two-thirds using fruit and candy-flavored products. The proposed regulations announced by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Castigates Mueller Investigation as 'Disgrace to Nation'; Probe 'Total Mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-seethes-against-russia-probe-disgrace-152133360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diatribe came amid claims that Trump is maneuvering to have Mueller fired or otherwise shut down before he can close in on the president and his inner circle, including family members. Last week, Trump sacked his attorney general Jeff Sessions, replacing him with Matthew Whitaker, who is on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazi's attorney calls ruling dangerous for free speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/neo-nazis-attorney-calls-ruling-dangerous-free-speech-162743650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA, Mont. (AP) — The attorney for a neo-Nazi website's founder says a judge's decision to allow a lawsuit to proceed against his client is "dangerous for free speech."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa National Guard soldiers told to return overpaid wages...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/iowa-national-guard-soldiers-told-return-overpaid-wages-155911765.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVENPORT, Iowa (AP) — Hundreds of Iowa National Guard soldiers have been told they were overpaid after a year-long deployment in the Middle East and must make immediate plans to repay the money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires head for exit at Miami tower...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-miamis-billionaire-bunker-another-wealthy-buyer-heads-for-the-exit-1542298197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real-estate developer Edward J. Minskoff is asking $16.5 million for his apartment at Faena House, a condominium tower that drew diplomats, billionaires and financiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNTRY MUSIC Awards Ratings Fall to All-Time Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cma-awards-down-34-percent-record-low/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC's CMA Awards took a tumble(weed) on Wednesday, plummeting 34% in TV ratings from 2017. The special was down 30% year over year in total viewers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO-CORTEZ: They're mistaking me for an intern!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/ocasio-cortez-theyre-mistaking-me-for-an-intern/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Democratic Representative-elect Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez may be a big hit with the media and younger crowd, but she’s not receiving any special treatment on Capitol Hill. The 29-year-old socialist is in Washington, D.C., this week for orientation. She and other newly elected officials are touring the Capitol building, meeting with lawmakers, and learning the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Gas Prices Highest Levels In 4 Years...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/11/14/natural-gas-prices-spike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost to heat most homes in Minnesota and Wisconsin may go up this winter. Natural gas prices jumped to their highest in four years Wednesday. Low supply and a frigid forecast may be to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troop levels at Mexico border likely at peak - commander...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-mattis-troops-exclusi/exclusive-u-s-troop-levels-at-mexico-border-likely-at-peak-commander-idUSKCN1NK0ID</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of U.S. troops at the border with Mexico may have peaked at about 5,8...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Dallas Cowboy comes out as gay, set to become first NFL player in same-sex marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.outsports.com/2018/11/14/18067464/jeff-rohrer-gay-dallas-cowboys-nfl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Rohrer played for the legendary Tom Landry. As he marries his boyfriend, his Cowboys teammates have his back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case Reveals Shame, Trauma of MALE Sex Trafficking Victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2018-11-15/case-reveals-shame-trauma-of-male-sex-trafficking-victims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince William slams FACEBOOK:  'Profits before values'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7749062/prince-william-intervention-accuses-facebook-profit-before-values/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE William has today accused Facebook and other social media giants of being “on the back foot” and putting their “profits before values”. The 36-year-old said he is “worried” because huge tech…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guard troops search for more CA wildfire victims; 56 dead... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/Wildfires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gray wolf population could lose federal protection under Republican bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article221647280.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gray wolves in Washington could lose their endangered species listing, and the habitat protection that comes with it, if Republicans succeed in passing a new bill through Congress. The bill’s proponents say the wolf population has recovered, but conservationists disagree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate captured at IHOP after escaping jail with help from mom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbs46.com/news/crime/police-locate-mother-and-son-who-escaped-from-jail/article_f223ee68-e85b-11e8-a002-6735cc4d8936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbs46.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newnan, Ga (CBS46) Deputies in Newnan have located 54-year-old Kathy Pence who helped her son, 27-year-old Joshua Gullatt, escape from his prison work detail on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shouts 'Heil Hitler' during 'FIDDLER ON ROOF' show...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/entertainment/bs-md-ci-hippodrome-20181114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man shouted a pro-Nazi and pro-Trump salute during a performance of “Fiddler on the Roof” at Baltimore’s Hippodrome Theatre on Wednesday night. Audience members feared the worst was about to happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer whales share personality traits with humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/killer-whales-share-personality-traits-13594766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These personality traits are similar because of the advanced cognitive abilities needed for complex social interactions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Castigates Mueller Investigation as 'Disgrace to Nation'; Probe 'Total Mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-castigates-mueller-investigation-as-disgrace-to-nation-says-probe-is-total-mess-1542292248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump asserted that special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election is in complete disarray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMCAST fires employee who is allegedly 'Proud Boys' member...</title>
      <link>https://www.phillymag.com/news/2018/11/14/comcast-fires-proud-boys-employee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.phillymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The YSL Documentary Pierre Berge Did Not Want Anyone to See...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/14/fashion/yves-saint-laurent-celebration-documentary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Bergé, the partner of Yves Saint Laurent, suppressed the film for years, but it is finally reaching theaters this month. Here’s what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA restricts sales of most flavored e-cigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/15/fda-restricts-most-flavored-e-cigarette-sales-pursues-menthol-ban.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Food and Drug Administration Commissioner Scott Gottlieb outlined a slew of policies, including restrictions on sales of flavored e-cigarettes, and essentially threatened to pull products from the market if manufacturers do not follow them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands without power...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/15/winter-storm-moves-midwest-east-coast-bringing-power-outages-school-closings/2009881002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pre-winter storm is blamed for five deaths. It's also leaving a trail of closed schools, traffic headaches and power outages across much of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why Are Young People Having So Little Sex?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2018/12/the-sex-recession/573949/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the easing of taboos and the rise of hookup apps, Americans are in the midst of a sex recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Burton's Live-Action 'DUMBO' Trailer Introduces Rest of Circus...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/dumbo-trailer-disney-releases-new-glimpse-tim-burton-movie-1161378</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though plot details are being kept closely under wraps, early descriptions of the film suggest that it's following some plot points of the original.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE SCENARIOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Dump-May-Approve-her-plan-Some-scenarios-for-13394680.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - Theresa May's premiership has been declared dead before. After her election losses last year, the British Prime Minister appeared to be on the brink of resigning. As she left 10 Downing Street on Thursday morning, members of her own party once again wondered: How long can she last? In the early morning hours, several British ministers resigned over May's deal to leave the European Union, which was released on Wednesday. Theresa May likely expected some resignations, but one came unexpectedly: Dominic Raab, her second Brexit minister. With the official who negotiated May's Brexit deal writing that he "cannot support the proposed deal," the British government was suddenly thrown into jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ARGUES: CAN BAN ALL REPORTERS FROM WHITE HOUSE!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/14/white-house-trump-has-broad-discretion-to-regulate-journalists-access-989916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'If the president wants to exclude all reporters from the White House grounds, he has the authority to do that,' a lawyer for the administration said during a hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana breaks records...</title>
      <link>https://www.wwltv.com/article/weather/parts-of-louisiana-breaks-records-with-early-snow/289-614431369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wwltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meteorologists say Wednesday's snowfall of as much as a half-inch across northeastern Louisiana broke the previous record set on Nov. 24, 1950.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Will Behead Khashoggi Killers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6392951/Jamal-Khashoggis-accused-killers-face-death-penalty-Saudi-prosecutor-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia's public prosecutor is seeking the death penalty against five suspects the regime accuses of murdering journalist Jamal Khashoggi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The drag queen Eagle Scout who dances on mountaintops...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/14/pattie-gonia-drag-queen-mountaineer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Balancing on cliffs in 6in heels, the ‘world’s first backpacking queen’ amassed 30,000 Instagram followers in a month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUP!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/politics/742629/theresa-may-brexit-statement-parliament-resignations-latest-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Database To Use Loyalty Rewards To Identify Shoppers...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-14/national-facial-recognition-database-use-loyalty-rewards-identify-american-shoppers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 million in path...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/14/winter-storm-roar-deep-south-new-england/2002785002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deadly winter storm will bring a messy mix of snow, sleet and freezing rain to portions of the central and eastern U.S. over the next two days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN: Money-making hypocrisy laughable...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/michelle-obamas-money-making-hypocrisy-is-laughable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — To read the worshipful press coverage you’d never know that, for Democrats, the unthinkable has happened: Michelle Obama has revealed herself as just another guru for sale. On Tuesday nig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI CAN FAKE FINGERPRINT...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/15/fake-fingerprints-can-imitate-real-fingerprints-in-biometric-systems-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeepMasterPrints created by a machine learning technique have error rate of only one in five</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURDER ON CARIBBEAN CRUISE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6390117/Husband-arrested-Aruba-choking-wife-throwing-cruise-ship-severing-leg.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American man was hauled off the Royal Princess cruise ship by investigators in Aruba on Wednesday morning on suspicion of killing the 52-year-old woman. They had departed from Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norovirus outbreak at shelter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/norovirus-outbreak-confirmed-at-california-wildfire-shelter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say there has been an outbreak of norovirus at a shelter housing people who evacuated their homes to escape the massive wildfire in Northern California. Butte County public health spokesw…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm animals may soon get new features through gene editing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f628e7c65c794995b19977b7c1cdc10c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKFIELD, N.Y. (AP) — Cows that can withstand hotter temperatures. Cows born without pesky horns. Pigs that never reach puberty. A company wants to alter farm animals by adding and subtracting genetic traits in a lab. It sounds like science fiction, but Recombinetics sees opportunity for its technology in the livestock industry. But first, it needs to convince regulators that gene-edited animals are no different than conventionally bred ones. To make the technology appealing and to ease any fears that it may be creating Franken-animals, Recombinetics isn't starting with productivity. Instead, it's introducing gene-edited traits as a way to ease animal suffering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadlines looming in pivotal, rancorous Florida recounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/058c5f727bab45be9372110fbba9c07a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida's bumpy election recount reaches a pivotal point Thursday as most counties across the state complete reviews that could determine the next senator and governor in one of America's top political battlegrounds. Barring a dramatic last minute court-mandated extension, Florida counties face a 3 p.m. deadline to wrap up their machine recounts. Some counties, such as the Democratic stronghold of Palm Beach County, have warned that they may not be able to make the deadline. Lawsuits that could spur further delays are still swirling, including one filed by U.S. Sen. Bill Nelson and Democrats that seeks to set aside the looming deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMUTER HELL: Transit riders, drivers brace for influx of AMAZON employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/transit-riders-drivers-brace-influx-060126549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commuters beware: New York and Washington's clogged streets and creaky subway systems are about to feel more pain as 50,000 more people descend on the two metro areas where Amazon will open new headquarters. An expansion of that scope in a city such as New York — where the regional subway, bus and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record tick diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/record-number-of-tickborne-diseases-lyme-disease-reported-in-us-2017/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the CDC shows that tickborne diseases like Lyme and Rocky Mountain spotted fever continue to rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSURGENTS SEEK FEMALE</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/416836-insurgents-seek-female-challenger-to-replace-pelosi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anti-Pelosi insurgents are coalescing around a new strategy in their quest to deny Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) the Speaker's gavel: recruit a woman to run against her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The looming threat to Trump boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/15/trump-economy-federal-reserve-tax-cuts-deficit-trade-967501</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sugar high — from tax cuts and other stimulus — is expected to wear off in the coming year, constricting economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia to Seek Death Penalty for Khashoggi Killers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/15/saudi-prosecutor-seeks-death-penalty-in-jamal-khashoggi-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Death penalty sought for five out of 11 suspects charged with the journalist’s murder</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meal of 50 Courses Over 6 Hours. Future of Dining?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/a-meal-of-50-courses-over-6-hours-is-this-the-future-of-dining#gs.tH0Yoo8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Meal of 50 Courses Over 6 Hours. Is This the Future of Dining?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rest easy: No link between insomnia and early death...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/no-link-between-insomnia-and-early-death-according-to-largest-study-r577335n9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is one less thing to worry about in the small hours. There is no link between insomnia and an early death, according to the largest study of its kind. The analysis of 37 million people found...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Supervolcano Headed For 'Large Volume Eruption'; Magma Building...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/campi-flegrei-magma-building-beneath-dangerous-supervolcano-could-signal-huge-1213424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
POUND PLUNGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-46219038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sterling loses about 1% against both dollar and the euro after Dominic Raab and Esther McVey quit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT CHAOS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181115103419-avfed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-British PM May suffers severe blow over Brexit as ministers quit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginkgo Supplement Was Ginkgo-Free, Watchdog Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ginkgo-supplement-was-ginkgo-free-u-s-watchdog-finds-1542239276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two dietary supplements promoted as improving memory using Ginkgo biloba contained either none of the ingredient or a lower amount than advertised, a federal watchdog said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>68% of Americans quit or taken break from socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/bailey-richardson-decided-to-quit-instagram-this-year-she-also-helped-create-the-social-media-app-1947551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the evening of Sept. 26, Bailey Richardson logged in to Instagram for the last time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO MORE GAVEL?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/pelosi-faces-daunting-challenge-in-speakers-bid-as-democratic-foes-stand-firm/2018/11/14/29c1e018-e83a-11e8-a939-9469f1166f9d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an electoral year marked by a record number of women joining the House, incoming female Democrats may help decide Nancy Pelosi’s fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump lawyers, CNN square off in federal court in Jim Acosta case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/media/cnn-trump-lawsuit-hearing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first hearing in CNN and Jim Acosta's federal lawsuit against President Trump and several top White House aides ended with the judge saying that he would rule on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell Says Fed Deserves Credit for Economic Growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/powell-credits-fed-policy-for-the-us-economy-being-in-a-good-place.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell expressed confidence in U.S. economic strength Wednesday and said markets will have to get used to the idea that the central bank could raise rates at any time starting in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Sees Uptick In Travelers Packing Turkeys Into Bags...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/13/tsa-expecting-record-setting-crowds-during-thanksgiving-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines and the TSA are not just expecting big crowds, but record setting crowds during this year's Thanksgiving travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI ON THE BRINK?	</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pelosi-challenges-unhappy-dems-block-her-bid-speaker-175012347--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As a steadfast Rep. Nancy Pelosi all but dared potential rivals for the gavel to come forward, a group of restive House Democrats vowed Wednesday to produce enough votes to block her from becoming the House's new speaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earliest Houston snowfall ever!</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/local/snow-vember-the-earliest-houston-snowfall-ever-just-happened/285-614153347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your eyes didn't deceive you -- it snowed in Houston today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-breathing premature baby revived by police officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/11/14/non-breathing-premature-born-boy-revived-by-oakland-police-officer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oakland police officer is being credited with saving the life of an infant boy, who he revived when the child stopped breathing after being born prematurely inside a car Tuesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant sues AMERICAN AIRLINES, says she was dragged down aisle mid-flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/american-airlines-flight-attendant-suing-scarf-assault-drag-down-aisle-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American Airlines flight attendant is suing the Fort Worth, Texas-based airline over a 2016 altercation with another crew member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE wants virtual assistant in every room of house...</title>
      <link>http://www.weny.com/story/39479577/google-wants-its-virtual-assistant-in-every-room-of-your-house </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Heather Kelly, CNN Business</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold San Antonio 'shatters' 102-year-old record...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/weather/article/Icy-San-Antonio-weather-shatters-102-year-old-13391345.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Antonio reached a low of 23 degrees at the International Airport this morning, which ties for the fourth coldest November low temperature on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK TURNS BEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/apple-bellwether-for-technology-stocks-falls-into-a-bear-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple dipped into a bear market on Wednesday as shares added to a 20 percent decline from recent all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 Buses with 900 More Near Border... </title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/14/22-buses-with-900-caravan-migrants-nears-u-s-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 900 Central Americans in 22 buses arrived in the northern border state of Sonora, escorted by state and federal police on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast, South brace for winter storm...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2018-11-14-winter-storm-avery-snow-ice-east-midwest-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With cold air in place, a wintry mess is moving in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flake vows to oppose judges unless Mueller protection bill gets vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/28c5f8d772fd4b3097e152c025336fd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Republican Sen. Jeff Flake said Wednesday that he won't vote to confirm judicial nominees unless GOP leaders hold a vote on legislation to protect special counsel Robert Mueller from being fired. Flake of Arizona and Democratic Sen. Chris Coons of Delaware went to the Senate floor on Wednesday and tried to bring the legislation up for a vote. But Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell objected. McConnell has said that the legislation is unnecessary because he believes Mueller won't be fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE downgraded, more iPhone estimates cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/apple-gets-downgraded-more-iphone-estimates-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guggenheim downgraded Apple to neutral from buy and removed its prior $245 price target. UBS cut its 12-month price target on Apple to $225 from $240 and lowered iPhone unit sales estimates for the current quarter to 73.5 million from 75 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DENIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/michael-avenatti-denies-alleged-domestic-violence-ive-never-been-physically-abusive-in-my-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVENATTI ARRESTED FOR DOMESTIC VIOLENCE...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2018/11/14/official-michael-avenatti-in-los-angeles-police-custody-on-domestic-violence-allegation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Avenatti, who skyrocketed to fame as a critic of President Donald Trump and the lawyer for porn actress Stormy Daniels, was released on bail after being arrested Wednesday and booked on a felony domestic violence charge, Los Angeles police said. The victim in the case had visible injuries, according to Officer Tony Im, a police spokesman. But Avenatti slammed the allegation as "completely bogus" in a statement released by his law firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She hit me first!'</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/11/14/michael-avenatti-arrested-domestic-violence-stormy-daniels-attorney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Avenatti was arrested for felony domestic violence against a woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crypto civil war' slams bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/14/bkcm-brian-kelly-crypto-civil-war-slams-bitcoin-but-not-for-long.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin had been coasting in recent months on fairly low volatility until "things exploded," says the cryptocurrency fund manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic bishops leave conference without acting on abuse reforms...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/news/catholic-bishops-baltimore-sex-abuse-cardinal-theodore-mccarrick-20181114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing the prospect of leaving their most closely watched gathering in years with no consensus response to the sex abuse crisis that has gripped their church since summer, the nation's Catholic bishops pushed Wednesday for something – anything – they might approve to show they were taking the problem seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURDER ON CRUISE SHIP SAILING IN CARIBBEAN?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/cruises/2018/11/14/princess-cruises-woman-dies-fall-ship-royal-princess/2001881002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American woman aboard a Princess Cruises ship died Tuesday in what authorities are treating as a possible murder case, according to several news outlets in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBC votes no confidence in DNC Perez...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/14/congressional-black-caucus-tom-perez-991270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cedric Richmond said members “felt that the DNC pitted them against their constituents.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Thanksgiving nears, mystery of drug-resistant Salmonella in turkey persists...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/as-thanksgiving-nears-regulators-food-processors-grapple-with-ongoing-salmonella-threat-in-turkey/500506282/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota has reported 17 cases, the most of any state. With Thanksgiving a week away, federal officials aren't telling consumers to stop eating turkey, but they are stressing the importance of proper handling and cooking techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock-Market Supercomputer to Launch With Glitches...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stock-market-supercomputer-to-launch-with-glitches-1542236446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A data warehouse created to track all U.S. stock market orders is expected to launch on Thursday with limited functionality because the contractor in charge of it hasn’t been able to make it reliably searchable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Dems 'Dog Whistle' Tactics Against Clyburn...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article221666375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after Rep. Jim Clyburn, D-South Carolina, accused detractors of using racially-motivated “dog whistle” tactics to undermine his bid to be House majority whip, Rep. Steny Hoyer, D-Maryland, came to his defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi battle for Speakership votes...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-congress-pelosi-speaker-20181114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi is whipping votes to try to regain the gavel as House speaker. More than a dozen Democrats have come out against her, and the result remains uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Filing confirms investigation will extend into next year...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mueller-isnt-done-former-trump-campaign-aide-gates-222015853.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Robert Mueller isn't done with former Trump campaign aide Rick Gates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafty crook fished $400K  out of PO boxes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/14/crafty-crook-fished-400k-in-checks-out-of-postal-boxes-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queens is a great spot to go fishing — for checks, that is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putino MILITARY CHURCH to bolster patriotism, spirituality...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1045323/russia-news-military-church-vladimir-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has unveiled plans to build a military church as Moscow seeks to reinforce the value of “patriotism, love, and devotion to our Motherland” into troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service loss TRIPLES as package deliveries rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-postal-service-results/u-s-postal-service-loss-triples-even-as-package-deliveries-rise-idUSKCN1NJ2HS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Postal Service lost almost $4 billion in 2018 even as package deliverie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'War on Terror' price tag to top $6,000,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2018/11/14/price-tag-of-the-war-on-terror-will-top-6-trillion-soon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The figure is several times higher than official Pentagon reports on war spending because it includes VA benefits and other related expenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guidance overhaul on college sex assault gives new rights to accused...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-betsy-devos-college-sexual-assaults-20181114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Education Secretary Betsy DeVos is set to release a sweeping overhaul of how colleges and universities must handle allegations of sexual assault and harassment.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
