<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>As Merkel prepares to leave office, many think Germany 'golden age' over...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/germanys-golden-age-is-over-most-europeans-think-as-merkel-leaves.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Europeans believe the Germany's "golden age" is over just as Chancellor Merkel prepares to leave office — including a majority of Germans, a poll shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin keeps Washington guessing on what he wants...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/572504-manchin-keeps-washington-guessing-on-what-he-wants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight over Democrats' $3.5 trillion spending bill is reviving one of Washington’s most perennial questions: What does Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) want?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 101, she's still hauling lobsters with no plans to stop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-oddities-maine-61b5c7bd559a5636e840c206cb990a32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCKLAND, Maine (AP) — When Virginia Oliver started trapping lobster off Maine’s rocky coast, World War II was more than a decade in the future, the electronic traffic signal was a recent invention and few women were harvesting lobsters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CRY MACHO' Test: Will Clint Eastwood's Fans Choose Theaters or Streaming?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cry-macho-will-clint-eastwoods-loyal-fans-choose-theaters-or-hbo-max/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eastwood's films have historically attracted older moviegoers from red states, but his core audience might take the streaming option this time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit's historic female genital cutting case is in limbo...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2021/09/15/detroit-female-genital-mutilation-case-doctor-jumana-nagarwala/8343451002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government is seeking to revive its historic female genital mutilation case with new charges. But the defense is pushing back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea release images of missiles being launched from train...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/north-korea-releases-terrifying-images-24995680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The images come after North Korea launched two deadly ballistic missiles towards Japan on Wednesday. Intelligences agencies are investigating the testing but no one was harmed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump still wins elections  -- for Dems?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/newsletter/2021-09-15/national-lessons-from-californias-recall-essential-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recall campaign offered insights that will inform strategies over the next 14 months. Here are three:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Newsom defeated recall: Early leads in suburbs, overwhelming margins in big cities...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-defeated-recall-early-leads-172700965.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of the more than 9.1 million votes tabulated as of early Wednesday, nearly 64% were in favor of keeping Gov. Gavin Newsom in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, Australia, UK unveil new security partnership as Beijing expands military, influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/us-uk-australia-unveil-new-security-partnership-as-china-expands-military.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new trilateral security partnership seeks to strengthen stability in the Indo-Pacific region as China expands its military might and influence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gymnasts offer scathing assessment of FBI...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/572452-us-gymnasts-offer-scathing-assessment-of-fbi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star U.S. gymnasts offered stark criticism Wednesday of the FBI's handling of its investigation into sexual assault and harassment in the U.S. gymnastics program, prompting criticism from lawmakers of the Department of Justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Clinically Dead For 45 Minutes Miraculously Brought Back To Life...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/09/14/baltimore-county-woman-is-brought-back-to-life-after-a-medical-miracle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Baltimore County woman is calling it a medical miracle after being brought back to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German police responding to possible synagogue threat... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/german-police-say-they-are-responding-possible-threat-synagogue-2021-09-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Germany said they had received information about a possible threat to a synagogue in the western town of Hagen and had put appropriate measures in place to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENDEAVOR's Growing Pains...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/endeavor-ipo-ari-emanuel-public-1235065405/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Endeavor defied its critics and the odds by successfully pulling off a public offering in April, but the company — a hodgepodge of live-events brands and talent representation — is facing major obs…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-national security officials funded by big tech claim antitrust laws would hurt USA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/15/ex-national-security-officials-claim-antitrust-laws-would-hurt-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former officials argue the measures could undermine the US in its competition with China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major NFT Marketplace Admits Employee Did Insider Trading...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxj43/major-nft-marketplace-admits-employee-used-insider-knowledge-to-profit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An OpenSea employee bought NFTs before they were promoted on the marketplace's homepage, which angered traders have compared to insider trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalio says if bitcoin really successful, regulators will 'kill it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/ray-dalio-says-if-bitcoin-is-really-successful-regulators-will-kill-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ray Dalio said regulators would ultimately take control of bitcoin if the cryptocurrency gains mainstream success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Australian fires boost carbon-capturing algae...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australian-fires-boosted-c02-carbon-171926968.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devastating Australian wildfires released twice as much climate-warming C02 than previously thought -- but also triggered vast algae blooms thousands of miles away that may have soaked up significant extra carbon, according to studies published Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Strategy Offers Republicans Warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/newsom-s-anti-trump-recall-strategy-offers-a-warning-for-2022-midterms/ar-AAOsJy0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN LEANDRO, Calif. — California basks in its clairvoyance. “The future happens here first,” says Gov. Gavin Newsom, calling his state “America’s coming attraction.” By emphatically turning back the effort to recall him from office, however, Mr. Newsom made clear that California’s cherished role presaging the politics of tomorrow was not as significant as another, larger factor in Tuesday’s results: the tribal politics of today. The first-term...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops face discipline for selfies with rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article254245798.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘If you want to take a photo, I’m not going to say no because we are always told to interact and keep the situation calm,’ one officer told investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER pushes for boosters...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pfizer-covid-vaccine-boosters-fda-approval-69ff9870-5e9a-4099-98ff-24085091cc7f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA's advisory committee is expected to review Pfizer's clinical trials on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How inflation is hitting cost of everything...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/how-inflation-is-hitting-online-prices-of-apparel-to-furniture.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prices of goods online have now risen for an unprecedented 15 consecutive months, following what was a historical period of declines, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Surges After Company Switches To 4-Day Work Week...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/14/dockwa-4-day-work-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The start-up company says since switching to a four-day work week, the numbers speak for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German election website hacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/german-election-commission-website-briefly-hacked-report-679590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top CEOs earned 351 times more than typical worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/15/in-2020-top-ceos-earned-351-times-more-than-the-typical-worker.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since 1978, CEO compensation has grown 1,322%, but typical worker compensation has risen 18%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 500 Americans have died of Covid since 1st infection...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/us-covid-deaths-how-many-americans-died-from-coronavirus-vaccine-cases/11022232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Tuesday night, 663,913 people in the US have died of COVID-19, according to Johns Hopkins University data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer whale 'committed suicide' by repeatedly ramming head against tank...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3667235/killer-whale-hugo-committed-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUGO the killer whale was said to have been so unhappy in his captivity at an aquarium that he slammed his head into the wall of his tank until he died. The orca suffered a brain aneurysm after rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swift growth of Latinos reshaping big states, small towns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/specials/new-latino-landscape/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The swift growth of U.S. Latinos is reshaping big states and small towns. Meet the faces of a new era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JENNER:  'You get the government you deserve'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/politics/1004868/caitlyn-jenner-tells-californians-who-voted-to-keep-newsom-you-kind-of-get-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://money.com/collection/best-places-to-live-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We found the Best Places to Live in 2021-2022 after analyzing data points regarding economic stability, cost-of-living, cultural diversity, safety, and education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chanhassen, MN Named 'Best Place To Live In America'...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/09/15/chanhassen-named-best-place-to-live-in-the-country-according-to-money-magazine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money Magazine has named Chanhassen the best place to live in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 out of 3 adults in TX!</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article254256643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC revealed an updated map showing which states have an adult obesity prevalence at or above 35%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest Living WWII Vet Turns 112, Says Key To Long Life Is Being Nice To Others...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/09/13/lawrence-brooks-americas-oldest-living-wwii-vet-112-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence Brooks, who was part of a Black army battalion, had a drive-by celebration at his New Orleans home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA LAUNCHES</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-north-korea-fires-unidentified-24986872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launch came after North Korea said it successfully tested a new long-range cruise missile last weekend, calling it "a strategic weapon of great significance"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Praises FOXNEWS for 90% Staff Vaccination, Daily Testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/14/media/white-house-fox-covid-policy-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSOM WINS IN BLOWOUT...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/photos-californians-stream-polls-recall-235042804.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California voters overwhelmingly rejected the attempt to remove Gov. Gavin Newsom before the end of his term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Developing 'Superhuman Immunity' Against Covid...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/09/14/researchers-superhuman-immunity-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s a descriptive term for an individual to generate very high amounts of neutralizing antibodies,” Dr. Mohanakrishnan Sathyamoorthy, Chair of Internal Medicine, TCU and UNTHSC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of states with high obesity rate doubles since '18...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/572357-number-of-states-with-high-obesity-prevalence-nearly-doubles-since-2018-cdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of states with an obesity rate of at least 35 percent has nearly doubled in two years, with continuing racial and ethnic disparities, according to research released by the Centers for Disease Control</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Unseat Trudeau, Canada's Top Conservative Leans Left...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/15/to-unseat-trudeau-canadas-top-conservative-leans-left/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA — The leader of Canada’s Conservative Party, Erin O’Toole, lacks the name recognition, celebrity pedigree and charismatic hair of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Shasta nearly snowless; Rare event helping melt glaciers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/mount-shasta-is-nearly-snowless-a-rare-event-that-is-helping-melt-the-mountain-s-glaciers/ar-AAOteLF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shasta’s glaciers have lost more than 50 percent of their volume and area in this 21st century, with 2021 as the largest year of volume loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GMA' Staffer Claims ABC Retaliated Against Her After Sex Assault Complaint...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/abc-news-michael-corn-lawsuit-good-morning-america-1234833941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer on Good Morning America has filed a new claim against ABC, contending that the network retaliated against her after she filed a formal complaint alleging that the show’s top produce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average American Sleeps Poorly 3 Nights A Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/average-american-sleeps-poorly-3-nights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four in five workers believe the quality of sleep they get at night directly sets the tone for the following day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Worst Pitch in MLB History?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/watch-pitcher-throws-the-ultimate-blooper-and-nearly-hits-himself-with-worst-pitch-in-mlb-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Royals trailing Oakland 7-4, reliever Jake Brentz opened the frame with a strike, before throwing what might be the worst pitch in MLB history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WEST SIDE STORY' Drops Grandiose Trailer for Spielberg Remake...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/west-side-story-trailer-steven-spielberg-remake-1235014279/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20th Century film is due in theaters Dec. 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shari Redstone Radical PARAMOUNT Overhaul Sets Up Clash With Filmmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/paramount-overhaul-sets-up-clash-with-filmmakers-1235013964/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the ViacomCBS mogul ousts film chief Jim Gianopulos, insiders expect the legacy studio to start churning out low-cost, often mediocre features for streamer Paramount+.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital doggies: Pet influencers on rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/digital-doggies-pet-influencers-rise-024806664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two fluffy white terriers wearing neckerchiefs pant quietly as their owner waves a treat and snaps a photo for the dogs' tens of thousands of Instagram followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'70s are back in '21...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/opinions-the-70s-are-back-in-2021-but-not-in-the-way-you-think/ar-AAOsViH </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor will sign religious exemption for vax if donate to his church...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/this-pastor-will-sign-a-religious-exemption-for-vaccines-if-you-donate-to-his-church/ar-AAOsOMt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pastor is a 29-year-old small-business owner running in the Republican primary challenge to Sen. James Lankford (Okla.) in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake news to fan culture: Beijing lays out what's allowed on 'Marxist civilized' Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/from-fake-news-to-fan-culture-china-lays-out-what-e2-80-99s-allowed-on-a-e2-80-98marxist-civilized-internet/ar-AAOsgmX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's over-arching idea is to ensure online content abides by “the guiding status of Marxism in the ideological cyberspace sphere,”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priciest Food Since '70s Big Challenge for Govts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/priciest-food-since-1970s-is-a-big-challenge-for-governments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Europe to Turkey and India, politicians are now handing out more aid, ordering sellers to cut prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival Koreas test missiles hours apart...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seoul-south-korea-north-korea-pyongyang-1bf74218556e36697983cf6669ec9166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North and South Korea tested ballistic missiles hours apart Wednesday in a display of military might that is sure to exacerbate tensions between the rivals at a time when talks aimed at stripping the North of its nuclear program are stalled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Westerns Enter New Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/15/movies/the-harder-they-fall-black-westerns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The genre dates back decades, when the films were made for segregated audiences. “The Harder They Fall” nods to the past but takes a new attitude altogether.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions wiped from Macau casino stocks as city eyes gambling review...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/macau-casino-stocks-tumble-as-city-proposes-gambling-industry-crackdown/ar-AAOs6Tp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macau casino operators saw billions wiped off their value Wednesday as their shares collapsed after officials in the world's biggest gambling city unveiled plans for a crackdown that would tighten their grip on the already beleaguered industry. The move comes as the government in mainland China embarks on a crackdown on a wide range of industries -- including tech and private education firms -- as it looks to tighten its grip on the world's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan jets land on highway for invasion wargame...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taiwan-jets-land-highway-chinese-055654323.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fighter jets practised landing on a highway in southern Taiwan on Wednesday as part of an annual live-fire military exercise that simulates defending the island against an invasion by China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Strategy Offers Republicans Warning...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/15/newsoms-anti-trump-recall-strategy-offers-republicans-a-warning-for-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN LEANDRO, Calif. — California basks in its clairvoyance. “The future happens here first,” says Gov. Gavin Newsom, calling his</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
