<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Record gas prices pushing up everyday costs, dampening economic recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2022/03/12/gas-prices-economy-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shipping, transportation, and even lawn care and mobile dog grooming services are getting more expensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland warns can no longer absorb refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/poland-e2-80-99s-two-largest-cities-warn-they-can-no-longer-absorb-ukrainian-refugees/ar-AAUXC8Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX judge suspends Abbott's order to treat gender-affirming care as child abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/texas-judge-suspends-gov-greg-abbott-e2-80-99s-order-to-treat-gender-affirming-care-as-child-abuse/ar-AAUXsxU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powered by AI, 'autonomous' border towers test support for surveillance technology...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/powered-by-artificial-intelligence-e2-80-98autonomous-e2-80-99-border-towers-test-democrats-e2-80-99-support-for-surveillance-technology/ar-AAUXpO8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump touted contest for small-dollar donors to dine with him in New Orleans. But no winner met him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-touted-a-contest-for-small-dollar-donors-to-dine-with-him-in-new-orleans-but-no-winner-met-him/ar-AAUVX6R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems move closer to cutting Iowa's first-in-the-nation status for presidential calendar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-move-closer-to-cutting-iowas-first-in-the-nation-status-for-2024-presidential-calendar/ar-AAUXGO5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER adds customer surcharge...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/With-gas-prices-soaring-Uber-adds-a-customer-16996516.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - As gas prices soar to record levels, ride-hailing giant Uber said it is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN SET FOR KYIV DEFEAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10605505/Kyiv-Putins-Stalingrad-Russias-assault-capital-doomed-fail-officials-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bulk of Russian ground forces are now around 15 miles from the centre but elements of the large column have dispersed in a bid to encircle the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS COLLECT RECORD TAXES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/1806838000000-federal-tax-collections-set-record-through</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government collected a record $1,806,838,000,000 in total taxes through the first five months of fiscal 2022 (October through February), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement released today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Intel points to heightened risk of chemical attack in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2022/03/11/intelligence-points-to-heightened-risk-of-russian-chemical-attack-in-ukraine-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Past Russian government behavior suggests that Moscow could resort to poison gas if the invasion falters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VOWS NO WWIII...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2022/03/11/president_biden_dont_kid_yourself_thats_called_world_war_three.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden said during a visit Friday to Pennsylvania that the U.S. supports Ukraine in the war against Russia up to what Russia will consider an act of war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melitopol mayor abducted...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/03/11/1086153544/melitopol-mayor-abducted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Ivan Fedorov was abducted on Friday, according to Ukrainian officials. He was reportedly seized by approximately 10 people while in the city center, and they put a plastic bag over his head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL TO ZELENSKY: SURRENDER</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-701041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin made an offer to end the Russian war with Ukraine, but it includes many Ukrainian sacrifices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Prices Could Leap 20% More...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/record-food-prices-could-leap-135000572.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Record-high global food costs could surge another 22% as Russia’s assault on Ukraine stifles trade and slashes future harvests, the United Nations warned. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Belarus Says Russia Is Sending ‘Modern’ WeaponsRussia Devises Plan to Seize Firms Abandoned in Foreigner ExodusRussia Bans Export of 200 Products After Suffering Sanctions HitUkraine Update: Russia Targeting Airfields in Western UkraineTech Walls Off Russia Like Never Before, Posing New Ri</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia strikes near Ukraine capital; Mosque reported hit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-chechnya-b1ce8f7db6408fc78e9204385b6dc754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LVIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces pounding the port city of Mariupol shelled a mosque sheltering more than 80 people, including children, the Ukrainian government said Saturday as fighting also raged on the outskirts of the capital, Kyiv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How companies hide inflation without charging more...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/2129426/inflation-and-supply-chain-snags-are-shrinking-your-products/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shrinkflation is causing consumers to pay the same or more for less.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside space plan to create 'oxygen farm' on MOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4874480/space-plan-oxygen-farm-moon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ESA is planning to build an oxygen plant on the Moon to help astronauts breathe in outer space. On Wednesday, a winner was selected by the European Space Agency (ESA) to be the first to constru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Point cadets ID'd as spring breakers who overdosed in FL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10603221/Six-Spring-Breakers-sickened-overdosing-fentanyl-laced-cocaine-Florida.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six West Point football players vacationing in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, during spring break were hospitalized after overdosing on fentanyl-laced cocaine and going into cardiac arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed men detain mayor in occupied city...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-11-22/h_722529676279d7b0f3933d94b6cbbca4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major cities in Ukraine -- including Dnipro in the center and Lutsk in the far west of the country -- were attacked by Russian forces Friday, Ukrainian officials said. Follow here for live news updates from on the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star QB Deshaun Watson won't face criminal charges for sex misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33478887/houston-texans-qb-deshaun-watson-face-criminal-charges-connection-sexual-misconduct-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grand jury has declined to indict Houston Texans quarterback Deshaun Watson following a police investigation sparked by lawsuits filed by 22 women who have accused him of sexual assault and inappropriate conduct during massage sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence knocks The Don, lays groundwork for possible presidential run...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mike-pence-knocks-trump-and-lays-the-groundwork-for-possible-presidential-run-212200455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence has spent the past week outmaneuvering Donald Trump, his old boss and potential 2024 primary opponent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unvaxxed MLB players can't travel to Canada to play BLUE JAYS, won't be paid...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/mar/11/unvaccinated-mlb-players-cant-travel-to-canada-to-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseball players who are not vaccinated against the coronavirus won’t be allowed to travel into Canada to face the Blue Jays in Toronto and won’t be paid for those games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norah O'Donnell's under fire at CBS 'EVENING NEWS': 'Toxic behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/11/norah-odonnells-attitude-under-fire-at-cbs-evening-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS “Evening News” anchor Nora O’Donnell is third place in the ratings, but sources at the network gripe that she’s got a first-class attitude — even as she faces gett…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Briefs TIKTOK Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-white-house-is-briefing-tiktok-stars-about-the-war-in-ukraine/ar-AAUWvbY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE announces massive drops in arrests, deportations
...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/mar/11/ice-announces-massive-drops-arrests-deportations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration slashed interior immigration arrests by about half compared to the Trump years, according to an overdue report released Friday that details the massive changes at U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How State Dept Turbocharged Theories About Bioweapons

...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/victoria-nuland-turbocharges-ukraine-bio-lab-theories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fringe theory largely confined to Russian state media and the far-flung outer regions of the internet was launched into the mainstream thanks to comments made by Under Secretary of State for Political Affairs Victoria Nuland. For years, Russia's government has accused the United States Department of Defense of working with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin blames almost everyone but himself in fatal shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/11/alec-baldwin-denies-responsibility-for-killing-halyna-hutchins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 63-year-old actor insisted that every single mistake leading to the Oct. 21 shooting on the New Mexico set of “Rust” was “performed by someone else.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How CNN Zucker and His Cronies Manipulated News...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/jeff-zucker-cnn-resign-affair-cuomo-trump-1319698/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texts, email exchanges, and 36 sources tell the true story behind the downfall of TV’s ultimate operator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen to miss Commonwealth Day service...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220311-queen-elizabeth-ii-to-miss-commonwealth-day-service-monday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II's heralded return to major public duties has been put on hold, as royal officials announced Friday she would not attend next week's Commonwealth Day service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Users freak as DUCKDUCKGO down-ranks 'Russian disinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/duckduckgo-search-engine-russian-disinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is DuckDuckGo turning on its users, or did they misunderstand the search engine to begin with?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas abortion clinics lose again in court...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2022/03/texas-clinics-lose-again-in-court-over-strict-abortion-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas abortion providers on Friday conceded a final blow to their best hope of stopping the nation’s most restrictive abortion law after a new ruling ended what little path forward the U.S. Supreme Court had left for clinics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China locks down amid biggest outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/World-News/2022/03/11/Changchun-COVID-19-outbreak-lockdown-Omicron/6901646993887/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities sent a northeastern city of nine million people into lockdown on Friday as the country has seen daily COVID-19 cases top 1,000 this week for the first time since the early days of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVOKES RUSSIA TRADE STATUS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-push-ending-normal-trade-relations-russia-rcna19660</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move would allow the White House to slap tariffs on Russian goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India 'accidentally' fires missile into Pakistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-60711653</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delhi blames a "technical malfunction" for the incident, which it called "deeply regrettable".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 injured after car drives into outdoor seating at DC restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/car-drives-outdoor-seating-parthenon-restaurant-washington-dc-connecticut-avenue-chevy-chase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DC Fire &amp; EMS is on the scene after a car drove into an outdoor seating area outside the Parthenon Restaurant&amp; Chevy Chase Lounge in Washington D. C. Friday afternoon. According to officials, they are triaging at least 9 patients at the Greek restaurant in the 5500 block of Connecticut Avenue NW and are calling it a "mass casualty" incident. Officials say there was no structural damage to the restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears Of 'False Flag' To Lure Belarus Into War...</title>
      <link>https://www.rferl.org/a/ukraine-belarus-false-flag-operation-russia/31748531.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rferl.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kyiv has accused Russia of firing at a settlement in Belarus near the border with Ukraine in a “false flag” attempt to draw Minsk into joining Moscow’s unprovoked invasion of its neighbor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's Top Propagandist Foretold Putin's Justification For Ukraine Invasion Through Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/deansterlingjones/russia-yevgeny-prigozhin-ukraine-trump-giuliani-films</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Putin’s Chef” Yevgeny Prigozhin’s network of state media sites used commissioned Cameo videos from Donald Trump Jr. and Rudy Giuliani to publicize another film that reimagines Russia’s role in the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle East volunteers deployed...</title>
      <link>https://nz.news.yahoo.com/putin-middle-east-volunteer-troops-101918296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nz.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin has given the green light for up to 16,000 volunteers from the Middle East to be deployed alongside Russian-backed rebels to fight in Ukraine, doubling down an invasion that the West says has been losing momentum.The move, just over two weeks since Putin ordered the invasion, allows Russia to deploy battle-hardened mercenaries from conflicts such as Syria without risking additional Russian military casualties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Claims USA Training Birds To Spread Bioweapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/44696/russia-just-made-a-batshit-claim-the-u-s-is-training-birds-to-spread-ukrainian-bio-weapon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin appears to be ramping up its disinformation campaign to a totally absurd degree as the conflict in Ukraine drags on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO 'MINX' Has So Many Penises It Would Make 'EUPHORIA' Blush...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hbo-minx-many-penises-euphoria-095854767.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO MaxMinx is epitomized by the closing shot of its fourth episode, in which a hunky male model struts in slow motion, brimming with empowered confidence thanks to his recent feminist awakening, his giant dick swinging in the air. There’s plenty more where that came from in Ellen Rapoport’s HBO Max comedy (March 17), which takes an amusingly breezy look at the creation of a groundbreaking (fictional) 1970s erotic magazine for women. Headlined by the winning pair of Jake Johnson and Ophelia Lovi</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
