<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pens scathing final letter...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/11/25/richard-spencers-last-letter-navy-chief-after-seal-gallagher-case/4295123002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the letter he submitted on his way out the door, Richard Spencer did not say that he resigned but rather stated, "I hereby acknowledge my termination."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gravy Infused With Cannabis -- To Ease Family Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/this-thanksgiving-gravy-infused-with-cannabis-should-ease-family-stress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insert obligatory munchies joke here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morocco rapper gets one-year jail for insulting police...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/morocco-rapper-gets-one-jail-insulting-police-210133121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salé (Morocco) (AFP) - A Moroccan court on Monday sentenced rapper Mohamed Mounir, known as Gnawi, to one year in jail for insulting police on social media, in what Amnesty condemned as "a disgraceful verdict". A defence lawyer said he believed his 31-year-old client was prosecuted because</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines, Veterans Riled by Conduct Unbecoming Support Animals...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/airlines-veterans-riled-conduct-unbecoming-195105884.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- It seemed, in retrospect, a bit of a low point -- a medium-size dog racing through an airplane at 30,000 feet, spraying diarrhea toward passengers throughout the cabin.But according to some transportation officials, it was an increasingly typical scene that has stemmed from the growing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER chief talking with NY prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/25/politics/national-enquirer-ami-david-pecker-prosecutors/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Pecker, the head of the company that publishes the National Enquirer, has spoken with prosecutors with the New York district attorney's office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos, Audio, Video Recordings From Associate...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/archives/allahpundit/2019/11/25/abc-schiffs-committee-photos-audio-video-recordings-rudy-associate-lev-parnas-involve-trump-giuliani/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus: Devin Nunes under the microscope?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA DMV Makes $50M a Year Selling Drivers' Personal Info...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/evjekz/the-california-dmv-is-making-dollar50m-a-year-selling-drivers-personal-information</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A document obtained by Motherboard shows how DMVs sell people’s names, addresses, and other personal information to generate revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Ruthless AMAZON Quotas Permanently Maiming Employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/11/amazon-warehouse-reports-show-worker-injuries/602530/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speedy robots. Constant surveillance. Ruthless quotas. A new investigation into why the injury rate for Amazon’s warehouse workers is sky-high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-boosting supplements could harm users, study warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/11/25/brain-boosting-supplements-contain-unapproved-drug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The doctor who led the study worries that consumers could be taking a drug under no medical supervision at a dangerous dosage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBD Demand Could Lead To Christmas Tree Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/11/22/demand-hemp-cbd-oil-christmas-tree-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Texans are starting to think about purchasing that Christmas tree, but those who sell them say don't think about it too long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House began storing texts, creating evidence cache for Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/tremendous-value-white-house-began-storing-texts-last-year-creating-evidence-cache-for-democrats/ar-BBXhzqw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOKTWITTER admit giving improper access to personal data to apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/25/facebook-and-twitter-says-users-gave-improper-access-to-personal-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook and Twitter announce that personal data of hundreds of users may have been improperly accessed after they used their accounts to log in to certain apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney general: Israel's Netanyahu not required to resign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3b02f97ee7bf4e2a8f576b1b9df2dd1b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel’s attorney general said Monday that Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is not required to leave office following his indictment on corruption charges, giving a small boost...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who owns most land in USA? 50 families have over 31 million acres...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/11/25/these-people-own-the-most-land-in-america/40649951/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 50 individuals, families, and heirs on this list, compiled by 24/7 Wall St., own about 1.4% of the total landmass of the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Did This Trump Official Just Get Outed as Anonymous? He's Not Exactly Denying It...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/did-this-trump-official-just-get-outed-as-anonymous-hes-not-exactly-denying-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new article alleges that former Secretary of Defense James Mattis' chief speechwriter Guy Snodgrass is the "Anonymous" official who wrote a book blasting President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMERICAN MUSIC AWARDS' Falls to Record Low Ratings with Taylor Swift... </title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/amas-2019-ratings-record-low-american-music-awards-taylor-swift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Sunday's American Music Awards (AMAs) set a new record low in the key ratings demo, the annual special avoided its smallest-ever overall TV audience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Americans Growing Tired Of Traditional Thanksgiving Meals, Open To Alternative... </title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gobbled-out-1-in-4-americans-are-tired-of-traditional-thanksgiving-food/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey of 2,000 Americans has revealed that more than a quarter (26%) have grown weary of the usual Thanksgiving food options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iguanas taking over Florida -- and state not sure what to do!</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/environment/article235513017.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Testing 'Digital Dog Nose' To Speed Up Screenings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tsa-testing-advanced-airport-security-technology-digital-dog-nose-innovation-checkpoint/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While passengers in Vegas are helping evaluate next-generation body scanners and ID checkpoints, researchers are developing new ways to detect and neutralize explosives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Kanye opera a 'Nebuchadsnoozer'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/25/kanye-wests-nebuchadnezzar-opera-was-a-loud-flop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a scream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE EPSTEIN SEX ISLAND</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/24/first-look-at-jeffrey-epstein-inside-his-pedophile-island-lair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is the first look at the monster in his lair. Newly surfaced photos obtained by The Post reveal for the first time how Jeffrey Epstein — and a horde of girls — spent time at his now-notor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court lets lawsuit by climate scientist continue against conservative outlets... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-supreme-court-lets-climate-144519288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday allowed a prominent climate scientist to pursue a defamation lawsuit against a conservative magazine and a think tank that compared him to a convicted child molester. The justices declined to hear appeals filed by National Review magazine and the Competitive Enterprise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In first jailhouse interview, Bill Cosby says he has no remorse...</title>
      <link>https://blackpressusa.com/nnpa-newswire-exclusive-bill-cosby-speaks-from-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blackpressusa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NNPA NEWSWIRE — He revisited his famous 2004 “Pound Cake” speech and clarified that he probably should not have addressed that controversial dissertation to all African Americans – the residents at SCI-Phoenix make for the perfect audience, Cosby stated. Cosby said he remains concerned, however, for all of Black America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted Navy secretary made secret deal with Trump... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2148f2182aa64d8c8102967d653b0ba0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Defense Secretary Mark Esper said Monday that President Donald Trump gave him a direct order to allow a Navy SEAL accused of war crimes to retire without losing his SEAL...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Deals and Food Gone Bad Plague Corner Stores. But Neighbors Fighting Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-11-22/drug-deals-bad-food-plague-corner-stores-but-neighbors-are-fighting-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIEVES CUT ALARMS WITH FIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dresden-green-vault-heist-treasures-valued-at-a-billion-dollars-stolen-from-german-palace-thieves-cut-alarm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of artifacts have been stolen from Germany’s Green Vault palace in Dresden in what police are calling the largest art raid since World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY SHOCKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/thieves-target-treasures-world-renowned-museum-dresden-germany-n1090421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Not only the State Art Collections were robbed, but we Saxons,” the prime minister of Saxony tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crashes OSCAR Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/sam-mendes-war-epic-1917-storms-oscars-2020-race-1257815 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Sam Mendes, cinematographer Roger Deakins and composer Thomas Newman should clear their schedules for the next few months, The Hollywood Reporter's awards columnist writes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SET NEW RECORDS!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/25/stock-market-wall-street-in-focus-amid-earnings-and-economic-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose as Wall Street looked for the market's rally to resume amid expectations that China and the U.S. will reach a trade deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE REAL STAR WARS:  US, China in space race...</title>
      <link>https://washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/24/china-raises-space-military-challenge-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and China are rapidly building space warfare capabilities as part of a race to dominate the zone outside Earth’s atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ship of death': 14,000 sheep drown after cargo vessel capsizes, sinks...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/ship-death-more-14-000-144507076.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 14,600 sheep have perished at sea after the cargo ship they were loaded on capsized off the coast of Romania into the Black Sea.The crew, which comprised 20 Syrians and one Lebanese, were rescued along with just 33 surviving animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Welcome to the vengeance election...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/879231/welcome-vengeance-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What 'billionaire tears' and 'lock her up' have in common</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr criticized by conservative lawyers for stance on executive power...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/471872-barr-criticized-by-conservative-lawyers-for-stance-on-executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, was one of a group of conservative lawyers and former senior level government officials to criticize Attorney General William Barr for remarks he made in a recent speech saying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  The Podcast Epidemic; 700,000 active programs...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/pod-delusion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl Ads Sell Out at Record $5.6 Million Each...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fox-says-super-bowl-ads-140000486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Fox Sports has sold out its inventory of Super Bowl ads after pricing 30-second spots for television’s biggest annual event at a record $5.6 million.The Fox Corp. unit finished selling all 77 national spots on Friday, according to Seth Winter, executive vice president for sports sales</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-con jailed on grand theft burrito charge...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/grand-theft-burrito-612047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOVEMBER 25--An Arizona felon is back behind bars following his arrest last Saturday night on a grand theft burrito charge, cops report. According to investigators, Timothy Bell, 29, approached a man</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGGEST ROBBERY IN HISTORY?!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10417712/billion-euros-worth-of-jewellery-and-diamonds-stolen-in-raid-on-german-museum-as-secure-as-fort-knox/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUDACIOUS thieves have stolen what could be the world’s biggest heist after grabbing a BILLION euros’ worth of treasure from a museum said to be as ‘secure as Fort Knox’. Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic cult fears as animals slaughtered, church sprayed with pentagrams...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10416065/satanic-cult-fears-new-forest-animals-slaughtered-church-sprayed-pentagrams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MODERN-DAY Satanists are feared to be slaying animals in the New Forest in Hampshire after several sheep and cattle were stabbed to death there earlier this month. Three cattle were found with stab…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alberta frustration fuels push for independence from Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/25/wexit-alberta-canada-independence-separatism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The oil-producing western province has endured years of recession and now a new party is channeling resentment towards the federal government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Erotic fresco depicting Greek myth unveiled in Pompeii...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/nov/25/erotic-fresco-depicting-greek-myth-unveiled-in-pompeii-leda-and-swan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well-preserved image of Leda and the swan was found during excavations last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rampaging monkeys turn against humans in violent turf war attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/rampaging-monkeys-turn-against-humans-20889334</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monkeys are becoming increasingly aggressive, murdering babies and running riot in gangs in a never-ending turf war with humans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rick Perry says Trump is 'chosen one'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/471868-rick-perry-says-trump-is-the-chosen-one</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Energy Secretary Rick Perry said in a portion of an interview released by "Fox &amp; Friends" this past weekend that he believes President Trump is the “chosen one.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Reaches Decision Stage as Democrats Review Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/impeachment-reaches-decision-stage-democrats-090000554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Democrats are starting to compress weeks of depositions, documents and testimony into a report almost certain to result in articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump, as the White House wages a campaign to discredit the investigation.Intelligence Chairman Adam Schiff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TREASURES STOLEN FROM MUSEUM...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-treasury-chamber-museum-dresden-robbed-000012551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robbers made off with three priceless diamond sets from a state museum in Dresden, police and museum directors confirmed Monday, in what German media have described as the biggest art heist since World War Two. The thieves broke into the Green Vault at Dresden's Royal Palace -- home to around 4,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug lord's empire devastating families with grip on small-town USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/crime/2019/11/24/el-menchos-mexican-drug-cartel-cjng-empire-devastating-small-towns/4181733002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With unparalleled speed, the Cártel Jalisco Nueva Generación, or CJNG, has set up shop in cities, towns and unsuspecting communities across America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QB misses last play of game taking selfie...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/24/us/redskins-quarterback-selfie-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haskins told reporters during a post-game interview that he thought the game was over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong winds may ground MACY'S Thanksgiving Day Parade balloons...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/25/strong-winds-may-ground-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-balloons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That’s deflating news. Gusty winds forecast for the city on Thursday may ground the popular giant balloons for the Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade. “It looks shaky for the balloons,” said Accu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange 'could die in prison' without urgent medical care...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/25/julian-assange-could-die-in-prison-without-urgent-medical-care-doctors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange is so sick, he could die in prison if he does not get urgent medical care, according to an open letter sent Monday to British authorities. More than 60 doctors wrot…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary Guards: Enemies will be destroyed if cross red lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-gasoline-protests-guards/revolutionary-guards-irans-enemies-will-be-destroyed-if-they-cross-our-red-lines-idUSKBN1XZ1H8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran will destroy the United States, Israel and Saudi Arabia if they cross Tehra...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Iran to Chile to Sudan, protests take hold around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-11-25/iran-chile-hong-kong-protests-around-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent months, protests have erupted around the world. Here's what you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Kanye West opera at Hollywood Bowl? Call it 'Nebuchadsnoozer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/story/2019-11-24/kanye-west-opera-hollywood-bowl-nebuchadnezzar-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West packs the Bowl for "Nebuchadnezzar," but the opera feels like a passion play or, worse, school production. Dare we wish for more Kanye-ness?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SACHA BARON COHEN: 'Silicon Six' spread propaganda. Time to regulate...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/The-Silicon-Six-spread-propaganda-It-s-time-to-14860308.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I get it: I'm one of the last people you'd expect to hear warning about the danger of conspiracies and lies. I've built a career on pushing the limits of propriety and good taste. I portrayed Borat, the first fake news journalist, along with satirical characters such as Ali G, a wannabe gangster, and Bruno, a gay fashion reporter from Austria. Some critics have said my comedy risks reinforcing old racial and religious stereotypes.  I admit that most of my comedy over the years has been pretty juvenile. However, when Borat was able to get an entire bar in Arizona to sing "throw the Jew down the well," it revealed people's indifference to anti-Semitism. When, as Bruno, I started kissing a man in a cage fight in Arkansas and nearly started a riot, it showed the violent potential of homophobia. And when, disguised as an ultra-woke developer, I proposed building a mosque in one rural community, prompting a resident to proudly admit, "I am racist, against Muslims," it showed a wide acceptance of Islamophobia.  The ugliness my jokes help reveal is why I'm so worried about our pluralistic democracies. Demagogues appeal to our worst instincts. Conspiracy theories once confined to the fringe are going mainstream, fueled in part by President Donald Trump, who has spread such paranoid lies more than 1,700 times to his 67 million Twitter followers. It's as if the Age of Reason - the era of evidential argument - is ending, and now knowledge is delegitimized and scientific consensus is dismissed. Democracy, which depends on shared truths, is in retreat, and autocracy, which thrives on shared lies, is on the march. Hate crimes are surging, as are murderous attacks on religious and ethnic minorities.  All this hate and violence actually has something in common: It's being facilitated by a handful of Internet companies that amount to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer Droids Geared to 'Wipe Out Swathes of Human Population'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201911251077396399-killer-robots-geared-to-wipe-out-swathes-of-human-population-warns-expert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of countries have been echoing calls to negotiate a treaty to retain “meaningful human control over the use of force”, including 30 states that want to ban fully autonomous weapons, also known as lethal autonomous weapons systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Good pope v bad pope?' Hopkins, Pryce star in Vatican drama...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/good-pope-v-bad-pope-hopkins-pryce-star-055539543.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in seven centuries the Catholic church has two living popes, and "The Two Popes" imagines a series of spirited debates between the strict, conservative Benedict and his charismatic successor. The two men on screen bridge their differences, bonding over Benedict's piano-playing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More college students look for mental health help on campus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08e5c195bf04471e9c4a127abe831d91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More college students are turning to their schools for help with anxiety, depression and other mental health problems, and many must wait weeks for treatment or find help elsewhere as campus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasures worth 'up to billion euros' stolen from museum...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/25/thieves-steal-priceless-treasures-dresden-green-vault-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police say thieves on the run after raid at historic Green Vault inside royal palace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore invokes 'fake news' law for first time over FACEBOOK post...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191125050130-v7vpg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE-FAKENEWS/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Singapore invokes 'fake news' law for first time over Facebook post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NXIVM cult leader hunted virgins on TINDER burned initials onto them...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/actress-reveals-cult-leader-who-20952362</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NXIVM cult leader Keith Raniere told one slave to tell her to “find other virgins” on Tinder “shorter than me, younger is fine”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web inventor unveils plan to save The Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/web-inventor-unveils-ambitious-rule-book-for-internet-responsibility-2019-11-24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Wide Web inventor Tim Berners-Lee released an ambitious rule book for online governance — a bill of rights and obligations for the internet — designed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child killed by ice sculpture at Christmas market...</title>
      <link>https://today.rtl.lu/news/luxembourg/a/1436406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;today.rtl.lu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child was fatally injured at the Place Guillaume II Christmas market on Sunday evening at around 8pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venetians protest over flooding, cruise ships...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venetians-protest-over-flooding-cruise-ships-233618064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Venetians took to the streets of the Renaissance city on Sunday to vent anger over frequent flooding and the impact of giant cruise ships. Braving heavy rain, between 2,000 and 3,000 people answered the call of environmental groups and a collective opposed to the boats. Critics say the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship with 14,000 sheep aboard capsizes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ship-14-600-sheep-aboard-capsizes-off-romania-220001331.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescuers were struggling Sunday to save 14,600 sheep loaded on a cargo ship that capsized in the Black Sea off the coast of Romania, they said. The Queen Hind bound for Saudi Arabia overturned for yet unknown reasons shortly after leaving Romania's Midia port. The crew of 20 Syrians and one Lebanese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS PROMISES MERRY BREXMAS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191124161456-yln5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-UK's Johnson offers up new Brexit promise for Christmas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense chief Esper ousts Navy secretary in Trump SEAL fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/defense-chief-esper-ousts-navy-secretary-in-trump-seal-fallout/ar-BBXh72X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Epstein 'madam' Ghislaine Maxwell set to come out of hiding, meet with FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10414777/prince-andrew-ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-reveal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew’s pal Ghislaine Maxwell will speak to the FBI about their links to paedo Jeffrey Epstein. Sources said the sex slaver’s “madam”, 57, aims to emerge from hiding within days. Sources sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon asks for Navy secretary's resignation over SEAL war crime case...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/navy/dod-chief-asks-for-navy-secretary-s-resignation-over-private-proposal-in-navy-seal-s-case-1.608539</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Mark Esper asked for the resignation of Navy Secretary Richard Spencer on Sunday after losing confidence in him over his handling of the case of a Navy SEAL accused of war crimes in Iraq, the Pentagon said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
