<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DEMS IN A RUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democrats-eye-quick-impeachment-probe-of-Trump-as-14471555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democratic leaders are eyeing a fast-paced investigation into the possible impeachment of President Donald Trump, instructing the committees handling the probe to wrap up their findings within weeks in hopes of concluding before the holiday season.  Multiple Democratic lawmakers and congressional aides said there is no formal timeline for the inquiry, but the "need for speed," as one aide put it, comes as Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., is under pressure from vulnerable freshmen to keep the investigation narrowly focused and disciplined.  The emerging strategy of a rapid investigation focused mainly on the explosive accusation that Trump urged Ukraine's president to dig up dirt about a political rival comes as lawmakers prepare to leave Washington on Friday for a two-week recess. In addition to Trump's call, a whistleblower complaint claimed that unidentified White House officials tried to keep the conversation a secret within the government.  "The consensus in our caucus is that our focus now is on this allegation," Pelosi told reporters earlier in the day, adding: "This is a coverup."  Pelosi and other leaders huddled in a basement conference room Thursday evening with more than a dozen "front-liner" members representing the toughest districts for incumbent Democrats to discuss the fledgling probe and, in the words of multiple attendees, "get on the same page."  Inside the room, the group urged the leadership to keep the messaging around impeachment on national security and the Ukraine probe being led by the House Intelligence Committee and Chairman Adam Schiff, D-Calif. - not on the litany of potential Trump offenses being investigated by other panels, including the House Judiciary Committee, which traditionally takes the lead in impeachment proceedings.  "I'm very supportive of Adam Schiff and what...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootleg marijuana vapes tainted with hydrogen cyanide...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/vaping/tests-show-bootleg-marijuana-vapes-tainted-hydrogen-cyanide-n1059356</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News commissioned laboratory tests of knock-off marijuana vapes that found a pesticide linked to hydrogen cyanide in 10 out 10 products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS Surprise: Clint Eastwood's 'RICHARD JEWELL' Set for December Release...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/clint-eastwood-directed-richard-jewel-gets-an-awards-release-1243923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie will open opposite Sony's 'Jumanji: The Next Level.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter who exposed racist tweets fired for own tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-49857358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Des Moines Register has been forced to hire extra security for its newsroom due to threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL FLASHBACK: If House acts, Senate must have trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2bc10ed20dbf4041935b37bec9542c53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and the House impeachment inquiry (all times local): 2:30 p.m. Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said months ago that if the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges Silicon Valley to avoid slide toward new 'barbarism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vatican-technology-ethics-idUSKBN1WC11N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis urged Silicon Valley giants on Friday to make sure technological ad...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters: VP, AG Involved In 'Conspiracy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/sarahmimms/maxine-waters-pence-barr-ukraine-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They’re all involved,” Waters told BuzzFeed News’ AM to DM on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan with human rights to begin new life in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-49856859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Sandra the orangutan won a landmark appeal in 2014 which deemed her a "nonhuman person".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE tech 'Orwellian nightmare' to spy in your home...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/google-rolls-out-orwellian-nightmare-technology-spy-you-your-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average age of car on American roads: 12 years old...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/09/27/new-cars-last-longer-and-interiors-need-more-durable-materials/2211617001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cars are lasting longer than ever. Sounds good, right? It's actually a problem, and automakers are scrambling to respond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Probes Communist Police Impersonators...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/california-probes-chinese-communist-police-impersonators/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in California are investigating at least two cases of people posing as Chinese police driving cars with markings of the Communist Party of China's People's Armed Police (PAP).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Busted for 'Shoplifting' Just Had Penis Bulge...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/09/27/shoplifting-bulge-pants-england/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Scottish man got into a very awkward situation this week when he was accused of stealing items from a shop and putting them into his pants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FACEBOOK begins to phase out 'Likes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/09/26/facebook-hides-like-counts-test-australia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is going to start hiding "Like" counts as part of a new test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOIGHT:  WAR AGAINST TRUTHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/09/26/jon-voight-impeachment-effort-against-trump-is-war-against-truths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran actor Jon Voight has called upon the country to "stand with our President Trump in a time of such evil words," as Democrats push for impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain security firm probed 'for spying on Assange for CIA'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spain-security-firm-probed-spying-assange-cia-152919133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Spanish private security firm, which is under investigation in Madrid, spied on Wikileaks founder Julian Assange on behalf of the CIA while he was inside the Ecudoran embassy in London, El Pais daily reported Friday. Citing unspecified documents and statements, the paper said Undercover Global Ltd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary rock-star treatment at progressive group...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020-vision-hillary-rock-star-treatment-at-progressive-group-profile-rises-as-trump-faces-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Hillary Clinton received a wild standing ovation at the 50-year anniversary celebration for NARAL, a nonprofit that advocates for abortions. NARAL President Ilyse Hogue introduced the “rightful 45th president of the United States” to the 50th Anniversary Celebration Dinner on Thursday at the Capitol Hilton in D.C., where the twice-failed presidential candidate …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF California voters consider leaving state...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-09-27/who-wants-to-leave-california-berkeley-igs-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many conservatives feel marginalized and want to leave California, and young people are stressed by housing costs, a Berkeley IGS poll for The Times shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers could draft articles of impeachment by end of October...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/27/complaint-in-hand-democrats-aim-for-a-fast-and-focused-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — A crucial cache of evidence in hand, House Democrats moved quickly on Thursday with an impeachment inquiry they said would be focused tightly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcript...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Almost-a-spy-Transcript-of-Trump-s-remarks-at-14471796.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump delivered wide-ranging remarks at the U.S. Mission to the United Nations on Thursday morning where he dismissed the complaint against him from an intelligence community whistleblower and suggested that the person's actions are akin to being a spy or committing treason.  The closed-door event was intended for staff and families of the U.S. mission to honor the work they'd done for the president's visit to the United Nations. The president focused on condemning the whistleblower, lambasting the media and bragging about the size of his political rallies.  Below is a transcript from a 9-minute video of Trump's remarks obtained by The Washington Post. The video begins as U.S. Ambassador to the United Nations Kelly Craft leaves the stage and Trump takes the podium:  - - -  "They tell you you're going to be a star, the only way you're going to be a star, no matter how you look or feel or talk is when you make good deals. I found that out over the years, you've got to make good deals otherwise it's over. And [Craft] is going to make great deals.  I was with her now for three days and she's developed incredible relationships in a very short period of time and we appreciate it. (Looks at her) You'll be out there. You'll be in the firing line today for us. For instance, today I just heard while I'm coming up here, you know they have a whistleblower (laughter) he turned out to be a fake, he's a fake, a highly partisan whistleblower. The lawyer contributed to Biden, they contributed to - the whole thing is - but more importantly, you know what the whistleblower [complaint] is? The same letter that we announced yesterday, which was perfect, I couldn't have written it better if I wrote it myself. I could not have said or had a better conversation.  And we had a really nice gentleman in the president of Ukraine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN:  BIDEN FRIST CASUALTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/patrick-j-buchanan/joe-biden-impeachments-first-casualty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi speaks to reporters on September 26 2019. (Photo by ANDREW CABALLERO-REYNOLDS/AFP/Getty Images)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/tictoc/status/1177396573283573760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“"That's close to a spy." WATCH: Trump demands to know who gave information to the whistle-blower in the #UkraineTranscript that has spurred the #Impeach45 drive. More @business: https://t.co/lmgTALLGsi https://t.co/WTFeEX7K96”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Plane Passenger Goes Berserk Over Long Bathroom Line, Threatens To Kill Pilot...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/09/27/jfk-flight-emergency-landing-unruly-passenger-upset-over-bathroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flight that left John F. Kennedy International Airport had to make an emergency landing Thursday after an angry passenger allegedly started making threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG GOES MOB...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/new-yorker-cover-shows-trump-and-giuliani-as-mobsters-murdering-uncle-sam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cover for the upcoming edition of the New Yorker depicts President Trump and his personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani as mobsters who are murdering Uncle Sam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia quietly building network of spy satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10017217/russia-spy-satellite-missile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has launched another of its secretive spy satellites designed to silently track nukes fired from the US. Hurled into orbit from a launchpad in northeast Russia, the probe can detect long-ran…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult led by female buddha raided...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/cops-raid-killer-exorcism-cult-20314410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING GRAPHIC IMAGES: It's alleged people were beaten for trying to run away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAN DIET BLAMED FOR NFL QUARTERBACK'S BAD SEASON...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/sports/nfl/carolina-panthers/article235295427.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein butler dishes on Paris pad guests including Bill Gates, Steve Bannon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/27/epsteins-butler-dishes-on-paris-pad-guests-including-bill-gates-steve-bannon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The butler who managed Jeffrey Epstein’s posh Paris pad claims he waited on a rotation of famous faces including Prince Andrew, Bill and Melinda Gates, as well as Steve Bannon, according to a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAYDON CARTER:  IT'S WON'T BE PRETTY...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2019-9-28/the-view-from-here-2019-9-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air Mail is a weekly newsletter that will unfold like the better weekend editions of your favorite newspapers. Air Mail is delivered to subscribers' in-boxes every Saturday at 6:00 AM E.S.T.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans Completely Unprepared For Recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/personal-finance/shocking-new-survey-finds-most-americans-are-completely-unprepared-next-recession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman with 'WiFi' allergy sleeps in copper bag; Fears 5G may kill her...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10014593/woman-wifi-allergy-copper-sleeping-bag/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN who claims she is allergic to WiFi sleeps in a £400 copper sleeping bag and is terrified that the rollout of 5G will kill her. Rosi Gladwell, 70, a self-diagnosed radiation sufferer has spe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Feels Like 1776 Kind of Fight'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/09/27/trump-impeachment-national-security-house-democrats-moderate-mikie-sherrill-228430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freshman congresswoman reckons with the historical weight of standing up to the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXORCIST: Cases getting darker...</title>
      <link>https://www.koin.com/news/oregon/oregon-priest-performs-exorcisms-cases-are-getting-darker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.koin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KOIN 6 News spent an afternoon with a self-professed exorcist as he cleansed a man of what he believed to be evil spirits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: China Unveils 'Super Surveillance Camera' That Links To Social Credit System...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/china-unveils-super-surveillance-camera-that-can-link-to-its-social-credit-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Device can identify individual faces out of crowds of tens of thousands; Will take mass surveillance to a new level</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers warn about threat of political deepfakes by creating one...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Lawmakers-warn-about-threat-of-political-14472593.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Michael Waltz wants Navy to beat Army in this year's football game, according to a newly released political deepfake - a video doctored with artificial intelligence. But it the content wasn't true, as Waltz is a former Army Green Beret.  But Waltz teamed up with Rep. Don Beyer, D-Va., to craft the mock deepfake for the House Science subcommittee to illustrate just how realistic this kind of disinformation can be. The SUNY-Albany and University of Chicago researchers took a recorded video statement from Beyer and transposed it onto Waltz's image - designed to be a jarring sight for subcommittee chair and former Navy pilot Mikie Sherill, D-N.J.  The resulting video is a warning for lawmakers - and the public - that bad actors could abuse this technology for much more nefarious purposes than having a friendly joke about a sports rivalry. Watch it here:  "You see how dangerous and misleading it could be; I'm sure we fooled a couple of people," Beyer said. "For instance, what if instead of 'Go Navy, Beat Army,' I said, 'It's time to impeach the president'? That would be viral everywhere."  "My friends might appreciate that, but I think he would not," he added of his Republican colleague.  As the 2020 election looms, Washington lawmakers are increasingly concerned that bad actors will use deepfake technology to sow chaos and stoke divisions among the American public - much like Russian actors did with traditional social media posts during the 2016 election.  Waltz and Beyer are warning that United States needs to be investing in technology to quickly detect such fakes to keep up in an arms race, as the tools to create misleading videos become even cheaper and more widely available.  "These videos and this technology have the potential to truly be a weapon for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Snake-like UFO returns to California...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/snake-like-ufo-returns-california-20097741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The man claims to have never seen anything like the object before, but similar UFOs have been spotted across the US in recent months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Skydiver collides with semi-truck in fatal jump...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/09/26/skydiver-killed-by-truck-after-landing-on-california-highway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A skydiver died after hitting a big rig on a Northern California highway Thursday, according to KTLA sister station KTXL in Sacramento. Around 2 p.m., witnesses told the California Highway Patrol they saw a parachute fall from the sky toward Highway 99 in Acampo, between Sacramento and Stockton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tense and divided Egypt braces for more protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-tense-and-divided-Egypt-braces-for-more-protests-14472351.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO - At checkpoints, white-uniformed police officers randomly stop people, demanding to see their identity documents, even their phones. At street corners around downtown Cairo, police in riot gear sit in trucks, waiting. The presence of plainclothes security agents has grown.  Throughout the week, the Egyptian government has been preparing for this day, widening its biggest security crackdown in years. A once-obscure whistleblower, Mohamed Ali, whose videos alleging high-level corruption have struck a chord with frustrated Egyptians, is urging millions to protest on Friday.  Their goal: to demand the fall of authoritarian President Abdel-Fatah el-Sissi.  "We are going to protest because we are on the right side, the good side," said Mohamed Ali Shawky, 19, a university student. "We are doing this because we believe in the justice of our cause. That is what is making us stronger even when we are scared to death. It gives us faith, even when the regime has weapons and soldiers."  Whether large numbers of protesters will join Shawki remains to be seen, but the Arab world's most populous nation is already more tense than at any moment since el-Sissi took office five years ago. Last Friday, several hundred protesters took to the streets in a demonstration that amounted to the biggest challenge to el-Sissi's rule.  Since then, the government has arrested more than 1,900 people, according to the Egyptian Center for Economic and Social Rights, and the number is likely to rise. Many were nabbed in random sweeps near downtown's Tahrir Square, the epicenter of Egypt's 2011 Arab Spring uprising that toppled longtime autocratic president Hosni Mubarak. Others were arrested in areas known to be populated by those who had joined the 2011 revolution, activists said.  Opposition politicians, journalists and activists have also been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese 'IRISHMAN' set to premiere in New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a124b89f75ad41ef95a8ab65f616e1b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Martin Scorsese's crime epic "The Irishman" is set to make its premiere at the New York Film Festival. The director's 209-minute opus, starring Robert De Niro, Al Pacino and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germ from dog's mouth led to amputation. Researchers blamed gene change...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/93d6868b1a3745528db01b3c17003968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST BEND, Wis. (AP) — It's hard to regard Ellie as a menace. When Greg Manteufel is frustrated or feeling down, she sits by him. At night, she sleeps under his covers. At dinner, she's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Chained Men and Boys Rescued From Islamic School...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-abuse/hundreds-of-captives-many-boys-in-chains-freed-in-nigeria-idUSKBN1WC0ZG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 300 captives, most of them children and many in chains, have been resc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline will warn if sitting next to baby on flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-airline-will-tell-you-where-babies-are-seated-on-your-flight-2019-09-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While some travelers seek out ways to avoid being seated next to kids, parents are complaining that airlines are splitting families up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: Attorney general 'gone rogue'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/463342-pelosi-attorney-general-has-gone-rogue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) on Friday accused Attorney General William Barr of going "rogue" in his efforts to protect President Trump from the fallout over a whistleblower complaint related to Trump's conversations with the president of Ukrai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto Workers Fear Electric Unrest...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/don-t-us-anymore-auto-090000599.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The milkman went missing thanks to the rise of refrigerators. Switchboard operators were done in by the dawn of direct dialing. And in the car industry, auto workers are deathly afraid the engine assembler will give way to battery builders.Dread over the prospect that plug-in cars -- which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin says hopes U.S. won't release details of calls...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190927093440-cuva6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/WHISTLEBLOWER-KREMLIN (URGENT):Kremlin says it hopes U.S. won't release details of Putin-Trump calls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goes Where Mueller Never Could...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-s-ukraine-scandal-grows-into-bigger-threat-than-mueller</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Whistle-Blower Goes Where Mueller Never Could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Knew of Whistleblower Allegations Soon After Trump Call With Ukraine Leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-knew-of-whistle-blowers-allegations-soon-after-trumps-call-with-ukraine-leader/ar-AAHToDz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani engaged parade of Ukrainian prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Giuliani-engaged-parade-of-Ukrainian-prosecutors-14471702.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rudy Giuliani spent months cultivating current and former prosecutors in Ukraine with a particular goal: Help President Donald Trump in next year's election by ensuring that Ukrainian authorities pursued allegations that could damage his Democratic rivals.  But the effort hit a snag. A political neophyte and comedian named Volodymyr Zelensky - who had once played a Ukrainian president on television in a sitcom - swooped in last spring and became the president of Ukraine for real. Some of Giuliani's efforts were thrown in doubt. One of the prosecutors Giuliani initially saw as an ally made public comments undermining his claims against former vice president Joe Biden. How Zelensky would act was unknown.  "New Pres of Ukraine still silent on investigation of Ukrainian interference in 2016 election and alleged Biden bribery of Pres Poroshenko," Giuliani tweeted on June 21, without evidence of the allegations, referring to the former president, Petro Poroshenko, whom Zelensky defeated. "Time for leadership and investigate both if you want to purge how Ukraine was abused by Hillary and Obama people."  The frustration helps explain why Trump, ahead of a July 25 phone call that is now the subject of a whistleblower complaint and a congressional impeachment inquiry, turned up the heat.  Amid uncertainty about Zelensky's willingness to work with Giuliani, Trump suspended military aid to Ukraine on July 18. Days later, Zelensky's party swept Ukraine's parliamentary elections, ushering in a wave of political newcomers and upping the uncertainty about whether Giuliani's efforts would come undone.  In the meantime, Trump had been withholding a date for a coveted bilateral summit with Zelensky. A call with the comedian was on the books - a chance for Trump to make his desires clear.  "I would like you to do us a favor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part of broader secrecy effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/effort-to-shield-trumps-call-with-ukrainian-leader-was-part-of-broader-secrecy-effort/ar-AAHUnST</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only the ballot box can deliver a final verdict!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/463164-only-the-ballot-box-can-deliver-a-final-verdict-on-president-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The history of impeachment can inform us but the ultimate decision remains with the voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Attacks Whistleblower's Sources, Alludes to Punishment for Spies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-branding-whistle-blower-spy-230248704.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump appeared to threaten a government whistle-blower who is protected under federal law, adding to the list of accusations that could fuel the impeachment inquiry in Congress.Trump said the unidentified whistle-blower had no direct knowledge of the president’s actions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson allies warn UK faces riots if Brexit fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10015632/boris-johnsons-britain-faces-la-riots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson’s allies have warned Britain faces LA-style riots if Brexit is reversed. A senior cabinet minister last night said the country risked a “violent, popular uprising” i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURN:  2 Republican governors support impeachment....</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Two-Republican-governors-say-they-support-14471605.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, two Republican governors have publicly supported the impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump, a new development in an intensifying political fracas that has so far been largely partisan.  Vermont Gov. Phil Scott and Massachusetts Gov. Charlie Baker, both outspoken critics of Trump, said Thursday that they favored the investigation, but Scott added that he would wait for more information before calling for further action against the president.  In a statement to The Washington Post, Scott called the inquiry "appropriate" and said it is a key part of Congress's duty as a co-equal branch of government.  "I think we have much more to learn and need to understand all the facts as this serious allegation is considered," he said. "Congress has a solemn responsibility to every American to fulfill its role in our government system of checks and balances."  But impeachment, he cautioned, "is a very serious issue and should not be taken lightly or abused."  At a Thursday event, Baker told reporters that, "It's a deeply disturbing situation and circumstance and I think the proper role and responsibility for Congress at this point is to investigate it and get to the bottom of it."  As governors, however, Scott and Baker have no role in the formal process, so their break from the Republican ranks is largely symbolic.  So far, two Senate Republicans have publicly expressed serious concern over revelations that Trump repeatedly urged the Ukrainian president to investigate former vice president Joe Biden, one of his foremost political rivals.  "There's obviously a lot that's very troubling there," said Sen. Ben Sasse, R-Neb., on Wednesday, adding that Democrats should still be careful when using the word "impeach."  Sasse opposed Trump's 2016 candidacy, but he has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCORCHED EARTH DEFENSE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-writes-the-gop-impeachment-playbook-scorched-earth-but-will-it-work/ar-AAHTPr2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America filled with anger and animosity digs in...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/impeach-trump-an-america-filled-with-anger-and-animosity-digs-in/ar-AAHTDK9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Pence-again-in-spotlight-despite-attempts-to-14471582.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As President Donald Trump fumed Thursday about a whistleblower complaint that accused him of abusing his power and endangering national security, Vice President Mike Pence was in his home state, sticking to the script.  "I came to Indiana to say it's time for Congress to pass the U.S.-Mexico-Canada Agreement, and pass it this year," Pence said at an Indianapolis machinery plant, where he touted a trade deal that has been put on the congressional back burner amid an impeachment inquiry into alleged misconduct by Trump.  Even as Pence distanced himself from the impeachment saga playing out in Washington, his penchant for sidestepping the Trump administration's most controversial episodes is perhaps facing its greatest test thus far. Congress is preparing to mount an aggressive probe into allegations that Trump pressured Ukraine to interfere in the 2020 elections and that the White House sought to cover it up - and Pence's dealings with Ukraine have already become part of the focus.  Pence did not participate in a controversial July 25 phone call in which Trump pushed Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky to investigate former vice president Joe Biden and his son, according to a senior administration official, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal deliberations.  But Pence's name has emerged in several other contexts - including as a potential successor should Trump be ousted from office - since Democrats announced this week that they were launching a formal impeachment inquiry.  The whistleblower complaint, released Thursday, said Pence canceled a planned trip to Ukraine at the direction of Trump, who was seeking to pressure the Ukrainians to help him politically.  Three people familiar with the matter confirmed that Pence's attendance had been requested at Zelensky's inauguration and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST WING 'SHELL-SHOCKED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/total-panic-shell-shocked-white-house-struggles-find-impeachment-footing-n1059251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many in the Trump White House are battle-tested from the Mueller investigation, this is starting to feel different, aides and advisers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House officials acted to 'lock down' record of call...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/whistleblower-complaint-reveals-witnesses-concern-over-handling-trump-ukraine-call-n1058941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official concluded that the president was "using the power of his office to solicit interference from a foreign country."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower Is CIA Officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/whistle-blower-is-a-cia-officer-who-was-detailed-to-the-white-house/ar-AAHToDz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Attacks Whistleblower's Sources; Punishment for Spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-attacks-whistle-blowers-sources-and-alludes-to-punishment-for-spies/ar-AAHTvMV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORED ON SEPARATE COMPUTER NETWORK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/26/biggest-bombshells-in-trump-whistleblower-complaint-cover-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whistleblower says senior White House officials intervened to "lock down" records of the call with Zelensky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are great white sharks swimming so close to beaches?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/why-are-sharks-swimming-so-close-to-north-atlantic-beaches-60-minutes-2019-09-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More sharks are showing up near coastlines in the North Atlantic Ocean. "60 Minutes" reports on what's bringing them there, Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA deploys air defense systems, troops to Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.baynews9.com/fl/tampa/ap-top-news/2019/09/26/us-deploys-air-defense-systems-troops-to-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baynews9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon says it will send one Patriot missile battery and four radar systems to Saudi Arabia, in what officials describe as the first steps to help the kingdom protect itself against Iranian attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATORS FRET TRUMP TRIAL</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/463113-senators-fret-over-prospect-of-trump-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launching of a House impeachment inquiry against President Trump is raising the prospect of a Senate trial — unnerving senators already anxious about an election-year battle where the Senate majority could be up for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' producer defends movie for holding 'mirror to our society'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/26/joker-producer-defends-movie-for-holding-mirror-to-our-society/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The executive producer of “Joker” has defended the movie over fears it may incite mass shooters — insisting people cannot “run” from the ugliest sides of society. “Loo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems accuse him of witness intimidation!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2f662aa7aa64030bed2dd496dfc3b0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on testimony by the acting director of national intelligence and a whistleblower complaint (all times local): 7 p.m. House Democrats are condemning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 2020 rivals avoid rush to defend him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/68f19fffdbdf4638ab94117b83f5c8f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidates are united in condemning President Donald Trump for seeking a foreign country's help to trash a domestic political rival. But when it comes to defending the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman put meth in bean dip served to co-workers...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/bean-dip-meth-508216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 26--An Oregon felon allegedly placed methamphetamine into bean dip that she served to co-workers at a Thriftway supermarket, according to cops who arrested the woman on multiple criminal cou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First let me take a selfie, El Salvador's president tells UN...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-let-selfie-el-salvadors-president-tells-un-211735780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Salvador's President Nayib Bukele, whose social media savvy helped win him power earlier this year, took a selfie before his maiden speech at the UN General Assembly, which he called "obsolete" and suggested scrapping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots could be headed to circus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/business/technology/article/Robots-made-famous-on-YouTube-could-be-headed-to-14471022.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) - Animal-like robots that started out as a military-funded research project might be shipped off to the circus instead of the battlefield.  Cirque du Soleil says it's in talks with robot maker Boston Dynamics about using the four-legged Spot robot in its live shows.  The agile robots walk, gallop and jump. They have become famous on YouTube but haven't been applied commercially since the company was founded in 1992.  That's changing this fall. The Waltham, Massachusetts, robotics firm revealed in a YouTube post this week that Spot is now in mass production and shipping to select customers for such uses as monitoring construction sites or inspecting energy facilities.  Cirque du Soleil says it's still in the "ideation" stage and evaluating Spot's potential in live entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas signs ex-MICROSOFT lawyer, others to aid in GOOGLE antitrust probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tech-antitrust-google-exclusive/exclusive-texas-signs-ex-microsoft-lawyer-others-to-aid-in-google-antitrust-probe-idUSKBN1WB14N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas attorney general's office has hired three consultants for a multi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Rouhani backs moving UN out of NYC to 'better' country...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/irans-rouhani-backs-moving-un-out-of-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani said Thursday that his country's delegation would vote for the United Nations headquarters to be moved out of New York if given the chance, in the latest sign of escalating tensions with the United States on the sidelines of the U.N. General Assembly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Republican governor comes out in support...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republican-vermont-governor-impeachment-inquiry-92b9ff2d-f64e-4913-832e-ea066efb08f1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His position is a departure from the party norm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owners seek expansion to 17-game NFL seasons...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/owners-seek-expansion-17-game-nfl-seasons-reports-191611325--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL owners are pushing to expand the regular season from 16 to 17 games, while reducing the number of pre-season contests, in talks with the players union, according to multiple reports Thursday. ESPN and The Athletic websites, citing unnamed sources, said team owners were making the pitch after NFL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Phones, Computers Creating Generation Of Porn Addicts...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/smart-phones-computers-generation-porn-addicts-public-health-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studies show children are typically first exposed to pornography at age 13.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Tlaib Leads Crowd In Profanity-Laced Chant...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/09/26/rashida-tlaib-leads-profanity-laced-impeachment-chant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan Democratic Rep. Rashida Tlaib on Thursday copied her viral video from earlier this year where she called President Trump a &amp;quot;motherf****r.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTING DNI TESTIFIES</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/09/26/whistleblower-complaint-top-moments-joseph-maguire-testimony/3774069002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph Maguire, the acting director of national intelligence, faced scrutiny Wednesday from lawmakers investigating the whistleblower complaint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 part costing nearly $1B for nuke modernization...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/smr/nuclear-arsenal/2019/09/25/nuclear-warhead-programs-need-850m-fix-heres-how-the-government-plans-to-cover-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delays to the B61-12 and W88 Alt 370 could cost taxpayers a lot of money, but the National Nuclear Security Administration has a plan.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
