<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'VIEW' struggles to find a Republican...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook/2021/12/27/the-view-struggles-to-find-a-republican-495553</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And coronavirus cases spike to record levels across the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Omicron hits Israel, restrictions may be eased. Why?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/article-689899</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu making comeback after unusual year off...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-flu-8895782660eb8491856e81fd387d6591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. flu season has arrived on schedule after taking a year off, with flu hospitalizations rising and two child deaths reported. Last year's flu season was the lowest on record, likely because COVID-19 measures — school closures, distancing, masks and canceled travel — prevented the spread of influenza, or because the coronavirus somehow pushed aside other viruses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windsor crossbow suspect pictured after masked man threatened Queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4348228/windsor-castle-suspect-pictured/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the first picture of the teen suspected of scaling Windsor Castle armed with a crossbow on Christmas Day. Jaswant Singh Chail, 19, was sectioned under the Mental Health Act, shortly after c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia extends prison sentence for Gulag historian who researched Stalin's purges to 15 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-extends-prison-sentence-for-gulag-historian-who-researched-stalin-s-purges-to-15-years/ar-AASbCOf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Puerto Rico became tax haven for high-flying...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/27/how-puerto-rico-became-a-tax-haven-for-crypto-millionaires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget “What do you do?” or “Where do you live?” There’s only one question on anyone’s lips in Puerto Rico right now. “‘How long have you been here?’ — it’s the first thing anyone asks,” said Keiko…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC SHORTENS QUARANTINES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-health-rochelle-walensky-d7d609c9c01e200d250df7ca7282c9d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. health officials on Monday cut isolation restrictions for Americans who catch the coronavirus from 10 to five days, and similarly shortened the time that close contacts need to quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Busting Record Numbers of Trap Houses in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3vw7w/uk-police-shut-down-record-trap-houses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Criminals are using the pandemic to force their way into the homes of vulnerable people and drug users like never before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 states see infections triple...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10347907/Seven-U-S-states-cases-triple-Omicron-continues-ravage-nation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is experiencing yet another winter Covid surge, with the situation expected to only worsen over in the weeks following the Christmas and New Years holidays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armored cars, safe rooms: Hollywood's answer to crime surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/armored-cars-and-safe-rooms-hollywoods-answer-to-the-crime-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles elites are using their wealth to fight back against the spike in violent crime that has gripped the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Create Biodegradable Batteries Buried In Ground After Use...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/biodegradable-zinc-batteries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biodegradable batteries could one day become an environmentally sustainable option for powering smartphones and flexible wearable electronic devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France Issues Work-From-Home Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/france-issues-work-from-home-mandate-n-y-tests-virus-update/ar-AASaefN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic migration spurs big Maine population growth...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2021/12/27/news/pandemic-migration-spurs-maines-biggest-population-growth-in-2-decades-xoasq1i29i/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state's population increased to just more than 1,372,000 as of July 2021, according to data from the U.S. Census Bureau, an increase of nearly 10,000 compared with a year prior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  25% of Navy warship crew infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-jacksonville-us-navy-cb7d190b7c1c1c52f5441b56740d44de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — About two dozen sailors on a U.S. Navy warship — or roughly 25% of the crew — have now tested positive for COVID-19, keeping the ship sidelined in port at Naval Station Guantanamo Bay Monday, according to U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA weed market should be flourishing. But bureaucracy blunting it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2021/12/21/californias-weed-market-has-a-bureaucracy-problem-1402260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;disconnect between city councils’ plans and lethargic government operations is hampering what should be a flourishing industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD warn of crime wave, but data show theft, robberies down...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/lapd-warn-crime-wave-data-show-theft-robberies-rcna9236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers tell one story, but recent messaging from the Los Angeles Police Department appears to be telling another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Testing Effectiveness of 4th Dose...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-study-will-test-effectiveness-of-4th-vaccine-dose/ar-AASb7hy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  'No federal solution' to pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-states-fix-omicron-covid-governors-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden said he agreed with two Republican governors on Monday that there is "no federal solution" to the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For NYC musician, not being fully vaccinated comes at cost...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/12/27/1065750796/new-york-city-musician-covid-vaccine-mandate-omicron-tinnitus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My ears are my life," says composer, pianist and teaching artist Beata Moon, who experienced ear ringing after her first vaccine dose. Around the same time, she also tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Women who have more sex have better developed brains...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/27/women-who-have-more-sex-have-better-developed-brains-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientific researchers have identified the brain region linked to genital touch in women, finding that it is better developed in those who frequently get steamy between the sheets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Ended Her Life After Blackmailed By Fake Narcotics Officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyp3nx/bhojpuri-actress-suicide-blackmail-narcotics-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She encountered the “officers” at a rave. They are being charged with abetting the woman’s suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones Downloads on Trump for Pushing Vax: Either 'Ignorant' or 'Most Evil Man Who Has Ever Lived'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/alex-jones-slams-trump-for-supporting-covid-19-vaccines-either-ignorant-or-the-most-evil-man-who-has-ever-lived/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right conspiracy theorist Alex Jones lit into former President Donald Trump on Saturday for his recent statements supporting the Covid-19 vaccinations. “This is an emergency Christmas Day warning to President Trump,” Jones said. Jones continued: You are either completely ignorant about the so-called vaccine gene therapy you helped ram through with Operation Warp Speed, or […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogan Predicts Michelle O Would Beat Donald: 'If She Runs She Wins'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/joe-rogan-predicts-michelle-obama-would-beat-trump-in-2024-if-she-runs-she-wins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Podcaster Joe Rogan believes that if Former First Lady Michelle Obama decides to run for President in 2024, she will win, Trump or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY HORROR:  Woman accused of killing boyfriend with sword on Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/woman-accused-of-killing-boyfriend-with-sword-on-christmas-eve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said they found the suspect standing outside her boyfriend’s home Friday night, covered in blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People seen CLIMBING OVER EACH OTHER for tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/ny-hospitalizations-top-5500-for-1st-time-since-february-amid-wild-scramble-for-tests/3468716/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Testing demand has gotten so intense, especially in New York City, throngs of people are climbing over each other trying to get free at-home kits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI 'prosecutor' can identify 'dissent' and press charges for common crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10346933/China-develops-AI-prosecutor-press-charges-97-accuracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The machine can file a charge based on a verbal description of the case and was built and tested by the Shanghai Pudong People's Procuratorate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Director Jean-Marc Vallée Dies Suddenly at 58...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jean-marc-vallee-dies-58-dallas-buyers-club-big-little-lies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian filmmaker Jean-Marc Vallee, the director behind Dallas Buyers Club, Big Little Lies and Sharp Objects, died suddenly at the age of 58.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury resumes deliberations at Ghislaine trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-entertainment-new-york-manhattan-jeffrey-epstein-83a1b46026e469f8c47ddfef53215269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A jury resumed deliberations Monday in the sex trafficking trial of Ghislaine Maxwell after a long holiday weekend. The British socialite is charged with recruiting and grooming teenagers as young as 14 to be sexually assaulted by financier Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health experts say Italy faces paralysis under quarantine rules...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211227142642-ejr3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY (PIX):Health experts say Italy faces paralysis under quarantine rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'21 was huge year for space exploration. '22 could be even bigger...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/2021-was-a-huge-year-for-space-exploration-2022-could-be-even-bigger/ar-AASaVdi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI PUSHES DOMESTIC TRAVEL VAX RULE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/fauci-says-domestic-travel-vaccination-rule-should-be-considered/ar-AASbcTj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Gene Found In People From Greenland Makes Ice Cream As Healthy As Broccoli!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/genetic-variant-sugar-healthy-greenland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say up to three percent of Greenlanders are able to process sugar differently, making ice cream as healthy as broccoli!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new rules of Monopoly...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/27/monopoly-antitrust-new-rules-tech-525161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington has spent decades playing from the same rulebook in the game of keeping dominant businesses from snuffing out the competition. But a new breed of antitrust enforcers say those rules are rigged against consumers — and in favor of Big Tech. They say it’s time to change the game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE:  THOUSANDS More flights canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/27/business/flights-canceled-omicron-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 2,000 flights have been canceled Monday as Covid cases surge across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostradamus predictions for '22: Cannibals, robots, cryptocurrency...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/27/nostradamus-predictions-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the year comes to a close, the news is getting grimmer, folks — at least according to long-dead, divining daddy Nostradamus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Justice Roberts Tops Federal Leaders in Approval...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/358373/justice-roberts-tops-federal-leaders-americans-approval.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of 11 prominent federal government officials, Chief Justice John Roberts is the best rated by Americans and the only one with the approval of all party groups.lyd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global gloom over New Year's celebrations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-soccer-sports-lifestyle-health-beab3be1a11d1ef021e66fa3c6061c47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — After struggling with the coronavirus for far too long, the world understands all too well Belgium's word of the year, “knaldrang!” — the urge to party, the need to let loose. Yet as New Year celebrations approach, the omicron variant is casting more gloom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol panel to investigate Trump call to WILLARD hotel in hours before attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/27/capitol-attack-panel-investigate-trump-call-willard-hotel-before-assault</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Committee to request contents of the call seeking to stop Biden’s certification and may subpoena Rudy Giuliani</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury to resume deliberations in Ghislaine sex abuse case...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/jury-resume-deliberations-ghislaine-maxwell-sex-abuse-case-2021-12-27/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury in British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell's sex abuse trial is secheduled to resume deliberations on Monday, after breaking for a long weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man banned from leaving Israel for 8,000 years over child support payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-689839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's Big Year and the Many Roadblocks Ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2021-12-27/elon-musk-in-2022-faces-many-roadblocks-at-tesla-spacex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Outlets hurt by dwindling public interest in news...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-presidential-elections-arts-and-entertainment-7cc91db0950a8e7e7bcf50d5d23dfc26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. To a large degree, 2021 represented the inevitable hangover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese citizens slam Musk after space station near-misses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinese-citizens-slam-musk-online-after-space-station-near-misses-2021-12-27/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese citizens lashed out online against billionaire Tesla founder Elon Musk's space ambitions on Monday after China complained that its space station was forced to take evasive action to avoid collision with satellites launched by Musk's Starlink programme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX film has 'wildest' sex scene of year with gruesome incest twist...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/netflix-film-two-wildest-sex-25792224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Netflix release is enough to make anyone's stomach turn but it also features a painful-sounding sex scene which gets even more gruesome following a family revelation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Exodus Sees Record Spend on Homes Outside City...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/london-exodus-sees-record-spend-on-homes-outside-city-ft-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London Exodus Sees Record Spend on Homes Outside City, FT Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican optimism grows over red wave in '22...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/587193-gop-optimism-grows-over-possible-red-wave-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With less than a year to go until the 2022 midterms, Republicans are increasingly bullish on the prospect of a red wave that could flip both chambers of Congress and end Democrats’ unified control in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your DNA Test Could Send Relative to Jail...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/27/your-dna-test-could-send-a-relative-to-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On any given day, CeCe Moore’s inbox is flooded with strangers asking her to solve the mysteries of life and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Disgust Explains Everything...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/27/how-disgust-explains-everything/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. Two distinguished</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Other Arab States Falter, Saudi Arabia Seeks to Become Cultural Hub...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/27/as-other-arab-states-falter-saudi-arabia-seeks-to-become-a-cultural-hub/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEDDAH, Saudi Arabia — A pregnant Saudi woman, far from home, finds herself stalked by inner and outer demons. A</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's president to visit Iran 'very soon'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/finance/news/venezuelas-president-visit-iran-very-021752928.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro said on Sunday he will soon visit Iran to finalize new agreements on cooperation with the Middle Eastern country, which has become Venezuela's top ally in boosting oil output amid U.S. sanctions. Venezuela and Iran have strengthened their ties since last year. Maduro's government has received vital equipment for its oil industry from Iran, which in return has received crude and other primary resources from the South American country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAMPION OF HUMAN RIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenationalnews.com/opinion/obituaries/2021/12/26/desmond-tutu-south-africas-unwavering-champion-of-human-rights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archbishop preached love and forgiveness throughout his lifelong struggle against discrimination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan gets her court-mandated public apology from British newspaper...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/snyde/ny-meghan-markle-mail-apology-20211226-icsoe326pfhurisqt5nkt7vphi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her lawsuit win, Meghan Markle got a front-page apology from the British newspaper that published parts of a personal letter she wrote to her father.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men across America are getting vasectomies 'as an act of love'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/men-across-america-are-getting-vasectomies-e2-80-98as-an-act-of-love-e2-80-99/ar-AAS9VJe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE:  Pandemic and weather complicate travel again...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pandemic-and-weather-complicate-travel-again-as-16730811.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic continued to scramble Americans' plans on the day after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Economy Now Set to Surpass $100 Trillion...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-economy-now-set-surpass-000500732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The world economy is set to surpass $100 trillion for the first time in 2022, two years earlier than previously forecast, according to the Centre for Economics and Business Research. Most Read from BloombergCoronavirus Can Persist for Months After Traversing BodyCases Surge Globally; Fauci Warns of Complacency: Virus UpdateWorld Economy Now Set to Surpass $100 Trillion in 2022China Reports Most Daily Local Infection Cases Since JanuaryAlex Jones' Wife Arrested on Domestic Violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's strict 'zero Covid' rules fail to stop spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4343809/chinas-strict-zero-covid-policy-lockdowns-failing-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA’S strict “zero Covid” policy with harsh lockdowns is failing in the battle against the Omicron variant. The country has the world’s strictest strategy with the most re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Border wait times swell as staffing shortages plague inspections booths...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2021-12-26/border-waits-look-ahead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public officials in the region have said they plan to press the federal government in the new year on the issue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military cracking down on 'questionable tattoos' to combat extremism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/military-is-cracking-down-on-e2-80-98questionable-tattoos-e2-80-99-to-combat-extremism-here-e2-80-99s-how/ar-AAS63zn?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci warns of complacency with virus set to fill hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/fauci-warns-of-complacency-with-virus-set-to-fill-hospitals/ar-AAS9LXW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corona can persist for months after traversing entire body...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/coronavirus-can-persist-for-months-after-traversing-body/ar-AAS9pry?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we feel pain when we dream?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/sleep/article-689779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot reacts to human invading its personal space!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/robot-compared-terminator-reaction-human-25789021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ameca the robot was filmed reacting to a human entering its "personal space" and it's sent the internet into a frenzy. Engineered Arts said the bot was "starting to freak us out"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MATRIX' FALLS INTO BOXOFFICE VOID...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/12/26/matrix-resurrections-is-the-sequel-no-one-wanted-and-no-one-went-to-see-doa-at-the-box-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
