<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'MATRIX RESURRECTIONS' Stuns With First Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/matrix-4-trailer-released-1235010322/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Warner Bros. franchise installment will be released theatrically and on HBO Max on Dec. 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX MANDATE FOR ALL FEDERAL WORKERS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/09/politics/joe-biden-covid-speech/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden on Thursday will impose more stringent vaccine rules on federal workers, and take steps to encourage private businesses to do the same, during a major speech meant to lay out a new approach to combating the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane could hit Los Cabos resorts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-caribbean-floods-storms-hurricanes-38c94cbeccf41ffb49aab906e8737154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Olaf was building toward hurricane force Thursday while on a track toward the Los Cabos resorts at the tip of Mexico's Baja California Peninsula. The U.S, National Hurricane Center said the storm was likely to bring hurricane conditions to the area overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania closest adviser to release book...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/09/politics/stephanie-grisham-book/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Grisham, whose career with the Trump administration included stints as East Wing communications director, White House press secretary and chief of staff to Melania Trump, has written a book that will be released next month, two people familiar with the project tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why everyone wants to punch Jake Paul in face...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/08/jake-paul-knows-you-want-to-see-him-knocked-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high school dropout, who went from social media influencer to Disney star to professional boxing, has courted controversy and negativity wherever he goes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KICKOFF: Brady, BUCS begin defense of title against COWBOYS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-nfl-tom-brady-bruce-arians-tampa-2ebf6cd8abf1261bf8c94ff870d53536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — Lofty, maybe even gargantuan, expectations don’t faze Tom Brady and the Tampa Bay Buccaneers. The reigning Super Bowl champions open the 2021 NFL season against the Dallas Cowboys on Thursday night, confident they have everything it takes — at least on paper — to become the first team to win back-to-back titles since Brady led the 2003 and 2004 New England Patriots to consecutive crowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi crackdown remaking Chinese society...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Xi-s-crackdown-is-remaking-Chinese-society-16445407.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The orders have been sudden, dramatic and often baffling. Last week,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman was late for flight. So she told airline workers there was bomb on plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-woman-was-late-for-her-flight-so-she-told-airline-workers-there-was-a-bomb-on-the-plane-police-say/ar-AAOfu8k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago mother's alleged bomb threat forced an airline to evacuate the plane, delaying the flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device tests for corona in armpit sweat...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210909-thai-device-tests-for-coronavirus-in-armpit-sweat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thai device tests for coronavirus in armpit sweat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffing shortage on Rikers spawning violent beatdowns, wild parties, fatal ODs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/09/staffing-shortage-on-rikers-breeding-beatdowns-and-fatal-ods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffing crisis on Rikers Island has created a dangerous and chaotic situation for inmates that’s allowed inmates to assault each other, fatally overdose and post TikTok videos of themselves part…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Holmes drawn as villain, underdog as trial begins...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elizabeth-holmes-trial-begins-70c62afae356279ef8706b3ac9f5bcae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JOSE, Calif. (AP) — Prosecutors and defense attorneys sketched dueling portraits of fallen Silicon Valley star Elizabeth Holmes as her trial got underway Wednesday, alternatively describing her as a greedy villain who faked her way to the top and as a passionate underdog whose spent years trying to shake up the health care industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Could Eventually Collapse, Swedish Central Banker Warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/cryptocurrency-news/bitcoin-could-eventually-collapse-swedish-central-banker-warns-2611490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin Could Eventually Collapse, Swedish Central Banker Warns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau struggles, two weeks before election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20210909-canada-s-trudeau-struggles-two-weeks-before-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triumphant Taliban start putting policies into practice...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210909-triumphant-taliban-start-putting-policies-into-practice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Triumphant Taliban start putting policies into practice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED warns of unpaid leave for staff given religious jab exemptions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/571409-united-airlines-warns-of-unpaid-leave-for-staff-given</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Airlines told its staff on Wednesday that those who are granted religious exemptions from getting vaccinated against the coronavirus will be placed on a temporary unpaid leave,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red states eye Texas abortion law as new model...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/571392-red-states-eye-texas-abortion-law-as-new-model</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican state legislators who oppose abortion rights are eyeing a just-implemented measure in Texas as a model for opening a new front in the war over reproductive choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to deliver six-step plan on pandemic... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210909085925-9os8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BIDEN:Biden to deliver six-step plan on COVID-19 pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proponents of Post-Trump Curbs on Executive Power Prepare New Push...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/09/proponents-of-post-trump-curbs-on-executive-power-prepare-new-push/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As Donald J. Trump’s norm-busting presidency careened through two impeachments, his departure set the stage for lawmakers to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Missouri '2nd Amendment Sanctuary' Fight...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/09/inside-missouris-2nd-amendment-sanctuary-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OZARK, Mo. — Brad Cole is a fiery defender of the Second Amendment, a set-jawed lawman with a lacquered alligator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Jew leaves...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-israel-afghanistan-evacuations-c616b5b847da79f0cfc1de6f0f37b0b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The last member of Afghanistan's Jewish community has left the country. Zebulon Simentov, who lived in a dilapidated synagogue in Kabul, kept kosher and prayed in Hebrew, endured decades of war as the country's centuries-old Jewish community rapidly dwindled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala rallies at critical time...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/2021/09/08/Harris-and-Newsom-align-at-critical-time-as-recall-vote-nears/stories/202109080146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president echoed Mr. Newsom’s campaign message that the outcome will ripple beyond the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen triggers alarm bells over debt ceiling cliff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/571413-yellen-triggers-alarm-bells-over-debt-ceiling-cliff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen is setting off alarm bells over a looming brawl about the nation's borrowing limit that could spark a global economic crisis if Congress fails to take action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CIGAR!</title>
      <link>https://heavy.com/entertainment/monica-lewinsky-cigar-bill-clinton-brand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;heavy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment: American Crime Story" aims to paint a more nuanced portrait of the Bill Clinton and Monica Lewinsky sex scandal and the resulting impeachment process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL 'cyber grave robbers' charged with condo collapse ID theft...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/three-charged-with-stealing-identities-florida-condo-collapse-victims-2021-09-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man and two women were arrested and charged with stealing the identities of seven victims of the Surfside condominium collapse near Miami Beach this summer and attempting to obtain credit cards in their names, a Florida prosecutor said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA on mission -- to get more social media followers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/08/the-cias-on-a-mission-to-get-more-social-media-followers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CIA wants to crack the code to Instagram popularity to soften up its shadowy image as part of a quirky new public relations campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol cops warn of potential for violence during September 18 rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/08/politics/capitol-hill-security-september-18-rally/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement officials are bracing for potential clashes and unrest during an upcoming right-wing rally in Washington, DC, as violent rhetoric surrounding the September 18 event has increased online and counterprotests are being planned for the same day, according to an internal Capitol Police memo reviewed by CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Starting 'Pass' Program...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2021/09/08/both-oahu-maui-will-implement-vaccine-pass-programs-will-other-counties-follow-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Oahu and Maui will be implementing “vaccine pass” programs soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder attacked by egg-throwing agitators...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/larry-elder-attacked-egg-throwing-agitators-los-angeles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican California gubernatorial candidate Larry Elder had eggs thrown at him while walking in Los Angeles on Wednesday, video of the incident reviewed by Fox News shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger says recall 'very dangerous' for Newsom...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/571369-schwarzenegger-says-recall-election-is-very-dangerous-for-newsom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arnold Schwarzenegger, the only candidate to ever win a recall election in California, says the state’s upcoming referendum on Gov. Gavin Newsom (D) is “very dangerous” for the incumbent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semen-filled syringe attacker sentenced to 10 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/maryland-man-whose-attack-on-a-woman-with-a-semen-filled-syringe-was-caught-on-camera-sentenced-to-10-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Maryland man who plunged a semen-filled syringe into a woman in an Anne Arundel County grocery store is headed to prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion gets closer with successful test of new magnet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/08/fusion-gets-closer-with-successful-test-of-new-kind-of-magnet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If fusion can be achieved on earth and commercialized, it will provide a nearly unlimited source of clean energy without producing the waste of nuclear fission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson Wins Vote to Push U.K. Taxes to Highest Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/johnson-wins-health-care-vote-to-push-u-k-taxes-to-highest-ever/ar-AAOevqf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson won a mandate from the House of Commons to raise taxes to the highest level on record to fund health and social care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates riot across prisons in Israel as manhunt for escaped prisoners continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/prison-transfers-postponed-due-to-resistance-concerns-report-678941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ofer Prison PIJ inmates were not transferred and dispersed as ordered due to fear of violent resistance • family members of the escapees were arrested as the third day of the manhunt is ongoing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER OF HOPE ENDS IN GLOOM</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-pandemics-coronavirus-pandemic-north-carolina-b9012bd212ef28dcceec583eb3ca7612</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The summer that was supposed to mark America’s independence from COVID-19 is instead drawing to a close with the U.S. more firmly under the tyranny of the virus, with deaths per day back up to where they were in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Germany's red scare is real...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/germany-election-2021-red-scare-angela-merkel-cdu-armin-laschet-spd-olaf-scholz-greens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Merkel warns that a vote for the SPD could let the far-left into government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Official Who Warned on Real Estate Was Active REIT Trader...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/economy/fed-official-who-warned-on-real-estate-was-active-reit-trader-2610684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed Official Who Warned on Real Estate Was Active REIT Trader</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Most expensive home in America defaults on $165 million in debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/08/most-expensive-home-in-america-defaults-and-heads-for-sale.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 105,000-square-foot Bel Air estate, known as "The One," was placed into receivership by the Los Angeles County Superior Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian minister dies during Arctic drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/yevgeny-zinichev-russia-emergencies-minister-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergencies Minister Yevgeny Zinichev dies at the age of 55.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Stern ROASTS Anti-Vax Radio Hosts Who Died...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/radio/howard-stern-roasts-anti-vax-radio-hosts-who-died-says-make-vaccine-mandatory-fck-them-fck-their-freedom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary shock-jock Howard Stern laughed at and mocked right-wing radio hosts who have died of Covid after preaching against vaccines, and made a forceful case that the vaccines should be mandatory. On Tuesday’s edition of Sirius XM’s The Howard Stern Show, the host gleefully derided the recent slew of conservative radio hosts who railed against […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC Bans Beer Because Bureaucrats Dislike Label...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/08/north-carolina-banned-this-beer-because-bureaucrats-dislike-the-label/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now they'll have to explain to a federal judge how this isn't a violation of the First Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Total Financial Surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/08/bidens-total-financial-surveillance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if every one of your noncash financial transactions was automatically reported to a beefed-up, audit-hungry IRS?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU lists rare nerve disorder as possible side-effect of ASTRAZENECA...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/eu-lists-rare-nerve-disorder-as-possible-side-effect-of-astrazeneca-covid-19-vaccine-678957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL judge allows mask mandates in schools after ruling against DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/webview/us/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-vaccine-updates-09-08-21/h_51ab48dff48e67b143f9a5ae28c2974a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 cases are rising in much of the US, and children now represent more than a quarter of weekly cases nationwide. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpaca, who health officials killed thinking he had bovine tuberculosis, might not have been sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/geronimo-the-alpaca-who-uk-health-officials-killed-thinking-he-had-bovine-tuberculosis-might-not-have-been-sick/ar-AAOe9fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geronimo was killed by the UK government last month after twice testing positive for bovine tuberculosis in a saga that featured protests and courts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial set to begin for fallen tech star Elizabeth Holmes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-entertainment-trials-california-san-jose-70c62afae356279ef8706b3ac9f5bcae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JOSE, California (AP) — Opening statements are scheduled for Wednesday in the highly anticipated trial of Theranos founder Elizabeth Holmes, the fallen tech star accused of duping financial backers, customers and patients into believing that her startup was about to revolutionize medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew bolts in bid to avoid being served sex assault papers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16078341/prince-andrew-bolts-for-balmoral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew has made a bolt for the safety of Balmoral and the Queen to avoid “multiple attempts” to serve sex assault legal papers at his Windsor mansion. The scandal-hit Duke of York was pictur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Reduced To ZOOM As Red Carpet Rolled Out for Taliban...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/kerry-reduced-to-zoom-as-ccp-rolls-out-red-carpet-for-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese diplomats relegated Biden climate czar John Kerry to a Zoom conference the same day China joined Taliban leaders in a photo-op to pledge "friendly relations" with the terror group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEE VILLAIN TRIPP IN A FAT SUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sarah-paulsons-portrayal-of-linda-tripp-in-impeachment-is-a-mess-heres-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Paulson has become Ryan Murphy’s go-to actress for knotty antiheroes and complex villains, and with good reason—but “Impeachment” (like that fat suit) does her few favors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  CARTOONISH...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/tv/tv-reviews/impeachment-american-crime-story-review-1218870/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fat suits, bad accents, and two-dimensional characters spoil the latest season of Ryan Murphy’s docudrama anthology series</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RYAN MURPHY AVOIDS HIS OWN PREMIERE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/impeachment-american-crime-story-premiere-monica-lewinsky-1235007363/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Wednesday's premiere, Beanie Feldstein, Sarah Paulson, Billy Eichner and Cobie Smulders discussed Lewinsky's role on set and how they feel about the real-life people watching their portrayals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES 300% HIGHER THAN YEAR AGO</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/daily-us-covid-cases-more-170000206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daily coronavirus cases are four times higher than they were following Labor Day weekend of last year with the number of daily deaths twice as high as they were this time in 2020, according to data from Johns Hopkins University. Since the global health crisis emerged in late 2019, the United States has recorded more than 40 million COVID-19 cases, including just 4 million in the last month ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.9 million: Another record for job openings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-67a34a2e9c416155bab6af1b0e3cfcf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. employers posted a record job openings for the second consecutive month in July — more affirmation that the labor market is bouncing back from last year's coronavirus recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under pressure to deliver on liberal priorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/we-re-out-of-time-biden-democrats-under-pressure-to-deliver-on-liberal-priorities/ar-AAOe79o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – President Joe Biden and congressional Democrats are expected to spend much of September negotiating the size and scope of a proposed $3.5 trillion budget bill that would fund a battery of new government programs. It’s a negotiation whose outcome Ady Barkan sees as life or death. The 37-year-old progressive advocate, who uses a wheelchair after being diagnosed with ALS in 2016, is ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems optimistic as Republicans divided over frontrunner...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-optimistic-ahead-of-california-recall-vote-as-gop-is-divided-over-its-frontrunner/ar-AAOdLgF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats have returned more than half of the 6.2 million ballots mailed in so far; Republicans account for a quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 years after 9/11, war on terror persists and there are more threats than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article253943783.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The day after the Sept. 11 attacks, the United States issued a warning to the Taliban: No government that provides a haven for terrorists is safe from the American military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 1% evading $163 billion year in taxes, Treasury finds...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/08/the-top-1-percent-are-evading-163-billion-a-year-in-taxes-the-treasury-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The wealthiest 1 percent of Americans are the nation’s most egregious tax evaders, failing to pay as much</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GO YOUR OWN WAY:  Lindsey Buckingham Has Survived It All...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/08/lindsey-buckingham-has-survived-it-all/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — One day in early February 2019, Lindsey Buckingham woke up to a wallop of a surprise: He</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia cuts Robert E. Lee statue into pieces...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/robert-e-lee-statue-virginia-removed-92955a351d9fda6319f379ddc28df8a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A crowd erupted in cheers and song Wednesday as work crews hoisted an enormous statue of Confederate Gen. Robert E. Lee off the pedestal where it has towered over Virginia’s capital city for more than a century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treehouses proliferate during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-arts-and-entertainment-environment-and-nature-colorado-778069ae4bc49a5d22efbdd8a2d83898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthropologists believe our ancient human ancestors spent their time in trees, so it should be no surprise we love treehouses today. Treehouses of all kinds are experiencing a renaissance. When an acre-size slice of land in Gold Hill, Colorado, came on the market earlier this year, local resident Jessica Brookhart, 41, snapped it up for $80,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AKON SAYS FAMOUS HAVE 'MORE ISSUES' THAN POOR AFTER MICHAEL K. WILLIAMS DEATH...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/09/08/akon-michael-k-williams-drug-overdose-od-rich-famous-poor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Akon is mourning the loss of his good friend Michael K. Williams, and says he's the latest example of how the "facade of success" can send celebrities into a tailspin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Chaotic Parking Lot Brawl After School Board Votes for Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/missouri-parents-have-chaotic-parking-lot-brawl-after-school-board-votes-for-mask-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos ensued after a Missouri school board voted to reinstate a mask mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES pilots, citing fatigue, plan protests...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/571242-american-airlines-pilots-planning-protests-citing-fatigue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines pilots are planning to protest work conditions, citing fatigue they say has been caused by their company's mismanagement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN: USA on track to default on debt in October...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/571237-yellen-us-on-track-to-default-on-national-debt-in-october</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Wednesday warned congressional leaders that the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Emergencies Minister Dies in Arctic Drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/09/08/russian-emergencies-minister-dies-in-arctic-drills-a74997</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yevgeny Zinichev, 55, died while trying to save a prominent filmmaker in what Putin described as “an irreparable personal loss.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke Monitors Say Surveillance Gear Missing in Iran...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nuclear-monitors-surveillance-gear-missing-091150312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A mysterious blast that shook a centrifuge workshop in Iran is still reverberating among international nuclear monitors who are now reporting that some of their surveillance equipment went missing following the June incident. The International Atomic Energy Agency told diplomats in a restricted report that failure to recover its recording devices could imperil inspectors’ ability to reconstruct activity at the facility in the town of Karaj, located northwest of Tehran. The worksho</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test of Biden clout?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-elections-california-health-business-7ca6a0c22fde159de796b16890f126fb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden has been beset by public health, military and climate crises in the past month. Not much time has been left for a potential political disaster brewing for his party in California.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
