<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Workers Block Roads in Mass Protest Against NY Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/hundreds-emergency-workers-block-new-york-roads-protest-against-vaccine-mandate-1642309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City workers have until October 29 to get at least one dose of the vaccine or go on unpaid leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD/COSTA: Trump Was Calling Into War Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.msnbc.com/morning-joe/watch/what-happened-behind-the-scenes-ahead-of-the-january-6-attack-124530245759</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Costa and Bob Woodward join Morning Joe to discuss new reports that prior to the January 6 insurrection, Trump lieutenants Rudy Giuliani, Steve Bannon and John Eastman were positioned in a Willard Hotel room with the goal of overturning the results of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Tallest Ferris Wheel Opens In Dubai; 38 Minute Ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/worlds-tallest-ferris-wheel-which-takes-38-minutes-to-ride-opens-in-dubai-70744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dubai Eye is almost double the size of the London Eye and can welcome 1,750 visitors at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman busted for striking mother in head with thrown tacos...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/domestic-battery/taco-battery-arrest-102358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a domestic taco battery, Florida police report. Braiden Lankford, 20, was arrested late Saturday evening for allegedly striking her mother in the head with two thrown tacos inside the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory loss and 'brain fog' may be side effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/10/25/memory-loss-long-term-covid-symptoms/6168210001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-term COVID-19 symptoms could be memory loss and other cognitive dysfunctions commonly labeled as "brain fog."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside AMAZON Worst Human Resources Problem...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/24/inside-amazons-worst-human-resources-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year ago, Tara Jones, an Amazon warehouse worker in Oklahoma, cradled her newborn, glanced over her pay stub on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA STAR RIPS NIKE: 'STOP SLAVERY'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/25/enes-kanter-china-nike-viral-video-modern-day-slavery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enes Kanter torched China and Nike in a new Twitter video. He criticized Nike for being &amp;amp;quot;silent&amp;amp;quot; on China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location Data Firm Got GPS Data From Apps Even When People Opted Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dgmqz/huq-location-data-opt-out-no-consent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news around location data firm Huq shows that data companies may not even really know if they've received consent to harvest information from ordinary phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepest quake ever detected struck 467 miles beneath Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/deepest-earthquake-ever-detected-struck-467-miles-beneath-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If confirmed, the temblor would be a shock to geologists who thought rocks that deep inside Earth were too putty-like to break and shake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After drought, west coast slammed by 'bomb cyclone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211025-after-drought-us-west-coast-slammed-by-bomb-cyclone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After drought, US west coast slammed by 'bomb cyclone'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Now Worth Over Quarter Trillion Dollars...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/elon-musk-quarter-trillion-dollars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So long, Jeffrey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor under fire for hiring registered child sex offender to inspect homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox32chicago.com/news/dolton-mayor-under-fire-for-hiring-registered-child-sex-offender-to-inspect-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox32chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: FOX 32 News has learned Lavelle Redmond spent 24 years in prison after pleading guilty to taking part in a brutal gang rape and beating in the Roseland neighborhood in 1991. He and three others kidnapped and sexually assaulted two girls, ages 13 and 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos wants to build tourism space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/25/tech/blue-origin-space-station-jeff-bezos-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin, the rocket and space tourism company founded by Jeff Bezos, is proposing a massive new commercial space station called "Orbital Reef" that could be used to host science experiments, vacation getaways, and potentially even in-space manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing removing domes from mosques to make them more 'Chinese'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/10/24/1047054983/china-muslims-sinicization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is removing domes and minarets from thousands of mosques. Authorities are taking down overtly Islamic architecture as part of a "sinicization" push to make them seem more traditionally Chinese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin open to it...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/578325-manchin-says-hes-open-to-tax-targeting-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) signaled on Monday that he's open to a tax targeting billionaires as Democrats scramble to figure out how to pay for their sweeping social spending bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds refused entry to Scotland in vaccine passport 'chaos'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-scotland-59034619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Scottish Hospitality Group says the first weekend of enforcement of the scheme was an "unmitigated disaster".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Ditching Iconic Palm Trees -- To Fight Climate 'Crisis'?</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/10/23/florida-is-ditching-palm-trees-to-fight-the-climate-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you think of The Sunshine State, beaches and palm trees come to mind. But what if those palm trees were slowly replaced with other trees? That could happen over time because of climate change, and communities in South Florida are trying to save the world from the climate crisis, one tree at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  TESLA hits $1 trillion market cap...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/25/tesla-shares-up-on-news-hertz-will-purchase-100000-electric-vehicles.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of the deal brought Tesla's stock to a record high, one trading day after shares hit a record high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Seven conspiratorial actions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/bob-woodward-finds-seven-conspiratorial-actions-by-trump-and-bannon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigative journalist Bob Woodward said his reporting shows "seven conspiratorial actions" between former President Donald Trump and Steve Bannon as part of an effort to overturn the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Israel become the OVER-inoculation nation on Covid?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/has-israel-become-the-over-inoculation-nation-on-covid-19-analysis-682027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The policy presents particular difficulties for those who were not vaccinated with Pfizer and for whom a booster might not be advisable or available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beckham slammed over $250 million deal to be Qatar ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10125357/Campaigners-fans-slam-David-Beckham-deal-Qatar-ambassador-face-World-Cup.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaigners and football fans alike have slammed David Beckham after it was reported he has signed a deal worth up to £150million to become the face of the 2022 World Cup in Qatar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A B U S E</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/the-facebook-papers-maid-abuse-94909f43c725af09522704348e35bd25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Two years ago, Apple threatened to pull Facebook and Instagram from its app store over concerns about the platform being used as a tool to trade and sell maids in the Mideast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HATE AND TERROR</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/the-facebook-papers-language-moderation-problems-392cb2d065f81980713f37384d07e61f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — As the Gaza war raged and tensions surged across the Middle East last May, Instagram briefly banned the hashtag #AlAqsa, a reference to the Al-Aqsa Mosque in Jerusalem’s Old City, a flash point in the conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Skirts Escalation as Erdogan Softens on Envoy Expulsions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/turkish-officials-seek-to-avoid-expulsion-of-western-ambassadors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish Officials Seek to Avoid Expulsion of Western Ambassadors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple nor'easters could take aim at Northeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/multiple-noreasters-could-take-aim-at-northeast/1037400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nor’easters, which will be unusual for this time of the year, will unleash miserable conditions and the rawest weather since way back on Memorial Day weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Electrician Says Result Of 'Negligence And Unprofessionalism'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/rust-serge-svetnoy-halyna-hutchins-alec-baldwin-negligence-unprofessionalism-1234861697/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serge Svetnoy, the gaffer, or chief electrician, on the set of Alec Baldwin’s Rust is laying the blame for the accidental shooting death of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins on the negligence o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Rules PROJECT VERITAS Is 'Political Spying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/judge-rules-james-o-keefe-s-project-veritas-is-political-spying/ar-AAPVc16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge has dealt conservative figure James O’Keefe a legal blow, ruling that his group’s undercover operations against a Democratic consulting firm can fairly be described at an upcoming million-dollar trial as “political spying.” Making matters worse for the right-wing star, the judge cited O’Keefe’s own book as evidence against him. In 2016, Allison Maass, an operative for O’Keefe’s Project Veritas group, took an internship at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady's historic day took backseat to encounter with 9-year-old cancer survivor...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/tom-brady-s-historic-day-took-a-backseat-to-his-encounter-with-a-9-year-old-cancer-survivor/ar-AAPVYUj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The youngster dissolved into happy tears at meeting his hero, who became the first quarterback to pass for 600 touchdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK LEAK SHAKES TECH GIANT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/25/facebook-whistleblower-documents-released-shares-under-pressure.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook Papers include stories from 17 U.S. news outlets with access to internal documents provided by former employee Frances Haugen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Now Worth Quarter Trillion Dollars...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-10-25/elon-musk-is-worth-a-quarter-of-a-trillion-dollars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How LIBERTY Discourages, Dismisses Student Sex Assault Reports...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/the-liberty-way-how-liberty-university-discourages-and-dismisses-students-reports-of-sexual-assaults</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The school founded by evangelist Jerry Falwell ignored reports of rape and threatened to punish accusers for breaking its moral code, say former students. An official who says he was fired for raising concerns calls it a “conspiracy of silence.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JFK nephews urge White House to reveal assassination records...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/24/jfk-nephews-biden-assassination-records-517049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president once more pushed back the scheduled release. But after 58 years, family members say the secrecy needs to end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Kamala, a shifting role: Fewer public events with president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-kamala-harris-a-shifting-role-fewer-public-events-with-biden/ar-AAPVLwb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has branded itself as the 'Biden-Harris' administration, but the two, once inseparable, are now spending more time apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEME COIN HITS ALL-TIME HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/25/business/shiba-inu-coin-price-soars-hnk-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parody cryptocurrency shiba inu coin just climbed to an all-time high and is one of the biggest digital currencies by market value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China warships circle Japan in joint drill...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/25/asia/china-russia-naval-flotilla-circles-japan-intl-hnk-ml/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A joint Chinese and Russian naval exercise, in which a flotilla of 10 warships completed a near circle around Japan's main island, has been touted by the two countries as a means of ensuring stability in a volatile region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona outlook worries experts as mask, shot mandate battles rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/arizona-s-pandemic-outlook-worries-experts-as-mask-and-vaccine-mandate-battles-rage/ar-AAPVLug</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state has caught up to New York in total reported covid-19 deaths per capita.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugs, crime, protests: Ecuador stares into abyss...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211025-drugs-crime-and-protests-ecuador-stares-into-the-abyss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drugs, crime and protests: Ecuador stares into the abyss</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris jokes to children that humans could be fed to animals to help planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10128185/Boris-Johnson-jokes-horrified-children-feeding-humans-animals-climate-change-event.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PM made the joke as he faced a grilling from youngsters about his environmental plans in the £2.6million Downing Street briefing room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People or profit?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/the-facebook-papers-whistleblower-misinfo-trafficking-64f11ccae637cdfb7a89e049c5095dca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook the company is losing control of Facebook the product — not to mention the last shreds of its carefully crafted, decade-old image as a benevolent company just wanting to connect the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripping military bases of Confederate names stirs passions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/richmond-race-and-ethnicity-virginia-army-congress-6e1fb44fddafa18efad132592215d3ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLACKSTONE, Va. (AP) — Civil War history casts a long shadow in Virginia, the birthplace of Confederate generals, scene of their surrender and now a crossroad of controversy over renaming military bases that honor rebel leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to start vaccinating children at age 3 as cases spread...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-business-beijing-travel-4680b533429a7e3e75c6f99745b3664b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Children as young as 3 will start receiving COVID-19 vaccines in China, where 76% of the population has been fully vaccinated and authorities are maintaining a zero-tolerance policy toward outbreaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasure trove for antitrust war...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/25/facebook-market-dominance-whistleblower-516918</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents collected by whistleblower Frances Haugen could give the company "a lot to regret" in its fights to prove it's not a monopoly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montanans used to live and let live. Now bitter confrontations cloud Big Sky Country...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Montanans-used-to-live-and-let-live-Now-bitter-16561244.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KALISPELL, Mont. - By the time the third teenager had died by suicide since the start of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady's latest milestone is another untouchable one...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-tom-brady-on-football-aaron-rodgers-ec16ae4f2693f997f39cb8d841b6fc8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — Tom Brady’s latest milestone is another untouchable one. Brady became the first player to throw 600 career touchdown passes and then tacked on two more in Tampa Bay’s 38-3 rout over Chicago on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Navy fight and win war?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/578216-can-the-us-navy-fight-and-win-a-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worrying question is whether the U.S. Navy is fit and prepared for a conflict with an adversary that is at least as well equipped and armed as it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Challenges Biden Again With Broad Cybersurveillance Operation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/25/russia-challenges-biden-again-with-broad-cybersurveillance-operation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEA ISLAND, Ga. — Russia’s premier intelligence agency has launched another campaign to pierce thousands of U.S. government, corporate and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case aginst Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2021/10/25/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-whistleblower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC has been asked to probe whether Mark Zuckerberg's ironclad management style, described in newly released documents and by insiders, led to disastrous outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIS CLOSE: McAuliffe, Youngkin tied in gov race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578241-mcauliffe-youngkin-dead-even-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin are locked in a tied race nearly one week out from Virginia's gubernatorial election, according to a poll released on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538: Biden approval rating dips to new low...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/biden-approval-rating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest polls on President Joe Biden’s approval ratings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Thai Temple Where Tattoos Come to Life...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/25/inside-the-thai-temple-where-tattoos-come-to-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sky was streaked with purple when I boarded the early-morning train from Bangkok to the Nakhon Chai Si District</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FACEBOOK Papers: Docs reveal internal fury and dissent over site's policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/facebook-whistleblower-documents-detail-deep-look-facebook-rcna3580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook whistleblower documents reveal internal dissent over the company's policies and frustrations with its efforts to address its problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tired of waiting for asylum in southern Mexico, thousands of migrants march north...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/tired-of-waiting-for-asylum-in-southern-mexico-thousands-of-migrants-march-north/ar-AAPUcDU </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden meeting with pope carries resonance as disputes divide U.S. Catholics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-e2-80-99s-meeting-with-the-pope-carries-resonance-as-disputes-divide-us-catholics/ar-AAPTpbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second Catholic president, like the leader of the Catholic church, is striving to move conservative institutions in a more liberal direction after rising to leadership late in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spent most of his covid business loan on one item: $57,789 POKEMON card...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-man-spent-most-of-his-covid-19-business-loan-on-16560641.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Department news releases document a litany of luxury items allegedly bought with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How party mom courted kids with SNAPCHAT, TIFFANY jewelry, Tahoe trip, drunken parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2021/10/24/how-los-gatos-party-mom-courted-their-kids-with-snapchat-tiffany-jewelry-tahoe-trip-drunken-parties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They thought she was the adult in the room. But they soon discovered how a Los Gatos boy’s mother was manipulating their kids through texts and Snapchat that would also be her undoing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West braces for Turkey's possible expulsion of 10 envoys...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/world/west-braces-turkeys-possible-expulsion-10-envoys-2266766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA: Turkey's relations with Western allies edged towards their deepest crisis of President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's 19-year rule on Monday (Oct 25) as world capitals braced for Ankara's possible expulsion of ambassadors from the US and nine other countries. The lira touched new historic lows ahead of a C</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria threatens lockdown for unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/578137-austrian-chancellor-considering-implementing-lockdown-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian Chancellor Alexander Schallenberg says he is considering imposing a lockdown on people who are not vaccinated against the coronavirus if case numbers continue rising, the Associated Press reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Dems plan billionaires' unrealized gains tax to help fund spending bill...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/24/dems-plan-billionaires-unrealized-gains-tax-to-help-fund-2t-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s spending package continues to stall as senior Democrats are hoping to finalize a proposal on a new annual tax on billionaires’ unrealized capital gains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Mexican Dealmaker in Shanghai Behind Trump's SPAC Deal...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meet-mexican-dealmaker-shanghai-behind-140550584.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A Mexican dealmaker in China was one of the key architects behind former President Donald Trump’s deal with a special purpose acquisition company. Most Read from BloombergCities' Answer to Sprawl? Go Wild.Hamburg Is at the Heart of Germany’s Growing Dilemma Over ChinaWhy Americans and Britons Are Rushing to Buy Idyllic Homes in ItalyOne of California’s Wealthiest Counties Could Run Out of Water Next SummerThe Top Money Maker at Deutsche Bank Reaps Billions From SingaporeShanghai-b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In France, Trump-like TV pundit rocks presidential campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-france-paris-europe-migration-a681f51a334fe7e2ccc680d2b52ab4b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A survivor of the terrible journey to Auschwitz remembered how the youngest wailed. There were 99 children squeezed among 751 adults gasping for air, crazed by thirst and hunger, aboard convoy No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin was practicing pointing revolver at camera...</title>
      <link>/https://nypost.com/2021/10/25/alec-baldwin-was-practicing-pointing-revolver-at-camera-during-fatal-prop-gun-mishap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Norah O'Donnell in danger of losing top spot at 'CBS EVENING NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/24/norah-odonnell-in-danger-of-losing-anchor-spot-at-cbs-evening-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norah O’Donnell is in danger of losing the top spot at “CBS Evening News,” as cost-slashing execs at the broadcasting giant quietly search for her replacement amid sagging ratings, The …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
