<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The Town Where WiFi Is Illegal...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/space/telescopes/a29589714/town-wifi-illegal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In order to do its important research, the Green Bank Observatory needs electromagnetic silence. Is that even possible anymore?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Officer Who Heard Trump's Ukraine Call Reported Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/army-officer-on-white-house-staff-reported-concerns-on-trumps-ukraine-dealings/ar-AAJuZ02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Is USA facing violent, '60s-style revolt?</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/10/trump-facing-violent-60s-style-revolt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday morning, President Trump announced that the world's worst terrorist, the head of the ISIS caliphate who had raped an American woman, had received justice. About to be captured and carried off in a helicopter by U.S. Special Forces, Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi blew himself up with an explosive vest in a compound in northwest Syria.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why would Fed cut interest rates a 3rd time?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-would-the-fed-cut-interest-rates-a-3rd-time-in-a-row-even-as-stocks-near-records-investors-may-soon-find-out-2019-10-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scant few think that Jerome Powell &amp; Co. will opt not to cut interest rates next week for a third time in as many gatherings of the rate-setting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS HUNTER WINS THE DAY...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/28/military-dog-wounded-chasing-al-baghdadi-already-back-on-the-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sit! Slay! This is the American dog of war who chased down and cornered evil ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi in his final desperate moments before the terrorist blew himself to hell with a suicide…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of model 'Zombie Boy' ruled an accident...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/death-canadian-model-zombie-boy-ruled-accident-official-191451384.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death last year of Canadian model and artist Zombie Boy at age 32 was an accident, a report from Quebec's coroner published Monday said, ruling out the initial theory that the heavily tattooed man had committed suicide. Rick Genest died of head trauma after he fell from a balcony on the third</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contenders cramming streaming arena...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/contenders-cramming-tv-streaming-arena-174938739.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Letting people watch whatever shows they want, wherever they wish on devices of their choice has become such a hit it is shaking up the television industry. Netflix began in 1997 as a DVD rental service and expanded a decade later to streaming films and television shows on demand. California-based</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX tests speed binge feature, draws industry outrage...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/tv/2019/10/28/netflix-speed-binge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if you could watch every episode of Breaking Bad 50 percent faster? That’s the feature the streaming service is…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU delays Brexit to Jan. 31; Boris election bid fails...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd63f54bee064ddda7435778490f4a45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain got Brexit breathing space but no clarity on Monday when the European Union granted a three-month delay to the U.K.'s departure from the bloc, postponing it until Jan....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: STOCKS HIT NEW RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1efc943a05c34b4285c395029cfaaf6a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 index closed at an all-time high Monday, extending a recent string of gains in what's mostly been a solid month for the market. The benchmark index closed at 3,039.42, around 14...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Argentina's left wins back power...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191028194238-d2l2x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARGENTINA-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Argentina's Fernandez pledges to 'turn the page' as left wins power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems going public with impeachment investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/shifting-course-democrats-plan-first-floor-vote-on-impeachment-inquiry/ar-AAJugj3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Televised hearings...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7623305/Democrats-hold-scale-vote-impeachment-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are proceeding this week with a resolution that would put the House on record for the ongoing impeachment probe being conducted by several House committees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD TAXES, RECORD SPENDING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-income-taxes-and-federal-spending-both-set-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amount of money the federal government collected in individual income taxes and the total amount of money it spent both set records in fiscal 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rarity for shielded president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e749219724ba489bb137d6086dc06676</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The boos were loud. And for President Donald Trump, they may have felt unfamiliar. Trump was showered with jeers, boos and chants (as well as some cheers) when he attended a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected threat emerging against Bernie: Andrew Yang...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/28/bernie-sanders-andrew-yang-gang-2020-057985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration extends TPS for Salvadorans... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-administration-extends-tps-for-salvadorans-allowing-thousands-to-stay-in-us/ar-AAJtGZB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>67-year-old gives birth -- after getting 'pregnant naturally'!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/28/asia/china-birth-older-woman-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 67-year-old retired doctor has given birth in China -- potentially making her the country's oldest new mother.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,000-pound great white shark swimming off FL coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/27/us/great-white-shark-south-carolina-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A great white shark that weighs over 2,000 pounds and measures 15 feet, 5 inches long has been swimming along the US East Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero Dog Pic Released...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/28/great-job-trump-declassifies-dog-isis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump declassified a photo of the dog who was involved in the U.S. mission that led to the death of ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope declares Vatican's Secret Archive not so secret anymore...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/22a89944ab2d404e8c829733ecb428e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis has declared that the Vatican Secret Archive isn't so secret after all. Francis on Monday officially changed the name of the Holy See archive to remove what...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA deploying more troops around Syria oil fields...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/oct/28/syria-us-troops-oil-fields-isis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has said he hopes to secure a US share of Syrian oil revenues, which is potentially a war crime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House to vote on impeachment resolution this week...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/28/house-to-vote-on-resolution-establishing-next-steps-in-impeachment-inquiry-000302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Asian Americans giving up traditional careers for farming...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/young-asian-americans-turn-farming-means-cultural-reclamation-n1072036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“While there are large populations of Asian American farmers, they're segregated in a way that they're not as visible as our white counterparts," one young farmer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of skeleton hijacked by Nazis, Soviets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-50082866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The identity of a 10th-Century skeleton fascinates experts - but was exploited by invaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos From Aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/28/photos-isis-leader-al-baghdadi-raid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first photos from the raid that killed ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi were published to photo wires Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBD Interest Surpasses Nearly All Other Health Products...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cbd-interest-among-americans-surpass-nearly-all-other-health-products/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say each month as many as 6.4 million Americans search Google for research or information on buying CBD products</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON's billion-dollar deal froze in desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Amazon-s-billion-dollar-deal-froze-in-Saudi-desert-14566796.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon and Saudi Arabia looked like perfect partners. Both had ambitions to become even more prominent players in the global economy. The world's biggest store and the world's second-biggest oil producer moved aggressively in the past few years toward a $1 billion deal to build Amazon data centers in the desert kingdom.  But in the year since Saudi operatives killed Jamal Khashoggi, the Saudi dissident who wrote columns for The Washington Post, the partnership appears to have stalled. No data centers are under construction. Amazon officials say there has been no movement on a deal this year. And when executives from dozens of major U.S. companies stream into Riyadh on Tuesday for an investment conference marking Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's return to the world stage, neither Amazon founder Jeff Bezos nor any of his top executives will be there, according to an Amazon official familiar with the company's plans.  Although no one on either side is willing to declare the ties between Amazon and the Saudis permanently severed, the freeze in what had been a promising relationship came about after a rapid-fire sequence of chilling events: After Khashoggi's killing in Istanbul, the planet's richest man, who also owns The Post, became the target of waves of criticism from Saudi-based online trolls.  And after the National Enquirer published an exposé this year detailing Bezos's extramarital affair, the billionaire revealed that the Enquirer had threatened to publish explicit photos of him unless he publicly stated that there had been no political motivation for the tabloid's story. Bezos would make no such concession; his security consultant, Gavin de Becker, alleged that the Saudi government had "access to Bezos's phone and gained private information." De Becker said the "Saudi government has been intent on harming Jeff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Models Banned After Flashing ASTROS Pitcher During Game...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/10/28/mlb-bans-models-julia-rose-lauren-summer-world-series-flashers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Models Julia Rose and Lauryn Summer are banned from attending any Major League Baseball games after they flashed Houston Astros pitcher Gerrit Cole during Game 5 of the World Series at Nationals Park in Washington DC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost empire that ruled Middle East 'wiped out by single apocalyptic dust storm'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10229948/akkadian-empire-mesopotamia-dust-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ADVANCED civilisation that ruled large swathes of the Middle East 4,000 years ago may have been wiped out by a spot of bad weather. The Akkadian Empire flourished during the Bronze Age and new e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Republican's retirement suggests doubts about retaking House...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/28/oregon-republican-greg-walden-to-retire-059814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House told in May of Ukraine president's concerns about Giuliani, Sondland...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/white-house-told-may-ukraine-president-zelenskiy-s-concerns-about-n1072776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House was alerted earlier than previously reported that Giuliani's pressure campaign was rattling the new Ukrainian president, say two sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBERT EVANS DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/robert-evans-dead-dies-chinatown-producer-1203385589/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Evans, the Paramount executive who produced “Chinatown” and “Urban Cowboy” and whose life became as melodramatic and jaw-dropping as any of his films, died on Saturday night. He was 89. Even…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Chicago, President calls city an embarrassment to USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1e156deb2004bd49ee40bf9af4c73ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — President Donald Trump used a conference of police chiefs on Monday to slam the host city as "embarrassing to us as a nation" under the leadership of its top cop, who skipped the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice John Roberts' role prompts recusal rumblings...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/27/john-roberts-supreme-court-chief-justice-impeachme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an impeachment trial in the Senate, President Trump would look up to see one of his Washington establishment foes, Supreme Court Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr., presiding over the historic proceedings from the dais in the upper chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta Force hails valor of military dog wounded...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/special-breed-of-courageous-delta-force-operator-hails-valor-of-military-dog-wounded-in-baghdadi-raid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though no U.S. forces were killed in the Saturday evening raid that led to the death of an ISIS leader, one military working dog suffered severe injuries in the line of duty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST faces backlash for obit...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/10/28/abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-washington-post-austere-headline/2483340001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter users are using the hashtag #WaPoDeathNotices to mock the outlet for its obituary headline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year after Tree of Life massacre, Jews still facing 'significant threats'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/10/27/tree-life-year-after-pittsburgh-attack-u-s-jews-threatened/2451390001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after the massacre at the Tree of Life synagogue in Pittsburgh, Jewish communities in the U.S. are still under threat. Here's the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Satellite' falls out of sky in Michigan...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/10/27/samsung-space-satellite-lands-rural-michigan-neighborhood/2478342001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World War 3 in space would 'destroy banking systems'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10212865/world-war-3-space-gps-banking-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT AN upcoming summit in early December, NATO is expected to declare space as a “warfighting domain”, partly in response to new developments in technology. If it does declare space a war zone, NATO…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quakes Shake Fire Zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/two-small-earthquakes-strike-in-sonoma-california-wildfire-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CalFire says blaze is only 5 percent contained as it speeds parts of Santa Rosa that were devastated by the Tubbs Fire in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Commandos IDed 'Mutilated' Terrorist So Quickly...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-us-commandos-ided-a-mutilated-abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-so-quickly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New technology includes a smaller and much faster DNA-reader that troops can haul into combat aboard their helicopters and use while the smoke is still clearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>67-year-old becomes China's 'oldest new mother'...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/67-year-old-becomes-chinas-oldest-new-mother-criticised-for-being-too-selfish</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AFP) - A 67-year-old woman has given birth in China, a hospital said on Monday (Oct 28), with the parents claiming they are the country's oldest couple to have a natural birth.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  Americans hate partisanship, but they're more partisan than they were... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Americans-hate-all-the-partisanship-but-they-re-14564537.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three years ago, the Pew Research Center released a study detailing the depths of partisan polarization across the country. A follow-up study released this fall found that, since the election of President Donald Trump, those divisions are even worse. Given the impeachment inquiry unfolding in Washington, things are almost certain to deteriorate further.  These divisions represent one of the great political challenges of these times, though there appears to be no immediate answer. Politics has become steadily more poisonous and the stakes with each election increase as fears of "the other side" having power course through the electorate. People talk longingly about restoring civility or returning to an earlier time. Little suggests that could happen soon.  There are moments when the light of hope breaks through. Friday's funeral in Baltimore for Rep. Elijah Cummings was a tribute to a politician who fought as hard as he could for the causes in which he believed but made few enemies in the process. But even his funeral conveyed the partisan differences that are today endemic.  Friendships across the political spectrum and within legislative bodies do exist, as Cummings' life showed. But such personal friendships struggle against the deep-seated animosities that now permeate politics. Many Americans decry these conditions and lament that political leaders do not do more to change them. But they contribute to the divisions.  The long-standing bipartisan Battleground Poll, produced by from The Tarrance Group and Lake Research Partners under the auspices of Georgetown University's Institute of Politics, reported last week that almost 9 in 10 Americans say they are "frustrated by the uncivil and rude behavior of many politicians."  About as many Americans say that "compromise and common ground should be the goal for political...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silicon Valley breeds boredom, loneliness and vanity...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/How-Silicon-Valley-breeds-boredom-loneliness-and-14567761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are glued to our smartphones for many reasons - to stay in touch with friends and family, to take photos and to read the news while waiting for the bus. With so many benefits come costs: Our phones distract us at work and while driving, at the dinner table and during life's quiet moments, so that even simple pleasures like watching a sunset become fodder for Instagram photos or tweets.  This assault on our attention has become so common that new technologies and routines have arisen to combat it. But features designed to police screen times, set time limits on app usage and schedule "wind down time," which turns screens to grayscale before going to bed are not enough. Nor are the periodic so-called digital Sabbaths and detoxes, which many undertake to be free of their phones.  To properly combat the million-dollar engineering that Silicon Valley deploys to hijack our attention, we need to recognize that technologies have long affected Americans' behaviors and feelings. Well before smartphones, new inventions shaped our culture and our emotions, and changed how we feel about vanity, loneliness and boredom. Today, Silicon Valley is the latest to exploit these feelings in an effort to keep us harnessed to our screens.  For centuries, moralists preached that pride and vanity were deadly sins. Humans shouldn't boast or think too much of themselves because they were fallible. Likewise Americans were taught to regard their accomplishments as hollow and fleeting because life was short. But popular technologies of the 19th century challenged these mores and helped inculcate new ones.  After photography was introduced to the United States in 1839, it took off quickly, and Americans flocked to photographers' studios. Photos were relatively inexpensive: by mid-century, very small photos were available for as little as 25 cents -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop told to 'tone down your gayness' awarded $20 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Jury-awards-nearly-20-million-to-police-sergeant-14567748.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Louis County Police Department Sgt. Keith Wildhaber had more than 15 years of experience on the force when he applied for a promotion in 2014, and by all accounts, he was a strong candidate. But shortly after Wildhaber applied, he said he was informed that there was one thing standing in his way of becoming a lieutenant: his sexual orientation.  "The command staff has a problem with your sexuality," a member of the St. Louis County Board of Police Commissioners allegedly told Wildhaber in February 2014. "If you ever want to see a white shirt" - i.e., get a promotion - "you should tone down your gayness."  A jury recently sided with Wildhaber, who filed a discrimination lawsuit against St. Louis County in 2017, awarding him nearly $20 million on Friday - a judgment intended to "send a message," the St. Louis Post-Dispatch reported.  County officials have heard the jurors' message and now plan to take action, starting with the police department's leadership.  "The time for leadership changes has come and change must start at the top," St. Louis County Executive Sam Page said in a statement Sunday. Page said the process would begin with overhauling the police board, which oversees the police chief, adding that an announcement on the new appointments is "forthcoming."  An attorney for Wildhaber did not respond to a request for comment late Sunday. The police department also could not be reached. The county's police union said Monday in a statement to The Washington Post that it has "a long history of fighting for equality for all of our members."  "While we are extremely embarrassed of the alleged actions of some of our Department's senior commanders, we look forward to the healing process that can begin to take place now that this has been heard in open court," the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New normal?</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/californias-new-normal-wildfires-ash-and-power-outages-could-last-a-decade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALDSBURG, Calif. - Ryan Schmaltz raced in his Ford F-150 down Highway 101 two weeks ago during the first set of rolling blackouts here to pick up the only industrial generator available within 60 miles. Without it, the winemaker risked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aide was key to his capture...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-baghdadi-capture-exclu/exclusive-baghdadis-aide-was-key-to-his-capture-iraqi-intelligence-sources-idUSKBN1X60SR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their long hunt for Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, Iraqi intelligence teams secured a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Trump watched from Situation Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/27/islamic-statebaghdadi-dead-donald-trump-000300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New face of ISIS appointed...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/isis-new-leader-baghdadi-running-things-1468025</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Katie Hill to resign amid allegations of sex with staffer...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/freshman-rep-katie-hill-resign-amid-allegations-affair-staffer-n1072611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is with a broken heart that today I announce my resignation from Congress," Hill tweeted Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALI BURNING</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Evacuations-Ordered-Near-Getty-Center-LA--563969391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-moving brush fire fanned by strong winds erupted in the hills above the 405 Freeway early Monday, burning homes and forcing evacuations in neighborhoods on Los Angeles' Westside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida needs python hunters. Thousands applying for the job...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-needs-python-hunters-a-man-in-iran-is-one-of-thousands-applying-for-the-job/ar-AAJg2Cq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Panels Threaten Contempt If Official Defies Subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/impeachment-panels-threaten-contempt-if-official-defies-subpoena/ar-AAJpw68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grieving monkey carries and grooms stillborn baby for 10 days after it dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/grieving-monkey-carries-grooms-stillborn-20741143 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: DISTRESSING CONTENT. The mother was desperate for her child to respond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Greeted by Boos, Chants of 'Lock Him Up' at World Series Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/watch-trump-greeted-by-boos-chants-of-lock-him-up-at-world-series-game-5/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Videos from Game 5 of the World Series shows a resounding number of boos and jeers for President Donald Trump, who was in attendance and was shown on National Park's jumbotron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super rich elite have more money than know what to do with...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-super-rich-elite-have-more-money-than-they-know-what-to-do-with-2019-10-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top 1% has run out of investing ideas, so they’ve parked $4.7 trillion in the bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frightening sense of deja vu...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-28/la-me-northern-california-residents-experience-anxiety-and-worry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kincade fire stokes anxiety of weary Northern California residents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKOUT FOR MILLIONS... </title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-28/intentional-blackouts-of-this-magnitude-unprecedented-in-california-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never before in California history have more than 2 million people gone five days without electrical power because of the intentional safety policy of a utility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods historic win astounds peers...</title>
      <link>https://www.golfchannel.com/news/tiger-woods-historic-win-astounds-peers-more-history-awaits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.golfchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he's done for more than two decades, Tiger Woods wowed his peers with his 82nd PGA Tour win. But there is more history to be made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan shop's Halloween display: Trump holding Obama head...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2019/10/28/michigan-auto-shops-scarecrow-showed-trump-holding-obama-head-on-rope/2478374001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The business has since changed the scarecrow, which had depicted President Donald Trump holding former President Barack Obamaâ€™s head by a rope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Shocking trade of forced organ donation while donors are still alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/organ-harvesting-china-survivors-victims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the stuff of nightmares. And it has been buried from public view, hard to prove, and shrouded beneath the cloak of silence for almost two decades. But anecdotes and evidence are slowly bubbling to the surface that the organs of members of marginalized groups detained in Chinese prisons and labor camps are being unwillingly organ harvested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital technology accused of racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90422523/biased-technology-that-favors-white-patients-runs-rampant-in-hospitals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study shows that a widely used algorithm for predicting which patients get additional care is disproportionately counting out black patients—and could have left tens of thousands without adequate medical care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs across USA could be Space Force craft built from secret military budget...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/ufos-across-could-space-force-20720906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The head of an anti-Space Force organisation has claimed the military is "testing technologies for space warfare that we can't even imagine"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia 'doubts' it occurred...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/isis-leader-abu-bakr-al-20738636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia said it has 'doubts' in Donald’s Trump’s claim that ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi has died</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: STOCKS HIT NEW RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/28/stock-market-investors-monitor-busiest-week-of-earnings-season.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 hit a record high, breaking above an all-time high set over the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Toilet Analyzes Human Waste...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/10/27/chinese-startup-develops-smart-toilet-that-analyzes-human-waste/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese startup company has reportedly developed a smart toilet that can digitally analyze human excrement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL takes beating on socials over empty stadiums...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/10/27/weak-eight-empty-seats-abound-most-nfl-teams/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Week 8 for the NFL and some teams can't seem to get fans onboard for the big centennial year as many stadiums still have many empty seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired Up Branson Prepares for Biggest Test as Space Shot Beckons...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/fired-up-branson-prepares-for-biggest-test-as-space-shot-beckons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.K. billionaire, a serial creator of firms spanning record labels to airlines to fizzy drinks, is in his element.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Business hiring 7-year low...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b0324178356449d4ba750fc1d3565b44 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A measure of hiring by U.S. companies has fallen to a seven-year low and fewer employers are raising pay, a business survey found. Just one-fifth of the economists surveyed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decision to withdraw troops from Syria 'jeopardized' mission...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/donald-trumps-decision-withdraw-us-122512211.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump’s abrupt order to withdraw US troops from Syria disrupted the planning of the raid on Isil leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi’s compound, it has emerged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/gtconway3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/AlexNBCNews/status/1188623568508203008</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Reaction at Nats Park as President @realDonaldTrump is introduced https://t.co/kO6EydX4lo”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDROID...</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.idrudgereport.iDrudgeReportUniversal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;play.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's all you need to know to use the app to it's fullest: *** NOTIFICATIONS *** On first open, iOS will ask you to allow notifications. Tapping allows results in alerts being sent to your phone whenever there is a siren, new banner or a highlighted headline (e.g. colored red.) Review these urgent headlines anytime by tapping on the urgent headlines button (bell with lines under it.) Then to modify which alerts you receive by tapping on the settings (gear) icon. *** SCROLL TO TOP *** Tap on the reload button.  *** COLUMN SWITCHING (phones) *** Tap on the columns icon once to be taken to the top of the first column. Tap again for the top of the second column. Tap for the third column. Tap one more time and you'll be brought to the top. Repeat as desired. A personal response for those who email in bug reports or suggestions for improvement. Posting bugs in the comments may not get the attention they deserve. webmaster@DrudgeReportArchives.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANIC: Sinkhole Swallows Bus On Busy Street In Pittsburgh...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/10/28/port-authority-bus-sinkhole-downtown-pittsburgh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive sinkhole opened up in downtown Pittsburgh during the Monday morning rush hour, swallowing the back half of a Port Authority bus and nearly a car as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans' love of drugs may soon bring nation's collapse...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/27/americans-love-of-drugs-may-soon-bring-mexicos-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy an avocado, boost a Mexican drug lord? Soon enough, it seems. Reports from south of the border say Mexican avocado farmers are taking up arms to protect their increasingly valuable crop from th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is the biggest there is'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-wins-big-baghdadi-death-intends-milk-175429358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump took a victory lap Sunday over the killing of Islamic State group leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi -- and he's likely just getting warmed up. "This is the biggest there is," Trump said at a White House appearance, reaching into his customary arsenal of superlatives after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May release partial video of raid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-may-release-partial-video-baghdadi-raid-135415441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Monday said he could release segments of video from the dramatic US raid to kill Islamic State leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi in Syria. "We may take certain parts of it and release it," Trump said on departure from Washington to Chicago, where he was due to address a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groups voice fear over German far-right surge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jewish-groups-voice-fear-over-german-far-surge-113820940.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jewish community leaders in Germany voiced alarm Monday over a surge in support for the far-right AfD in a regional election Thuringia state, just weeks after an anti-Semitic attack. Led by one of its most radical figures, Bjoern Hoecke, the anti-immigrant, anti-Muslim Alternative for Germany party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL ON 405</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/10/28/getty-fire-mandatory-evacuations-ordered/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze broke out on the west side of the 405 Freeway just after 2:30 a.m. Mandatory evacuations were issued for an area with upwards of 10,000 homes and commercial buildings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Emerging Scenario Where Buttigieg Wins Nomination...</title>
      <link>https://iowastartingline.com/2019/10/26/an-emerging-scenario-where-buttigieg-wins-the-nomination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;iowastartingline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is a potential scenario in which a long primary produces a Pete Buttigieg Democratic nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN! RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://granite3.com/advertise/drudge-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;granite3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>44% of consumers have expenses exceeding incomes...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/consumer-cracks-emerge-banks-everything-140026753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.Jamie Dimon has been quick to trumpet the strength of U.S. consumers. Federal Reserve chief Jay Powell calls them a bright spot that is countering weakness in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 1 IN 3 MILLENNIALS SEE COMMUNISM AS FAVORABLE...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/28/millennials-communism-socialism-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials show increasing support for both Communism and Socialism, a poll shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE APP IPHONE, IPAD...</title>
      <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/official-drudge-report-free/id375614185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apps.apple.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‎Welcome to the all new version 6 of the one and only official app of the Drudge Report. Here's all you need to know to use the app to it's fullest: *** NOTIFICATIONS *** On first open, iOS will ask you to allow notifications. Tapping allow results in alerts being sent your phone whenever there is…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tip, the raid, the reveal: Takedown of al-Baghdadi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/89e8716887514b95af5fea38d604ee30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The helicopters flew low and fast into the night, ferrying U.S. special forces to a compound where Islamic State leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi was hiding in Syria. Half a world...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing uncertainty looms over Dem primary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/66b6b14798ac4e609ab32871ee9d0a65</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSCATINE, Iowa (AP) — Look no further than Pearl City Station, a plain brick building set along the banks of the Mississippi River, to understand the growing sense of uncertainty seeping into the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfires erupt in LA, burn in wine country...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/267bdaa248344305bfdbc40a2ec980cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA ROSA, California (AP) — Firefighters battled destructive wildfires in Northern California wine country and on the west side of Los Angeles on Monday, trying to beat back flames that forced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Lloyd Grove coverage by The Daily Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news, politics, culture, technology, health, and more, through its articles, podcasts, videos, and flagship magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://www.pravdareport.com/world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pravdareport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Rep. Katie Hill (D-Calif.) is resigning from Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Times Opinion columnists, editorials and op-eds. Analysis from David Brooks, Maureen Dowd, Charles Blow, Paul Krugman and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mediaite is the top U.S. website covering the intersection of media and politics with original reporting and bi-partisan commentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRAP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>http://www.jewishworldreview.com/0219/shapiro_archives.php3#.XG2A5KJKhhE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jewishworldreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELLO! brings you the latest celebrity &amp; royal news from the UK &amp; around the world, magazine exclusives, fashion, beauty, lifestyle news, celeb babies, weddings, pregnancies and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC is the world leader in business news and real-time financial market coverage. Find fast, actionable information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch CBSN the live news stream from CBS News and get the latest, breaking news headlines of the day for national news and world news today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill breaks down another week of bat sh*t crazy news with Jason Dick of CQ-Roll Call, Niambi Carter of the Political Science Department at Howard University and Chris Lu, former Assistant to Pres. Obama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking the biggest stories in celebrity and entertainment news. Get exclusive access to the latest stories, photos, and video as only TMZ can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and analysis from the U.S. and around the world at WSJ.com. Politics, Economics, Markets, Life &amp; Arts, and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden -- least formidable front-runner ever...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/10/joe-biden-2020-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s the least formidable front-runner ever. Will it matter?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Magazine energizes people around shared interests, igniting important conversations on the news, politics, style, and culture that drive the world forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Living laboratory': New Dubai city pushes for green revolution in desert...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191028103204-lpspo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comprising low-lying villas that are home to thousands, the city aims to be a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 40 skulls found at altar in den of Mexico cartel suspects...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191028003742-4li6z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/TEPITO:Over 40 skulls found at altar in den of Mexico cartel suspects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France on high alert for revenge attacks...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191027171600-vtfgo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-CRISIS/BAGHDADI-FRANCE-VIGILANCE (URGENT):France on high alert for revenge attacks following death of Baghdadi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News stories from Boston, Massachusetts and beyond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
