<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Robots to walk catwalk at London Fashion Week...</title>
      <link>https://fashionunited.uk/news/fashion/robots-to-walk-the-catwalk-at-london-fashion-week/2018082938534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fashionunited.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ohmni robot developed by Silicon Valley’s OhmniLabs will walk the catwalk for the first time at London Fashion Week in partnership with House of icons and Los Angeles-based designer, Honee. The robot will take to the catwalk wearing a o</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii residents hit by floods from Hurricane Lane as new storm forms...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hawaii-residents-hit-floods-hurricane-lane-storm-forms-012516367.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii was spared a direct hit from a major hurricane as Lane diminished to a tropical storm as it approached and then drifted west, further from land. "It has been a steady rain since after Lane but I got up 2:30 a.m. (Hawaiian Standard Time) to the National Weather Service flash flood advisory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Wants Appeals Court to Define 'Commercial Sex Act'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/harvey-weinstein-wants-appeals-court-define-a-commercial-sex-act-1137996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ruling two weeks ago by a New York judge could be consequential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They read your face!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180829-kid-you-not-goats-can-read-face</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myrtle Beach Considers Jail for Profanity...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/cursing-could-cost-you-$500-in-myrtle-beach/4077395/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some refer to Myrtle Beach as "Dirty Myrtle," but make sure you don't have a dirty mouth when you're there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica Rules 300,000 Gun-Owners Turn Over Weapons... </title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-28/land-confiscations-loom-south-africa-rules-300000-gun-owners-turn-over-their</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Group challenges anti-panhandling ordinances...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/civil-liberties-group-challenges-anti-panhandling-ordinances-175900272.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — A civil liberties organization and an advocacy group for the homeless said Tuesday they are taking on Iowa city ordinances that restrict the ability of homeless people to ask for money in public areas, saying the local laws are unconstitutional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> BOOM: Affluent Buyers Splurge...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tiffany-sells-more-blue-boxes-as-affluent-buyers-splurge-1535459052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiffany reported soaring profit and sales in its latest quarter, underscoring the willingness of well-heeled shoppers to flex their spending muscle with luxury brands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marrakesh becomes hot destination; Tourists flock...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/a-construction-boom-to-lure-visitors-to-morocco-s-red-city-/17802699/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARRAKECH, Morocco — One of the first stops for visitors to this city is the medina, the cacophonous mazelike Arab quarter of the city, bustling with snake charmers, henna artists and shopkeepers selling spices, pottery and textiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronaut quits halfway through training; 1st in 50 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/First-astronaut-candidate-in-50-years-resigns-13186166.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robb Kulin, a 2017 astronaut candidate for NASA, is resigning Friday for “personal reasons,” becoming the first candidate to do so in 50 years, NASA officials confirmed Monday. Kulin, a 35-year-old Alaska native, reported to NASA’s Johnson Space Center in Houston for his two-year astronaut training in August 2017. He was one of about 18,300 applicants — a record number for the space agency — vying for the 12 spots in the 2017 astronaut class. The 2017 class application was the third he had submitted to NASA, according to the Anchorage Daily News. “It’s a long process,” Kulin told The Verge last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER bans more for 'divisive commentary'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/08/28/twitter-suspends-more-accounts-for-engaging-in-coordinated-manipulation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has banned a further 486 accounts for sharing "divisive commentary," including many based in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top GOOGLE News Story: CNN Declares GOOGLE News Not 'Rigged'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/08/28/top-google-news-story-is-cnn-claiming-google-news-isnt-rigged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top story on Google News is currently a CNN article defending Google News, following President Trump's criticism of Google's biased news results.results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurse under investigation after posting on anti-vax page...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/texas-nurse-investigation-posting-patients-measles-anti-vaccination/story?id=57443736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She works at a Texas hospital where a toddler tested positive for measles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man accusing Pope...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-fg-pope-francis-papal-nuncio-20180828-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archbishop Carlo Maria Vigano has ignited global controversy after accusing Popes Francis of covering up for sex abuse by now-disgraced Cardinal Theodore McCarrick, the former archbishop in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice shoots for Moon in Hollywood-heavy film festival...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180828142341-4qvjp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FILMFESTIVAL-VENICE/PREVIEW (PIX, TV):Venice shoots for the Moon in Hollywood-heavy film festival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another study finds searches steer left...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/08/study-affirms-google-search-results-lean-left/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An indepth study of Google search results found that despite the tech giant’s claim to be “a fair and balanced arbiter of facts,” 40 percent more searches produce material that leans politically either to the “left” or the “far left” rather than the “right.” The researchers for CanIRank concluded Google’s “ranking algorithms aren’t designed to […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart attacks now predicted years in advance?</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/health/fatal-heart-attacks-early-warning-system-trial-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad for movie ridiculing Pelosi, Waters -- BLOCKED...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/facebook-blocks-ad-for-upcoming-diamond-and-silk-dummycrats-movie-ridiculing-pelosi-waters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s campaign against Diamond and Silk continues. The pro-Trump duo are featured in a movie to be released in October and presented by The American Mirror, titled “Dummycrats.” The film follows them in Maxine Waters’ Los Angeles district, pursuing her in Washington, D.C., and tackling issues of importance to the country, including border security and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust looms? </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/28/trump-google-search-tweet-758110</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the president has few direct ways of going after the company, his administration and allies in Congress could find ways to make life difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> GOOGLE robot cars frustrating humans; 'I hate them'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/28/locals-reportedly-frustrated-with-alphabets-waymo-self-driving-cars.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet's self-driving cars are reportedly annoying their neighbors in Arizona, where Waymo has been testing its vehicles for the last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen of Soul makes regal entrance to public viewing...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/08/28/aretha-franklins-casket-makes-regal-entrance-to-public-viewing/?_ga=2.134193030.905048545.1535396288-1325753039.1529437084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive crowd broke out in cheers as Franklin's body was taken out of the classic car by a half-dozen white-gloved pallbearers and gingerly wheeled into the Charles H. Wright Museum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM MAKES HISTORY IN FLORIDA!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8ed1460be6af4ee3a81df4e2215611b2/The-Latest:-DeSantis-is-Florida's-GOP-gubernatorial-nominee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — The Latest on primaries in Arizona and Florida and a runoff election in Oklahoma (all times local):        6:20 p.m.        Tallahassee Mayor Andrew G</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens at FACEBOOK Unite to Challenge Its 'Intolerant' Liberal Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/28/technology/inside-facebook-employees-political-bias.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rare sign of internal dissent, more than 100 employees have formed a group to agitate for better representation of conservative views.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BOSTON HERALD moving out of town...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/business/2018/08/28/boston-herald-move-braintree/a5VlDmyJK67IMj7MGZEugL/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move comes just over six years after the tabloid moved its newsroom from the South End, where it operated for more than half a century, to the Seaport District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goats attracted to happy humans...</title>
      <link>http://www.irishnews.com/magazine/science/2018/08/28/news/no-kidding-goats-prefer-to-interact-with-humans-who-look-happy-1418729/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has found the first evidence that goats respond differently to happy and angry humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil sends army to border as Venezuelans flee crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/peru-declares-emergency-border-venezuelans-flee-crisis-home-182233823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil said it was sending armed forces to keep order near the Venezuelan border area, while Peru declared a health emergency, as a regional crisis sparked by thousands of Venezuelans fleeing economic collapse escalated on Tuesday. In Brazil, where residents rioted and attacked Venezuelan immigrants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Brown signs bill eliminating money bail in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article217461380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Jerry Brown on Aug. 28, 2018, signed Senate Bill 10, which eliminates cash bail in California starting in 2020 and replaces it with a system of risk assessment and nonmonetary conditions of release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K. Faces Backlash After Return To Stand-Up...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/louis-c-k-faces-twitter-backlash-after-return-to-stand-up-stage-raising-questions-about-metoo-road-to-redemption-1202453748/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Louis C.K. has faced an avalanche of criticism on Twitter since dropping in at New York’s famed Comedy Cellar on Monday night for a surprise 15-minute set. The outrage over the comed…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unease in Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/404086-the-memo-trump-takes-aim-at-tech-giants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump twice hit out at tech giants on Tuesday, raising the stakes for companies that are already in the political firing line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body found in fish tank in missing man's home...</title>
      <link>http://www.cbs46.com/story/38981147/body-found-in-fish-tank-in-missing-mans-san-francisco-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbs46.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco police say they found human remains in a fish tank inside the home of a man who was reported missing for weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Suspends Investigation Into Handling Of Weinstein Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/albertsamaha/vance-weinstein-investigation-cuomo-suspended-sexual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan DA Cy Vance Jr.’s initial decision not to charge Harvey Weinstein after allegations of sexual misconduct led to the investigation, which BuzzFeed News learned is now on hold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies Raising Prices at Brisk Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/08/28/trump-pump-priming-is-helping-companies-make-prices-higher-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Pump-Priming Is Helping Companies Make Prices Higher Again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATTIS:  Military Exercises With SKorea To Resume...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-considers-future-of-military-exercises-as-north-korea-talks-stall-1535490061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Jim Mattis said the U.S. doesn’t plan to suspend any more military exercises with South Korea, as talks continue with the North, but added that no decision had yet been made on conducting another large maneuver next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROSECUTOR:  Vatican knew of PA sex abuse cover-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vatican-knew-pennsylvania-sex-abuse-cover-prosecutor-says-214718782.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - The Vatican knew of a cover-up of child sex abuse by Roman Catholic priests in Pennsylvania through secret archives that bishops in the state shared with church leaders in Rome, the state's attorney general Josh Shapiro said on Tuesday. Shapiro first made the allegations against the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay rights group chief resigns after racial slur in re-telling story...</title>
      <link>https://www.metroweekly.com/2018/08/head-hrc-foundation-resigns-after-using-racial-slur/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.metroweekly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Beth Maxwell used the slur while recounting upsetting instances where the word was used</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bees besiege Times Square, swarm tourists...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180828213702-3bi6s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK-BEES/ (PIX, TV):Bees besiege Times Square street, drawing swarm of tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns Russia, Syria against chemical weapons use...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-warns-russia-syria-against-chemical-weapons-202557092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senior U.S. officials are warning the Russian and Syrian governments against chemical weapons use in Syria as forces allied with its President Bashar Assad prepare for an offensive on a rebel stronghold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers' Almanac predicts 'teeth-chattering' winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmtw.com/article/maines-farmers-almanac-predicts-teeth-chattering-winter-lots-of-snow/22839742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmtw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be hard to think about the cold and snow at the end of August, but 2019 Farmers' Almanac is out with its winter predictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana case could block first grizzly hunts in 40 years...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/montana-case-could-block-first-grizzly-hunts-40-202815918.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. judge this week will hear arguments in a case aiming to restore protections for Yellowstone area grizzlies or clear the way for trophy hunting of the famed bears for the first time in over 40 years. Two of those, Wyoming and Idaho, plan trophy hunts beginning Sept. 1. A hearing tied to lawsuits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety, depression = heart attack, stroke...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/anxiety-depression-tied-higher-risk-heart-attack-stroke-203104266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers enrolled 221,677 people age 45 and older without any history of heart attack or stroke and tracked them for an average of nearly five years. In this age group, compared to men without mental health issues at the start, men with moderate psychological distress were 28 percent more likely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preteen suicides SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/08/28/preteen-suicide-concern-school-mental-health/1119752002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicide was the 10th leading cause of death for elementary school-aged children in 2014, the CDC reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran arrests 'tens of spies' in state bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-security-espionage/iran-says-it-has-arrested-tens-of-spies-in-state-bodies-idUSKCN1LD2E8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security forces in Iran have arrested tens of spies working in state bodies, Intelligence Minister said on Tuesday, at a time of rising tensions between Iran and the West following the reimposition of U.S. sanctions on Tehran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort Defense Hints at Major Strategy Change for Second Trial...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/manaforts-defense-hints-at-major-strategy-change-for-second-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis does not view homosexuality as a disease, Vatican says...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/pope-francis-homosexuality-gay-children-psychiatry-vatican-catholic-church-a8510721.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pontiff did not intend to suggest homosexuality was a 'mental illness', says spokeswoman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rejects atheists' appeal over 'In God We Trust' on money...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/u-court-rejects-atheists-appeal-over-god-trust-173316736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 8th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in St. Paul, Minnesota rejected claims by 29 atheists, children of atheists and atheist groups that inscribing the national motto on bills and coins violated their First Amendment free speech and religious rights. Newdow is also known for unsuccessful litigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After stinging defeats, ISIS revamps to survive...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-6105601/After-stinging-defeats-IS-revamps-survive.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four years after announcing its cross-border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ANTI-SOCIALS...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-accuses-google-hiding-fair-media-coverage-him-132225776--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's attack against the Alphabet Inc unit follows a string of grievances against technology companies, including social media Twitter Inc and Facebook Inc, which he has accused of silencing conservative voices, and Amazon.com Inc, which he has said is hurting small businesses and benefiting from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renaming Senate office building after McCain sparks backlash...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/senate/404018-renaming-senate-office-building-after-mccain-sparks-gop-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A push to rename a Senate office building after the late Sen. John McCain (R-Ariz.) is facing political headwinds on Capitol Hill, from Republican lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Warns of Invincible Gonorrhea...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2018-08-28/common-std-cases-hit-new-us-record-cdc-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guitar-strumming Bolivian may be 19th century's last survivor...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/americas/article/2161641/guitar-strumming-bolivian-julia-flores-colque-may-be-last</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her national identity card says she is 117 years and 10 months old, which would make the oldest person alive, and the third oldest of all time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDs set new record in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/sexual-health/stds-continue-rapid-rise-u-s-setting-new-record-cdc-n904311?ds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say many factors have contributed to the increase, though the biggest one may be less frequent condom use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't want police to find you through DNA database? Too late...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article217037455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As public DNA databases grow, law enforcement may soon have the ability to track down nearly anyone, even people who never submitted their genetic material for analysis. The technique they are using is called “familial searches.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stingray surveillence devices intefere with 911 calls...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/08/28/stingray-cell-phone-surveillance-devices-may-interfere-with-911-calls-senator-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senator has confirmed that the use of cell site simulators for conducting real-time surveillance on cell phones may interfere with 911 calls. In a letter to the attorney general, Sen. Ron Wyden said that devices, widely known as “stingrays,” can jam cell phones from sending or receivi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bono Promoting U2 Tour By Penning Pro-EU Op-Eds...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/quartzy/1371967/u2s-bono-wrote-a-pro-eu-op-ed-in-a-german-newspaper-to-promote-upcoming-tour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How else was the band going to explain the "provocative" idea of waving of a massive EU flag on stage during the tour's first concert?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp Wins In Oral Contract Battle With Ex-Lawyer; Hollywood Jolted...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/johnny-depp-lawsuit-win-millions-former-attorneys-malpractice-hearing-1202445633/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Johnny Depp and his former attorneys may be talking about a settlement in their $30 million malpractice suit but today in court the two sides locked horns and Hollywood got a potential …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lonely dolphins alters 'speech' to talk with local sea life...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/08/28/lonely-dolphin-stranded-scottish-firth-alters-speech-fit-local/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dolphin living alone in the Firth of Clyde has learned to communicate with local harbour porpoises, a marine expert has claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Refuses to Testify at Senate Hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/28/google-ceo-pichai-faulted-by-senators-for-declining-to-testify</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google’s Sundar Pichai is facing bipartisan criticism for refusing to testify at a Senate Intelligence Committee hearing next week, but the panel’s chairman signaled he’s unlikely to issue a subpoena to force the chief executive officer to appear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defenders rally around Pope, fear escalating Church war...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-abuse-escalation/defenders-rally-around-pope-fear-conservatives-escalating-war-idUSKCN1LD27Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters of Pope Francis have rushed to his defense after a former top Vatican official launched an unprecedented attack on him, a move they say dangerously escalates a campaign to weaken his papacy by conservatives who condemn him as too liberal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orban, Salvini Seek to Rally Europe Anti-Immigrant Forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/28/orban-and-salvini-seek-to-rally-europe-s-anti-immigrant-forces#gs.y3WGJXo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orban and Salvini Seek to Rally Europe's Anti-Immigrant Forces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ polling locations closed due to machine malfunctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/elections/2018/08/28/arizona-election-primary-2018-voting-live-updates/1047958002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today is Election Day in Arizona. Several races could change the makeup of state leadership, from the U.S. Capitol to City Hall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW WHAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/28/at-new-a-new-record-high-the-stock-market-has-reached-its-now-what-moment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And after seven months of retrenchment, repair and recovery, the broad stock indexes have notched a hard-won breakout to a record high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros-founded university pulls refugee course over new tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/soros-founded-university-pulls-refugee-course-over-tax-164738919.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prestigious Hungarian university founded by liberal US billionaire George Soros said Tuesday it is suspending education programmes for refugees and asylum-seekers due to a new government tax on groups deemed to support migration. The Budapest-based Central European University (CEU) said it had pulled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela official says migrant crisis staged to undermine govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/28/venezuela-diosdado-cabello-refugee-footage-fake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diosdado Cabello implied that photos of refugees are fake as the UN warns the situation is nearing a ‘crisis moment’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Headless corpse found in San Fran fish tank...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/Headless-Corpse-Found-Inside-SF-Home-of-Man-Reported-Missing-491862811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcbayarea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A corpse with no head and no hands was found inside a fish tank at the San Francisco home of a man reported missing, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUMAN SKULL: Nose cut, ears mutilated for skeletal look...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6106443/Kalaca-Skull-half-nose-cut-ears-mutilated-eyes-tattooed-look-like-skull.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tattoo artist Kalaca Skull had extreme surgery to make his face look like a skull. The Colombian man had his nose cut off, ears mutilated and eyes tattooed on his face so his head can look like a skull.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO out of adult entertainment...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-hbo-adult-20180828-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WarnerMedia unit has dropped its erotic films and documentary series from its channels and streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tired of Swiping, Singles Try Slow Dating...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tired-of-swiping-right-some-singles-try-slow-dating-1535468479</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Younger daters exhausted by larger apps like Tinder have found ways to meet possible partners by considering fewer of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politician says being 'slut shamed' over pics...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/28/politician-says-shes-being-slut-shamed-for-burning-man-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California councilwoman says someone is trying to “slut shame” her into dropping her re-election bid — by creating a website filled with scantily clad photos of her at Burning Man. Rachel H…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders asks AMAZON workers to share struggles...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/senate/403981-bernie-sanders-reaches-out-to-amazon-employees-please-share-your-experiences</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) is inviting Amazon employees to share their experiences working for the online retail giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme film-art project to rebuild Berlin Wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/epic-extreme-film-art-project-rebuild-berlin-wall-152715979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive film-art project in the German capital is set to rebuild part of the Berlin Wall to create a closed-off mini-state, complete with visa checks, organisers said Tuesday. The walled-in "city within a city" will host the world premiere of the mysterious and mammoth "DAU" film</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge in Manafort DC Trial Bans Press from Jury Selection...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/judge-in-paul-manafort-d-c-trial-to-ban-press-from-jury-selection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US ARMY BIG GUNS BACK FOR NEAR-PEER FIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2018/08/27/return-of-fires-how-the-army-is-getting-back-to-its-big-guns-as-it-prepares-for-the-near-peer-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From guns to formations to soldiers, the Army is finding old and new ways to bring back some big firepower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor: Evidence Vatican knew of cover-up...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/news/politics/state/vatican-coverup-josh-shapiro-priest-sex-abuse-pope-francis-20180828.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The redacted grand jury report contains dozens of references to the Vatican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREBALL LIGHTS UP MISSOURI SKY...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/article217439200.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 people reported seeing a fireball over Missouri Monday evening. The bright meteor was primarily seen in Missouri, but the American Meteor Society received sighting reports from people in Kansas, Oklahoma, Arkansas, Illinois, Iowa, Indiana and Nebraska.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: CNN 'Deliberately Lied' In Blockbuster Story?</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/28/cnn-credibly-accused-of-lying-to-its-audience-about-a-key-claim-in-its-blockbuster-cohen-story-refuses-to-comment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen lawyer Lanny Davis says he was an anonymous source for CNN's blockbuster story. CNN told viewers he refused to comment. Who is lying?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER CONFIDENCE RISES TO 18-YEAR HIGH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a9444498173d4f42a52c83adb947fa74/US-consumer-confidence-rises-to-18-year-high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Americans' consumer confidence rose in August to the highest level in nearly 18 years as their assessment of current conditions improved further and their expect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Despite strong economy, many Americans struggling to get by...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1d31cf4b56e449769ab4cb456237ea1f/Despite-strong-economy,-many-Americans-struggling-to-get-by</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a strong economy, about 40 percent of American families struggled to meet at least one of their basic needs last year, including paying for food, health care, housing or utiliti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agent says bureau leaked stories, then used them to get FISA warrants...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/28/fbi-agent-says-bureau-leaked-stories-then-used-them-to-get-fisa-warrants.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top FBI special agent admitted to House committees last week that bureau officials were known to leak information to the press and then use the resulting articles to help obtain surveillance warrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller 'gearing up' to subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/alan-dershowitz-robert-mueller-gearing-up-to-subpoena-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Alan Dershowitz suspects special counsel Robert Mueller's team of federal prosecutors is preparing to subpoena President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Majority can't name a single Supreme Court justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/poll-majority-cant-name-a-single-supreme-court-justice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every voter in the nation believes that the U.S. Supreme Court impacts their everyday life, but a majority can’t name a single justice on the all-important bench, according to a new survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  How Online Media Companies Are Suppressing Conservative Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/ashley-rae-goldenberg/2018/04/16/censored-how-online-media-companies-are-suppressing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Summary Like it or not, social media is the communication form of the future — not just in the U.S., but worldwide. Just Facebook and Twitter combined reach 1.8 billion people. More than two-thirds of all Americans (68 percent) use Facebook. YouTube is pushing out TV as the most popular place to watch video. Google is the No. 1 search engine in both the U.S. and the world. War is being declared on the conservative movement in this space and conservatives are losing — badly. If the right is silenced, billions of people will be cut off from conservative ideas and conservative media. It’s the new battleground of media bias. But it’s worse. That bias is not a war of ideas. It’s a war against ideas. It’s a clear effort to censor the conservative worldview from the public conversation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS OUT GOOGLE FOR BIAS SEARCH, CENSORSHIP; VOWS ACTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/28/trump-accuses-google-of-rigging-search-results-in-favor-of-bad-coverage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump accuses Google of altering search results to prioritize negative coverage and left-leaning outlets and warns that the issue "will be addressed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH GIANT RESPONDS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/303cecf1f4fc43c0a466955622c3ecb0/Trump-takes-on-Google-in-complaints-about-social-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump promised Tuesday to address what he says is the "very serious situation" of social media companies "suppressing" conservative voices and "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas dethrones Seattle as nation's hottest housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/real-estate/seattle-dethroned-as-nations-hottest-housing-market-for-first-time-in-nearly-two-years/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Vegas is now the nation's hottest housing market, overtaking Seattle, which had held the top spot every month since August 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH GIANT RESPONDS...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/president-trump-accuses-google-of-rigging-search-result-1828647850</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s first tweet of the day, sent at 5:24am local time, has accused Google of rigging search results against conservatives. Right-wing media personalities often claim, without evidence, that companies like Twitter and Facebook are conspiring against them, but Google search results aren’t often part of that conversation. They certainly are now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica land expropriation bill withdrawn for further reconsideration...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/business/437051-south-africas-ruling-anc-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa's African National Congress (ANC) said that a bill allowing the government to seize private land without compensation has been withdrawn by the Portfolio Committee on Public Works pending further study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover genetic link between marijuana and SCHIZOPHRENIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/scientists-discover-genetic-link-between-13151184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large-scale genetic study is the biggest of its kind ever to look at the potential side effects of cannabis use</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SMASH RECORD ON NEW NAFTA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/28/us-markets-us-mexico-trade-deal-and-economic-data-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Tuesday, boosted by an improved outlook on global trade after the U.S. and Mexico struck a deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast Set to Sweat With Temps Near 100 Degrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/28/u-s-northeast-set-to-sweat-with-temperatures-near-100-degrees#gs.CKk9__0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Northeast Set to Sweat With Temperatures Near 100 Degrees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Atlantic About to Wake Up?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2018-08-27-tropical-atlantic-about-to-wake-up-september-peak-hurricane-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could the Atlantic finally show signs of life as we approach the peak of the hurricane season?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to be human: The man who was raised by wolves...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/aug/28/how-to-be-human-the-man-who-was-raised-by-wolves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long read: Abandoned as a child, Marcos Rodríguez Pantoja survived alone in the wild for 15 years. But living with people proved to be even more difficult</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enraged Student Arrested After Snatching MAGA Hat Off Classmate's Head, Slapping Teacher...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/08/27/maga-trump-hat-taken/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jo-Ann Butler is facing battery charges after an altercation in her classroom over a Donald Trump “Make America Great Again” campaign hat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provocative Erdogan statue erected for German art festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/provocative-erdogan-statue-erected-german-art-festival-112926287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A golden effigy of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan evoking the famous statue of Saddam Hussein has been erected in a central German city as part of an art festival whose motto is "bad news."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans can't pay for basic needs?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/almost-half-of-americans-cant-pay-for-basic-needs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a growing economy, even the middle class is struggling to pay for rent, groceries, utilities or health care</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dull Skin? Restless Sleep? There's Drink for That...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/dull-skin-restless-sleep-theres-a-drink-for-that-1535457600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money is pouring into developing beverages that claim to do much more than quench thirst. Conglomerates and startups alike are placing bets on “enhanced” drinks that promise everything from better sleep to a more youthful complexion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley Takes Another Step Toward Autonomous Flying...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/28/technology/autonomous-flying-emergency-silicon-valley.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new flying ambulance service will use small helicopters outfitted with tech that could eventually let them fly without pilots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of 22 grizzly bears up to judge's decision. Should trophy hunters be allowed to kill?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/08/28/grizzly-hunt-pits-tourists-against-sportsmen-wyoming/1065854002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge is deciding whether to let trophy hunters kill grizzly bears near Yellowstone National Park or put them back on the Endangered Species list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri first state to regulate use of word 'meat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/08/28/animal-meat-missouri-law/1114285002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meat must come from animals, not plants or labs, according to the new law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Saudi Arabia's barbaric plan to behead human-rights activist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/27/saudi-arabias-barbaric-plan-to-behead-a-human-rights-activist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israa al-Ghomgham has spent nearly three years in prison for her nonviolent advocacy of greater rights for Saudi Arabia’s Shiite minority — and now her government wants to execute her. It’s barbari…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Droid butlers coming to Miami hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article217154420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three robots will roam the halls of YotelPad Miami delivering towels, soap and mail to guest and residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CALLS OUT GOOGLE FOR BIAS SEARCH, CENSORSHIP; VOWS ACTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-takes-aim-at-google-claims-search-results-rigged-against-him-illegal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE DRUDGE LINK THAT STARTED IT ALL...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/google-search-results-show-pervasive-anti-trump-anti-conservative-bias/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does Google have its thumb on the scale?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECESSION: Redstone Civil War Heats Up Again As Daughter Prepares To Take Control...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/sumner-redstone-mental-capacity-hearing-cbs-viacom-shari-redstone-1202453307/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood and Wall Street has long wondered how much Sumner Redstone really knows about what is being done and said in his name. Now, thanks to an irate filing today by lawyers for the rarely seen …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marquee Republican Races Set to Test Loyalty to President...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/florida-arizona-and-oklahoma-hold-primaries-for-midterms-1535448600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona and Florida have contested primaries for both parties, while Oklahoma Republicans will choose a candidate for governor. The marquee Republican contests are tests of loyalty to President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After driving ban ends, Saudi women taste thrill of speed...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/207/after-driving-ban-ends-saudi-women-taste-thrill-speed-doc-18j0bd1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope silent on claim he ignored abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pope-hold-giant-mass-dublin-abuse-victims-rally-030337491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has declined to comment on a claim that he ignored sexual abuse allegations against a senior clergyman amid speculation conservative elements in the Catholic hierarchy are using the issue to mount a "putsch" to remove the liberal pontiff. Archbishop Carlo Maria Vigano, a former</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCain Death, Florida Shooting Cast Shadows On Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/08/28/642402809/mccain-death-florida-shooting-cast-shadows-on-tuesdays-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Senate candidate in Arizona raised eyebrows with comments about McCain a day before he died. A Trump ally is vying to be governor of Florida, where a gun debate was reignited by a weekend tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals defend selves over cover-up storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180828-us-cardinals-defend-themselves-over-cover-storm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crippling costs of war reporting and investigative journalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180828-crippling-costs-war-reporting-investigative-journalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading journalists join call for EU copyright reform...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-08-journalists-eu-copyright-reform.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading journalists from more than 20 countries joined a call Tuesday for European MPs to approve a controversial media reform aimed at forcing internet giants to pay for news content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immunity Deal Shows Value of CFO in Prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/immunity-deal-shows-value-of-cfo-in-prosecution-1535448600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors granting Allen Weisselberg immunity after he testified before a grand jury in the investigation on President Trump’s former lawyer, underscores the critical role accountants and CFOs play in criminal prosecutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Car Sales Hit Speed Bump After Decade of Growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-car-sales-hit-speed-bump-as-demand-slows-and-trade-tensions-loom-1535448601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After nearly a decade of growth, new-vehicle sales in the world’s largest auto markets are entering their first sustained slowdown since the global financial crisis as uncertainty around the U.S.’s trade policies looms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths from drugs, alcohol, suicide now outpace diabetes...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/deaths-drugs-alcohol-suicide-now-outpace-diabetes-study/story?id=57438591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More people now die from drugs, alcohol and suicide than from diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Org CFO provided info on at least one probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/immunity-deal-shows-value-of-cfo-in-prosecution-1535448600 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors granting Allen Weisselberg immunity after he testified before a grand jury in the investigation on President Trump’s former lawyer, underscores the critical role accountants and CFOs play in criminal prosecutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Global-Warming' Advocates Pressure Media to Silence Skeptics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/global-warming-alarmists-pressure-media-to-end-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “experts” don’t get to decide when “the debate is over.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
