<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Elderly woman dies after smacked for not social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/29/elderly-woman-dies-after-being-shoved-for-not-social-distancing-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 86-year-old woman awaiting treatment for bowel blockage at a Brooklyn hospital yesterday died after being punched by a fellow patient — for not engaging in “social distancing” amid the coronavir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Shares Cautionary Tale: 'I Was Alone. Crying. Suffocating. Gasping For Air'...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/03/29/coronavirus-young-healthy-patient-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When her symptoms worsened Friday, it was time to go to the emergency room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'President Cuomo' new daydream for those fretting over Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/president-cuomo-daydream-those-fretting-100000517.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- While Americans are stuck at home, the Democrat dominating the airwaves to counter President Donald Trump’s messaging about the coronavirus is not the one seeking to replace him in the Oval Office -- it’s New York Governor Andrew Cuomo.And that’s causing some daydreaming for political</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER removes Bolsonaro tweets questioning quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-economy-cant-stop-coronavirus-bolsonaro-233240524.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two tweets by Brazilian president Jair Bolsonaro in which he questioned quarantine measures aimed at containing the novel coronavirus were removed Sunday, on the grounds that they violated the social network's rules. Twitter explained in a statement that it had recently expanded its global rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu self-isolating after aide tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200330110528-z7cq1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-NETANYAHU (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Netanyahu self-isolating after aide tests positive for coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rampaging monkeys launching attacks sign of biblical plague, claims rabbi...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/rampaging-monkeys-launching-attacks-sign-21774648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rabbi Yosef Mizrahi refers to Deuteronomy 7:22, which states those who follow God’s laws are blessed – while there is a plague promised for those who break them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist 'saw' demon with no eyes mimicking possessed teen in ritual...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/exorcist-saw-demon-no-eyes-21752934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exorcist claimed to see a vile-looking demon which had taken control of a 17-year-old girl and made her swear and hurl abuse at her family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia primed to feast on Italy's devastation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mafia-primed-feast-italys-virus-devastation-103659112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Italy mourns thousands of coronavirus dead, and survivors brace for life in an economic wasteland, one rung of society looks to win big: organised crime. "The Italian mafia can turn threats into opportunities," top government anti-mafia investigator Giuseppe Governale told AFP. Over 10,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses Die, Doctors Fall Sick, Panic Rises on Front Lines...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/30/nurses-die-doctors-fall-sick-and-panic-rises-on-virus-front-lines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A supervisor urged surgeons at Columbia University Irving Medical Center in Manhattan to volunteer for the front lines because half</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Already Too Diseased to Go Back to Work Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/30/americans-are-already-too-diseased-to-go-back-to-work-right-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health measures to slow the spread of Covid-19 have already taken a staggering toll on the economy, with the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandma is gone: Coronavirus keeps kids from older family...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f295c91756b2625ab83f339d3e92fdd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A few weeks ago, Debbie Cameron saw her grandsons most days, playing the piano, making after-school snacks or singing nursery rhymes with the baby in her Chandler, Arizona,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo infection spike AFTER Olympic delay sparks questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c346402f4a0ef8796c6eb0afebe342f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Before the Olympics were postponed, Japan looked like it had coronavirus infections contained, even as they spread in neighboring countries. Now that the games have been pushed to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blissful ignorance? Submariners likely unaware of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/82739c3cf06b8acc415b71fd3c950aa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LE PECQ, France (AP) — Of a world in coronavirus turmoil, they may know little or nothing. Submariners stealthily cruising the ocean deeps, purposefully shielded from worldly worries to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to run daily temp checks on workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/608338/amazon-temperature-checks-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON has said it will start taking daily temperatures of its employees after reports that at least 17 company locations have had employees test positive for the coronavirus. The retail giant will…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers who break distancing rules face fines of $500...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/albany/story/2020/03/29/new-yorkers-who-break-social-distancing-rules-will-now-face-fines-up-to-500-1269545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fines will be a last resort, but de Blasio has authorized police officers to give them out to people who are ordered to disperse but fail to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megachurches Still Packing In Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-megachurches-are-still-packing-in-crowds/ar-BB11SBxU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Social Distancing Looked Like in 1666...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/29/what-social-distancing-looked-like-in-1666/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of English people believed 1666 would be the year of the apocalypse. You can’t really blame them. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man hosts party, gets arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/coronavirus/article241605346.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugs, Kisses, Dining Out During Virus Raise Fear in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/hugs-kisses-dining-out-during-virus-raise-fear-in-mexico/ar-BB11SinY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CITY WILL BE SPARED</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/dr-deborah-birx-issues-coronavirus-warning-we-dont-think-any-city-will-be-spared</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump sought to keep the public safe Saturday when he said he was considering a mandatory quarantine for the New York City metro area, a key member of his Coronavirus Task Force said Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Armed 'vigilantes' in Maine cut down tree to quarantine men from New Jersey...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8165415/Armed-vigilantes-cut-tree-use-roadblock-quarantine-workers-New-Jersey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said they were called on Friday afternoon to the island of Vinalhaven to reports of  several people with guns threatening a man who had left his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON LOCKDOWN COULD GO MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8165169/Coronavirus-lockdown-SIX-MONTHS-says-Dr-Jenny-Harries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Jenny Harries told a Downing Street press conference that people should not be viewing the coronavirus crisis as something that will blow over soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vaunts his TV ratings amid pandemic..</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-vaunts-tv-ratings-amid-virus-pandemic-201026555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump took to Twitter on Sunday to vaunt the television ratings of his daily briefings on the coronavirus pandemic gripping the United States. "Because the 'Ratings' of my News Conferences etc. are so high... the Lamestream Media is going CRAZY," the president tweeted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Orders All Residents to Stay Home...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/moscow-mayor-orders-residents-stay-home-192601827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow's mayor announced strict isolation rules for the city from Monday, the latest in a series of measures introduced in Russia to fight the spread of the coronavirus. The new restrictions would apply to all the city's residents, regardless of age, mayor Sergei Sobyanin said in a statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field hospital set up in Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/field-hospital-set-yorks-central-park-202813283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In New York's Central Park on Sunday, a field hospital was going up. Samaritan's Purse, a US-based Christian global relief agency, is setting up the hospital on the park's East Meadow lawn, where workers in face masks unloaded a white tarp and other equipment on the grass. The site is right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing, testing, testing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d851c87c07a7e0f67c245abe0d86e56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As President Donald Trump looks for ways to restore normalcy in parts of the U.S., his foremost infection disease expert says the country could experience more than 100,000...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Why Second Wave of 1918 Spanish Flu Was So Deadly...</title>
      <link>https://www.history.com/news/spanish-flu-second-wave-resurgence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.history.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first strain of the Spanish flu wasn’t particularly deadly. Then it came back in the fall with a vengeance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Tried to Build New Fleet of Ventilators. Mission Failed...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/29/the-u-s-tried-to-build-a-new-fleet-of-ventilators-the-mission-failed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen years ago, a group of U.S. public health officials came up with a plan to address what they regarded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 MORE MONTHS? Lockdown could last to June...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11279739/coronavirus-lockdown-june-death-toll-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN must stay in full coronavirus lockdown until June to beat coronavirus, a health chief has warned. It comes after the UK’s death toll for the deadly bug surged to 1,019 last night R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ER doctor fired after criticizing his hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/coronavirus/2020/03/er-doctor-fired-after-criticizing-coronavirus-response-at-his-hospital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The physician complained on Facebook that the hospital was slow to screen visitors, negligent in not testing staff, wrong to rely on a company that was taking 10 days to process COVID-19 test results, and derelict in obtaining protective equipment for staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Tried to Build New Fleet of Ventilators. Mission Failed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/29/business/coronavirus-us-ventilator-shortage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus spreads, the collapse of the project helps explain America’s acute shortage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate states encounter beleaguered national stockpile...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desperate-for-medical-equipment-states-encounter-a-beleaguered-national-stockpile/ar-BB11QGh3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First federal inmate dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/coronavirus-disease-covid-19-latest-news-2020-03-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total number of cases in the U.S. increased to more than 124,000, with more than 2,100 deaths, including an infant in Illinois.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why antibody testing in one town could provide way forward...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/antibody-testing-colorado-town-provide-forward/story?id=69856623&amp;</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Testing going on in the Colorado ski town could allow lifting of restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida state border checkpoints begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2020/03/28/florida-coronavirus-cases-pass-4000-border-checkpoints-vacation-rentals-suspended/2934407001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis tells travelers, "Don't come here" as cases pass 4,000. The state is also checking Louisianians crossing the border by car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Spreaders Poised to Unleash Second Wave of Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/coronavirus-silent-spreaders-poised-to-unleash-second-wave-of-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Trump repeatedly suggesting restrictions might ease in a matter of days or weeks, the prospect of silent spreaders wreaking epidemiological havoc looms large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Month: How Failure to Test Blinded USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-lost-month-how-a-failure-to-test-blinded-the-us-to-covid-19/ar-BB11Qo84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment, Shutdowns Raise Risks...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/03/27/pandemic-related-unemployment-and-shutdowns-are-a-recipe-for-social-unrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple run Dubai balcony marathon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/couple-run-dubai-balcony-marathon-beat-coronavirus-blues-095259686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South African couple who ran a marathon on the balcony of their Dubai apartment, streaming it online, plan to take the project global to help people shake off the coronavirus blues. Collin Allin, 41, and wife Hilda covered the 42.2-kilometre (26-mile) distance by running more than 2,100 laps of their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OF CIVIL UNREST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/069d01bafbb1f15b1f6c4a4479ab1456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST BLOOMFIELD, Mich. (AP) — More than a fifth of Detroit's police force is quarantined; two officers have died from coronavirus and at least 39 have tested positive, including the chief of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religious exemptions could keep pews full in some states...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/states-crack-gatherings-due-coronavirus-exemptions-religious-groups/story?id=69847021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some states have not barred churches from gathering despite COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
