<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Vampire video game sinks teeth into the 1%...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2020/feb/21/vampire-the-masquerade-bloodlines-2-video-game-1-per-cent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vampire: The Masquerade – Bloodlines 2 mixes sex and the shadow economy in a fiercely political horror fantasy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of animals mysteriously drop dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/hundreds-animals-mysteriously-drop-dead-21547076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have admitted they have discovered mass animal deaths in the epicentre of the outbreak Hubei province</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President won't pardon -- for now...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/20/politics/donald-trump-roger-stone-exoneration/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Thursday he won't act to grant clemency to his friend and former associate Roger Stone right now, saying he wants the process to play out before making a decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone gets 40 months in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/20/trump-friend-roger-stone-sentenced-to-prison-for-wikileaks-lies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's friend Roger Stone was sentenced to more than three years in prison for crimes related to lying to Congress and tampering with a witness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. and Taliban announce first step in Afghanistan peace process...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/afghanistan-taliban-state-department-peace-03dfeee7-4cad-46b2-b8aa-9dbdf4217e14.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Afghanistan war is the longest war in U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow deploys facial recognition for quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200221114452-s7xez</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The clamp down on quarantine rules comes after a woman in St. Petersburg staged an elaborate escape from a hospital where she said she was being kept against her will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange fate hangs in balance as court considers extradition bid...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200221062406-9dnsz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ASSANGE/ (PIX, TV):Assange's fate hangs in balance as UK court considers U.S. extradition bid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands light up joints during Hindu festival in Nepal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb2f19e99e314662ef4f46df339b3d05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KATHMANDU, Nepal (AP) — Hindu holy men were joined by devotees and the public Friday at a revered temple in Kathmandu where they lit up marijuana cigarettes during an annual festival despite...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to raise police presence after racist shooting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a1535c0b97159ab84d829a35b13f2909</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German authorities will step up the police presence throughout the country and keep a closer watch on mosques and other sites after the racially motivated shootings that killed nine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another hotspot surfaces: Prisons...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8028275/More-500-new-coronavirus-cases-detected-PRISONS-China.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It comes as Iran confirmed 13 new cases of the killer virus as well as two new deaths, bringing its total fatalities to four, the highest outside of mainland China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivals worry Sanders building 'insurmountable' Super Tuesday lead...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/483944-rivals-worry-sanders-building-insurmountable-super-tuesday-lead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS - Sen. Bernie Sanders’s rivals are sounding the alarm over his growing strength and warning that the Vermont senator could effectively secure the nomination on Super Tuesday if Democrats don’t quickly align behind an alternative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PARASITE' studio fires back after president's criticism: 'He can't read'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/483999-parasite-studio-fires-back-after-trump-criticism-he-cant-read</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie studio behind the South Korean film “Parasite” clapped back on Thursday after President Trump criticized the f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome to unveil tomb that may belong to wolf-suckled king...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rome-unveil-tomb-may-belong-wolf-suckled-king-085513622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ancient tomb thought to belong to Rome's founder Romulus will be presented to the world on Friday, bringing to a head months of investigation by history sleuths. The 6th century BC stone sarcophagus, with an accompanying circular altar, was discovered under the Forum in the heart of Italy'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Culture war rages amid glitter at Rio carnival...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/culture-war-rages-amid-glitter-rio-carnival-022955144.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sanctuary at her evangelical mega-church in Rio de Janeiro is where Eleonor Teresa Sousa comes to feel closer to God, and farther from the sin of a city gearing up for carnival. Sousa, 75, proudly counts herself among the conservative Christians in Brazil who condemn the show planned this year by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Builds Progressive Campaign Arm to Challenge Dems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/21/ocasio-cortez-builds-progressive-campaign-arm-to-challenge-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez plans on Friday to endorse an all-female slate of progressive candidates through her new political</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals panicking...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/21/like-an-umbrella-had-covered-the-sky-locust-swarms-despoil-kenya/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAMBA, Kenya — When the dense, dark smudge started blocking out the daytime sky, many in a sleepy pastoralist hamlet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Americans in voluntary quarantine to stop spread of coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/431674/coronavirus-voluntary-quarantine-thousands-california-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of travelers are doing a voluntary self-quarantine after returning to the US from coronavirus-ridden China, officials say. These US citizens are being asked to stay home for two weeks for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pressure on Barr...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/20/us/politics/trump-attacks-justice-system.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In lashing out at the prosecution of his adviser Roger Stone, the president once again disregarded the attorney general’s pleas to stop publicly commenting on individual cases involving his friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely voters say they'll vote in 2020. Who will that benefit?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/unlikely-voters-say-theyll-vote-in-2020-who-will-that-benefit/ar-BB10cGIz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT PAGE ONE FRIDAY:  Russia Backs Trump's Re-election, and He Fears Dems Will Exploit Its Support... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/russia-backs-trump-e2-80-99s-reelection-and-he-fears-democrats-will-exploit-its-support/ar-BB10dBOd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Drags Paul Ryan Into His War on FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-fumes-at-fox-news-over-analysis-by-hater-on-cavuto-blames-fox-board-member-paul-ryan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is stewing over a Fox News segment in which a guest analyst offered a harsh critique of his 2016 debate performances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic locust swarm stops traffic as sky turns black...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/apocalyptic-locust-swarm-stops-traffic-21543509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swarm of locusts was filmed bringing cars to a standstill in Bahrain. The plague of bugs has been destroying crops across Africa and the Middle East and since crossed the border in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joaquin Phoenix Rescues Cow And Her Calf From L.A. Slaughterhouse...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/watch-joaquin-phoenix-rescue-a-cow-and-her-calf-from-l-a-slaughterhouse-1202864856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than 48 hours after Joaquin Phoenix hoisted the first Oscar of his career the Joker star was cradling a newborn calf that he rescued from a Los Angles slaughterhouse. A just-released video fro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Jury Wants To Review Testimony From Annabella Sciorra; Day 3 Of Deliberations... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-annabella-sciorra-miriam-haley-jury-deliberations-1202864285/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, end of day: The jury in the Harvey Weinstein sexual misconduct trial completed its third day of deliberations today without a verdict – but with a last-minute request to review even …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG VOWS TO KEEP FIGHTING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f487bca6e473646b7a7d69b2a97685f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — His aura suddenly shattered, a defiant Michael Bloomberg sent a pointed message Thursday to a political world grappling with his underwhelming presidential debate debut: He's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected Americans flown home against CDC's advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/coronavirus-infected-americans-flown-home-against-cdcs-advice/ar-BB10ddna</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi Comes Out Swinging...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections/Benjamin-Netanyahu-to-Post-Democratic-president-cant-stop-Trump-plan-618271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What I do in an hour, my opponents can’t do in a year," the prime minister said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN warns of stock market correction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/20/investing/goldman-sachs-stocks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks keep reaching record highs. Goldman Sachs is worried that leaves investors vulnerable to surprises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: TITANS, RAIDERS Favorites To Land Tom Brady...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/02/20/tom-brady-update-tennessee-titans-favorite-right-now-patriots-ranked-third/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're all just guessing. The latest educated guesses involve the Titans as the top dog to land Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find novel antibiotic to kill superbugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/02/20/machine-learning-finds-novel-antibiotic-able-to-kill-superbugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When tested in mice, the molecule treated the gastrointestinal bug clostridium difficile, a common killer of hospitalized patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds charge man for threatening whistleblower attorney...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/20/man-charged-threatening-whistleblower-attorney-116379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man allegedly emailed the attorney in November, calling him a “traitor” who “must die a miserable death.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President hints pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-tweeting-a-tucker-carlson-segment-hints-of-possible-pardon-for-roger-stone/ar-BB10bYpw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI stocks up on hand sanitizer, face masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/20/fbi-orders-40000-in-hand-sanitizer-and-face-masks-in-case-of-a-coronavirus-pandemic-in-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration last month declared the virus a public health emergency, but the virus has not yet met world health officials' designation of a global pandemic that spreads widely throughout the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC issues record $1 billion in traffic, parking tickets...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/features/7-on-your-side/dc-issues-a-record-1-billion-in-traffic-and-parking-tickets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (WJLA/ABC7) &amp;ndash; D. C. has long been considered one of the most onerous places in the country for traffic fines, seeing a steady climb year to year in tickets issued and revenue generated. But recently the District broke into stunning new territory, issuing more than $1 billion in tickets in just three years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuees greeted with air kisses...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/20/tone-deaf-princess-cruises-president-greets-coronavirus-ship-evacuees-with-air-kisses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shows Jan Swartz forming a heart over her head as she faced the Diamond Princess ship in Yokohama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROHRABACHER: I DID OFFER ASSANGE PARDON...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rohrabacher-confirms-he-offered-trump-pardon-to-assange-for-proof-russia-didnt-hack-dnc-email-131438007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former congressman Dana Rohrabacher confirmed to Yahoo News he told Julian Assange President Trump would pardon him if he turned over information proving Russians weren't the source of Democratic emails published by WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli criminal investigation into Netanyahu challenger's failed company jolts election...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-february-20-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue and White chief expresses confidence in law enforcement, accuses Likud of pushing for investigation into Fifth Dimension; Netanyahu: 'The public must know the truth'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER testing new ways to fight 'misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/twitter-testing-new-ways-fight-misinformation-including-community-based-points-n1139931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leaked demo features bright red and orange badges for tweets that have been deemed “harmfully misleading."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport worker with no pilot license takes plane for spin near DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/airport-worker-no-pilot-license-takes-plane-spin-near-d-n1139956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan Guy Parker allegedly "bounced" the landing and spun out when he touched down at the end of one harrowing flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Omar did marry brother, reveals Somali community leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8013283/Ilhan-Omar-DID-marry-brother-reveals-Somali-community-leader.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Congresswoman Ilhan Omar told friends years ago that the man who went on to become her second husband was in fact her brother, DailyMail.com can confirm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro pushes political incorrectness to the limit...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-pushes-political-incorrectness-limit-182454696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro regularly offends opponents with political incorrectness and far-right diatribes, but he is taking heavier fire than usual for suggesting a respected journalist tried to get dirt on him with offers of sex. The man dubbed the "Tropical Trump" has racked up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33.5 MILLION VIEWERS!</title>
      <link>http://press.nbcnews.com/2020/02/20/nbc-news-and-msnbc-break-ratings-record-again-with-the-most-watched-democratic-debate-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;press.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will have to turn over tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/429826/roger-stone-jail-time-trump-pardon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROGER Stone was sentenced to three years and four months in prison today for lying to Congress – but Trump has hinted at a pardon. The longtime Trump ally was branded an “insecure person who …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fiscal hawks' now endangered as US shrugs at debt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fiscal-hawks-now-endangered-us-shrugs-debt-015153979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At their national convention in 2012, Republicans mounted a clock counting the growing US national debt on the wall, a warning of the looming financial catastrophe they said imperiled Americans. Eight years later, the clock has stopped under Republican President Donald Trump, and the "fiscal hawks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secession fever spikes in five states as conservatives seek to escape blue rule... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/19/secession-fever-spikes-conservatives-seek-escape-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separation fever is sweeping the nation as quixotic but tenacious bands of frustrated rural dwellers, suburbanites and conservatives seek to break free from states with legislatures increasingly controlled by liberal big cities and metropolitan strongholds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Ring Surveillance Controversy Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cybersecurity/2020/02/house-subcommittee-knocking-amazons-door-over-ring-data/163224/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of a House Oversight panel wants a briefing with Amazon officials about the consumer security tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian couple facing death penalty in Saudi Arabia declare love for each other live on TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/lesbian-couple-saudi-arabia-facing-21536871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lesbian couple 'Fad' and 'Nanz', from Saudi Arabia, feared being killed in their home country, but have now found happiness in London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Iran regime plan to destroy tomb of Esther and Mordechai?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Does-Irans-regime-plan-to-destroy-the-tomb-of-Esther-and-Mordechai-618155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US religious group blasts Iran for threats to Esther and Mordechai tomb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG RATINGS</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/democratic-debate-criminal-minds-tv-ratings-wednesday-feb-19-2020-1280119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary figures for the ninth face-off, and the first featuring Mike Bloomberg, are ahead of NBC's last debate broadcast in June 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human brain seized at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickondetroit.com/news/local/2020/02/19/cbp-human-brain-inside-jar-seized-at-blue-water-bridge-in-port-huron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickondetroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection discovered something very unusual during a routine truck inspection last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE NEXT WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/south-carolina-democratic-debate-moderators-cbs-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"CBS Evening News" anchor Norah O'Donnell and "CBS This Morning" co-host Gayle King will moderate the debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone declines to address court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f25972591780e9750d6fc17bcff506b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roger Stone, a staunch ally of President Donald Trump, faces sentencing Thursday on his convictions for witness tampering and lying to Congress. The action in federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USS Nimitz captain reveals his pilots have to watch out for UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8013327/USS-Nimitz-captain-says-crew-obligation-ensure-airspace-clear-UFOs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Captain Max Clark, commanding officer of the USS Nimitz, tells DailyMail.com it is important his ship and everybody on it is kept safe from UFOs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Trump Job Approval Steady at 49%...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/286280/trump-job-approval-steady.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval rating is holding steady at 49%. U.S. satisfaction is at a 15-year high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey cancels tour on doctor's orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thefader.com/2020/02/20/lana-del-rey-cancels-european-tour-illness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thefader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lana Del Rey has cancelled her European and U.K. tour dates due to illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Mardi Gras Parade Float Runs Over and Kills Woman in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/crime_police/article_8bcc8086-538e-11ea-8960-3305004323e0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was run over by a Krewe of Nyx parade float and killed in New Orleans on Wednesday night, devastating paradegoers and krewe members on what is typically a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Pop Smoke murder 'was targeted hit'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8024249/Pop-Smokes-murder-targeted-hit-not-robbery-gone-wrong.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop Smoke was shot dead at a Hollywood Hills home early Wednesday morning in what was initially thought to be a botched robbery but is now reportedly being treated as a gang-related hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devil worship...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2020/02/20/german-gunman-shared-far-right-conspiracy-theories-killing-nine-people-12272458/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He killed nine people when he opened fire at two shisha bars in Hanau, Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two former cruise ship passengers die in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4030470d394aec0c982acb55744b1648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Two elderly passengers taken off the quarantined cruise ship Diamond Princess because they were infected with the new virus have died, Japan's Health Ministry said Thursday, becoming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Devastating': Alcoholic liver disease soars among younger people...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/02/20/alcoholic-liver-disease-rates-soar-among-millennials/4802917002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors are worried over a surge in alcohol-related liver diseases such as hepatitis and cirrhosis in people in their 30s and 40s, particularly women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague of locusts threatens economies as UN sounds alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/20/plague-of-locusts-threatens-east-african-economies-as-un-sounds-alarm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst desert locust infestation in 70 years is ravaging East Africa, potentially endangering economies in a region heavily dependent on agriculture for food security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals across USA prepare for pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/19/hospitals-across-the-us-prepare-for-coronavirus-outbreak-to-become-global-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COVID-19 outbreak across the U.S. could overwhelm emergency rooms and cause shortages of face masks and other crucial medical supplies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
