<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>11 earthquakes rattle Tennessee in month...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article239943558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus hoax forces flight back to airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article239945633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre moment two disc-shaped objects appear in sky  -- before 'multiplying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/bizarre-moment-two-disc-shaped-21428429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two ring-shaped flying objects appeared above the city of Irkutsk before a third ring emerged from behind as citizens sparked dicussion online of the mysterious phenomenon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg Shrugs Off Criticism After Claiming Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iowa-caucus-buttigieg-responds-to-election-chaos-shrugs-off-mayorcheat-twitter-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Looking at all of the data that we've got, it was an extraordinary night and we are absolutely victorious coming into New Hampshire," Buttigieg told "CBS This Morning."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah on Defense in Two Separate Controversies...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/features/oprah-winfrey-american-dirt-russell-simmons-documentary-1203491393/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before signing an open letter asking Oprah Winfrey to rescind her endorsement of Jeanine Cummins’ “American Dirt,” her latest book club pick, Jose Antonio Vargas spent the day digging around on You…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY NOT BE FIRST IN NATION EVER AGAIN!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/481391-iowa-meltdown-threatens-future-of-states-caucuses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa — Iowa political experts and observers are worried their state’s first-in-the-nation status in presidential nominating contests is in jeopardy after technical issues marred Democratic caucuses on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman, 68, repeatedly tased husband, 73, after he asked for separation...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/taser-separation-anxiety-908351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 4--Pamela Carr’s husband delivered some stunning news Sunday morning: He wanted a separation after nine years of marriage. The 68-year-old Carr’s response was equally shocking: She pulled ou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warned About Problems Last Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/iowa-democrats-were-warned-about-app-problems-last-week-says-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The app—which was designed to report Iowa Democrats’ results to party officials—has been partially blamed for a deeply embarrassing night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of poisoned babies deepens after probe blunder...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/mystery-of-poisoned-babies-deepens-after-german-probe-blunder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT AM MAIN (AFP) - Fresh questions emerged on Tuesday (Feb 4) in the mysterious case of five newborn babies who were drugged with morphine at a German hospital, after police said they made "a mistake" when they arrested a nurse on suspicion of attempted manslaughter.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT MESS IOWA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/iowa-democratic-party-blames-app-coding-issue-delay-caucus-results-n1129701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some precinct captains and organizers had expressed doubt about the app in the days leading up to the vote on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voter Freaks Out on Buttigieg Precinct Capt. After Finding Out Pete Gay...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-iowa-voter-freaks-out-on-buttigieg-precinct-capt-after-finding-out-mayor-pete-is-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nikki van den Heever, a caucus precinct captain for former South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg, tried to talk down an Iowa woman who was incensed to find out — in real time during a caucus, after she'd signed a card supporting him — that the candidate is openly gay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He says mass shooting threat was joke. Case may answer whether such posts are crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/he-says-his-mass-shooting-threat-was-a-joke-his/article_62696a4b-8a5d-5618-9373-b472320e79e6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — David Puy headed out to meet friends for dinner in West Boca. “On my way! School shooter,” he wrote in a Snapchat post with his photo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor was one of first to warn about virus. He got detained -- and infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-Chinese-doctor-was-one-of-the-first-to-warn-15028767.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As word of a mysterious virus mounted, Li Wenliang shared suspicions in a private chat with his fellow medical school alumni.  The doctor said that seven people seemed to have contracted SARS - the respiratory illness that spread from China to more than two dozen countries and left hundreds dead in the early 2000s. One patient was quarantined at his hospital in Wuhan, Li said. He urged people to be careful.  Li and seven other doctors were quickly summoned by Chinese authorities for propagating "rumors" about SARS-like cases in the area - but their warnings were prescient. Soon, health officials around the world would be scrambling to combat a novel virus with a striking genetic resemblance to SARS. The outbreak in Wuhan has exploded to more than 20,000 confirmed cases just in China.  Among the ill: the ophthalmologist who was censured for sounding an early alarm.  "The diagnosis is finally confirmed," Li posted Jan. 31 on the social media platform Weibo.  Li's situation has drawn rare acknowledgment of official missteps in China, where a bureaucratic culture that prioritizes political stability over all else probably allowed the new coronavirus to spread farther and faster. Late last month, China's highest court admonished the Wuhan police for the detentions.  "If society had at the time believed those 'rumors,' and wore masks, used disinfectant and avoided going to the wildlife market as if there were a SARS outbreak, perhaps it would've meant we could better control the coronavirus today," the court said. "Rumors end when there is openness."  Li, an ophthalmologist at Wuhan Central Hospital, had shared his concerns the same day that Chinese authorities confirmed they were investigating 27 cases of viral pneumonia. Officials at the epicenter in Wuhan - the capital of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prank forces Jamaica-bound flight back to Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200204-coronavirus-prank-forces-jamaica-bound-flight-back-to-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus prank forces Jamaica-bound flight back to Canada</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Also set to be used in Nevada!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/04/politics/iowa-caucus-app-issues/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mobile app that has apparently caused issues during the Iowa caucuses is due to be used in the Nevada Democratic caucuses later this month, a person familiar with the app told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  TRUMP POPS TO 49% APPROVAL</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/284156/trump-job-approval-personal-best.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval has climbed to 49%, his highest to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILVER: Might Have Screwed Up Whole Nomination Process...</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/iowa-might-have-screwed-up-the-whole-nomination-process/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In trying to build a forecast model of the Democratic primaries, we literally had to think about the entire process from start (Iowa) to finish (the Virgin Isla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due back on stand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd97b161a67d367421c9b516d20023cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A key accuser in the New York City rape trial of Harvey Weinstein is due back on the witness stand for a third day of testimony after she broke down in tears Monday, halting an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems have no caucus results, blame 'coding issue'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/65327a2b9acbc9c903ef7f906bfce1f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Democratic party officials in Iowa worked furiously Tuesday to deliver the delayed results of their first-in-the-nation caucus, as frustrated presidential candidates...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Painting showing Hitler as Cain displayed in Berlin museum...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5b71d0b6ae5e9ce0364d26f444e4dded</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A 1944 painting by German artist George Grosz that depicts Nazi leader Adolf Hitler as the Bible's fratricidal Cain went on display at the German Historical Museum in Berlin on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BESTS OBAMA </title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2020/02/04/politics/donald-trump-gallup-poll/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has never made it to the 50% approval mark in Gallup polling, which makes him the first president never to rise above the halfway mark in the poll. But he's pretty damn close right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Forcibly Taken Away After Refusing Quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/residents-hauled-away-after-refusing-be-quarantined-new-accounts-china-detail-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS head claims Dems refused to let department test app...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/dhs-head-claims-iowa-democrats-refused-to-let-department-test-failed-caucus-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic Party in Iowa declined an offer from the Department of Homeland Security to vet the app that failed during the state's caucuses on Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is China Doing on Dark Side of Moon?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/what-the-hell-is-china-doing-on-the-dark-side-of-the-moon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite Trump’s ambitions to put man back on the moon, experts believe that Beijing might be preparing to make a giant leap of its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muddle adds new urgency to NH, as candidates flock there...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/iowa-muddle-adds-new-urgency-to-new-hampshire-as-2020-candidates-flock-there/ar-BBZDSzs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baboon grooms little lion cub in South Africa's Kruger park...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/018e5fd57ceb38d25669329c8e05f870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — A male baboon carrying and grooming a lion cub is an unusual sight, yet it happened over the weekend in South Africa's Kruger National Park. The baboon took the cub up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross drives her to tears...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/key-weinstein-accuser-driven-to-tears-is-due-back-on-stand/2277523/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key accuser in the New York City rape trial of Harvey Weinstein is due back on the stand for a third day of testimony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech firm started by Clinton campaign vets linked to debacle...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/technology/story/2020-02-04/clinton-campaign-vets-behind-2020-iowa-caucus-app-snafu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shadow, a developer of campaign tools started by veterans of Hillary Clinton’s 2016 run, built the app being blamed for delayed results from the Iowa Democratic caucuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem convention host committee under investigation over 'work environment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/investigations/daniel-bice/2020/02/03/dnc-host-committee-leaders-sidelined-amid-probe-toxic-work-culture/4645443002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The committee tasked withÂ raising $70 million for the Milwaukee-hostedÂ 2020 Democratic National Convention this summer is in turmoil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami sees return to Cold War cultural hard line on Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-sees-return-cold-war-050212122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Platinum-selling reggaeton act Gente de Zona were barred from a New Year’s Eve concert in a Miami park. The mayor of Miami declared another Cuban singer persona non grata and her concert in a private club was cancelled. Fellow artists Jacob Forever y El Micha were shut out of a July 4 concert the neighboring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA adds 'low yield' nuke to sub arsenal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b910d5f4f2076d558416ae021b511517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. military has deployed a new addition to its nuclear arsenal — a long-range missile armed with a nuclear warhead of reduced destructive power. The so-called low-yield...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Russia stalking American spy satellite in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/615129/a-russian-satellite-is-probably-stalking-a-us-spy-satellite-in-orbit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This isn’t the first time Russia has engaged in such maneuvers. It’s very unclear how the US will respond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap Between Haves and Have-Nots Widens...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/big-techs-runaway-growth-widens-the-gap-tween-the-haves-and-have-nots-of-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite regulatory scrutiny and pressure from lawmakers, the industry’s wealthiest are continuing to grow at remarkable speeds for big companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Stock Skyrockets As Bulls Think It Will Keep Climbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/tesla-stock-surging-yet-again-tsla-jumps-past-800-in-early-trading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surge on Tuesday comes after Tesla on Monday climbed nearly 20%, its biggest one-day gain in six years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Hangs Up On Precinct Captain On Live TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iowa-caucus-results-chaos-is-the-big-winner-in-the-iowa-democratic-caucuses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Monday turned to Tuesday, there was no victor. There weren't even officially reported votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Rivals Barrel Towards New Hampshire...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/04/turning-to-new-hampshire-democratic-rivals-jostle-for-advantage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES — With a glaring question mark hanging over the Iowa caucuses, a frustrated pack of Democratic presidential candidates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Is Paradise, but Whose?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/04/hawaii-is-a-paradise-but-whose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Locals in Oahu know that the best way to get from Waikiki’s crowded beaches to the cool North Shore is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to Execute 'CIA Spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/iran-sentences-alleged-cia-spy-to-death/a-52249837</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesman for Iran's judiciary has said one man was to be executed as a US spy. Two other suspects were given jail sentences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Death' smog over Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/fears-thick-death-smog-over-21426098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Chinese nationals have shared their concern over a fog which has engulfed Wuhan, fuelling fears the death toll inside coronavirus-hit China is higher than what has been reported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE INTERNALS SHOW THEM WINNING...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/02/04/sanders-campaign-release-caucus-numbers-iowa-buttigieg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internal numbers, with 40 percent of precincts, put Sanders at 29.7 percent of the vote, closely followed by former South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg at 24.6 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acquittal may have profound impact on presidential power...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/481290-trumps-acquittal-may-have-profound-impact-on-presidential-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s acquittal at the end of his Senate trial could set a new bar for future impeachment trials, according to experts and historians interviewed by The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump set to confront his impeachment foes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/481291-trump-set-to-confront-his-impeachment-foes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After sitting impatiently on the sidelines for months, President Trump on Tuesday night will finally get a chance to address — face to face — the House Democrats who impeached him and the senators who will soon vote on whether to end his presidenc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASTOR: Locust Invasion, Rain Not Normal. Repent...</title>
      <link>https://nairobiwire.com/2020/02/locust-invasion-january-rain-not-normal-repent-pastor-nganga-urges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nairobiwire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial city preacher James Ng’ang’a was in Kajiado last week to pray for the country and ask for God’s forgiveness following the locust invasion in parts of the country. Speaking last Friday after spending five days praying for the country, the Neno Evangelism church leader urged Kenyans to repent. “It is not normal that the country …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Systemwide Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/04/a-systemwide-disaster-how-the-iowa-caucuses-melted-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES — Sean Bagniewski had seen the problems coming. It wasn’t so much that the new app that the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'QUALITY CONTROL' OF VOTES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/69dd698aed24770b925add5fb69b501f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Problems with a mobile app appeared to force a delay in reporting the results of the Iowa caucuses Monday, leaving the campaigns, voters and the media in election limbo and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT MESS 2020...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/04/iowa-caucus-biden-campaign-blasts-democratic-party-over-reporting-meltdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, IOWA — Joe Biden’s campaign lawyer sent an excoriating late-night letter to the chair of Iowa’s Democratic Party over Monday’s caucus meltdown demanding an explanation…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS DOOMED?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/03/iowa-caucus-2020-election-110600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iowa caucus results appear to be indefinitely delayed, leaving the Democratic candidates in a lurch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APP FAILURE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/news/iowa-results-delayed-as-precincts-struggle-with-caucus-phone-app/ar-BBZCKFe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> CAUCUS CONSPIRACY AGAINST SANDERS?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/iowa-caucuses-results-reporting-delays-revive-bernie-sanders-supporters-concerns-and-conspiracy-theories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Des Moines, Iowa — Workers on Bernie Sanders’s presidential campaign already had suspicions about the logistics and fairness of the Iowa caucuses. Counting delays by the Iowa Democratic Party are stirring those concerns anew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delegates decided by coin flips...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/893489/iowa-officially-first-caucusdeciding-coin-flips-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some cases, Iowa is leaving the Democratic caucuses up to chance. In the case of a tie during Monday night's caucuses, the state is resorting to an old-fashioned coin flip to decide which candidates win delegates. A couple have already occurred. Buttigieg and Warren tie. Coin toss about to happen pic.twitter.com/fJVqDDN5pS â€” John Pemble (@johnpemble) February 4, 2020 Final count: Pete - 44Biden - 31Bernie - 31Amy - 29 Pete picks up most people from 1st to 2nd round. Amy back from the dead. Biden and Bernie now settling tie through ancient democratic practice of a coin flip. pic.twitter.com/Nwz2feXF4t â€” Eric Lach (@ericlach) February 4, 2020 This is nothing new â€” in 2016, Hillary Clinton won all six of her Iowa caucus coin tosses. The current candidates are surely hoping they have that kind of luck. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustration, questions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/481310-frustration-questions-as-delays-hamper-iowa-caucuses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustrations mounted late Monday night after the Iowa Democratic Party said it found “inconsistencies” in the reporting of the caucus results and delayed releasing any precinct vote tallies to ensure the integrity of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone shortages predicted, chaos in supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/352809/iphone-shortages-predicted-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOP tech analyst has predicted that Apple could be hit hard by the coronavirus outbreak, slashing his estimate for iPhone sales in the first quarter. Ming-Chi Kuo, known by some as the world̵…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELAY, DELAY, DELAY</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-blog/iowa-caucuses-live-updates-2020-democrats-make-their-final-pitches-n1128596</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iowa's 41 pledged delegates are up for grabs in the first nominating contest of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Stock Skyrockets As Bulls Think It Will Keep Climbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/tesla-stock-share-price-market-capitalization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The electric carmaker's market capitalization went as high as $139 billion on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOWA ELECTION FIASCO</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/iowa-caucuses-how-to-watch-6aa273e2-fd22-43ef-8260-012f825f6c9d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a real chance that different campaigns walk away with different types of "wins."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC 'QUALITY CONTROL' OF VOTES</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/iowa-caucuses-live-results-coverage-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters are set to settle a tight four-person contest as Iowa becomes the first state to vote in the 2020 Democratic presidential primary. Follow here for live updates and results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong confirms first death...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/3048839/coronavirus-hong-kong-confirms-first-death-39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City suffers first fatality related to deadly virus originating in Wuhan. Quarantined patient, from Whampoa Garden, dies from sudden heart failure on Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSH LIMBAUGH REVEALS LUNG CANCER...</title>
      <link>https://www.rushlimbaugh.com/daily/2020/02/03/rush-shares-his-cancer-diagnosis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rushlimbaugh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSH: I have to tell you something today that I wish I didn't have to tell you… The upshot is that I have been diagnosed with advanced lung cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entrance poll shows dip in first-timers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/iowa-caucuses-turnout-entrance-poll-shows-dip-first-timers-n1129381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's level of new participants is well shy of that in 2008, when a whopping 57 percent of Democrats said they had never caucused before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY INTERVIEW WITH TRUMP PULLS 10 MILLION VIEWERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/sean-hannity-draws-biggest-audience-ever-for-super-bowl-interview-with-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean Hannity, the most-watched host on cable news, scored his biggest audience ever for his Sunday Super Bowl interview with President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa Caucuses Have Correctly Predicted Nominee In 7 Of Past 9 Contested Races...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iowa-caucus-will-caucuses-predict-2020-democratic-presidential-nominee-7-of-past-9-elections-it-did/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How good is Iowa's track record in selecting the eventual presidential nominee?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precinct Chairs Struggle with App...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-03/poll-gives-fresh-evidence-for-a-twitter-debate-campaign-update</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEFS Head Coach Reid To Attend White House Ceremony: 'I'll Be There, It's Quite An Honor'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/2020/02/03/super-bowl-2020-chiefs-head-coach-andy-reid-visiting-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kansas City Chiefs have won Super Bowl LIV and head coach Andy Reid will no longer be [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Richest Man in the World Jeff Bezos Got $8 Billion Richer --  in Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/02/jeff-bezos-amazon-stock-richest-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos, on average, makes $149,353 a minute. But last Friday, he made a whole lot more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/live-blog/iowa-caucus-2020-election-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest updates and results from the 2020 Iowa caucuses on Monday, Feb. 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems split on best challenger for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ea52b33d206238118686bcf7d855684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Iowa Democrats are fiercely united by the goal of unseating President Donald Trump, but they were sharply divided Monday over which candidate was best equipped to do so,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases have tripled...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2020/02/03/802212047/coronavirus-cases-have-more-than-tripled-in-past-week-17-000-now-sick-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week, China had 4,400 cases of the Wuhan coronavirus. On Monday alone, Chinese health officials reported 2,829 new cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret poll influences coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/bensmith/iowa-caucus-poll-des-moines-register-selzer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You can’t help it affecting how you’re thinking,” one reporter said of the spiked Des Moines Register poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could delay results...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/03/issues-with-smartphone-app-could-delay-iowa-caucus-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Issues with the new smartphone app for reporting the results of the crucial Iowa Democratic caucus could delay the count of the votes tonight in the bellwether contest. Precinct chairs across the H…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1M In Dried Shark Fins Seized At Port Miami...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/02/03/wildlife-inspectors-seize-dried-shark-fins-1-million-portmiami/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 1,400 pounds of dried shark fins were seized by wildlife inspectors at PortMiami.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://ktar.com/story/2957599/heres-why-some-iowa-caucuses-are-being-held-in-arizona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross drives her to tears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0fc0cc2d04583e62aac2548d18463b3f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A key accuser in the New York City rape trial of Harvey Weinstein broke down in tears on the witness stand on Monday during an exhaustive cross-examination over the nature of her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tbilisi...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2020/2/3/21083813/iowa-satellite-caucuses-paris-tbilisi-glasgow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why Iowa caucuses are being held internationally, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caucusgoers have a new place to vote: Overseas...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/02/01/iowa-caucuses-2020/4620445002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, Iowa's Democratic caucuses are going international with three sites outside the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin calls for censure...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/manchin-swing-vote-dem-urges-censure-over-removal-for-trumps-ukraine-actions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic West Virginia Sen. Joe Manchin, speaking on the Senate floor about the impeachment efforts Monday, urged his colleagues to formally censure President Trump -- saying that while the president's dealings with both Ukraine and Congress were "simply wrong," he is "struggling" over whether to vote to convict and remove him from office and potentially "tear the country apart."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind AMAZON's HQ2 Fiasco: Bezos Was Jealous of Musk...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-03/amazon-s-hq2-fiasco-was-driven-by-bezos-envy-of-elon-musk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glasgow...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-scotland-glasgow-west-51358556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, one of the three international satellite caucuses outside the US is to take place in Glasgow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Also Florida...</title>
      <link>https://whotv.com/2020/02/03/watch-live-satellite-caucus-in-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whotv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT CHARLOTTE, Florida  --  The Iowa Caucuses have already begun outside of the state's borders. Watch live as Iowans living in the Sunshine State gather to caucus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Accuser Details 'Golden Shower' Encounter...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/weinstein-accuser-details-gross-golden-shower-encounter-with-disgraced-film-mogul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I was in shock by it,” Jessica Mann testified. “I turned into the corner of the shower and just looked away.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Citizen Scientists Helped Discover a New Aurora...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/citizen-scientists-helped-discover-aurora-201800019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been dubbed 'the dunes' for its wavy shape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why liberal white women pay lots to learn how they're racist...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/03/race-to-dinner-party-racism-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of women are paying to confront their privilege – and racism – at dinners that cost $2,500</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-imaging study shows 'hot spot'...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/02/03/brain-imaging-study-may-explain-why-african-americans-feel-greater-pain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The greater pain that African Americans feel from the identical physical experience stems from brain circuits that interpret pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping fan was Clinton-connected CEO...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/03/sleeping-super-bowl-fan-was-clinton-connected-ceo-declan-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The guy who snoozed at the Super Bowl is Clinton family crony Declan Kelly, Hillary Clinton’s former economic envoy to Northern Ireland and co-founder of a powerful, Clinton-tied consulting f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 People Shot, 2 Dead At Texas A&amp;M University-Commerce...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/02/03/3-people-shot-texas-am-university-commerce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An active criminal investigation is ongoing at Texas A&amp;M University-Commerce where three people were shot, two are confirmed dead and another was taken to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>102 MILLION VIEWERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/super-bowl-liv-draws-102-million-viewers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Super Bowl LIV scored 102 million total viewers on Sunday, counting Fox, Fox Deportes and Fox's, the NFL's and Verizon's digital properties</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Reporters Know Anything?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/02/03/iowa-road-trip-do-reporters-know-anything-110523</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six questions to ponder while you wait for caucus results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunting 'slowly dying off,' creating crisis for many endangered species...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hunting-is-slowly-dying-off-and-that-has-created-a-crisis-for-the-nations-many-endangered-species/ar-BBZA5Pc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden allies lower expectations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/481210-biden-allies-lower-expectations-for-iowa-most-feel-its-not-going-to-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s campaign team is setting expectations low for the Iowa caucuses Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Paid $75 Million For 'HAMILTON'; Biggest Film Acquisition Deal Ever?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/disney-paid-75-million-hamilton-movie-deal-lin-manuel-miranda-largest-film-acquisition-ever-1202849929/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: When Lin-Manuel Miranda tweeted the news Monday that the movie adaptation of his groundbreaking Broadway show Hamilton was set for release by Disney in fall 2021, he omitted one of the m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's Productivity Decline Worst in 250 Years!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/britain-e2-80-99s-productivity-decline-is-the-worst-in-250-years/ar-BBZBOQl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump congratulates 'Great State of Kansas'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/481150-trump-mocked-for-super-bowl-tweet-confusing-missouri-for-kansas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A since-deleted tweet from President Trump erroneously congratulating the state of Kansas for the Kansas City Chiefs’ Super Bowl victory led to a number of tweets mocking the president over the mistake on Sunday night and Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Includes OJ Simpson In Tribute!</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/2020/02/03/super-bowl-2020-social-media-explodes-oj-simpson-pre-game-tribute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the NFL included former running back O.J. Simpson in a pre-game tribute during Super Bowl [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE to ban 'manipulated' content linked to elections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/youtube-ban-manipulated-content-linked-elections-161210011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube said Monday it would remove election-related videos that are "manipulated or doctored" to mislead voters, as part of its efforts to stem online misinformation. The announcement underscores differing policies by major social networks on disinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quest for HIV vaccine continues after latest trial fails...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/quest-hiv-vaccine-continues-latest-trial-fails-164708580.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US health authorities said Monday they were halting a trial in South Africa of an experimental HIV vaccine after it proved ineffective at preventing the infection. The study, named HVTN 702, began in 2016 and involved the only vaccine candidate ever shown to provide some protection against the virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yield-Curve Inversion Sending Message...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yield-curve-inversion-sending-message-133011038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The yield curve just inverted -- again.Driven by fears of a potential coronavirus pandemic that could cause widespread economic disruption, investment capital sought shelter in longer-term bonds. This flight to safety caused the curve to invert, at least for now.The sages will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm bankruptcies hit 8-year high...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-farm-bankruptcies-are-on-the-rise-123431788.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to U.S. Courts data, U.S. farm bankruptcy rates increased by 20% in 2019, which is an eight-year high. There were a total of 595 Chapter 12 bankruptcies filed by family farmers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 tech companies now make up 18% of the stock market...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-powerful-tech-companies-now-make-up-18-of-the-stock-market-heres-why-this-could-be-a-bad-thing-145710881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors clearly remain obsessed with big-cap tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Using GRINDR To Lure 'Dates' To Upscale Hotels, Then Robs Them With Stun Gun...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/01/31/dating-danger-man-using-dating-app-to-rob-victims-with-stun-gun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four attacks in all since December, one of them took place at the Cambria Hotel. They are all centered in the downtown and Gold Coast areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After NPR dust-up, Pompeo defends press freedom abroad...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0d0601584df837998c2c7bac33da18d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TASHKENT, Uzbekistan (AP) — For the past four days, U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has been calling for authoritarian governments in eastern Europe and Central Asia to ease restrictions on...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
