<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>30% of koalas may have been killed in Australia's bushfires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/27/australia/koala-bushfire-australia-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost a third of koalas in Australia's New South Wales region may have been killed in deadly bushfires, which have been burning out of control, the Federal Environment Minister Sussan Ley said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Low-Wage Workers Getting Bigger Raises Than Bosses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/low-wage-workers-are-getting-bigger-raises-than-bosses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wage growth for the lowest-paid workers is now outpacing that of the country's top-earning professionals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In season of Lamar and Russell, NFL officiating overshadows...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/season-lamar-russell-nfl-officiating-overshadows-195711880--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how many spectacular plays Lamar Jackson and Russell Wilson made, officiating overshadowed the NFL this season. Regardless of the record stream of receptions by Michael Thomas, the sacks by Chandler Jones and long field goals by nearly every kicker, the headlines regularly were about referees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mile high ugh: What you should know before you eat airplane food... </title>
      <link>hhttps://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/mile-high-ugh-what-you-should-know-you-eat-airplane-n1060461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fountain Of Youth Drug? Organ-Transplant Medication May Slow Skin Aging...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fountain-of-youth-drug-organ-transplant-medication-rapamycin-may-slow-skin-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Drexel University say that Rapamycin, an FDA-approved drug usually used to promote organ acceptance after transplant surgery, may also be able to drastically slow down the aging of human skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON, Ring's 'design' lets hackers access cameras, suit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article238749528.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-cardinal sent cash to church leaders during abuse probe...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/27/ex-cardinal-sent-cash-to-church-leaders-during-abuse-probe-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgraced former cardinal Theodore McCarrick sent hundreds of thousands of dollars in church funds to Catholic leaders as he faced mounting sexual abuse allegations, according to a report. McCarric…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Schumer said he wasn't impartial juror in 1999...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/27/politics/chuck-schumer-impeachment-1999-kfile/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democratic Leader Chuck Schumer has blasted his Republican counterpart Mitch McConnell in recent days after he described himself as "not an impartial juror" ahead of President Donald Trump's Senate impeachment trial, but Schumer himself repeatedly expressed similar sentiments in the late 1990s when senators weighed the removal of President Bill Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren's campaign sounds the alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/27/elizabeth-warren-campaign-sounds-alarm-as-fundraising-slows-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren's campaign told supporters in an email on Friday that, so far, it has raised just over $17 million in the fourth quarter, a significant drop from her fundraising haul during the third quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural disconnect: Majority in some Alabama counties don't have internet... </title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/2019/12/rural-disconnect-majority-in-some-alabama-counties-dont-have-internet-access.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama is near the bottom of national rankings for households without internet access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Unlimited Supply Of Borrowed Cash Is Destroying Higher Education...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/12/27/how-an-unlimited-supply-of-borrowed-cash-is-destroying-higher-education/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 most dangerous volcanoes in the US, ranked...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/20-most-dangerous-volcanoes-us-113700279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US Geological Survey list of volcano threats has been updated for the first time since 2005. California, Oregon, Washington, and Hawaii are at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa swung fiercely to Trump. Will it swing back in 2020?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e05ce4b46a1aab025ef4aa8bb42fec97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Few states have changed politically with the head-snapping speed of Iowa. Heading into 2020, the question is whether it's going to change again. In 2008, its voters...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS 'beheads 11 Christian hostages' on Christmas Day in execution video...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10625706/isis-beheads-11-christian-hostages-christmas-day-execution-video-nigeria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLOODTHIRSTY ISIS terrorists have reportedly beheaded 11 Christian hostages on Christmas Day in Nigeria. The militants said in a sickening video that the mass killing was in revenge for the deaths …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors in day spa prostitution sting turn up heat on PATRIOTS owner Kraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-robert-kraft-prostitution-case-appeal-fight-20191227-h7aepphb2jfzvl52qpmn5a2ibu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In court documents, attorneys for Florida argue that billionaire Robert Kraft's two misdemeanor charges of soliciting prostitution constitute a felony offense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE PREDICTS:  4 MORE YEARS!</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/12/26/michael_moore_predicts_2020_trump_victory_trumps_level_of_support_has_not_gone_down_one_inch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with Amy Goodman of Democracy Now!, Michael Moore said if the election were held today that President Trump would win a second term. However, Moore predicted the Democratic candidate for president would win the popular vote count by 4 to 5 million people.  Moore warned the "problem" is support for Trump in the Midwest has not gone down by "one inch" and that Trump voters are "even more rabid" than before because they are afraid he may lose. "I think if the election were held today," Moore said of a Trump victory. "Hillary won by 3 million popular votes. I believe whoever the Democrat is next year is going to win by 4 to 5 million popular votes. There’s no question in my mind that people who stayed home, who sat on the bench, they’re going to pour out, in California, New York and — you know, but also in Texas and whatever, I mean, places that Trump will probably win, but, yeah, there’s going to be a much higher percentage of people voting against him." "The problem is, if the vote were today, I believe, he would win the electoral states that he would need, because, living out there, I will tell you, his level of support has not gone down one inch," he said. "In fact, I’d say it’s even more rabid than it was before, because they’re afraid now. They’re afraid he could lose, because they watched his behavior. So they are voracious in their appetite for Donald Trump. That’s the bad news." Moore said the good news is that 70% of the electorate next year will be women, people of color and young adults who he says are "on our side." Moore said Democrats, who are going in with the momentum of demographics, have to make sure they don't give people "another Hillary Clinton" to vote for. He said Democrats must put someone on the ballot that comes across as a "fighter" that excites the base of women, people of color, and young people. "What we have to do is we have to make sure we don’t give them another Hillary Clinton to vote for," he said. "The Democrats who are encouraging moderation, go to the center — you know, 'Let’s not upset the angry white guys' — that’s really what it is." "Ninety thousand wanted to send a message to the Democratic Party: "You forgot us a long time ago out here, and we will not put up with this anymore. We’re not going to vote for Trump, but we’re not going to tolerate you sending us another Republican-lite Democrat,'" Moore said. "If we go that route, it’s guaranteed we will lose the Electoral College," Moore continued. "We will win when we put somebody on that ballot that excites the base — women, people of color, young people. When they wake up that morning and they feel the way that many of us, many of you watching, felt the morning that you were going to — in 2008, and you were going to get to go and vote for Barack Obama." "That feeling has got to happen in the 18-to-35-year-old demographic," he said. "It has to happen with people of color and with women. We already feel that way. They already feel that way. It’s just: Will they come out and vote for a centrist, moderate candidate. I don’t think that is going to happen. They’re going to come out and vote for the fighter, for the person that shares their values." Moore said that political polarization is a "good thing" and complained that it is always talked about like it's a bad thing. "Polarization is always talked about like it’s a bad thing," Moore told Goodman. "I think it’s a good thing. I think if you think women should have the right to vote, I don’t think there’s a middle position on that. You either believe that women should vote or women shouldn’t vote. You either believe that a fertilized egg is a human being or not. There’s no middle ground there." Transcript, via Democracy Now! AMY GOODMAN: So, that’s President Trump, impeachment night, in your state. But interestingly, you kind of agree with him. You think he would win now. MICHAEL MOORE: I think if the election were held today — Hillary won by 3 million popular votes. I believe whoever the Democrat is next year is going to win by 4 to 5 million popular votes. There’s no question in my mind that people who stayed home, who sat on the bench, they’re going to pour out, in California, New York and — you know, but also in Texas and whatever, I mean, places that Trump will probably win, but, yeah, there’s going to be a much higher percentage of people voting against him. The problem is, is that he will — if the vote were today, I believe, he would win the electoral states that he would need, because, living out there, I will tell you, his level of support has not gone down one inch. In fact, I’d say it’s even more rabid than it was before, because they’re afraid now. They’re afraid he could lose, because they watched his behavior. So they are voracious in their appetite for Donald Trump. That’s the bad news. The good news is, again, number one, never forget, there’s more of us than there are of them. The majority of the American people agree with us. Seventy percent of the voters next year are women, people of color and young adults. OK? All that on our side. So, what we have to do is we have to make sure we don’t give them another Hillary Clinton to vote for. The Democrats who are encouraging moderation, go to the center — you know, “Let’s not upset the angry white guys” — that’s really what it is. You know, the voter they’re trying to convince — “That’s why we’ve got to have Biden. You know, we’ve got to have Klobuchar. We’ve got to have somebody that is somewhere there, wherever that middle is now.” There’s really nobody in that middle, by the way. Even the Fox News poll last week showed that 54% supported impeachment and conviction, and 40-some percent didn’t. And then they asked the question: How many of you would support impeachment but no removal? It was at 4%, 5%. I mean, it was like — there’s nobody in that trying to have it both ways. So, it is polarized, but for a good reason. Polarization is always talked about like it’s a bad thing. I think it’s a good thing. I think if you think women should have the right to vote, I don’t think there’s a middle position on that. You either believe that women should vote or women shouldn’t vote. You either believe that a fertilized egg is a human being or not. There’s no middle ground there. And so, our side has got to take this by the reins, and it’s got to have the courage of our convictions to fight this. And if we do this, then he won’t win the electoral states. Remember, Hillary only lost Michigan by two votes per precinct. That’s it. And it’s not because Lunch Bucket Joe stayed home, you know, or voted for Trump. It’s because the — when they talk about the working class, Amy, this just drives me crazy. “Oh, you know, Trump won all these working-class votes in Michigan and Pennsylvania.” No. What happened was, is that the Democratic Party didn’t stand up in the way that they should have for what the youth wanted, for what people of color needed. And there were 90,000 people in Michigan, almost 90,000, who went to the polls, mostly Democrats, in very large numbers of them, in Detroit, Flint, Pontiac, Saginaw — these are all black cities, majority black. They stood in line in the cold for two to three hours to vote. They went in there, and they voted for state rep, state Senate, county commission. We don’t have dog catcher. We have drain commissioner, the person in charge of the sewage. That’s the lowest name on the ballot. They stood there. They voted for the Democrats all down ballot and left the top box blank. She only lost Michigan by 10,000, 11,000 votes. Ninety thousand wanted to send a message to the Democratic Party: “You forgot us a long time ago out here, and we will not put up with this anymore. We’re not going to vote for Trump, but we’re not going to tolerate you sending us another Republican-lite Democrat.” If we go that route — if we go that route, it’s guaranteed we will lose the Electoral College. We will win when we put somebody on that ballot that excites the base — women, people of color, young people. When they wake up that morning and they feel the way that many of us, many of you watching, felt the morning that you were going to — in 2008, and you were going to get to go and vote for Barack Obama, and you couldn’t believe this was happening in your lifetime, that if you remember that feeling — you know, I’m not talking about — we’re not going to discuss his eight years; I’m just talking about that morning. That feeling has got to happen in the 18-to-35-year-old demographic. It has to happen with people of color and with women. We already feel that way. They already feel that way. It’s just: Will they come out and vote for a centrist, moderate candidate. I don’t think that is going to happen. They’re going to come out and vote for the fighter, for the person that shares their values. And the values of the majority of this country are the progressive values, in my opinion. I’m for Bernie Sanders. But I understand why people want to vote for Elizabeth Warren or — I don’t know — well, nobody else, actually, has those particular values. So, both of them are good. I’ve had Elizabeth in a couple of my films. But Bernie Sanders, Bernie Sanders has the record. When Elizabeth said there, a few weeks ago, that she voted Republican until 1996, that really kind of took me. But I think, “OK, well, we welcome everybody. And if you used to vote for Republicans, fine.” But Bernie, go back to Bernie in 1963, the photo of him — I don’t know if anybody has it in the control room — of him being arrested as a college student in a civil rights demonstration in Chicago, 1963. That’s Bernie Sanders. They’re hauling him away. He’s not doing the thing that they teach us to do in civil disobedience where you just go limp and let them take — he’s actually — he’s fighting the cops. You know, that’s Bernie Sanders. He’s never, never changed. And so, I know that there’s a history. So many of his ideas are now the popular way, in terms of minimum wage, in terms of equal pay, mass incarceration, these things, you know. And look, I mean, just like any candidate, he’s a politician. You know, people watching this will have their disagreements or whatever. But one thing you can’t disagree with is, he has been true to his convictions. He will fight like hell for us. The fact that 52% of young people are for him — in the latest poll, 52% of young voters are for him; the millennial that’s running, 2%. Two percent of 18-to-35-year-olds are for the person their age. Young people want — AMY GOODMAN: You’re talking about Pete Buttigieg? MICHAEL MOORE: Yeah, Pete Buttigieg, yes. I’m not trying to avoid trying to pronounce the name. It is Buttigieg. No, but the youngest people want the oldest person. Why? Why? How could that be? I think it’s because they know their future is screwed. The future of this planet is — they probably think, and they may not be right, that it’s already too late. I mean, Bill McKibben came on this show 10, 12 years ago and told us if we’ve got above — if we went above 350 parts per million of carbon in the atmosphere, that’s it. There’s no turning back. There’s no reversing it. We’re at 415 parts. The younger generation — see, myself, you know, I will probably make it out of here without the awful, horrific collapse. I’ll see some of it. We’re seeing some of it now. Bernie, he’s fighting for this. They know he’s fighting for their future. Bernie has no future. No offense, if he’s watching. I mean, live long and prosper. But let’s just admit, he’s in the final quarter of his life. You know? And he’s willing to give up his final years to fight so that these 18-to-35-year-olds will have a future. And they know that. That’s why they’re for him. And I say to other adults my age, “Maybe we owe it to the young people, because we were supposed to leave them a better country. We were supposed to leave them a better planet. And we, the '60s and ’70s generation, we haven't done that. So maybe we owe it to these young people to get behind the person they want. It’s their future. That’s our responsibility.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Wants AI-Powered Swarms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/12/pentagon-wants-ai-driven-drone-swarms-search-and-rescue-ops/162113/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The project will likely require AI and unmanned systems developers to work together under the Joint Artificial Intelligence Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PEOPLE'S PM:  Inside Boris Johnson's $26,000-a-week Caribbean holiday villa...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/inside-boris-johnson-carrie-symonds-21169326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tory Prime Minister has vowed to lead a 'People's Government' - but not before he and his girlfriend have a bit of R&amp;R at Mustique, the luxury island hideaway for the rich and famous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wages rising fastest in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/wage-increases-workers-2019-high-low-skill-5208fb9f-20c2-486a-b572-fc20737546f3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The benefits of a tightening labor market are finally being passed on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Sales Soar...</title>
      <link>https://newsbureau.co.za/no-line-to-board-private-jets-but-there-is-a-line-to-buy-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbureau.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa rally slays records...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asian-stocks-xmas-tech-results-cheer-wall-street-040748889.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London (AFP) - A Santa rally rode through European and US stock markets on Friday, with Wall Street pushing further into record territory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2010s = 1984: The decade we finally understood Orwell...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/1984-george-orwell-2010s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It isn't about the surveillance. It's about seizing control of the truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY characters say tourists inappropriately touched them...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ef382b99d281ae18367a573dce1e97fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Walt Disney World employees who portray Mickey Mouse, Minnie Mouse and Donald Duck each filed police reports this month claiming they were inappropriately touched by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists discover remains of vast Mayan palace...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/dec/27/archaeologists-discover-remains-of-vast-mayan-palace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancient building found 100 miles west of Cancùn estimated to be more than 1,000 years old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghana lures Americans, some to stay...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/news/article/Ghana-lures-Americans-some-to-stay-14933898.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACCRA, Ghana - The man from Boston stared at the ocean and thought: Maybe I'll never go back. He'd come to coastal Ghana for an adventure, he told friends, but his motivation ran deeper. Pierre Delva, 32, craved a fresh start without the question that had bothered him since childhood. "Is it because I'm black?" the used-car salesman said, reclining at a seaside bar in the nation's capital, Accra. "You don't have to wonder here." What started as an anniversary promotion called the Year of Return - a government-funded call for the African diaspora to explore Ghana four centuries after the first slave ship reached Virginian soil - has enticed some Americans to stay for good. Officials in this West African nation of roughly 29 million people say interest has overwhelmed the tourism office as the annual flood of visitors has more than doubled and A-list celebrities spark frenzies around the capital. By December, border agents were running out of visa stickers. Applications to enter Ghana shot up from about 1,000 per week to a staggering 10,000, said Akwasi Agyeman, chief executive of the Ghana Tourism Authority. Most visitors are American, he said. More surprising, he said, was the number of people who have decided to stay: 126 were granted citizenship this fall, including 46 Americans, in the country's biggest naturalization ceremony since 2016. "We could not have imagined this," Agyeman said. The rush to Ghana, where millions of Africans were forced into servitude before the slave trade ended in 1870, intensified after tweets from President Donald Trump. Trump told four congresswomen - including Ilhan Omar, a Somali refugee - to "go back" to "the totally broken and crime infested places from which they came" in July, sparking outrage around the world. (All four are U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey mother refuses to leave dead baby after hit by car...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkey-mother-refuses-leave-body-21170305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAPHIC IMAGES: A mother monkey was filmed holding the corpse of her baby after it was killed by a car while crossing a road in Kruger National Park, South Africa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael sister dies on Christmas -- exactly three years after his death...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7830457/George-Michaels-sister-Melanie-dies-aged-55-Christmas-Day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Michael's sister Melanie Panayiotou has died at the age of 55 exactly three years since his death on Christmas Day 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skier buried alive for five hours under 16ft of snow in avalanche -- survives...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7830409/Skier-buried-alive-five-hours-16ft-snow-Austria.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 26-year-old man, who is yet to be identified, had hit the slopes on Christmas Day on the eastern face of the Pletschnitzzinken, around 50 miles southeast of Salzburg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The guy is freaking evil'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7830351/Eddie-Gallaghers-fellow-Navy-SEALS-evil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEALS were interviewed by naval criminal investigators more than a year before Edward Gallagher was charged in September 2018 - and then later acquitted - of war crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Brown working out for SAINTS in late-season twist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/27/antonio-brown-working-out-for-saints-in-late-season-twist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Brown suddenly has a slim chance to get back in the NFL this season. The mercurial wide receiver is working out for the New Orleans Saints Friday morning, just two days before their Week 17…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China launches powerful rocket in boost for 2020 Mars mission...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-launches-powerful-rocket-boost-2020-mars-mission-133359884.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Friday launched one of the world's most powerful rockets in a major step forward for its planned mission to Mars in 2020. The heavy lift Long March 5 rocket carrying a test satellite payload blasted off from the Wenchang launch site on the southern island of Hainan at 8:45 pm (1245 GMT), a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: BERNIE BOUNCES BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/27/bernie-sanders-resurgence-democrats-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two months ago the Vermont senator had a heart attack and trailed Warren in the polls – now he’s bearing down on Biden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young girl from DELTA flight has cardiac arrest, dies at LAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/lax-delta-young-girl-dies-medical-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airline says the flight to Seattle returned to the airport shortly after takeoff due to the medical emergency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Launches Giant Rocket as Space Race Heats Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-12-27/china-launches-giant-long-march-rocket-as-space-race-heats-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS releases video of jihadists executing dozen Christians...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/27/isis-monsters-execute-nearly-a-dozen-christians-around-christmastime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISIS-aligned jihadists have released a video claiming to show the execution of 11 blindfolded Christian men in Nigeria, in what analysts say was a barbaric act that was clearly timed to coincide wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://grabien.com/story.php?id=266347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘You could tell he was perfectly O.K. with killing anybody that was moving’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual Seismic Activity On West Coast...</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/very-unusual-seismic-activity-on-the-west-coast-has-some-experts-extremely-concerned-about-what-could-happen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The west coast never stops shaking, but lately the shaking has gone to an entirely new level, and this has many people deeply concerned about what may be coming.  Last summer, a series of alarming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big And Bizarre Drone Mystery Unfolding In Rural Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/31631/there-is-a-big-and-bizarre-drone-mystery-unfolding-in-rural-colorado</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large groups of drones are flying grid pattern routes over the region at night and nobody knows who they belong to or what they're doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 In 4 People Aren't Friends With Any Of Their Neighbors...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sign-of-the-times-75-of-adults-arent-friends-with-any-of-their-neighbors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey of 2,000 British adults shows the staggering extent to which the concept of a neighborhood community has fallen by the wayside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. base near NKorea accidentally blares emergency siren -- instead of taps...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-U-S-base-near-North-Korea-accidentally-blared-14933793.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Army base in South Korea accidentally blasted an emergency siren Thursday night instead of the somber notes of taps, officials said, igniting brief panic on the base amid North Korean leader Kim Jong Un's threats of an unwelcome "Christmas gift."  Taps, the melancholy bugler's song played at military funerals, was supposed to be sounded on Camp Casey's announcement system at 10 p.m., as is custom at Army installations to mark the end of the day, said Army Lt. Col. Martyn Crighton, a spokesman for the 2nd Infantry Division.  But Crighton said "human error" instead prompted the sounds of an emergency siren wafting through the freezing air throughout Camp Casey, the closest U.S. Army base to the North Korean border - and a likely prime target for missile strikes in the event of an attack.  The mistake bewildered service members on base, who said in a Reddit thread posted soon after the incident that soldiers were "riled up," and some ran through the halls in full uniform before the error was realized.  A short time after that, U.S. Army WTF! moments, a popular digital hangout for soldiers, posted a video it said it received from a soldier at Camp Casey. Crighton said he couldn't confirm the video was from Thursday.  The siren heard is commonly called an air raid siren. That is one function among others to generally warn soldiers to begin "alert procedures," he said.  Soldiers were "immediately" notified of the mistake, and control measures were put in place to ensure it is not repeated, Crighton said, though he did not say how much time passed between the false alarm and notification of the mistake.  Although it is unclear how the incident occurred Thursday, it appears similar to a 2018 incident in Hawaii, when an operator at the emergency management agency accidentally...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Richest Earn $1.2 Trillion!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/world-s-richest-gain-1-2-trillion-as-kylie-baby-sharks-prosper</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emergence of atypical fortunes underscores just how much money the uber-rich accumulated in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying Cars, Hyperloops and Other Tech Predictions That Didn't Pan Out...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/flying-cars-hyperloops-other-2020-100051517.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Predicting the future is hard, even for the people with the most power to influence it. In 2013, Jeff Bezos said he expected Amazon.com Inc. would be delivering packages by drone in four to five years. Here we are seven years later, the flying delivery robots Bezos envisioned are still</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu shores up base -- but obstacles remain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7dc5d35714994a238bbe5cdff85bd953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu shored up his base with a landslide primary victory announced early Friday, but he will need a big win in national elections in March if...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia commissions intercontinental hypersonic weapon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/597e7f2b20b21af959e4c6983b255c37</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia's defense minister reported to President Vladimir Putin that a new hypersonic weapon of intercontinental range became operational Friday following years of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anguish and Anger From Navy SEALS Who Turned In Gallagher...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anguish-and-anger-from-the-navy-seals-who-turned-in-edward-gallagher/ar-BBYnIkN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD investigating 5 possible anti-Semitic hate crimes this week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/26/us/anti-semitic-investigations-new-york-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five possible anti-Semitic incidents occurred in New York this week, all during the Jewish festival of Hanukkah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVEN MORE RECORDS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/27/stock-market-investors-run-to-traditional-assets-as-market-rally-continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures point to a higher start to the trading day as optimism continues to drive year-end rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/26/apple-hits-all-time-high-and-trader-sees-more-record-highs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's having its best year in a decade, and one market watcher says the run is far from done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brace for 'bloody' primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/475972-democrats-brace-for-bloody-primary-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are bracing for a long, drawn-out primary season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession, robots, rockets: Another roaring 20s for world?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191227093756-u0bly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARKETS-OUTLOOK/2030 (ANALYSIS):ANALYSIS-Recession, robots and rockets: another roaring 20s for world markets?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP OUTS WHISTLEBLOWER</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-retweets-article-which-names-alleged-whistleblower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump retweeted an article, Thursday night, which contained the name of a person alleged to be the whistleblower who filed a complaint relating to the commander-in-chief's dealin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCA-COLA Plans to Offer Cannabis Drink?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/video-fuels-speculation-coca-cola-plans-to-offer-a-cannabis-drink/ar-BBYmT7j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Goes on Global Offensive to Defend 'Fake News' Law...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/singapore-goes-global-offensive-defend-210000012.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Singaporean diplomats are taking the lead in defending a two-month-old fake news law, challenging international media outlets and free-speech advocates it says are publishing misleading claims on the contentious legislation.Since the law was enacted in October, authorities in the Southeast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-extends-rally-solidifying-2019-182123025.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc. shares rose on Thursday, hitting their latest in a series of record highs as the iPhone maker remained on track for its best annual performance in a decade.The stock rose as much as 1.6% in the first U.S. trading day after Christmas, when markets were closed. Contributing to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Is 'Little Rocket Man' winning?</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/12/little-rocket-man-winning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong-un is pushing the envelope. He is taunting the Americans. We have told him what he must do. And he is telling us where we can go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow rooted for the Steele dossier to be true. Then it fell apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2019/12/26/rachel-maddow-rooted-steele-dossier-be-true-then-it-fell-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various news outlets cited instances of vindication for the Steele dossier. Then came the Horowitz report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE REPORTER 2019:  I often can't recall what story was two days ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/washington/my-year-of-covering-the-trump-white-house/article_b1133d73-417c-54eb-b976-84043ac31f81.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A year of President Donald Trump is better measured in dog years, with so much being packed into 12 months — a Mueller report, trade talks, tweet storms,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephants in Thailand 'broken' for lucrative animal tourism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/elephants-thailand-broken-lucrative-animal-tourism-000910080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separated from their mothers, jabbed with metal hooks, and sometimes deprived of food -- many Thai elephants are tamed by force before being sold to lucrative tourism sites increasingly advertised as "sanctuaries" to cruelty-conscious travellers. Balanced precariously on hind legs, two-year-old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Los Angeles prosecutors reviewing 8 cases against Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/308062beead91476ff566c1e993114a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Prosecutors in Los Angeles are reviewing eight cases accusing disgraced film mogul Harvey Weinstein of sexual assault, an official said Thursday. The Los Angeles and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  CONDE NAST shakes up board of directors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/26/conde-nast-shakes-up-board-of-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Magazine powerhouse Condé Nast is shaking up the board of directors of its money-losing International subsidiary as it forges ahead with the combination of its US and overseas operations. Jonathan …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eccentric socialite to blame for CA wild pig problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/sfhistory/article/One-eccentric-socialite-is-to-blame-for-14916088.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's wild pigs are a hybrid breed, a mixture of two animals that have no place in California. The first is the standard domesticated pig, introduced by Spanish colonizers in the mid-1700s. Russian immigrants also apparently let some loose near Fort Ross in Sonoma in the 1800s. And as Gold Rush settlers flowed into the state, they killed the hogs' biggest predator, the bear. So the once-domestic pig spread, becoming a feral pig out in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ TOPS 9,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks/nasdaq-tops-9000-on-boosts-from-amazon-trade-optimism-idUSKBN1YU0QL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nasdaq crossed the 9,000-point mark for the first time on Thursday as all th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled union honchos' lavish spending exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/embattled-union-honchos-lavish-spending-exposed-villas-four-figure-dinners-cigars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work hard, play hard -- and on the union's dime. That might as well have been the motto for some former top officials at the United Automobile Workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Jails Use Kinder Approach To Solitary Confinement...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/12/26/california-jails-solitary-confinement-changes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate in solitary confinement at a California jail was refusing to leave his cell. The jailers' usual response: Send an "extraction team" of corrections officers to burst into the cell and drag him out.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
