<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>In possible first, Cuba allows march by animal activists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1fbc4c9865b4c398f5f1e1f5bd5e9b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — On Sunday morning a group of animal-lovers will march a mile down one of Havana's main thoroughfares waving placards calling for an end to animal cruelty in Cuba. Short,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Election Ads, to Stir up the Base, Anything Goes... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/03/world/middleeast/israel-election-ads-netanyahu-gantz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are some commercials riling up voters on social media. They are in Hebrew and Arabic, but need no translation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Agents Granted Wide Latitude Trying To Catch Drivers Seeking To Enter Illegally...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trapped-in-a-deadly-chase/ar-BBVBO50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince William delves into secretive spy world ...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1110843/royal-news-prince-william-mi5-gchq-spy-terror-threat-kate-middleton-princess-charlotte</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE William has spent the last three weeks secretly embedded with Britain’s intelligence services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhetoric gets tougher...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/media/As-Trump-struggles-to-curb-unauthorized-1479843.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD to scrap some crime data programs after criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2f53080e081042fc82fa00178b0f7dd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A newspaper reports Los Angeles Police Chief Michel Moore plans to make changes to a controversial program that uses data to identify people who are most likely to commit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhetoric gets tougher...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/as-trump-struggles-to-curb-unauthorized-immigration-his-rhetoric-gets-tougher-but-quick-solutions-are-elusive/2019/04/06/8780ac92-57b7-11e9-814f-e2f46684196e_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is grasping to deal with an unprecedented spike in migrant families without a well-defined strategy and with significant divisions roiling Trump’s team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA: Military intervention 'very serious option'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/us-military-intervention-on-the-table-for-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A military intervention to oust Venezuelan strongman Nicolás Maduro remains “a very serious option” for the United States, according to President Trump’s national security team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PM May says final choice between leaving EU with deal or no Brexit at all...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/apr/06/furious-tory-mps-will-bid-to-oust-may-if-uk-fights-euro-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime minister says Brexit could ‘slip through our fingers’ as Tory party fears that taking part in EU election would boost far right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America deals with new kind of candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-Pete-Buttigieg-America-deals-with-a-new-kind-13747087.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST HOLLYWOOD, Calif. - Pete Buttigieg sat in the back of a black SUV with a couple of staffers, sipping a still-steeping cup of tea to ease the fatigue from his suddenly frenetic schedule, when he looked out the window and interrupted himself.  "Man," said Buttigieg, taking in the rainbow-hued signs and colorfully dressed passersby that signaled he had entered West Hollywood, Los Angeles' de facto gay neighborhood. "It got real gay real quick out there."  Few Democratic presidential candidates could assess their surroundings so bluntly without seeming painfully out of line. But Buttigieg is not like any other Democratic presidential candidate - in part, if not exclusively, because he is gay.  He was also a Rhodes Scholar, a McKinsey &amp; Co. consultant who pored over grocery prices and a military officer in Afghanistan. He was a mayor at 29 and re-elected at 33. All of those experiences, he says, have chiseled him into the surprising presidential candidate he is at 37, barely beyond the constitutional age requirement for the job.  So has the fact, Buttigieg says, that he needed the Supreme Court to give him the freedom to marry his partner, Chasten Glezman. Same-sex marriage was illegal in Indiana until 2014, and he cites that to illustrate how government alters lives; his marriage exists, he tells voters at every stop, "by the grace of one vote on the Supreme Court."  Buttigieg's emergence gives Americans their second openly gay presidential candidate - activist Fred Karger sought the GOP nomination in 2012 - but the first, by far, to earn so much attention. Many gay Americans are celebrating Buttigieg's quick climb as a sign of tangible progress. Others, mainly outside that community, wonder whether talking about Buttigieg's candidacy as historic means undermining the notion that sexuality doesn't matter.  "I don't...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans march to demand power, water and end to Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/venezuelans-march-to-demand-power-water-and-end-to-maduro-idUSKCN1RI0L1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After weeks of power cuts and limited access to water, tens of thousands of Vene...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-abortion film a surprise boxoffice success...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-anti-abortion-film-surprise-box-office-success-010603753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A movie produced by a Christian studio about a former employee of an organization that provides abortions who became a "pro-life" activist is proving to be a surprising box office hit. "Unplanned" comes amid a resurgent campaign in the United States by opponents of abortion, which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN expert to visit Assange, assess violation of privacy claims...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-expert-visit-assange-assess-violation-privacy-claims-172848295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An independent rights expert will visit WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange at the Ecuadoran embassy in London to assess whether privacy violation claims involving him merit investigation, the UN rights office said Thursday. "The Special Rapporteur on the right to privacy, Joe Cannataci, plans to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is 'threat to world' says dissident writer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-threat-world-says-dissident-writer-063237464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dissident writer dubbed the "Chinese Solzhenitsyn" said Friday that his homeland is a "threat for the whole world". Liao Yiwu, who was jailed for writing a poem called "Massacre" about the Tiananmen Square protests, told AFP that it would be better for mankind if the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes erupt as Greek police stop migrants from entering...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190406153610-otfp2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-MIGRANTS/GREECE-BORDER (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Clashes erupt as Greek police stop migrants from reaching border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela street rallies show deep divide in struggle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b5de526e1c034541964a3f2e2a39f717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Rival political factions took to the streets across Venezuela on Saturday in a mounting struggle for control of the crisis-wracked nation, where U.S.- backed opposition...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE, BETO FACE OFF IN IOWA!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af719047b5fc4a6d8cafc7bc1ce59bd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's Bernie versus Beto in Iowa on a busy campaign weekend in the early nominating states. The two 2020 Democratic presidential candidates are holding dueling events just days after Bernie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren says Dems need more than anti-Trump cry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0047c702eec64130b5d0969b27dd8b5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on the 2020 presidential race (all times EDT): 3:45 p.m. Elizabeth Warren says the Democrats running for president will have to do more than campaign on an anti-Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest's 150-Year-Old Heart Being Worshipped in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/new-york/articles/2019-04-06/french-priests-150-year-old-heart-being-worshipped-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avg Person Has Just 4 Hours, 26 Minutes Free Time -- Per WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-average-american-free-time-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How much free time do you get to enjoy each week? If you're like the most people, it's hardly enough to even be excited about. A new survey finds that the average American logs just four hours and 26 minutes of time to themselves in a given week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to designate elite Iranian force terrorist org...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran/u-s-to-designate-elite-iranian-force-as-terrorist-organization-idUSKCN1RH2I4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is expected to designate Iran's elite Revolutionary Guard...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generational challenges lie ahead for Joe, Mayor Pete...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Generational-challenges-lie-ahead-for-Joe-Biden-13746930.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes the confluence of unrelated events provides a moment of clarity in politics. So it is with the recent travails of former Vice President Joe Biden and the recent emergence of Pete Buttigieg in the 2020 presidential race. They highlight the challenges that generational politics will play as Democrats select a nominee to run against President Donald Trump.  The two men are virtually bookends in the Democratic race. At 76, Biden is more than twice the age of Buttigieg, who at 37 is just two years past the constitutional requirement to stand for the presidency. Americans have never elected a president as young as Buttigieg, just as the nation has never elected a president as old as Biden.  Biden brings longer experience than anyone else in the field. He has been in the public arena for more than half his life, having been elected to the Senate at an age younger than Buttigieg is. That experience will be a principal attribute as he tries to make the case to Democrats that he is their party's most electable candidate and, if he were to win the nomination, that he is capable of settling down the country and able to be president from day one.  Biden served eight years at the right arm of President Barack Obama, chaired two of the most important committees in the Senate (Judiciary and Foreign Relations), has been in the middle of many of the important domestic policy fights and in the forefront of the most significant foreign policy issues over the past few decades. He has been on the winning and losing side of these debates, and, given how events played out, on the right side and the wrong side of history as well. He has admirers and critics for the positions he has taken.  Buttigieg, the mayor of South Bend, Indiana, offers a far shorter résumé, but one that nonetheless is marked by accomplishment. After graduating...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher faces suspension for showing videos with nudes...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/south-florida-teacher-faces-suspension-for-showing-videos-with-nudes/article_50b23ce2-92e1-5b34-8a3b-f40757616708.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pictures displayed by a high school art teacher showed nudity, for sure. The question is whether they were artistic or obscene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-US Sen 'Fritz' Hollings dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/48ba0b0130d14b97998b1e65a220ad23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — Ernest F. "Fritz" Hollings, the silver-haired Democrat who helped shepherd South Carolina through desegregation as governor and went on to serve six terms in the U.S. Senate,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For American Jews, Trump key figure...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/202753dd5041400daeeb5012f5c550b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Donald Trump isn't on the ballot for Israel's national election, yet he's a dominant factor for many American Jews as they assess the high stakes of Tuesday's balloting. At...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg could hurt Trump in Rust Belt...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/06/how-pete-buttigieg-could-beat-trump-in-his-bases-backyard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg is many things. At just 37, he is the mayor of South Bend, Indiana. He is a military veteran and a deeply religious gay man who is married but also enjoys sandwiches from the (anti-g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Y2K Revisited as GPS Reset May Send Devices Haywire...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apos-y2k-revisited-gps-reset-171424753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to a quirk in how Global Positioning Systems keep track of time, some devices are due to have their calendars reset at 7:59 p.m. EDT on Saturday. Fortunately, the glitch only affects older GPS systems or ones that haven’t been updated, and the U.S. Department of Homeland Security says it isn’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Genre...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lil-nas-xs-old-town-road-remix-feat-billy-ray-cyrus-is-a-turning-point-for-country-music</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 19-year-old rapper’s unlikely story of trap-country music domination could only have happened on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly 2020 Campaign -- for New Job in Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-megyn-kellys-2020-campaignfor-a-new-job-in-right-wing-media </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly’s antipathy towards Donald Trump may torpedo a return to right wing media—while the NBC ‘blackface’ controversy may prevent her from rejoining the media mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police suicides worry law enforcement brass...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bad-now-law-enforcement-brass-shine-spotlight-police/story?id=62136841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More officers die from suicide every year than in the line of duty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper tribute: Crips, Bloods march together in first gang truce for 27 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8805583/crips-bloods-tribute-nipsey-hussle/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GANG rivals the Bloods and the Crips have put aside their differences to march in memory of murdered rapper Nipsey Husssle. The gangs reportedly met up earlier this week to discuss a truce – …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why baseball spent more than $1bn on three players in month...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/apr/06/why-baseball-spent-more-than-1bn-on-three-players-in-a-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three of the richest contracts in sports history would appear to bust the baseball-is-dying narrative, but underlying trends have exposed a rot within the mechanics of the sport’s economics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She loves you...si, oui, ja: How pop went multilingual...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/apr/06/latin-spanish-pop-takes-over-from-english-language</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop stars once had to sing in English to win global fame. Now Spanish and other languages are taking over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOGETHER AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;objectid=12219976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angel Merkel is a leader that has always made her feelings clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Area 51 uncensored...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6893863/Roswell-UFO-Incident-Area-51-hoax-orchestrated-Soviet-Union-journalist-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Area 51: An Uncensored History' provides an inside look at one of the United States' greatest mysteries - the Roswell UFO Incident of 1947 that rocked Area 51.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black actor: Trump has done more for me than Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6893717/Greys-Anatomy-actor-slams-Obama-praises-Trump-inviting-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He tweeted his thanks to Trump while criticizing Obama in a series of posts. Washington was at the White House to celebrate a prison reform bill the First Step Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA: I worry progressives may undercut Dem allies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/437692-obama-im-worried-progressives-may-form-a-circular-firing-squad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Obama expressed concern about the progressive wing of the Democratic Party, saying he feared it could end up undercutting allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Didn't Rush Into 2020. The Race Came to Him Anyway...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-didnt-rush-into-2020-the-race-came-to-him-anyway/ar-BBVFZDE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK removes 'European Union' from Brit passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/uk-british-passports-european-union-eu-remove-words-brexit-delay-a8857501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones lawyer: If want INFOWARS host silenced, you're scarier than he is...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/opinion/op-ed/hc-op-norm-pattis-alex-jones-0406-20190405-howpjy3tq5eqhcvttscjbcawhq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What motivates hate is fear. Alex Jones and his listeners are afraid of what this country is becoming. You are afraid of Alex Jones and his outlandish conspiracy theories. You’re more alike than you think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showdown of world powers in Venezuela enters dangerous phase...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/05/showdown-of-world-powers-in-venezuela-enters-dangerous-new-phase.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first major showdown of our new era of great power competition, unfolding with accelerating speed over the past ten weeks in Venezuela, has entered a dangerous new phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet animals that dress up, start fires, have sex -- just for fun...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/06/why-some-animals-dress-up-start-fires-and-have-sex-just-for-fun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2007, a 15-year-old chimpanzee named Julie started sporting a stiff blade of grass behind one ear — a trend that drove her fellow apes wild. First, her son donned his own ear ornament, followed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRET EASTON ELLIS: Liberal lunatics deeply wrong about Kanye...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/06/bret-easton-ellis-why-liberal-lunatics-are-deeply-wrong-about-kanye-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2018, various journalists wanted to talk to me about a couple of tweets I’d posted in favor of Kanye West. They couldn’t seem to believe that I supported his “crazy” feed, especially when he sai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMS Head Coach Latest High-Profile LA Burglary Victim...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/04/05/encino-home-rams-coach-sean-mcvay-burglarized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean McVay is just the latest victim targeted in a spree of celebrity home burglaries in the L.A.-area over the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO NEW BARRIER?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d604da469caf44fb854fd05a67ee15d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Declaring "our country is full," President Donald Trump on Friday insisted the U.S. immigration system was overburdened and illegal crossings must be stopped as he inspected a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic rock next Hollywood gold mine?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2019/04/elton-john-biopic-rocketman-bohemian-rhapsody-classic-roc-movies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Bohemian Rhapsody’s near-billion-dollar take at the box office, studios are eyeing many a project steeped in F.M. nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billy Ray Cyrus Joins Lil Nas X. Country Enough for BILLBOARD Now?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/04/05/lil-nas-x-adds-billy-ray-cyrus-to-old-town-road-zooms-to-number-1-on-itunes-after-billboard-boots-him-from-country-chart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lil Nas X would not take ‘no’ from Billboard after they booted his “Old Town Road” from the country charts. He got country royalty Billy Ray Cyrus and added him to a remix o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog owners much happier than cat owners, survey finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2019/04/05/dog-owners-are-much-happier-than-cat-owners-survey-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pet owners and non-pet owners are equally happy (or unhappy) but among pet owners, there is a big difference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACKPAGE gone, but more graphic version fueling prostitution busts...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/news/breaking/mc-pol-sex-trafficking-backpage-shutdown-skip-the-games-20190322-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local authorities are attributing a sudden surge in prostitution-related activity in the Lehigh Valley to a new website that has picked up where controversial site Backpage.com left off when it was shut down a year ago. The site, Skip the Games, has been described by local police and prosecutors as a more graphic and “in-your-face” version of Backpage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists to unveil first pic of black hole...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190406-scientists-set-unveil-first-picture-black-hole</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists set to unveil first picture of a black hole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 hangover: Sanders supporters still upset...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cc72546e934b462ea4243cf19770516d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — It was hard to miss Cheri Pichone's excitement about Bernie Sanders' second presidential run. She showed up to a recent Iowa rally decked out in Sanders gear, complete with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-govt protests prompt talk of 'Balkan Spring'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ae6880bd49394933a208ff4090d13050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PODGORICA, Montenegro (AP) — It all started with a video posted on social media: a secret recording from 2016 that appears to show a well-known local tycoon hand over an envelope containing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump struggles with growing problem on border...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/aabc13ab07604b39b09710f08bc42a4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Tensions are rising, fingers are pointing and the search for solutions is becoming increasingly fraught. Overwhelmed by an influx of migrants at the U.S.-Mexico border that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight begins over Trump taxes, lawyer slams Dem request...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190405221130-dg84n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/TAX (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Fight begins over Trump's taxes, lawyer slams Democrats' request</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Infection, Spanning Globe in Climate of Secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/deadly-germs-lost-cures-a-mysterious-infection-spanning-the-globe-in-a-climate-of-secrecy/ar-BBVFPi7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu, consummate political survivor, faces voter test and legal peril...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-israel-election-netanyahu-survival-20190405-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has survived stinging political setbacks and years of scandals, but many Israelis wonder if next week's election, and a looming graft indictment, could presage his downfall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mummified Mice and Falcons Found in Ancient Egyptian Tomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-47838077</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The highly decorated chamber, in the desert near the Nile, is thought to be more than 2,000 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN NOT SORRY...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/437582-biden-im-not-sorry-for-anything-that-i-have-ever-done</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden said Friday that he's not sorry for his past actions that some women have said made them uncomfortable, but that he's sorry he didn't understand more at the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JILL BOTHERED BY HUSBAND'S TOUCHING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6890849/Jill-Biden-admits-Joe-feel-strange-uncomfortable-began-dating.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jill Biden has revealed how her husband Joe has been handsy since they first began dating in 1975, in her upcoming memoir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARCH JOBS: +196K...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/05/nonfarm-payrolls-march-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers came a month after February's jaw-dropping gain of just 20,000, which was revised up to 33,000 in the March report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 51%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_apr05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
