<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Outbreaks of deadly Ebola virus 'new normal', warns WHO...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/784012/ebola-virus-outbreak-new-normal-who-ebola-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female hunter defends viral photo of giraffe kill: It was 'delicious'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/american-hunter-tess-talley-has-no-regrets-about-viral-photo-of-slain-giraffe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I am proud of that giraffe," she said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unhappy with HBO 'CHERNOBYL,' Russia plans own series -- blaming CIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-nz/entertainment/tv/russia-makes-own-version-of-chernobyl-disaster-series-blaming-cia-agent-for-nuclear-explosion-following-success-of-sky-original-mini-series/ar-AACxhyu?li=AA5a2l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian couple says attacked on bus in London after refusing to kiss...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/london-bus-homophobic-attack-lgbt-melania-geymonat-chris-camden-a8948321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/USNavy/status/1136978500185919488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“BREAKING: #USNavy has released video of #USSChancellorsville being forced to maneuver to avoid collision, after #Russian destroyer Udaloy I made an unsafe and unprofessional approach in the Phillippine Sea, June 7th. (2/2) https://t.co/bM9ZHuYSUM”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CULTURE WARS: Spike Lee calls for Hollywood to 'shut it down' in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7a6057d36bcf4f55b767ba5fd98eae65</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man killed in fight over water in India amid deadly dust storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-killed-fight-over-water-india-amid-deadly-111543304.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 33-year-old man died after a fight over water in southern India, police said Friday, as the country gasped from extreme heat and storms that killed 24 in the north. The argument broke out on Wednesday when a 48-year-old man and his three sons were allegedly syphoning large quantities of water from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow detains anti-corruption journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-journalist/russian-anti-corruption-journalist-detained-in-moscow-idUSKCN1T80V0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian journalist known for investigating corruption among Moscow city offici...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give up password or go to jail: Police push legal boundaries to get into phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/give-your-password-or-go-jail-police-push-legal-boundaries-n1014266</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The world should know that what they’re doing out here is crazy,” said a man who refused to share his passcode with police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu not-so-secret weapon: His son Yair, defender in chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-israel-yair-netanyahu-20190607-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yair Netanyahu might not be as well known internationally as Donald Trump Jr., but there are certain unmistakable similarities between the two.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was arrested at 13. Now Saudi Arabia wants to execute him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2019/06/middleeast/saudi-teen-death-penalty-intl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Murtaja Qureiris was a child, he led protests demanding rights for Saudi Arabia’s Shia minority. Now he faces the death penalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested, accused of Times Square grenade plot...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/06/07/fbi-arrest-explosives-times-square/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police sources tell CBS2 that the suspect was taken into custody by the Joint Terrorism Task Force, which includes both the NYPD and FBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: USPS Mail Carrier Pepper-Sprays Dog Calmly Sitting In Front Yard...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/06/06/video-home-security-camera-catches-mail-carrier-pepper-spraying-dog-in-the-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I just feel like the time that she took to take out the spray, drop it, shake it and still spray him she could have just left the mail," said the dog's owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis sees 65 overdoses in just 9 days...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/minneapolis-sees-65-overdoses-fatal-days-police/story?id=63543727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minneapolis sounded the alarm on the cities overdose crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airplane door falls into Vegas neighborhood; Hits apartment, car...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/airplane-door-falls-las-vegas-neighborhood-hits-apartment/story?id=63543842</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of a neighborhood in Las Vegas got an unwelcome surprise in the form of an airplane door falling out of the sky and hitting an apartment building and car. The incident took place near Nellis Air Force Base, which is just northeast of Las Vegas. It is unclear what type of plane the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 lions escape from world-famous game reserve...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/14-lions-escape-south-africas-kruger-park-residents/story?id=63544292</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South African authorities are trying to recapture a pride of 14 lions that escaped from the world famous Kruger National Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Fabulously Wealthy in Silicon Valley: No Coding Required...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2019-silicon-valley-real-estate-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennial dads have pathetic DIY skills compared to baby boomers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/06/millennial-dads-have-pathetic-diy-skills-compared-to-baby-boomers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are dads’ essential DIY skills in decline? According to new research, millennial dads are less capable than their own dads when it comes to everyday DIY fixes, preferring to rely on professional he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESQUIRE turmoil amid masthead exodus...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/06/esquire-magazine-faces-turmoil-amid-masthead-exodus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is chaos at Esquire, as the entire top of the masthead has either resigned or been let go following the resignation of Editor-in-Chief Jay Fielden last week. Bruce Handy, features editor, who…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariffs Already Wiped Out Tax Savings for Average Americans...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tariffs-wiped-most-families-080000425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the president makes good on his threats to impose levies on virtually all imports from China and Mexico, those middle-earning households could pay nearly $4,000 more. Subtract the tax cut, and the average household will effectively be paying about $3,000 more in taxes through additional levies on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia accuses US of 'dangerous maneuvers' after warships 'nearly collide'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-russia-accuses-dangerous-manoeuvres-16460957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's Pacific Fleet claims the USS Chancellorsville came within just 50 metres of its destroyer the Admiral Vinogradov</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Don Lemon speaks out about harassment...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cnns-don-lemon-says-he-was-called-fot-shooting-show-1216386</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I was doing a shoot in the park the other day and someone said, 'We built this country. I can't wait for CNN to fire your black ass,'" the anchor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-Day 75...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/567d5642eef242119ff75aeda3a2371c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico to Treat Opioid Abuse  -- with Pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/new-mexico/articles/2019-06-06/new-mexico-expands-medical-marijuana-program</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO BUST...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-poll/beto-orourke-a-democratic-darling-in-2018-struggling-on-national-stage-idUSKCN1T72A6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O’Rourke, the former Texas congressman who nearly won a U.S. Senate seat la...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico President to Hold Border 'Unity' Rally in Tijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/national-international/Mexico-United-States-Tariffs-Unity-Rally-510919421.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's president said Thursday he will hold a 'unity' rally on the border in Tijuana two days before the U.S. is set to impose tariffs on all Mexican imports. President Andrés Manuel López Obrador announced a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED Rethinks Hollywood Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/buzzfeed-rethinks-hollywood-strategy-names-new-studios-chief-1216382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cindy Vanegas-Gesaule is adding oversight of film and TV projects to her existing role as head of programming for BuzzFeed News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of Trump's economy hinging on Fed he distrusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Fate-of-Trump-s-economy-is-hinging-on-a-Fed-he-13953011.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO - President Donald Trump has pummeled the Federal Reserve with insults in recent months, calling it "crazy" and blaming it for any stock market dives or ugly economic data. But now the president has thrust the fate of the economy into the hands of the organization - and the man - he has suggested he doesn't trust.  Fed Chair Jerome Powell and other Fed officials have signaled this week that they may have to cut interest rates in coming months to keep the economic expansion going - and counter any economic harm from Trump's escalating trade war.  Such a move would be highly unusual. It would come at a time when the economy has been growing quickly, and inflation and unemployment are low. And it could serve almost as an insurance policy on the impact of actions taken by the president, potentially facilitating his use of tariffs in unpredictable ways.  "The Fed never had to rescue the economy from past presidents' trade wars, or from policies that presidents embarked upon against the wishes of advisers," said Gary Richardson, an economics professor at the University of California at Irvine who used to be the official Fed historian.  The Fed is likely to signal its next step at its policy meeting this month, and markets are forecasting at least three interest-rate cuts by the end of the year. Powell said this week at a Fed conference in Chicago that the Fed is prepared to take "appropriate" action to keep the economy from a downturn, and stocks surged as a result.  The Fed could cut rates as soon as this month, or at policy meetings in July, September, October and December. Joseph LaVorgna, an economist at the investment bank Natixis, pointed out in a research note Thursday that "the Fed has never disappointed the markets' call for action."  The new trajectory is a sharp U-turn from where the Fed had been heading and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS:  Space exploration necessary to 'save Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/06/jeff-bezos-remars-speech-disrupted-by-protester-pushes-space-travel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protestor rushes on stage at Amazon Re:MARS conference during keynote by Jeff Bezos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Biden set for dueling campaign stops in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/06/biden-and-trump-both-plan-campaign-stops-in-iowa-on-tuesday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden plans to return to Iowa next Tuesday, marking only his second trip to the key caucus state since formally declaring a 2020 run for the White House. He may bump into President Donald Trump who also plans a visit to the state that day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content creators lash out at YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/06/06/youtube-under-fire-from-independent-creators-over-voxadpocalypse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube has begun demonetizing any content deemed to "brush up" against its rules following complaints from Vox journalist Carlos Maza. The backlash by video creators and site users against the Google-owned platform, called #VoxAdpocalypse, became the top trend on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement? Four in 10 Americans Don't See It Ever Happening...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/retirement-four-in-10-americans-don-t-see-it-ever-happening-1.1269777</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists seek out limit to human endurance...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-seek-limit-human-endurance-202528909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US scientists who studied the performance of myriad athletes -- including adventurous souls who spent five long months running across the United States -- have come up with an estimate of the absolute physiological boundary of human endurance. The limit to human endurance is measured in multiples of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBODOG FOR SALE...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2019/06/05/boston-dynamics-robot-spot-going-on-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Dynamics’ ambitions in the field of robotics have been the stuff that Internet virality is made of. The engineering and robotics company has already produced incredibly skillful machin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,072,000 ILLEGALS THIS YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/new-border-surge-prompts-10-jump-in-2019-prediction-to-1-072-000-illegal-immigrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calling the surprising May surge in illegal immigrant arrests on the border the “worst case scenario,” a top immigration analyst has boosted the expected level of crossings 10%, to over 1 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing brands America 'evil'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9236736/trump-china-trade-war-evil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump threatened to hit China with tariffs on “at least” another $300bn worth of goods today – as a Beijing propaganda campaign painted the US as evil bullies. Tensions bet…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ABORTION TURN</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/06/06/biden-flips-hyde-amendment-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden reversed his position on the Hyde Amendment Thursday after facing intense backlash from within his own party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA solves century-old jailhouse rape. Victim: His grandmother...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/virginiahughes/dna-test-rape-family-tree</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commercial DNA tests showed that Hiram and Bruce were related. But their link proved to be much deeper — and darker — than either could have imagined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blasts the 'Patriarchy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/madonna-feels-raped-by-her-new-york-times-profile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna says she feels "raped" by a New York Times profile done on her, adding that the outlet "is one of the founding fathers of the Patriarchy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top US commander: Iran 'threat imminent'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/military/u-s-commander-says-american-forces-face-imminent-threat-iran-n1014556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine Gen. Frank McKenzie says he believes the Iranians or their proxies may orchestrate an attack at any moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY goes monthly...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/entertainment-weekly-going-monthly-names-new-editor-1216303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The frequency change takes effect in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY MAIL Traffic Drops 50% After GOOGLE Algorithm Update...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90360580/googles-core-june-2019-algorithm-change-hurts-daily-mail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The search giant just tweaked its algorithm with a core update for June 2019, and there already seems to be an impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy QUITS Legal Team...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7113393/Rudy-Giuliani-QUITS-says-no-longer-Trumps-personal-lawyer-Mueller-fallout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani plans to quit as President Donald Trump's personal lawyer as the dust begins to settle after Special Counsel Robert Mueller concluded his Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New strategy in subpoena battles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cbf87e7a34b74e829f3e5e0e14788274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University may return $21.5M after donor's abortion remarks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7f6e8edff7f842bfa53a7e1524e3c3d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom in electric scooters leads to more fatalities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33f376b91e5945efbcbb2c460b1d0dcc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic hands ready in next 10 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-amazon-com-conference/amazon-ceo-bezos-says-robotic-hands-ready-for-prime-time-in-next-10-years-idUSKCN1T72JB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc Chief Executive Jeff Bezos said on Thursday he expects there will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's in -- and out -- of first debates...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/06/democratic-debates-2020-election-1356115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barring a last-minute change, Montana Gov. Steve Bullock will not make the stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA may delay Mexico tariffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/06/stock-market-wall-streets-rally-is-set-to-slow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose on Thursday, adding to a sharp two-day rally on expectations of looser monetary policy from the Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY goes monthly...</title>
      <link>https://www.adweek.com/digital/entertainment-weekly-goes-monthly-taps-jd-heyman-as-new-editor-in-chief</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People Magazine’s deputy editor succeeds Henry Goldblatt, who is exiting the brand after 17 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Invades the Swamp as DC Catches Antitrust Fever...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/06/facebook-google-amazon-apple-hire-lobbyists-as-dc-catches-antitrust-fever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, Google, Facebook, and Apple are preparing for all-out war with Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Dems Learned Wrong Lesson From Clinton Impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/06/did-clintons-impeachment-actually-hurt-republicans/591175/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It didn’t actually cost the GOP all that much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murders, cellphones, drugs: Feds strike at Aryan Brotherhood CA prison gang...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article231253023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contempt resolution for Barr, McGahn introduced...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/447318-dems-officially-introduce-contempt-resolution-for-barr-mcgahn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats have officially introduced a resolution to hold Attorney General William Barr and former White House counsel Don McGahn in contempt of Congress for failing to comply with congressional subpoenas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of 'arson' fires across Israel...</title>
      <link>http://www.israelnationalnews.com/News/News.aspx/264287</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.israelnationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erratic sleep linked to higher health risks...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/health/irregular-sleep-routine-linked-higher-health-risks-study-finds-t155636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having an erratic sleep schedule can do a number on your health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Gone Wild: High Drama Inside DC's Most Elite Private School...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/education/archive/2019/06/sidwell-friends-college-admissions-varsity-blues/591124/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Sidwell Friends, the high school of Chelsea Clinton and the Obama children, college counselors find themselves besieged by Ivy-obsessed families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas Ink SPOTIFY Deal to Produce, Host Podcasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/obamas-ink-deal-spotify-produce-host-podcasts-1216253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through Higher Ground Audio, Barack and Michelle Obama will develop, produce and lend their voices to audio shows for the music streaming service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN STATE Bans From Playoffs...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/06/06/golden-state-warriors-fan-ejected-confrontation-toronto-raptors-kyle-lowry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Golden State Warriors minority owner, who was ejected from Game 3 of the NBA Finals after shoving Toronto's Kyle Lowry, will not be attending any more NBA Finals games at Oracle Arena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London getting 'world's first' 360-degree infinity pool...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/style/article/infinity-pool-london-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London might soon get a 55-story building topped with a 600,000-liter, 360-degree infinity pool, which the designers say would be a world first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Trump shelves politics at anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-dday-anniversary-macron-trump/hugs-not-macho-handshakes-trump-shelves-politics-at-d-day-anniversary-idUSKCN1T71TM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump briefly set aside politics and his testy relationship wit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY lands podcast deal with Obamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/spotify-lands-exclusive-podcast-deal-barack-michelle-obama-n1014536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landing the former first couple is a major win as the podcast industry grows and the fight for rights to premium shows and creators becomes more contentious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela now a top source of asylum claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/venezuela-now-a-top-source-of-us-asylum-claims-poses-a-challenge-for-trump/ar-AACsEQa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems don't have a majority for impeachment, but support is growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.libertyheadlines.com/democrats-dont-have-majority-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.libertyheadlines.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When House Speaker Nancy Pelosi spoke last weekend at the California Democratic Party convention, she was greeted with cries of “Impeach! Impeach!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private border wall -- not working...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/salvadorhernandez/border-wall-gofundme-sunland-park-residents-migrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Regardless of what they build, they’re still coming in,” one resident said. “This is just political crap.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge of African migrants continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/06/06/500-african-migrants-apprehended-since-may-30-in-single-border-patrol-sector/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Del Rio Sector Border Patrol agents apprehended more than 500 migrants from the continent of Africa since May 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PART OWNER SHOVES RAPTORS PLAYER...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-warriors-fan-who-shoved-raptors-player-is-a-part-owner-5e2a1ded-9f3a-4ca0-9f52-3a008b644284.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Stevens is a venture capitalist and part owner of the Warriors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German nurse who murdered 87 patients given life sentence...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/02efea20c2cb468c98ec10ca36afcdb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Stabbed Self Three Times Because 'Tired Of Living In Trump's Country'...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/donald-trump/palmetto-stabbing-941685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman told police that she stabbed herself in the stomach with a kitchen knife because, “I’m tired of living in Trump’s country, I’m tired of Trump being president.” Cops found the 46-yea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA allowing illegals to fly without proper documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/tsa-allowing-illegal-migrants-to-fly-without-proper-documents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas — The federal agency tasked with overseeing security at transportation hubs has been violating its own policy by allowing migrants who have been released from federal custody onto flights despite not having required documents, according to several Department of Homeland Security…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Army Soldiers Have Worse Heart Health Then Civilians...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/soldiers-us-army-worse-heart-health-than-civilians-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One might think that the rigorous training and expectation to maintain good health would mean active Army soldiers have healthier hearts than the average civilian, but a shocking new study released by the American Heart Association reveals the opposite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Point cadet killed, 22 injured in training rollover...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/20-west-point-cadets-involved-vehicle-rollover-crash-n1014456?F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The accident happened Thursday morning near the Camp Natural Bridge training site, the U.S. Military Academy said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAKE TROLLS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/06/drake-instantly-trolls-warriors-klay-thompson-with-questionable-photo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA Finals are quickly becoming the Drake vs. Klay show — and Wednesday night went to the famed rapper. Drake trolled Warriors star Klay Thompson after his Raptors steamrolled Golden Stat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Bat Inside NYC Subway Car Spooks Passangers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/06/05/bat-on-subway-f-train-mta-new-york-city-bat-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Somehow, a bat made its way onto a subway over the weekend, startling the people inside. One straphanger recorded the incident on his cellphone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Nightmare: Finals Ratings Crash To 12-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/06/kawhi-leonard-raptors-win-nba-finals-ratings-crash-game-3-steph-curry-warriors-abc-1202628013/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anyone thought the Toronto Raptors were going to go extinct against the Golden State Warriors once the 2019 NBA Finals moved to back to America, last night’s Game 3 tore that theory apart. A res…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash Over Boston 'Straight Pride Parade'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/06/05/straight-pride-parade-boston-group-planned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before Boston's Pride parade fills city streets, celebrating the LGBTQ community, another parade proposal is causing an uproar on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontrunner Biden campaigning for president on his terms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2c57969955c4ed8bee6fb64bad9faae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Massive migrant mob WALKS AROUND border wall...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-massive-migrant-mob-walks-around-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a big beautiful border wall in Arizona, and the illegal immigrants who walk right around it are gladly turning themselves in to Border Patrol agents to begin their new life in the land of opportunity. Video of a large group of 134 Central Americans walking around the end of the border wall in Sasabe …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
