<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bans don't seem to be lessening reach of Alex Jones, INFOWARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mystatesman.com/business/bans-don-seem-lessening-reach-alex-jones-infowars/Xo1jC96JodMuYqZDYMVQjO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mystatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the nation’s largest technology and social media companies have tried to stop Alex Jon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan vows to defy US 'threats' after currency crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-vows-defy-us-threats-currency-crash-131332606.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Recep Tayyip Erdogan vowed Saturday to defy US "threats" over a detained pastor, showing no signs of concessions in a bitter row that has caused the Turkish lira to crash. Relations between the two NATO allies have sunk to their lowest point in decades over a string of issues including</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives call for constitutional intervention last seen 230 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/11/conservatives-call-for-constitutional-convention-alec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers push for ‘constitutional convention’ to restrict federal government – and it’s not as far fetched as it sounds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyprogress.com/racialstrife/unite_the_right/inside-jason-kessler-s-rise-in-white-nationalist-movement/article_0dd0d0d6-9d84-11e8-a196-d711b92783fe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyprogress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. - Jason Kessler needed a friendly media outlet to vent and portray himself as a victim. So he dialed Stormfront Action, a white-nationalist online radio show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane stolen by 'suicidal' employee crashes near Seattle...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6049669/Commercial-airliner-hijacked-Seattle-Tacoma-Airport-say-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 76-seater Horizon Air turboprop Q400 took off at around 8pm, and two F-15 fighter jets scrambled 'minutes later' to intercept it, according to Pierce County Sheriff's Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy security...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3a42449af0f4abc86973f858ab2295d/Heavy-security-as-Charlottesville-anniversary-weekend-opens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. (AP) — Police blocked off streets and mobilized hundreds of officers for the anniversary of white supremacist violence in Charlottesville, Virginia. The secur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY ON  BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/11/with-turkey-crisis-erupting-bankers-gather-for-emergency-talks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan is showing no signs of backing down in a standoff with the U.S. that rattled markets. As investors worry about Turkey sliding toward a full-blown financial crisis, the big question now is how far the pain may spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The September Issue is dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/11/the-september-issue-is-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In years gone by, the September issue was the Super Bowl of fashion magazines. Fat with ads and glossy shoots cherry-picking the best looks of fall — the most important season in the fashion calend…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California super volcano swirling with magma...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1001733/california-volcano-USGS-Long-Valley-Caldera-supervolcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SUPER-VOLCANO in California which erupted with devastating results hundreds of thousands of years ago has a vast reservoir of semi-molten magma measuring a staggering 240 cubic MILES, a new study has suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: 20 shot in night; 'I'm scared to walk to store'...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-chicago-violence20180810-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 18-year-old was shot in the head and killed on the Southwest Side Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlottesville tense...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6049431/Authorities-ban-skateboards-bats-rocks-Charlottesville-rally-GUNS-permitted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is nothing to stop anyone bringing an actual gun, even an AR-15, to Charlottesville - the on-edge Virginia city as it marks the anniversary of last year’s deadly Unite the Right rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Braces For White Nationalist Rally...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/08/11/unite-the-right-2-rally-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Permits for Sunday’s “Unite the Right 2” rally indicated that about 400 demonstrators are expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final call...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6991591/seattle-plane-hijacker-reveals-why-stole-jet-final-call-before-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MECHANIC stole a plane from Seattle airport and joked with air traffic controllers before crashing into an island. The airport employee, 29, “hijacked” the plane before performing stu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chased by fighter jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/video/2018/aug/11/plane-stolen-from-seattle-airport-chased-by-fighter-jets-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plane has been stolen from Seattle-Tacoma international airport by an airline employee and crashed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charity says heat wave put flamingoes in the mood...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/british-charity-says-heat-wave-put-flamingoes-mood-135243122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A British conservation charity says record-breaking temperatures have encouraged a rare flock of Andean flamingos to lay eggs for the first time since 2003.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP Congressman suspends campaign amid insider trading allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/11/ny-gop-congressman-chris-collins-suspends-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Collins was arrested by federal agents Wednesday in Manhattan. Prosecutors accused him of illegal activity related to securities of Australian biotech company Innate Immunotherapeutics, on whose board of directors he served.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glyphosate under fire from San Fran to Sri Lanka...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/glyphosate-under-fire-san-francisco-sri-lanka-132906775.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glyphosate, the world's most widely used herbicide and the active ingredient in Monsanto's weedkiller Roundup, is the subject of fierce controversy all across the globe and is classified by the World Health Organization as "probably" being carcinogenic. A San Francisco court ordered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Town of 11 People, Mysterious Disappearance Turns Neighbor Against Neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/11/world/australia/larrimah-mystery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumors abound in a small outback town. Was Paddy Moriarty fed to a pet crocodile? Or could he have been baked into a meat pie?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight for FOX Local Sports Channels Could Shake Up Broadcasting...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/11/fight-for-fox-local-sports-channels-could-shake-up-broadcasting </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fight for Fox Local Sports Channels Could Shake Up Broadcasting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians involved in murder of Brazilian activist: govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180811-politicians-involved-murder-brazilian-activist-govt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay up or else: Spain warns of online 'sextortion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180811-pay-or-else-spain-warns-online-sextorsion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year in Paris as bad for health as smoking 183 cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180810-year-paris-bad-health-smoking-183-cigarettes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by the European Transport &amp; Environment association published on Friday confirmed that spending a few days in various popular European capitals is equivalent to smoking between one and four cigarettes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane stolen by 'suicidal' employee crashes near Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/701faeff7c7a44ab89b1186f6ffa63be/Plane-stolen-by-'suicidal'-employee-crashes-near-Seattle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATAC, Wash. (AP) — A "suicidal" airline employee stole an empty Horizon Air turboprop plane, took off from Sea-Tac International Airport and was chased by military jets before c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RELENTLESS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cbc36115f3c4dfda26693ffe1a2b5c8/Crews-battle-growing-wildfire-near-homes-in-California</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE ELSINORE, Calif. (AP) — Firefighters worked furiously Friday to keep a Southern California wildfire from burning more homes while crews in the north finally gained ground on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN ROCKET LIFTOFF! NASA GROUNDBREAKING MISSION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3c0d9bcef5904bf3a01717d66250cb3b/Last-minute-technical-problem-delays-NASA's-flight-to-sun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A last-minute technical problem Saturday delayed NASA's unprecedented flight to the sun.        The early morning launch countdown was halted wi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine row erupts in Italy as populist govt seeks to ease rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vaccine-row-erupts-italy-populist-govt-seeks-ease-031324205.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A row is erupting over vaccines in Italy as the country's new populist government fights to roll back a law that bans children from attending school if they haven't received a series of jabs. The law, adopted last year by the centre-left government that was booted out of power in March, made</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels' lawyer says Dems must fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/porn-star-lawyer-avenatti-takes-fighting-message-iowa-044149208--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEAR LAKE, Iowa (AP) — Michael Avenatti, the self-styled provocateur taking on the president for porn actress Stormy Daniels, told Iowa Democrats on Friday that the party needs a bare-knuckle fighter to take back the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Intelligent' crows to pick up litter at theme park...</title>
      <link>https://www.expatica.com/fr/news/country-news/France-tourism-birds-offbeat_2031808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.expatica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six crows specially trained to pick up cigarette ends and rubbish will be put to work next week at a French historical theme park, its president said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed by 2 pit bulls while on walk...</title>
      <link>http://www.montgomeryherald.com/news/article_a7fc2186-9cb4-11e8-8110-735d9be7ce56.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.montgomeryherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montgomery County Sheriff Chris Watkins released this statement Friday, August 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury Rules ROUNDUP Caused Groundskeeper's Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-jury-finds-monsanto-guilty-roundup-trial-224845050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California jury ordered chemical giant Monsanto to pay nearly $290 million Friday for failing to warn a dying groundskeeper that its weed killer Roundup might cause cancer. Jurors unanimously found that Monsanto -- which vowed to appeal -- acted with "malice" and that its weed killers Roundup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN ROCKET LIFTOFF! NASA GROUNDBREAKING MISSION...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nasa-sending-spacecraft-straight-suns-glittering-crown-192254533.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA is sending a spacecraft straight into the sun's glittering crown, an atmospheric region so hot and harsh any normal visitor would wither.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RELENTLESS!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/man-suspected-sparking-huge-california-forest-fire-facing-175454287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities battling massive wildfires in large swathes of California issued mandatory evacuation orders and health warnings Friday over the worsening air quality as the flames grew ever closer to populated areas. After almost a month of wildfires, the National Weather Service warned that satellite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba charges leading dissident with attempted murder... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cuba-charges-leading-dissident-attempted-murder-230745752.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of one of Cuba’s largest and most active opposition organizations was charged Friday with attempted murder after being held incommunicado for a week in eastern Cuba. Jose Daniel Ferrer, leader of the Patriotic Union of Cuba (UNPACU), was charged with deliberately trying to run over an official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border police: Woman in 80s smuggled drugs! </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/10/80-year-woman-caught-tecate-port-92-pounds-heroin-say-border-police/959529002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An older United States citizen attempted to cross the U.S./Mexico border near San Diego on Wednesday with 92 pounds of heroin in her car. Officials say cartels are known to manipulate people into carrying drugs over the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Acted with malice or oppression'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/aug/10/monsanto-trial-cancer-dewayne-johnson-ruling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court finds in favor of DeWayne Johnson, ill man who was first to take Roundup maker to trial over allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The stunning, devastating, weekslong journey of an orca and her dead calf... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-stunning-devastating-weekslong-journey-of-13147693.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grieving orca was spotted off the coast of Washington state Thursday, carrying her dead calf through the Pacific Ocean for the 17th day in a journey that has astonished and devastated much of the world. Tahlequah, as the mother has come to be called, gave birth on July 25 in what should have been a happy milestone for her long-suffering clan. As Allyson Chiu wrote for The Washington Post, the pod of killer whales that roams between Vancouver and San Juan Island has dwindled to 75 members over the decades. The cause is no mystery: Humans have netted up the whales' salmon, driven ships through their hunting lanes and polluted their water, to the point that researchers fear Tahlequah's generation may be the last of her family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Cities Dominate List of 'Boomtowns'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/texas/2018/08/10/texas-cities-dominate-list-of-u-s-boomtowns/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study this week that found Texas dominated the list of U.S. "boomtowns" and Austin scored the top spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orders MONSATO To Pay $290M In Damages...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/08/10/jury-rules-roundup-pesticide-caused-former-groundskeepers-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Francisco jury Friday ruled in favor of a former Benicia Unified School District groundskeeper who blamed his deadly cancer on the popular herbicide "Roundup" and sued its manufacturer Monsanto for damages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran test-fires ballistic missile...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/08/10/iran-test-fires-ballistic-missile-for-first-time-in-2018-officials-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in more than a year, Iran test-fired a ballistic missile in a brazen display of defiance months after President Trump pulled the United States out of a landmark nuclear deal and days before his administration slapped new sanctions on the Islamic Republic, three U.S. officials with knowledge of the launch tell Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA: All new music sounds same...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/08/10/madonna-slams-todays-music-everyone-sounds-same.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with Vogue Italia pop star Madonna talks about her year living in Lisbon and how most new songs sound the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump dines with APPLE Cook... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/401348-trump-to-dine-with-apple-ceo-tim-cook </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump will dine with Apple CEO Tim Cook on Friday, according to a tweet he sent late Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of living rises at fastest rate in decade... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/401321-cost-of-living-rises-at-quickest-rate-in-10-years </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of living in the U.S. is rising at its fastest rate in 10 years, according to new data from the Labor Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Why We Dug Through His Wife's Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/10/reader-center/bett-kavanaugh-wife-foia-request.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Readers have asked about the kind of public information requests our journalists make. Two of our investigative reporters explain how this worked with recent requests on President Trump’s Supreme Court nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N-WORD DRAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/10/omarosa-trump-book-the-apprentice-memoir</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Apprentice contestant and ex-White House adviser writes in new memoir that she witnessed ‘truly appalling things’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAROSA SHOW: INTERVIEW CONTRADICTS BOOK!?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/08/10/636955054/omarosa-tells-npr-she-heard-trump-n-word-tape-contradicting-her-own-tell-all-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former reality TV star and Trump aide Omarosa Manigault Newman spoke to NPR about explosive allegations in her new book, Unhinged, but part of her account changed in the interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER CIRCLING ROGER STONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/manhattan-madam-kristin-davis-testifying-before-grand-jury-1533919583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Stone claimed he had interactions with WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange during the 2016 presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauffeur May Bring Down Argentina's Political Elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/quicktakes/2018/08/10/how-a-chauffeur-could-bring-down-argentina-s-elite-quicktake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a Chauffeur Could Bring Down Argentina’s Political Elite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private TESLA? That's One Big Tiny Automaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/10/private-tesla-would-be-dwarfed-by-world-s-largest-automakers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Private Tesla? That’s One Big Tiny Automaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreigners face ban on buying homes in New Zealand after apocalypse bolthole fad hikes prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/10/foreigners-face-ban-buying-homes-new-zealand-apocalypse-bolthole/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreigners are set to be banned from buying homes in New Zealand after a spate of millionaires seeking luxury doomsday boltholes has apparently crowded out local buyers and pushed up property prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washed up whales on Irish beaches killed by military activity?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/dead-whales-washed-ashore-military-sonar-cuviers-beaked-royal-navy-a8485576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Catastrophic event’ likely to be behind ‘highly unusual’ multiple strandings, says marine conservation group</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE: 500,000+ Venezuelans fled to Ecuador this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/10/more-than-half-a-million-venezuelans-fled-to-ecuador-this-year-un-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quito declared a state of emergency after 30,000 migrants escaping violence and a collapsing economy came the first week of August</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Unable To Name Legislative Accomplishment...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/10/kamala-harris-unable-to-name-a-legislative-accomplishment-when-asked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris struggled to name a specific legislative accomplishment the 2020 hopeful was a part of.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
