<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower: The company knows it's harming people!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/05/facebook-whistleblower-testifies-before-senate-committee.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frances Haugen unmasked herself Sunday as the source behind leaked documents at the core of a revealing Wall Street Journal series about Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan calls for new 'digital order'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/turkish-beef-with-social-media-gets-louder-after-facebook-outage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Erdogan’s Beef With Social Media Gets Louder After Facebook Outage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber Launches Own Line Of Pre-Rolled Joints...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/news/justin-bieber-launches-pre-rolled-joints-called-peaches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After releasing six studio albums and becoming one of the best-selling music artists of all time, [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Third Of Americans Open To Abolishing Or Limiting Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/abolishing-limiting-supreme-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;38 percent believe that if Congress disagrees with the Supreme Court, “Congress should pass legislation saying the Supreme Court can no longer rule on that issue or topic.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools Seeing 'Massive' Staff Shortages...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/04/north-texas-seeing-massive-shortages-in-education-no-teachers-no-subs-no-cafeteria-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some schools are combining classrooms with double the number of students. Students are seeing more of their teachers, and coaches, driving buses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Unions Back First Strike Threat in Streaming Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hollywood-guild-iatse-strike-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood's below-the-line workers have authorized a strike, a move backed by other unions looking to see their own gains in streaming revenues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Gives Unvaxxed Staff Daily Nose Swab Option...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/swab-job-fox-folks-nix-vax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of Fox News employees in the Washington bureau apparently refuse vaccination, preferring daily nasal swabs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grisham Confesses Her Enabling The Don Cost Lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/i-do-stephanie-grisham-straight-up-confesses-her-enabling-trump-cost-lives-during-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Grisham came clean on a number of massive issues during a Tuesday morning interview with CNN's New Day, including harming democracy and costing lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man reported missing unknowingly joins his own search party!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-reported-missing-joins-search-party-seeking-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man joined a search party for a missing person not realizing the individual being pursued was him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TREASURY PLANS EMERGENCY $1 TRILLION COIN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trillion-dollar-platinum-coin-mint-janet-yellen-223e7722-d7ba-47c9-b5f6-49a841d181de.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coin could be deployed to help bridge the gap between the money running out and the debt ceiling increasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS:  Lavish real estate revealed in Pandora Papers...</title>
      <link>https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/pandora-papers-real-estate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architecturaldigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From clifftop mansions in Malibu to stately town houses in London, these are the properties world leaders allegedly use to hide their wealth and avoid taxes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA STAR SAYS YOU DON'T OWN YOUR BODY AFTER GETTING JABBED...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/05/andrew-wiggins-vaccinated-forced-dont-own-your-body/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Wiggins doesn&amp;amp;#039;t sound too happy about being vaccinated. He said he felt forced to get the vaccine and people don&amp;amp;#039;t own their bodies for work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frantic fight to protect coast as worsening Orange County oil spill stalks beaches...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frantic-fight-protect-coast-worsening-140745036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A map projecting the movements of the oil spill indicates the greatest threat to the shore remains in the area between Huntington Beach and Laguna Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY largest health provider fires 1,400 for refusing shots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-new-york-health-72287faf1ccbe739df8826e51378d96a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Northwell Health, New York state's largest health care provider, announced that 1,400 employees have been terminated for refusing to be vaccinated against COVID-19. The terminations represent less than 2% of the total workforce of Northwell, which runs 23 hospitals and more than 700 outpatient facilities across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg apologies have been staple of FACEBOOK scandals. Now, defiance...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/zuckerberg-e2-80-99s-apologies-have-been-a-staple-of-facebook-scandals-now-the-company-offers-defiance/ar-AAP8FWt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gone is the familiar script in which chief executive officer Mark Zuckerberg issues a formal apology then takes responsibility and promises change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adele announces comeback with new single...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/adele-announces-comeback-single-142234983.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There had been widespread speculation the singer was close to confirming her return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police investigating suspicious vehicle in front of Court...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211005140027-initt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CAPITOL/SECURITY (URGENT):Capitol Police says it investigating suspicious vehicle in front of U.S. Supreme Court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG TERRIBLE WEEK</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/technology/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-terrible-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race to save wildlife...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/finance/news/orange-county-oil-spill-sparks-120055671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first victims are seabirds, graceful creatures that alight upon the ocean's surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SQUID GAME' violence erupts in Paris: Fans of show brawl in street...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10060581/Squid-Game-violence-Paris-Fans-Netflix-brawl-700ft-queue-forms-pop-store.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage shows several Squid Game fans locked in a heated fist fight in Paris on Sunday after they queued for hours to get inside a pop-up store for the popular Netflix horror series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Woman shoves bystander into approaching subway train at Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10059513/Woman-shoves-commuter-approaching-NYC-subway-train-Times-Square.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspect (inset) pushed another commuter into the train as it approached the platform. The 42-year-old victim suffered facial injuries and was taken to the hospital in stable condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen warns debt ceiling breach could trigger recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/janet-yellen-congress-debt-ceiling-recession-9bea45fa-7c67-4c9b-81f8-a0c7dd79f543.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yellen has warned that defaulting would bring permanent damage to the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to investigate threats against teachers, school board members nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/575295-doj-to-investigate-threats-against-teachers-school-board-members</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice announced that it is investigating threats made against teachers and school board members nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High School Cancels Football Season After Players Sodomize Teammate With Object, Post Video On Social Media...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/10/04/its-bad-its-bad-proctor-teens-say-students-used-item-to-sodomize-teammate-shared-video-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WCCO has uncovered disturbing new details about why a Minnesota high school canceled its football season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas braces for surge of 60,000 Haitian migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/texas-braces-for-surge-of-60-000-haitian-migrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas — State officials are bracing for what could be the largest surge of migrants ever to attempt to enter the country illegally from Mexico, weeks after thousands of Haitians did so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan president warns of 'catastrophic consequences' if island falls to China...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/oct/05/taiwan-president-warns-of-catastrophic-consequences-if-island-falls-to-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tsai Ing-wen says Taiwan will ‘do whatever it takes to defend itself’ against an increasingly assertive Beijing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal inquiry into Trump election interference gathers steam...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/oct/05/donald-trump-criminal-investigations-georgia-election-interference</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disgraced former president faces a range of possible charges – including conspiracy and election fraud</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Got Gas? Poor Mental Health May Explain Why...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gas-symptoms-poor-mental-health-flatulence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say a poorer quality of life, stress, anxiety, and depression appear to be to blame for several gas-related symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDakota Biggest Haven in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pandora-papers-tax-haven-south-dakota/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amount of wealth being hidden in the Mount Rushmore State — safe from taxes, creditors and even child support — has quadrupled in a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once shunned, people convicted of felonies find more employers open to hiring them...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/once-shunned-people-convicted-felonies-113052753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labor shortages are prompting more companies to consider the 20 million people with convictions, but criminal background checks, job restrictions and other barriers hold back hiring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Future Could Soon Look Like Dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-s-future-could-soon-look-a-lot-like-the-u-s-dollar-1.1661919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dollar is entering the crypto age, and the U.S. government is poised to give its clearest signal yet on how that will happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: Record Manhattan Home Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/manhattan-homebuyers-send-sales-soaring-to-best-in-three-decades/ar-AAP8WZX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan apartment sales surged to a record in the third quarter as buyers grabbed what they could while inventory remains high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What science can tell about benefits of religion...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/What-science-can-tell-us-about-the-benefits-of-16509987.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People have turned to religious practice to help them deal with issues of life and death,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law Firm Helped Elite Hide Billions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/law-firm-at-center-of-pandora-helped-global-rich-hide-billions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The story, as told by Aleman in his autobiography, “Honesty is Priceless,” was the beginning of an offshore-entity boom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane flying 'will you marry me' banner crashes, killing passenger...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/plane-flying-marry-banner-crashes-221832344.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The banner remains somewhere in the St-Lawrence River</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,700-year-old toilet found in Jerusalem was a rare luxury...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-jerusalem-middle-east-israel-555ddebe8076d1c7c99c384dae08fc78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli archaeologists have found a rare ancient toilet in Jerusalem dating back more than 2,700 years, when private bathrooms were a luxury in the holy city, authorities said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic clergy in France likely abused 330,000 minors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-france-child-abuse-sexual-abuse-by-clergy-religion-ab5da1ff10f905b1c338a6f3427a1c66</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — An estimated 330,000 children were victims of sex abuse within France’s Catholic Church over the past 70 years, according to a major report released Thursday that is France’s first major reckoning with the devastating phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French child kidnap plot shows global sway of QANON style...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-europe-kidnapping-health-79761187c5d2767a8a27072a0e2d81ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The old music box factory had been abandoned for years on the outskirts of the Swiss mountain town, with paint curling at the edges of its dingy grey and yellow walls. It was the perfect hiding place for the young French mother and her 8-year-old daughter at the heart of Operation Lima, an international child abduction plot planned and funded by a French group with echoes of the far-right extremist movement QAnon .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD'S MILITARY POWERS SET FOR DRILLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/dueling-u-s-china-military-drills-highlight-rising-taiwan-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dueling U.S., China Military Drills Highlight Rising Taiwan Risk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA heads into 20th anniversary with new challenge: Unruly passengers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/575271-tsa-heads-into-20th-anniversary-with-new-challenge-unruly-passengers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration (TSA), which marks its 20th anniversary next month, is facing a new challenge with the recent surge in unruly airline passengers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK whistleblower bringing sharp criticisms to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/facebook-haugen-congress-testimony-1daac7a76ca7bf0b0802cc46e732b51b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A former Facebook data scientist has stunned lawmakers and the public with revelations of the company’s awareness of apparent harm to some teens from Instagram and her accusations of dishonesty in its fight against hate and misinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Army investigating after Confederate flag raised at barracks in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-army-investigating-after-confederate-flag-is-raised-at-barracks-in-germany/ar-AAP9ElL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandora Papers' political fallout grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-pandora-papers-e2-80-99-political-fallout-grows/ar-AAP8UsQ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scrutiny Intensifies on Federal Reserve After Trades Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/scrutiny-intensifies-on-federal-reserve-after-trades-revealed/ar-AAP9BCw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve is coming under greater scrutiny from inside and outside its walls following revelations about market trading by senior officials in 2020 as the coronavirus forced the central bank to leap to the rescue of the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks on Sinema turn increasingly personal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/575254-attacks-on-sinema-turn-increasingly-personal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attacks on Sen. Kyrsten Sinema (D-Ariz.) are becoming increasingly personal as she faces blowback for refusing to support the massive $3.5 trillion budget that progressives are demanding pass alongside the $1.2 trillion bipartisan infrastructure deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic clergy in France likely abused 200,000 minors...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/10/05/europe/france-catholic-church-abuse-report-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the Catholic clergy sexually abused more than 200,000 minors in France over the last seven decades, a survey carried out as part of an independent probe into abuse within the church estimates, according to the head of the commission that produced the report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice, Overwhelmed by Tourists, Tries Tracking Them...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/04/venice-overwhelmed-by-tourists-tries-tracking-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE — As the pandemic chased away visitors, some Venetians allowed themselves to dream of a different city — one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd Most-Watched 'SNF' Ever; 28.5M Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/tom-brady-patriots-buccaneers-rating-surge-sunday-night-football-nbc-1234849100/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 1:04 PM: Tom Brady has rarely been second place at anything, but the seven-time Super Bowl champ and NFL passing yardage record holder may be cool with this one. The QB’s much promote…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian film crew blasts off to make first movie in space...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-science-business-kazakhstan-anton-shkaplerov-aca1f3fac57a8033473d20fca577d628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A Russian actor and a film director rocketed to space Tuesday on a mission to make the world’s first movie in orbit. Actor Yulia Peresild and director Klim Shipenko blasted off for the International Space Station in a Russian Soyuz spacecraft together with cosmonaut Anton Shkaplerov, a veteran of three space missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST MONDAY IN OCTOBER:  Abortion, guns, religion top big Supreme Court term...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-college-admissions-donald-trump-amy-coney-barrett-courts-e245e6b581143bc2f87c402f7c667535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The future of abortion rights is in the hands of a conservative Supreme Court that is beginning a new term Monday that also includes major cases on gun rights and religion. The court's credibility with the public also could be on the line, especially if a divided court were to overrule the landmark Roe v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese detective in exile reveals extent of torture against Uyghurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/04/china/xinjiang-detective-torture-intl-hnk-dst/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese policeman turned whistleblower has revealed rare details on what he described as a systematic campaign of torture against ethnic Uyghurs in the Xinjiang region's detention camps -- claims China has denied for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship anchor the cause?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211004211753-4rlcq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-OILSPILL/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-California oil spill cause probed, ship anchor cited as possibility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couric banned from plugging bombshell book on CBS...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/10/04/katie-couric-banned-from-promoting-her-book-on-cbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Couric — who hosted “CBS Evening News” from 2006 to 2011 — had been booked on “CBS This Morning” with Gayle King, until CBS News chiefs and producers read the book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Hospital Melting Masks To Help Deal With 'Mountain Of Waste'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/10/03/face-masks-recycling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's estimated 129 billion single-use face masks are used every month around the world, and millions of plastic ones are ending up in the trash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney's legal team has star's mansion swept for bugs, surveillance cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3791278/britney-spears-legal-team-mansion-swept-bugs-spying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’ legal team ordered a professional security sweep of her mansion in the wake of allegations she was spied on, Sun Online can reveal. Lawyer Mathew Rosengart brought in former m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren urges SEC to open insider trading probe into Fed Vice Chair, others...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/04/warren-urges-sec-to-open-insider-trading-probe-into-fed-vice-chair-clarida-others.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren on Monday urged the SEC to investigate whether Fed Vice Chair Richard Clarida "may have violated insider trading rules."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioters exploited little-known weakmess:  Unreinforced windows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jan-6-rioters-exploited-little-known-capitol-weak-spots-a-handful-of-unreinforced-windows/ar-AAP76Tc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two windows and two doors used by Jan. 6 rioters were among only a few that weren't reinforced during a Capitol security upgrade that started in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG LOSES BILLIONS</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/zuckerberg-loses-7-billion-hours-180950725.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mark Zuckerberg’s personal wealth has fallen by nearly $7 billion in a few hours, knocking him down a notch on the list of the world’s richest people, after a whistleblower came forward and outages took Facebook Inc.’s flagship products offline.Most Read from BloombergChristmas at Risk as Supply Chain ‘Disaster’ Only Gets WorseReshaped by Crisis, an ‘Anti-Biennial’ Reimagines ChicagoThis Is What Europe’s Green Future Looks LikeWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for Inve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Trans Doctors Blow Whistle on 'Sloppy' Care...</title>
      <link>https://bariweiss.substack.com/p/top-trans-doctors-blow-the-whistle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bariweiss.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In exclusive interviews, two prominent providers sound off on puberty blockers, 'affirmative' care, the inhibition of sexual pleasure, and the suppression of dissent in their field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOURS AFTER WHISTLEBLOWER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/facebook-whatsapp-instagram-outage-8b9d3862ed957029e545182a595fdce1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook along with its Instagram and WhatsApp platforms suffered a worldwide outage Monday that has extended more than three hours. Facebook's internal systems used by employees also went down. Service has not yet been restored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL GIANT WIPED FROM WEB</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10058203/Verizon-T-Mobile-T-leaving-thousands-without-mobile-internet-phone-services.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between 11.50am EST and 11.52am EST, Facebook made a series of updates which caused it to 'disappear' from the internet, according to the Chief Technology Officer at CloudFare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNS Records Vanish...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/facebook-instagram-whatsapp-experience-global-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China PCR test orders soared before first reported case...</title>
      <link>https://asia.nikkei.com/Spotlight/Coronavirus/China-PCR-test-orders-soared-before-first-reported-COVID-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;asia.nikkei.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government contracts show surges in Wuhan-area purchases starting May 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shots fired on AMTRAK train in AZ; 1 in custody...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amtrak-tucson-arizona-shootings-fc9d1467b21a8bb5a1cefc80594a94a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person is in custody after someone opened fire Monday aboard an Amtrak train in Tucson, Arizona, causing passengers to flee, police said. The shooting happened just after 8 a.m. on a train parked at the station in the city's downtown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-Right Writer Refused Entry to UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxn4d/rafal-ziemkiewicz-a-far-right-writer-was-refused-entry-to-the-uk-and-poland-is-freaking-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rafal Ziemkiewicz, who has been accused of anti-Semitic, Islamophobic and homophobic views, was denied entry to the UK. That’s sparked a wave of online abuse against a British MP who has previously called him out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA raids WASHINGTON FOOTBALL TEAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/sports/feds-searched-washington-football-team-training-facility-ryan-vermillion-dea/2820559/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators executed a search warrant at the Washington Football Team’s training facility and a nearby home on Friday, law enforcement sources tell News4. The team’s head athletic trainer is on leave because of an investigation, the team said.  Ryan Vermillion, the WFT’s director of sports medicine and head athletic trainer, is on leave, the team said in a brief…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH SCHOOLERS Training To Drive 18-Wheelers Amid Driver Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/teens-are-being-trained-to-drive-18-wheelers-amid-truck-driver-shortage-70302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside Edition visited student participants of Patterson High School who are participating in one of the first truck-driving programs for high schoolers in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNION STRIKES</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/iatse-strike-vote-result-1235079382/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The members of the International Association of Theatrical Stage Employees have voted to approve a strike authorization, giving the union president the power to shut down film and TV production acr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple Accidentally Buys Exorcist Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2021/09/27/honey-we-bought-the-exorcist-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would you want to live in the place that inspired a famous horror movie?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain implant lifts woman's severe depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencenews.org/article/brain-implant-severe-depression-activity-stimulation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencenews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An experimental device interrupts brain activity linked to a woman’s low mood. The technology, she said, has changed her lens on life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask mandates effective against delta? Not really...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/coronavirus/article/California-mask-mandates-delta-COVID-19-data-works-16502191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here is a breakdown comparing the course of the delta wave in notable California...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Post Office Be Bank? New Services Test Progressive Priority...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/return-postal-banking-postal-service-tests-new-financial-services-rcna2502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Postal banking may be making a comeback. The U.S. Postal Service will announce Monday that it has started testing a handful of new financial services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Shout Down Lindsey Graham for Pushing Jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/republicans-shout-down-lindsey-graham-for-pushing-vaccine/ar-AAP7zWK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC) was booed by Republican activists Saturday after he suggested they should consider taking the coronavirus vaccine, making him the latest prominent Republican to face a backlash from the party’s grassroots over the vaccine. Speaking at a county Republican event in Summerville, South Carolina, Graham said he had received the vaccine and encouraged audience members to take the vaccine as well. “If you haven’t had the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE DAY FACEBOOK GOES DOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/04/facebook-instagram-and-whatsapp-are-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Instagram and WhatsApp were offline on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING WARNS USA</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211004144313-afbyb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-China mounts largest incursion yet near Taiwan, blames U.S. for tensions</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
