<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NYU Cancels 'Reporting on Far Right' Class; Only 2 Students Enrolled...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/nyu-cancels-former-new-yorker-fact-checker-talia-lavins-journalism-class/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We cancelled it because too few students enrolled," says Adam Penenberg, director of undergraduate studies at NYU's Arthur L. Carter Journalism Institute</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA READY TO THREATEN MEX WITH TARIFFS...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-immigration-trump/trump-ready-to-threaten-mexico-with-tariffs-over-immigration-washington-post-idUKKCN1T01GQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump is preparing to threaten Mexico with tariffs to put ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Stepmom whipped 26-year-old stepson for missing curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/woman-reportedly-beat-her-26-year-old-stepson-for-coming-home-late/67-3de9af51-89ce-4e8c-a137-611ca5d3c9d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtsp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said she admitted to hitting him 30 times in the buttocks with a belt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodents run free at rat-infested bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/food/article/Rat-infested-pop-up-bar-to-open-in-San-Francisco-13907463.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same folks behind the San Francisco Dungeon at Fisherman’s Wharf are bringing a new pop-up to the city called the Rat Bar. The event will feature, among other things, an area where people can play with rodents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military testing fish as underwater spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/fish-spies-underwater-us-military-defence-trump-navy-a8936051.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600-lb drug dealer sentenced in ambulance backed up to loading dock...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/crime/crime-and-courts/2019/05/29/carthage-man-pleads-guilty-sentenced-inside-ambulance/1270100001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Moving Kirk Smith from the ambulance would endanger his health and well-being," the judge said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Girl Facing Child Porn Charges -- for Making Sex Vid of Herself...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/05/29/16-year-old-girl-sex-porn-child-court-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A finding of guilt would be an attack on the autonomy and self-ownership of all young people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA FINALS:  RAPTORS fan sets off fireworks at WARRIORS hotel at 3 am...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/warriors/article/warriors-st-regis-toronto-hotel-fireworks-13907356.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A misguided Toronto Raptors fan reportedly set off fireworks outside of the Warriors' team hotel at 3 a.m. in an attempt to rouse the team from its pre-NBA Finals slumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Found In Trunk Of Car At Auto Auction...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/05/30/man-found-trunk-car-manheim-auto-auction-northern-lancaster-county-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers processing the vehicle found the man Thursday at the Manheim Auto Auction facility, about 90 miles west of Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB attendance down -- again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6a7ffdc19830442fb968492024428e89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Tampa Bay Rays and Miami Marlins drew 12,653 Wednesday night — combined. Baltimore, Cincinnati, Minnesota and Tampa Bay set stadium lows this year. Kansas City had its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man builds fence around illegaly parked car-share vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/seattle-property-owner-holding-illegally-parked-car-to-go-vehicle-hostage-demanding-payment/953109205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Seattle property owner upset with a car share vehicle parked illegally in his driveway is now holding that car hostage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Biographer pens explosive report on MLK...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-news/biographer-garrow-pens-explosive-report-martin-luther-king/fqPKW1dndGA5g4oAkzRoIJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Luther King Jr. allegedly had sexual relations with at least 40 women, according to explosive new research published Thursday by historian David Garrow. The allegations were included in decades-old FBI files, formerly sealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Bullying increases chances of obesity...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/30/bullying-increases-chances-of-adult-obesity-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We know that adolescent bullying can have long-lasting effects on a child psychologically, but a new study in the journal Pediatric Obesity reveals that it can also negatively impact their health i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA Membership Dues, Contributions Rebounded...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/nra-membership-dues-contributions-rebounded-in-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association of America and its associated groups saw a sizable increase of both membership dues and contributions in 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F-35 Dogfight 'Accidentally' Results in Sky Penis...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/05/30/f-35-dogfight-accidentally-resulted-sky-penis-officials-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six F-35 Joint Strike Fighters simulating aggressor air training accidentally created contrails that resembled a penis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTV Unveils First 'Sexually Fluid' Reality Dating Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/mtv-reveals-first-sexually-fluid-reality-dating-show-1214412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The groundbreaking eighth season of the network's hit series 'Are You the One?' is set to premiere on June 26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Money Funding China Surveillance State...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/us-money-funding-facial-recognition-sensetime-megvii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of dollars from US university endowments, foundations, and retirement plans have helped fund two billion-dollar Chinese facial recognition startups: SenseTime and Megvii. The Chinese government is using their technologies to surveil and profile its own citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailing Dems angry over new debate rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.theolympian.com/news/politics-government/national-politics/article230987028.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theolympian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP MORGAN biggest-ever settlement in anti-dad bias case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/jpmorgan-agrees-to-biggest-ever-settlement-in-anti-dad-bias-case/ar-AAC8ZtT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last State Retirees Want To Live: New Jersey......</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/30/retirees-are-fleeing-these-3-states-in-droves.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether it's the traffic, the taxes or the snowstorms, more New Jersey residents have had it with the Garden State. Not only did New Jersey experience an outbound flight in 2018, 1 in 3 people leaving cited retirement as a primary driver, according to a survey from United Van Lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peace plan hopes dim...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/279a8c1163f24b44b59dcd2877d76464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — President Donald Trump's son-in-law and senior adviser Jared Kushner met with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Thursday to push the Trump administration's long-awaited...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top sheriff warns: Trump's 'done' if immigration isn't slashed...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/top-sheriff-warns-trumps-done-if-illegal-immigration-isnt-slashed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of America’s top sheriffs and supporter of President Trump is warning that if the administration doesn’t curb the explosion of illegal immigration across the southern border, the president will lose reelection in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most atheists believe in supernatural...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2204958-most-atheists-believe-in-the-supernatural-despite-trusting-science/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While atheists say they don't believe in a god, a survey has found that the majority hold at least one supernatural belief, such as life after death or reincarnation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border agents apprehend over 1,000 illegals in record round-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/border-agents-apprehended-over-1-000-immigrants-record-round-n1011956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most are from the Northern Triangle countries of Central America — El Salvador, Guatemala and Honduras — and included 63 children traveling alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RAMBO' AT 72: Stallone Debuts New Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/rambo-v-last-blood-trailer-sylvester-stallone-faces-his-past-watch-1214376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sylvester Stallone returns for part five his in iconic war/action franchise that opens Sept. 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Trump set for Iowa showdown with simultaneous visits...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2019/05/30/joe-biden-plans-june-visit-iowa-campaign-donald-trump-caucus-election/1282027001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the former vice president's second visit to Iowa since he declared his bid for president. He will visit the same day Trump is in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI BALKS ON IMPEACHMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/29/politics/democrats-mueller-reaction-congress-impeachment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and House Judiciary Chairman Jerry Nadler resisted pressure from the left to open an impeachment inquiry on Wednesday, following special counsel Robert Mueller's announcement he's closing his office and would not provide information beyond his already public report in any appearance before Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMON &amp; SCHUSTER drops Tony Robbins...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/katiejmbaker/tony-robbins-latest-book-has-been-scrapped</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Simon &amp; Schuster dropped the book after BuzzFeed News revealed the self-help guru has berated victims of rape and domestic abuse, and former fans and staffers have accused him of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor who correctly predicted 9 elections says Trump in 2020, unless... </title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/446136-professor-who-has-correctly-predicted-nine-presidential-elections-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American University professor who has correctly predicted the last nine presidential elections says President Trump will win the 2020 election unless congressional Democrats, “grow a spine,”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Biggest threats are economic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biggest-threats-trump-election-110013193.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are signs, however, that the economy may be headed for a repeat of the slowdown that preceded the 2016 election — and which almost certainly contributed to the Democrats’ loss of the White House. Prediction models that measure the eagerness of voters for change based on economic conditions and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Huge Shark Circles Woman Off FL Beach...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/30/video-shark-checks-out-swimmer-florida-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman swimming off the shoreline of Panama City Beach got a bit too close for comfort to a pretty big shark and someone in a nearby hotel captured the close encounter on video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Hillary blisters Trump during commencement address as grads zone out, yawn...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-hillary-blisters-trump-during-commencement-address-as-grads-zone-out-yawn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When is the mainstream media just going to treat Hillary Clinton like a presidential candidate-in-waiting? The failed 2016 Democrat nominee blistered President Trump to a group of college graduates on Wednesday, underscoring she’s thinking about politics as students are hoping for a positive message to send them out to their careers. ﻿ Speaking to graduates …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45 minutes after leaving jail, man robs 91-year-old woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/nation-world/national/article230980488.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana salmon hatchery to raise first genetically modified animal cleared for human consumption...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-genetically-modified-salmon-indiana-hatchery-20190502-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say GMO animals will likely be necessary to feed the world’s growing population, but others are fearful about what might end up on their dinner plate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP Revised Lower; Corporate Profits Tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-05-30/q2-gdp-revised-lower-30-corporate-profits-tumble-most-three-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Predatory Malibu Rehab Guru Who Ripped Off Obamacare...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/christopher-bathum-the-predatory-malibu-rehab-guru-who-ripped-off-obamacare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While running one of the nation’s most high-profile rehab centers, Christopher Bathum was busy as a sexual predator, an alleged insurance fraudster, and a phony psychotherapist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREEP: TERM 'TOXIC MASCULINITY' HARMFUL TO BOYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/meryl-streep-toxic-masculinity-big-little-lies-season-2-qa-talk-a8936156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mecca to host summits focused on Iran tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190530-mecca-host-three-summits-focused-iran-tensions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mecca to host three summits focused on Iran tensions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Biggest Threats to Trump Re-Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2019-05-30/trump-2020-not-all-economic-indicators-point-to-his-re-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Levees strained...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d8f92dd1d84548769987d9cb2e3c9ba2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT SMITH, Ark. (AP) — The Arkansas River held steady at record levels Thursday morning, putting enormous pressure on aging levees and offering little relief to areas enduring historic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing set over imperiled Missouri clinic... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/05ac6edea1974dd0b1d5f615178b95d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS (AP) — A hearing is scheduled in a St. Louis court Thursday on an effort by the only abortion clinic in Missouri to retain its license after the state raised concerns about care...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Will 'ROCKETMAN' Soar at Box Office?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/05/rocketman-movie-review-box-office-elton-john-taron-egerton-runtime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for liftoff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TWEET DELETE...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-deletes-tweet-admitting-russia-helped-him-get-elected-while-lashing-out-at-mueller/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evidenced by his Twitter feed, President Donald Trump woke up Thursday morning with Special Counsel Robert Mueller -- and his stunning nine-minute press conference -- very much on his mind. In a remarkable development, however, it appears that Trump is publicly admitting, for the first time at least, that Russia interference helped get him elected president, as has been stated repeatedly by numerous U.S. intel and Justice Department investigations, including the office of Special Counsel. That is until he deleted the tweet. Here are the screenshots of the tweets in which Trump says he "had nothing to do with Russia helping me get elected." While Mueller, in his press conference on Wednesday, mostly reiterated much of what was in his 400+ page report into the investigation into Russian interference into the 2016 general election, there were a few eyebrow-raising moments. Mueller made clear that if he was certain that Trump had not committed crimes, he would have said as much. He also</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puncture?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/782137/international-space-station-satellite-nasa-india-struck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK robots to scan faces, judge emotional state...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7085789/Facebook-wants-send-emotional-robots-explore-scan-faces-help-users-make-friends.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept was outlined in a European patent filed on May 16, 2019. Each machine would be equipped with cameras to allow them to assess the 'likely emotional state' of people they encounter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer algorithm reopens dozens of cold cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/51636cba5e0b43d6b84a56be34d9ac9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The bodies turned up in some of Chicago's most derelict places: alleys, abandoned buildings, weed-choked lots and garbage containers. The victims were mostly black women who had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RASMUSSEN: BIDEN 33% SANDERS 15% WARREN 7% HARRIS 6%...</title>
      <link>https://scottrasmussen.com/democratic-primary-polling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scottrasmussen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the first Democratic debates just a month away, former Vice President Joe Biden remains the clear frontrunner in the race for the right to challenge President Trump in 2020.  A ScottRasmussen.com national survey of Democratic voters and Democratic leaning Independents found that Biden is the first choice for 33%. Senator Bernie Sanders is still his closest challenger at 15% followed by Senator Elizabeth Warren at 7% and Senator Kamala Harris at 6%.These top four candidates are in the same order and generally the same position as in our previous two surveys (earlier in May and April).  Data released</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISS faces mounting threat from satellite junk...</title>
      <link>http://tass.com/science/1060628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India’s PM said in a televised address to the nation on March 27 that the country’s Air Force had successfully tested its own anti-satellite weapon, shooting down a satellite in low near-Earth orbit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Child 'falls 30 feet off rollercoaster'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9185031/lightwater-valley-twister-theme-park-accident-news/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A YOUNG boy was today airlifted to hospital after apparently falling 30ft from a rollercoaster. Stunned eyewitnesses reported seeing the youngster – believed to be aged between four and six &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PET SEMATARY' cat dies mysteriously weeks after film release...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9184746/pet-sematary-star-leo-the-cat-dies-mysteriously-just-weeks-after-films-release/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE furry star of the 2019 remake of Pet Sematary has died just weeks after the movie was released. Leo the Cat captured audiences’ hearts in the film adaptation of Stephen King’s 1983 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moneyball for Cattle Creating American Steak Renaissance...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/moneyball-cattle-creating-american-steak-090014061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Reliance is a black Angus bull with a long, fluid stride. He has a quiet confidence when he walks. It’s one of the qualities that led cattlemen to bid up the prized animal to $150,000 during a recent bull sale at Woodhill Farms in Viroqua, Wisconsin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUBS Player Breaks Down In Tears After Line-Drive Foul Strikes 4-Year-Old Girl...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/05/29/foul-ball-hit-by-cubs-albert-almora-jr-hits-young-child-almora-jr-shaken/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Cubs player Albert Almora Jr. hit a hard line-drive foul into the stands at Wednesday's game against the Astros, striking a child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavily processed food linked to early death...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/may/29/studies-link-too-much-heavily-processed-food-to-early-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two major studies add to body of evidence against foods made with industrial ingredients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury Over Rapper Calling to 'Kill White People'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/europe/201905301075472395-rapper-burn-france/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French self-produced rapper of Cameroonian origin Nick Conrad did not enjoy much interest before he entered the spotlight with a music video titled “Hang White People”; however, shortly after a trial over the notorious clip, he released another creation that featured him strangling a white woman, apparently representing France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Dating Apps Targeting Americans Expose 42.5 Million Records Online...</title>
      <link>https://securitydiscovery.com/chinese-dating-apps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;securitydiscovery.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers found a non password protected database that contained millions of dating app records. Read more about the Chinese dating app data leak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cameras and crackdowns: Another Tiananmen 'impossible'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cameras-crackdowns-another-tiananmen-impossible-china-050223645.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty years after the crackdown on Tiananmen protesters, the tanks that lined Beijing's central avenue have been replaced by countless surveillance cameras perched like hawks on lampposts to keep the population in check. The Chinese Communist Party has gone to great lengths to prevent another pro-democracy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING CEO on 737 MAX problems: 'We clearly fell short'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/boeing-ceo-dennis-muilenburg-says-he-would-put-his-family-737-max-without-any-hesitation-exclusive-2019-05-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing CEO Dennis Muilenburg spoke with Norah O'Donnell in an exclusive interview for the first time since two deadly crashes grounded the 737 Max</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMY 'Google Earth On Steroids' Can Look  Inside Buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-05-28/armys-google-earth-steroids-can-look-inside-buildings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stuck' weather pattern fuels month of Mayhem....</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/05/29/tornadoes-stuck-weather-pattern-brings-month-mayhem/1273501001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "stuck" weather pattern has produced a month of stormy mayhem across the central USA, one that's fueled hundreds of tornadoes and boatloads of rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife of man killed in Hawaii shark attack: 'He went out for one last swim'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article230917393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REMATCH:  Despite Warning From Trump, Roy Moore Says He Can Win Alabama Senate Seat... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/29/roy-moore-hits-back-at-trump-in-defiant-interview-1487921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial former judge says the president &amp;quot;doesn't control&amp;quot; Alabama voters, and he can win despite Trump's opposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER bans passengers with low ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/05/29/728005817/uber-to-start-banning-passengers-with-low-ratings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Respect is a two-way street, and so is accountability," a company official announced. Riders will get advice on how to improve their ratings before being deactivated, including being polite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI BALKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article230951583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The dam has burst'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article230956313.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district to become first to use facial recognition technology...</title>
      <link>https://www.lockportjournal.com/news/local_news/lockport-to-test-new-school-safety-system-next-week/article_159eff1c-74f1-5490-83ac-1ba1c5123ab9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lockportjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockport City School District will begin testing its new facial and object recognition system next week, Superintendent Michelle Bradley announced Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL UNPRECEDENTED REPEAT ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Elections-set-for-Sept-17-after-coalition-talks-fail-591044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactly one month after the 21st Knesset were sworn in, a majority of the Knesset voted late Wednesday to disperse themselves and initiate an unprecedented repeat election on September 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY IGER: 'Very Difficult' to Work in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/bob-iger-very-difficult-disney-work-georgia-new-abortion-law-enacted-1214329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has filmed blockbuster movies in the state such as 'Black Panther' and 'Avengers: Endgame.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Makes Texas play...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/05/29/dallas-mayor-mike-rawlings-endorsesjoe-biden-president-spurning-beto-orourke-julian-castro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas Mayor Mike Rawlings is backing Joe Biden for president, saying the nation needs someone who will beat Donald Trump in 2020.Job No. 1 is to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military doomsday plane can endure aftermath of nuke blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/29/us-military-doomsday-plane-can-withstand-aftermath-of-nuclear-blast.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The modified Boeing 747 is born and bred for battle, standing nearly six stories tall, equipped with four colossal engines and capable of enduring the immediate aftermath of a nuclear detonation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Mexicans Arrested Crossing -- Canadian Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/05/29/four-mexican-migrants-arrested-in-vermont-after-crossing-canadian-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swanton Sector Border Patrol agents and a K-9 arrested four Mexican nationals who illegally crossed the Canadian border into Vermont.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA passenger mauled by emotional support dog files lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/business/delta-passenger-mauled-emotional-support-dog-files-lawsuit/EVZblhoh7JXtDtu4k19GxN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who was attacked by another passenger's emotional support dog on a flight has sued Delta Air Lines and the other passenger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu's future in turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-hold-elections-netanyahu-apos-213023687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli leader couldn’t cobble together a coalition government within the allotted six weeks, which expired Wednesday night. Elections were set for Sept. 17. “Elections are like wars,” said Shmuel Sandler, a political science professor at Bar-Ilan University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rain intensifies flooding in saturated Arkansas, Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2e3e7bb59268450ebdb214e9d469d13c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT SMITH, Ark. (AP) — Brad Hindley planned to be vacationing on a lake this week. Instead, he's been on a boat in his swamped Fort Smith neighborhood trying to keep gas in generators that are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuels Impeachment Push...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/251faa8cfa8347438b6513e65d34ab62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller's first — and possibly last — public statement on the Russia investigation is fueling fresh calls on Capitol Hill to begin impeachment proceedings...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabid bat hiding in iPad attacks senior...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/south-hampton-man-bit-by-bat-hiding-in-his-ipad-case/27617219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Hampton man is on the mend after a bat somehow got inside his home and bit him last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!  Bernie backers see DNC-media sabotage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/29/bernie-sanders-supporters-distrust-joe-biden-poll-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For hardcore Bernie Sanders supporters, Joe Biden’s early domination of the race smacks of 2016, when the Democratic National Committee attempted to sabotage Mr. Sanders and clear the way to the nomination for Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's smallest newborn who weighed same as an APPLE survives birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/9181959/worlds-smallest-baby-survives-saybie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MIRACLE baby thought to be the world’s tiniest newborn at 8.6oz survived despite her parents being warned she’d only live for an hour, it was revealed last night. The little girl, nam…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal prosecutors demand Cindy Yang records from Mar-a-Lago, Trump campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article230946518.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski's Wife Takes Aim at Tarantino Over 'HOLLYWOOD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/roman-polanskis-wife-criticizes-tarantino-including-husband-once-a-time-hollywood-1213976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish actor Rafał Zawierucha plays Polanski in Tarantino's film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sets himself on fire outside White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7083457/Man-sets-fire-seen-engulfed-flames-near-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man set himself on fire Wednesday near the White House, the Secret Service said. He was taken to hospital with 'life threatening injuries' after suffering burns to 85% of his body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese video urges war with USA...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/chinese-video-urges-war-with-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Communist Party-controlled media stepped up a war of words with the United States recently urging an escalation of the trade dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER RETIRES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/94323cfc164c4759ba6bf84ad2a46203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller said Wednesday that charging President Donald Trump with a crime was "not an option" because of federal rules, but he used his first public remarks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGING TRUMP 'NOT OPTION'</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-counsel-robert-mueller-make-statement-amid-democratic/story?id=63344952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller said Wednesday he does not intend to testify as Democrats want, says charging Trump with a crime was "not an option."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHTMARE:  Man lifts toilet seat and is bitten by python snake rising from bowl...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/toiletsnake-attacks-189536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 29--As a Florida Man lifted the toilet seat in his bathroom early Sunday morning, a four-foot ball python “rose out of the toilet and bit him” on the arm, according to a police report brimming w</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana Democrat Governor Set to Sign Strict Abortion Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/baton_rouge/news/politics/legislature/article_203ff9f8-80ba-11e9-b1d1-af1136fb73ae.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana lawmakers have approved a bill that would ban abortions at about six weeks of pregnancy, if upheld by the courts, sending it to the governor's desk without exceptions for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot summer ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/05/robert-mueller-press-conference-impeachment-politics-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel just upped the pressure on those in the party who think impeaching Trump is politically ill-advised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key differences with Barr...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Mueller-s-statement-highlights-key-differences-13905087.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Departing special counsel Robert Mueller finally spoke publicly Wednesday, and his carefully chosen comments highlight the ways in which he disagrees with his boss, Attorney General William Barr, about the facts and the law surrounding the investigation into President Donald Trump.  "If we had confidence that the president clearly did not commit a crime, we would have said that," Mueller said Wednesday.  Barr had that confidence. He declared in March that while Mueller's principal conclusions did not include a determination of whether the president had committed the crime of obstruction of justice, Barr had reviewed the evidence and concluded that Trump did not break the law.  "The Special Counsel's decision to describe the facts of his obstruction investigation without reaching any legal conclusions leaves it to the Attorney General to determine whether the conduct described in the report constitutes a crime," Barr wrote to Congress at the time.  In his report and his public remarks, Mueller indicated that he holds a different view on the question of potential presidential crimes, refusing to clear Trump and alluding to Congress' impeachment power as the constitutional arbiter.  Mueller's remarks also made clear how heavily his office relied on a long-standing legal opinion from the Justice Department's Office of Legal Counsel that a sitting president cannot be indicted. That opinion, Mueller said Wednesday, "says that the Constitution requires a process other than the criminal justice system to formally accuse a sitting president of wrongdoing."  Asked about his disagreements with Mueller, Barr has made a point of emphasizing that when the two men met privately on March 5 to discuss the findings, Mueller said he would not say the president would have been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare color footage brings D-Day memories alive...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/europe/2019/05/rare-color-footage-brings-d-day-memories-alive-75-years-on/slide/9/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprising color images bring an immediacy to wartime memories</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python leaps out of toilet to bite man...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/coral-springs/fl-ne-coral-springs-snake-attack-20190528-togijbdkvvgspd2nfjptngzsh4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Florida, beware of creatures that may lurk in the toilet bowl. A 52-year-old man opened the seat of his toilet and found a ball python, which bit him. (On the arm, not on the ... well, you know.)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana Democrat Governor Set to Sign Strict Abortion Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/politics/2019/05/louisiana-lawmakers-pass-a-strict-ban-on-abortion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana lawmakers pass a strict ban on abortion as early as six weeks of pregnancy, without rape or incest exceptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange health 'deteriorating', moved to prison hospital wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7084541/Julian-Assange-moved-hospital-wing-Belmarsh-prison-losing-weight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement, WikiLeaks said: 'WikiLeaks has grave concerns about the state of health of our publisher, Julian Assange, who has been moved to the health ward of Belmarsh prison.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing leads to censoring political satire, dissent?</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/613592/facebook-pelosi-video-misinformation-censorship-free-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking down the ‘drunk ’ Pelosi video could set a precedent for censoring political satire or dissent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER SLAPS PRESIDENT ON WAY OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/robert-mueller-make-public-statement-about-russia-probe-wednesday-n1011331?DFds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel, speaking publicly for the first time, said in a statement that he was bound by Justice Department policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD NOT CLEAR HIM OF OBSTRUCTION!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-mueller-says-hes-not-confident-that-trump-did-not-commit-a-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller finally made a public statement today, weeks after finishing his investigation and his report––with redactions––was made available to the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V I D E O</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?461196-1/special-counsel-robert-mueller-make-statement-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PODHORETZ: Disgraceful Mess...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/29/muellers-final-statement-was-a-disgraceful-mess/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special prosecutor Robert Mueller’s statement upon the shuttering of his two-year investigation into the Trump campaign was weird even by the standards of the weirdness of the past couple of years.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER RETIRES</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/latest-white-house-says-told-mueller-might-speak-141544632--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on special counsel Robert Mueller and the Russia investigation (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOSES OFFICE</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mueller-first-public-statement-russia-135537084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If we had had confidence the president clearly did not commit a crime we would have said so,” Mueller said in his first public remarks in the two years since he was named special counsel. The special counsel also said he found “insufficient evidence to charge a broader conspiracy” on election interference</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
