<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NATO to toughen G7 message on China despite Beijing's cries of 'slander'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/nato-welcomes-biden-pivotal-post-trump-summit-2021-06-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO leaders are expected to brand China a security risk to the Western alliance on Monday, a day after the Group of Seven rich nations issued a statement on human rights in China and Taiwan that Beijing said slandered its reputation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane center monitors tropical disturbances by Gulf, Carolinas...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-hurricane-center-tropical-storm-sunday-update-20210613-rjyygh6hojhk7c76rrs3z4svlq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meteorologists are tracking two tropical disturbances in the Gulf of Mexico and North Carolina coastlines, with potential of becoming the next tropical depression or storm by next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercar maker experimenting with volcano fuel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/autos/news/koenigsegg-the-maker-of-243-million-supercars-experiments-with-volcano-fuel/ar-AAL151k </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans can reproduce on Mars as scientists discover sperm survives in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/proof-humans-can-reproduce-mars-24313557</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scientific experiment involving mice has found that sperm can survive on Mars and in space, something previously thought to be impossible and a major barrier to life on other planets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA crew subdue unruly off-duty flight attendant...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/12/us/delta-unruly-passenger-flight-diverted/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An off-duty Delta Air Lines flight attendant apparently commandeered the intercom on an Atlanta-bound flight Friday night, leading to a scuffle that forced the plane to land in Oklahoma City, an airline spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Heat wave to bring days of dangerous temps across west...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/exceptional-western-us-heat-wave-to-bring-days-of-dangerously-high-temperatures/961965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One city may top its all-time record high for June while another traditionally toasty city endures a potentially historic stretch of 115-degree heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five big upcoming Supreme Court decisions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/558102-five-big-upcoming-supreme-court-decisions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court is poised for a whirlwind end of term, with justices expected to clear the court’s docket of more than 20 pending cases before July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden prepares to confront Putin...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/558083-biden-prepares-to-confront-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin in Geneva this week marks the latest chapter in a highly adversarial relationship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI OUT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-middle-east-israel-26478abe63c32f0d22a2c27029a8ce68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — For the first time in 12 years, Israelis on Monday woke up to a new government and a new prime minister, after Naftali Bennett secured the backing of parliament and ousted longtime leader Benjamin Netanyahu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops investigate 'apparent suicide' of TV anchor who wrote Clinton expose...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3070657/alabama-football-player-anchor-christopher-sign-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHRISTOPHER Sign, an award-winning TV news anchor who wrote a 2016 exposé on Bill Clinton, has died. Local police chief Keith Czeskleba said on Saturday the death is being investigated as a suicide…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala 'annoyed Secret Service agents at Pride parade'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3069469/kamala-harris-visits-pride-dc-refuses-visit-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KAMALA Harris “annoyed Secret Service agents” during a surprise appearance at a Pride parade after refusing the visit the southern border. George Conway pointed out that the vice presid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Has Local News Collapsed? Readers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/06/12/local-news-demand-493495 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite all the impassioned pleas to salvage local news coverage, the reality is there’s a demand-side problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists issue UK warning: July will be horror month...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/health/health-problems/scientists-issue-warning-that-uk-could-see-100000-daily-covid-cases-by-july/news-story/6eb043015cee1bc3130e42f27555ec73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have issued a stark warning that the Covid-19 variant known as Delta is shaping up to cause devastation in the UK as soon as July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Discovery Highlights How Jews, Christians Were Once Naughty with Magic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-discovery-highlights-how-jews-and-christians-were-once-naughty-with-magic/ar-AAKZHt1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli Antiquities Authority recently released an announcement about their acquisition of an ancient magical amulet, reportedly from Arbel in Northern Israel, that bears the Divine Name of God. The fifth-sixth century CE magical device, which was worn to ward off evil, was apparently found at the site of an ancient synagogue. The discovery is making waves because—in popular understandings at least—ancient Jews were not supposed to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bennett: Tech millionaire son of Berkeley 'left-wingers' poised to take over...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/naftali-bennett-the-tech-millionaire-son-of-berkeley-left-wingers-who-is-poised-to-take-over-from-israel-s-benjamin-netanyahu/ar-AAKL5lb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naftali Bennett is a software tycoon with hard-right nationalist views, a controversial military career, and an anti-Arab track record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians call for day of rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/palestinians-call-for-day-of-rage-to-combat-jerusalem-flag-march-670892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamas has demanded that its supporters come to Temple Mount and the streets of Jerusalem's Old City for a "day of rage" to demonstrate against Tuesday's Jerusalem flag march.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lapid: From TV anchor to coalition architect...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210613-israel-s-lapid-from-tv-anchor-to-coalition-architect</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's Lapid: from TV anchor to coalition architect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board members calls for 'jihad' at high school graduation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/dem-tells-high-school-grads-theyre-entering-capitalism-white-supremacy-remember-jihad-reject-objectivity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A school board member gave a graduation speech in which she told a mainly-immigrant class of high schoolers that they were entering a world filled with Fairfax County school board member Abrar Omeish told a mainly-immigrant class of high school gradautes that they were entering a world filled with &amp;quot;racism, extreme versions of individualism and capitalism, [and] white supremacy,&amp;quot; and encouraged them to remember their &amp;quot;jihad&amp;quot; and reject the concepts of objectivity and neutrality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid 'alarm' can SMELL if someone has infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9681391/Covid-alarm-SMELL-infection-Device-detect-virus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The device, by Cambridgeshire-based RoboScientific, detects chemical changes in the skin and breath of Covid-infected people and could analyse the air in a room in as little as 15 minutes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos in Manhattan: Volent mob runs riot again...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9680831/Man-raves-blighting-Washington-Square-Park-NYC-says-fed-residents-move.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The park saw two people stabbed, one man mugged and an elderly cook shoved against a plate glass window in the early hours of Saturday alone, amid spiraling crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After historically deadly 2020, Atlanta homicides up 60%...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/after-historically-deadly-2020-atlanta-homicides-are-up-nearly-60-in-2021/N63RJ5OKQZCZVOCNH2D6376S3E/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta police have investigated 63 homicide cases in 2021, a 58% increase over this time last year. The surge follows a historically deadly 2020, when authorities investigated 157 homicide cases — the most in more than two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemonium at Washington Square Park...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/12/violence-and-chaos-continues-to-overrun-washington-square-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violence continued to spiral out of control on Saturday in and around Washington Square Park, where anti-cop graffiti was scrawled on its arch, a man was beaten and robbed of his cellphon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Lobsterman's whale of tale sounds fishy, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/12/cape-cod-lobstermans-whale-of-a-tale-sounds-fishy-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one doctor at the Cape Cod hospital that Michael Packard, who claims he was nearly swallowed by a humpback, expressed skepticism to The Post about the tale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING:  Small groups do not rule world...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/g7-summit-china-says-small-074738447.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The G7 leaders, who are meeting in England, have sought a unified position over China's rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI ON THE BRINK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-iran-nuclear-health-coronavirus-pandemic-deea22832a1cb2d95736f342958083fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel's parliament approved a new coalition government on Sunday that sent Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu into the opposition after a record 12 years in office and a political crisis that sparked four elections in two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rash of mass shootings stirs summer fears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-gun-politics-shootings-health-3a38e35db46f4b3b76af3ed566e47c0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Two people were killed and at least 30 others wounded in mass shootings overnight in three states, authorities said Saturday, stoking concerns that a spike in U.S. gun violence could continue into summer as coronavirus restrictions ease and more people are free to socialize.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
