<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pence cancels political events...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Pence-cancels-some-political-events-because-of-15371360.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) - Vice President Mike Pence called off campaign events in Florida and Arizona this coming week as the states experience a surge in new coronavirus cases.  Pence will still travel to those states, which have set records for new confirmed infections in recent days, the White House confirmed, saying he will meet with governors and their health teams.  Pence said Friday during a briefing by the White House's coronavirus task force that he would be visiting Florida, Texas and Arizona to receive a "ground report" on spiking cases of COVD-19 across the region. The three states' Republican governors have come under criticism for pushing for aggressive reopening after virus-related lockdowns as cases in the states rise.  Pence is traveling to Dallas on Sunday to attend a "Celebrate Freedom Rally" at First Baptist Church Dallas before meeting with Texas Gov. Greg Abbott. But planned political events later in the week have been pushed off.  On Tuesday, Pence was supposed to address a Trump-Pence campaign "Faith in America" event in Tuscon, Arizona, before meeting Gov. Doug Ducey in Yuma. The campaign event has been postponed.  In Florida on Thursday, Pence was to embark on a bus tour, including an appearance in Lake Wales at an event organized by the pro-Trump group America First Policies billed as the "Great American Comeback tour." The group announced that "out of an abundance of caution at this time, we are postponing the Great American Comeback tour stop in Florida. We look forward to rescheduling soon."  The Sarasota County Republican Party confirmed in a note to supporters that Pence's campaign event along the Gulf Coast of the state was also postponed. He was still set to meet with Gov. Ron DeSantis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House denies knowledge...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jun/27/russia-offered-bounties-afghanistan-militants-killing-us-soldiers-report-outrage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fierce response from top Democrats after US intelligence finding was reportedly briefed to Trump in March, but the White House has yet to act</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BATTLE OVER MARY BOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lawyer-for-robert-trump-says-mary-trumps-tell-all-book-violates-decades-old-nda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Trump’s attorney Charles Harder said Mary Trump signed a confidentiality agreement that prohibits her from writing a book about the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRUNI:  Biden's Best Veep Pick Is Obvious...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/06/27/opinion/sunday/tammy-duckworth-biden-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She, more than anyone, can get under Trump’s skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Russia Secretly Offered Bounties to Kill US Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-secretly-offered-afghan-militants-bounties-to-kill-troops-us-intelligence-says/ar-BB160RXX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White voters on fence?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-god-guns-and-trump-country-simmering-doubts-about-the-president/ar-BB162YvD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED STATES RISK</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/with-trump-leading-the-way-america-s-coronavirus-failures-exposed-by-record-surge-in-new-infections/ar-BB162SAS?li=BBnb4R7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOS ANGELES 'CRITICAL' </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/la-county-faces-critical-moment-as-coronavirus-cases-keep-surging/ar-BB162AQ5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida reports 9,585 new cases, setting ANOTHER daily record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/florida-reports-9585-new-coronavirus-cases-setting-a-daily-record-in-statewide-surge/ar-BB162LNF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bats carry but don't get sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/coronavirus/coronavirus-covid19-bats-immune-inflammation-bucknell-20200627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These nocturnal flying mammals might hold the key to fighting the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:   3 dead after drinking hand sanitizer; 4th permanently blinded...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/27/us/new-mexico-hand-sanitizer-deaths-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An additional three people are in critical condition. "All seven people are believed to have drunk hand sanitizer containing methanol," health officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duckworth!</title>
      <link>https://twnews.us/us-news/tammy-duckworth-is-biden-s-best-running-mate-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twnews.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen to This Op-EdAudio Recording by AudmTo hear more audio stories from publishers like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android.Whatever his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measures to protect  scale up...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/06/26/politics/donald-trump-coronavirus-protocols/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump appears ready to move on from a still-raging coronavirus pandemic -- skipping the first White House task force briefing in months and moving the event out of the White House itself. But the measures meant to protect him from catching the virus have scaled up dramatically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC reveals three new virus symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1047021/cdc-three-new-coronavirus-symptoms-diarrhea-runny-nose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has revealed three new coronavirus symptoms including diarrhea and runny nose. Congestion or runny nose, nausea and diarrhea were added to the wide ra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyacht linked to Epstein 'madam' Ghislaine Maxwell spotted in New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1026384/superyacht-ghislaine-maxwell-new-zealand-epsteins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SUPERYACHT previously named after the fugitive socialite Ghislaine Maxwell has been spotted in New Zealand after sailing from Australia. But the mystery of her whereabouts remains after the crew …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK has become hotbed for pimple poppers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/1047472/tiktok-has-become-a-hotbed-for-pimple-poppers-and-these-videos-will-make-you-squirm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FROM squeezing whiteheads to bursting cysts, the latest trend on TikTok is so disgusting that you’ll have a hard time watching it without being sick. Desperate to rack up the likes, people ar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who led protests against stay-at-home... tests positive!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/27/politics/reopen-maryland-tim-walters-coronavirus/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The co-founder of a Maryland group that protested the state's stay-at-home order and has pressured Republican Gov. Larry Hogan to ease restrictions amid the ongoing coronavirus pandemic says he has tested positive for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consideres his illness a spiritual challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.capitalgazette.com/coronavirus/ac-cn-tim-walters-coronavirus-20200626-5l3epvbptng4dn4ys5btb5zika-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capitalgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A co-founder of the ReOpen Maryland movement has said on social media that he tested positive for coronavirus this week but won’t work with public health officials trying to track the spread of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONES THREATEN TO SUE OVER RALLY ANTHEM...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/rolling-stones-trump-rallies-bmi-stop-use-cant-always-get-what-you-want-1234692381/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, it has seemed as if Donald Trump can always get what he wants, at least when it comes to using classic rock and pop hits at his campaign rallies against the wishes of the original artist…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE IN RURAL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c48b10419a28caec8012b0c65244424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many states and counties in the U.S., the dark days of the coronavirus pandemic in April unfolded on their television screens, not on their doorsteps. But now, some places that appeared to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADER JOE'S CUSTOMER GOES NUTS OVER FACE MASKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/06/27/trader-joes-customer-goes-nuts-over-face-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Trader Joe's was the backdrop for an explosion of anger by a customer who felt it was her right to shop without a face mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tale of a global debt crisis foretold...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/504842-the-tale-of-a-global-debt-crisis-foretold</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hopefully the world’s economic policymakers do not have their heads in the sand about the risk of a real economic crisis in Italy and Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange County Dems call for John Wayne Airport to be renamed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/orange-county-democrats-condemn-racist-130011889.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic Party of Orange County officials passed an emergency resolution condemning film legend John Wayne's "racist and bigoted statements" and calling for an airport name change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA, ARIZONA PEAK</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200627153137-mpr6i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Florida, Arizona hit daily highs for COVID-19 cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSPITAL STRAIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ee2b6a57f5ce03ea0279597487457ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — They saw the ominous photos: Crowded hospitals, exhausted nurses, bodies piling up in morgues. It was far away, in New York, northern Italy and other distant places. Now,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to wear: Feds' mixed messages sow confusion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26f0cb8ed836a76f0e019357cbea7f58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forgive the American people if they're in a fog about face masks. President Donald Trump and the federal government have done a number on them. First there was the don't-do-it phase. Then...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Rhythm Coming From Another Galaxy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/06/fast-radio-burst-rhythm-pattern/613369/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers have been tracking fast radio bursts for years, but they’ve never caught one like this before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump increasingly concerned about how would appear if sick...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/922478/trump-reportedly-grown-increasingly-concerned-about-how-appear-contracted-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publicly, President Trump has appeared undaunted by the coronavirus. He mostly refuses to wear a mask in public, eschewing federal guidelines, and has recently held large campaign rallies in states where the pandemic is really just taking off. But privately the president is reportedly concerned about contracting COVID-19, primarily because he's aware of how it would affect both the country's view of him and his ability to lead, CNN reports. So, despite Trump's more casual attitude while he's speaking to crowds and posting on Twitter, the White House has gone to great lengths to make sure the commander-in-chief doesn't get infected. Every venue he enters while traveling is first inspected by advance security and medical teams, bathrooms designated for his use are scrubbed and sanitized before his arrival, and staff maintain a close eye on whom he'll come into contact with to make sure they get tested prior to any sort of meeting, people familiar with the matter told CNN. So far, the practice has worked out for the president, although several campaign aides and Secret Service personnel recently tested positive. But, per CNN, some of Trump's advisers and allies have become more and more concerned that he is publicly moving on from the pandemic too soon, a decision that seems all the more paradoxical considering how watchful the White House is behind the scenes. Read more at CNN. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark days inside the cinema business...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/922063/dark-days-inside-cinema-business</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can Hollywood survive without theaters?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER FLORIDA PEAK</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcmiami.com/news/local/florida-again-sets-daily-record-for-new-coronavirus-cases-with-more-than-9500/2254792/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcmiami.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida once again shattered its daily record for new coronavirus cases Saturday with more than 9,500 confirmed, pushing the state’s total to more than 132,500 as cases continued to rise rapidly in the state. The 9,585 new COVID-19 cases brought the state’s total to 132,545, according to figures released by the Florida Department of Health. Saturday’s total comes just one…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archbishop of Canterbury says Jesus 'shouldn't be portrayed as white'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/archbishop-canterbury-says-jesus-shouldnt-22263022?d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Most Revd Justin Welby insists the church must not ignore the Black Lives Matter movement after the death of George Floyd and that some statues "will have to come down"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tribe of monkeys in epic dead of night jailbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/marauding-monkeys-epic-jailbreak-tribe-22246387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zookeepers were furious doing their morning inspection to find their clever primates had gone. They'd outwitted them and cleverly made a bid for freedom from their locked enclosure in a jailbreak as epic as classic movie The Great Escape</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Set for Pardon?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/06/26/roger-stone-asks-trump-for-pardon-or-commutation-after-court-rules-he-must-report-to-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday on Fox Business Network's "Lou Dobbs Tonight," former Trump adviser Roger Stone reacted to a U.S. District Court ruling he must report on July 14 for his prison sentence. Stone likened the possibility of being incarcerated to a "death sentence," given the threat of COVID-19. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas mayor orders curfew...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200627140034-372cx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (PIX):Texas mayor orders curfew, as states hard-hit by COVID-19 backtrack on reopening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi could strip Confederate symbol from state flag... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fdb1408a077b4988a71be339e4c94c2e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — Mississippi lawmakers could vote in the next few days to remove the Confederate battle emblem from the state flag, a symbol that has come under intensifying criticism in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA 'likely' to see shortage of drugs if outbreak continues...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/us-shortage-pharmaceutical-drugs-coronavirus-outbreak-continues-intelligence/story?id=71487474</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decrease in generic drugs would hurt low-income and unemployed Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Summer Implodes as 'MULAN' and 'TENET' Delayed...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2020/06/27/hollywoods-summer-implodes-as-mulan-and-tenet-delayed-to-august/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With reported cases of the coronavirus surging, Warner Bros. on Thursday postponed the release of Christopher Nolan’s “Tenet,” further delaying Hollywood’s summer kickoff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>272 NYPD cops file for retirement...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/27/272-nypd-cops-file-for-retirement-since-floyd-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops are hanging up their handcuffs in huge numbers. The flurry of Finest farewells began after the police-involved killing of George Floyd on May 25, with 272 uniformed cops putting in retirement …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milton Glaser, designer of 'I Love NY' logo, dies on 91st birthday...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/06/milton-glaser-new-york-and-iny-designer-dies-at-91.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A giant of graphic design and illustration for seven decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Woke Up Gasping For Air': 28 Members Of Family Contract...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/06/26/28-family-members-contract-covid-19-father-dies-from-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard said 28 extended family members have tested positive for COVID-19, most recovering at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who led protests against stay-at-home orders positive...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/coronavirus-updates-miami-close-beaches-july-weekend/story?id=71488310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. coronavirus death toll has surpassed 125,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beaches To Shut Again...</title>
      <link>https://patch.com/florida/miami/miami-area-beaches-shut-down-again-amid-coronavirus-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;patch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami-Dade county's mayor announced he plans to shut down Miami-area beaches during the upcoming July 4 holiday weekend and possibly longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of who's most at risk just got longer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/list-whos-most-risk-severe-200328821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The older you are, the greater your risk for a severe case of COVID-19, the CDC says as it expands its list of risky underlying health conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Supreme Court rebukes cost him evangelical voters?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/could-supreme-court-rebukes-trump-171204080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelical voters backed Trump with an eye on shaping the Supreme Court for decades. But recent rulings could undermine that support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump and Black Lives Matter Movement Changed White Voters' Minds...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/27/how-trump-and-the-black-lives-matter-movement-changed-white-voters-minds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of American voters support the demonstrations against police brutality and racial injustice that have roiled the country over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in nuclear particles from 'weapons test' detected on Baltic coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mystery-rise-nuclear-particles-weapons-22261778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cutting edge radiation sensors in Stockholm have detected higher-than-usual levels of isotopes produced by nuclear fission –potentially coming from a nuclear weapons test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MULE: American jailed in Spain was unwitting drug trafficker...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7cc44c5d0e0541c40755f2a2989c621d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Victor Stemberger wasn't about to ignore the emails inviting him into a multimillion-dollar business opportunity, so he pitched himself as perfect for the job. In a way he was —...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
