<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Republican, Democrat Chairs Trade Racism Charges In 'Unity' Segment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/republican-and-democrat-chairs-trade-accusations-of-racism-in-meet-the-press-unity-segment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea eyes Swiss, Singaporean-style success...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c874f3a400eb459daac89b9d46909810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — North Korea is exploring a grand plan to become a regional transportation hub, inspired in part by the successes of Singapore and Switzerland, and would be open to joining world financial institutions such as the International Monetary Fund if current member states give up their "hostile" policies toward it, a senior government economist has told The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger jet crashes mins after take off from Jakarta...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/7605999/indonesian-plane-crash-lion-air-aircraft-crashed-take-off-jakarta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PASSENGER plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Jakarta, Indonesia, according to reports. The Lion Air flight between Jakarta and Pangkal Pinang lost contact with air traffic control earl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk students overload ER, cause mayhem at University hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/education/article220233790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palmetto Health Baptist in Columbia treats many drunk students from the University of South Carolina on game days, and more Richland County EMS ambulances are needed at Williams-Brice Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCarolina Warns About Secret Service Impostor: Gun, badge, siren...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article220769255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Greenville County Sheriff’s Office is warning SC residents and businesses about a man with a gun, badge who is pretending to be a police or Secret Service officer seen driving a Ford Explorer with a siren.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Isolated loner'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6326657/Synagogue-shooters-neighbors-knew-forgettable-bland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday, police and FBI agents raided the Baldwin, Pennsylvania apartment of Robert Bowers, 46, who is charged with 29 federal crimes and faces the death penalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 Hondurans break cordon, attempt to join...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/1-000-honduran-migrants-break-guatemala-police-cordon-011019246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a thousand Honduran migrants broke through a Guatemalan police cordon on the border with Mexico Sunday as they attempted to join a larger caravan of compatriots heading towards the United States, police and rights groups said. Guatemala's human rights ombudsman, Jordan Rodas, called on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds search for suspect who set fire to Republican HQ...</title>
      <link>https://trib.com/news/state-and-regional/federal-authorities-offer-reward-for-suspect-in-gop-headquarters-fire/article_5df64367-0037-5a63-8449-333299c8e372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LARAMIE — Federal authorities are offering a $5,000 reward for information on the whereabouts of a man charged with vandalizing and setting fire to a local Republican Party headquarters in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India to unveil world's tallest statue; 2x Statue of Liberty height...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/india-unveil-worlds-tallest-statue-13495377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An astonishing £330 million has been spent on the 600ft tribute to Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel in Gujarat, India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple finds hidden camera in cruise ship bedroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2018/10/28/travelers-found-hidden-camera-their-carnival-cruise-bedroom/1800150002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida couple discovered aÂ recording deviceÂ hidden among TV wires in their stateroom last October on a Carnival Fantasy cruise to the Caribbean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat majority could undermine Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/28/mueller-democrats-house-majority-trump-probe-940032</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Democrats retake the House, they want to aggressively open probes into issues the special counsel is also investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-old raped in NYC public bathroom...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/11-year-girl-raped-in-public-bathroom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is looking for a teenager wanted in the rape of an 11-year-old girl in the public bathroom of a Bronx Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals rescued from 'hellish' Albanian zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/animals-rescued-hellish-albanian-zoo-212853415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Albanian police on Sunday broke open cages at a private zoo and removed 11 animals including three lions and a bear being kept in "hellish" conditions, animal welfare workers said. After the owner of the zoo at Fier, around 100 kilometres (60 miles) south of the capital Tirana, allegedly refused</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Concert Threats Continue with Image of Cleaver-Wielding Jihadist...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-concert-threats-continue-with-image-of-cleaver-wielding-jihadist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Third media group picks up month of online depictions of attacks on concert venues; latest calls on Western Muslims to "take an example" from homegrown jihadists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Moore Reveals Footage of Bomb Suspect Cesar Sayoc at Trump Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/michael-moore-reveals-video-bomb-suspect-cesar-sayoc-at-trump-rally-1155772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'Fahrenheit 11/9' director compares Cesar Sayoc to "a lost dog with no direction home."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA ON EDGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/shooting-leaves-sense-of-shock-in-peaceful-pittsburgh-enclave-1540744437</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Saturday’s mass shooting, people have gathered in Pittsburgh’s Squirrel Hill neighborhood to try to process the horror that took the lives of 11 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father apologizes for dressing son as Hitler for Halloween...</title>
      <link>https://www.tristatehomepage.com/news/local-news/owensboro-man-s-nazi-costume-sparks-criticism-online/1552705089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tristatehomepage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Owensboro man says he regrets dressing he and his son in Nazi costumes during Thursday evening’s trick or treat event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEAD HEAT IN 3 SENATE RACES</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tight-contests-mark-critical-senate-races-cbs-news-battleground-tracker-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New CBS News polling shows close Senate races in three key states with just over a week until Election Day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bowers: Anti-Semite, anti-migrant and gun fanatic...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/robert-bowers-anti-semite-anti-migrant-gun-fanatic-194143092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the months leading up to Saturday's massacre at a Pittsburgh synagogue, Robert Bowers used a little-known social network to spew hatred toward Jews, calling them the "Children of Satan" as he showed off his "family" of firearms. "HIAS likes to bring invaders in that kill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countries Push Digital Taxes on Tech Giants...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/countries-push-digital-taxes-on-tech-giants-1540742400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inspired by the EU, more governments across the world are contemplating a tax based on the revenue of foreign technology companies like Facebook and Google rather than their profit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bland neighbor from Apartment 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/pittsburgh-synagogue-assailant-was-the-bland-man-from-apartment-1/17952638/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH — Robert Bowers poured out murderous, anti-Semitic hatred online. But in person at home, people remembered him Sunday as the bland neighbor from Apartment 1 who offered no clues about his racist views, his dark plans, or really anything at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue check mark... </title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/How-Gab-became-a-white-supremacist-sanctuary-13343295.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was a blue check mark next to Robert Bowers's name, meaning that the social media account was verified. His bio said that "jews are the children of satan," his banner image a clear reference to a white supremacist meme. His last message, posted Saturday morning, read "Screw your optics, I'm going in." The account is believed to belong to the same Robert D. Bowers who is suspected of opening fire in a Pittsburgh synagogue during prayers, killing 11 people and wounding six others. The profile, which has since been removed, lived on Gab, a social media platform that has become a haven for white supremacists, neo-Nazis and other adherents to extreme ideologies that have found themselves increasingly unwelcome on Twitter and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peanut reactions become 'almost epidemic'... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/26/why-peanut-food-allergies-have-become-almost-epidemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allergies to peanuts and other types of food continues to climb, but experts say there is some progress in controlling or preventing life-threatening reactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Allies Reject Linking Words, Action...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/as-violence-rises-trump-allies-reject-link-of-words-to-action</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Allies Reject Link of RhetoricÂ to Increased Violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wants to privatize state companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-28/brazilians-on-course-to-usher-in-new-era-of-hard-right-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's first private rocket fails after launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-space-landspace/chinese-privately-developed-rocket-fails-to-reach-orbit-idUSKCN1N2078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A privately developed Chinese carrier rocket failed to reach orbit after lifting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro confident of victory...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-election/far-right-bolsonaro-confident-of-victory-as-brazilians-vote-in-divisive-election-idUSKCN1N203K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilians voted on Sunday in the most polarized election in decades as anger ov...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As housing market stagnates, homeowners staying put for longest stretches ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/as-the-housing-market-stagnates-american-homeowners-are-staying-put-for-the-longest-stretches-ever-2018-10-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owners of homes that were sold in the third quarter had been in their properties for the longest stretch on record, a by-product of low levels of home equity after the crisis as well as a lack of different properties on the market into which to move up or down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Includes Pipe Bomb Instructions On First Page Of Results...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/10/27/google-amazon-pipe-bombs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'If you want to kill and injure a lot of people'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilians Head to Polls in Divisive Presidential Election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d1a52960f0fe41ed877b37f87579533e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO (AP) — Brazilians on Sunday were weighing their hunger for radical change against fears that the presidential front-runner could threaten democracy as they cast ballots in the culmination of a bitter campaign that split many families and was frequently marred by violence. Far-right congressman Jair Bolsonaro has won over many voters by painting a picture of a Brazil at war — with criminals, corrupt politicians and leftist ideas that he says could turn the country into Venezuela — and promises to change the tide with force and clean governance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military moving equipment to southern border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4258f2e25da84951860e0d2664e613c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRAGUE (AP) — The U.S. military has already begun delivering jersey barriers to the southern border in conjunction with plans to deploy active duty troops there, U.S. Defense Secretary Jim Mattis said Sunday as a caravan of Central Americans slowly heads across Mexico toward the United States. Mattis told reporters traveling with him that details of the deployment are still being worked out but he should have them Sunday night. They will include exactly how many forces are needed. It was unclear when the details will be made public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel party hammered in key regional vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/key-merkel-allies-threaten-quit-coalition-183733506.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Merkel's junior coalition partners threatened Sunday to quit her governing coalition, blaming bitter infighting in Berlin for massive losses to both the chancellor's conservative party and the centre-left in a regional vote. "The state of the government is unacceptable," Social</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Tropical Trump' poised to win in dramatic swing right...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/brazil-votes-far-candidate-favorite-053359098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilians cast ballots Sunday in a divisive presidential run-off election whose front-runner, far-right former army captain Jair Bolsonaro, is vowing to rescue the country from crisis with a firm grip. Bolsonaro -- who has tapped deep anti-establishment anger, but repulsed many with his denigrating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Fed-up Americans crave unity amid violence...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/5f7eba286663432189978cb11d541112/enough-enough-fed-americans-crave-unity-amid-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — She flipped through television channels and radio stations, scanning from conservative to liberal media, searching for any sign that the polarized nation had finally reached its tipping point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOODBATH DURING BRIS...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/017eca5511ec4834b4406ac8c6b5bb13/open-door-and-massacre-gunman-kills-11-synagogue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — The suspect in the mass shooting at a Pittsburgh synagogue expressed hatred of Jews during the rampage and told officers afterward that Jews were committing genocide and that he wanted them all to die, according to charging documents made public Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Sex Workers' Addiction Struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-sex-workers-struggles-with-addiction-i-used-to-be-the-last-person-my-family-would-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year where we’ve lost so many porn stars to drugs, sex workers open up to Aurora Snow about their personal battles with addiction—and how they overcame it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley nannies phone police for kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Silicon-Valley-Nannies-Are-Phone-Police-for-Kids-13341649.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - Silicon Valley parents are increasingly obsessed with keeping their children away from screens. Even a little screen time can be so deeply addictive, some parents believe, that it's best if a child neither touches nor sees any of these glittering rectangles. These particular parents, after all, deeply understand their allure. But it's very hard for a working adult in the 21st century to live at home without looking at a phone. And so, as with many aspirations and ideals, it's easier to hire someone to do this. Enter the Silicon Valley nanny, who each day returns to the time before screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF spends $300,000 to register noncitizen voters; 49 sign up...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/SF-spends-300-000-to-register-noncitizen-voters-13340917.php?t=1cc71b89e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco's effort to get noncitizen parents to the ballot box is pretty much a bust the first time out, with only 49 signing up to vote in the Nov. 6 election. Back in July, the city began registering noncitizens - including undocumented immigrants - to vote in school board elections. The program is the first-of-its-kind in California and followed passage of a 2016 San Francisco ballot measure opening school elections to noncitizens who are over the age of 18, city residents and have children under age 19. The city spent about $310,000 setting up the new registration system and encouraging people to sign up. But Donald Trump's election quickly put a damper on enthusiasm for the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Races Shift...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/27/politics/cnn-house-key-races-late-october-update/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 10 days until Election Day, Democrats are poised to make significant gains in the US House, propelled by eye-popping fundraising hauls from Democratic challengers and a clear edge on the generic congressional ballot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims identified...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/10/28/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooting-victims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The identities of the victims that were inside the Tree of Life Synagogue Saturday are now being released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enough is enough: Fed-up Americans crave unity amid violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/enough-enough-fed-americans-crave-unity-amid-violence-130716016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — She flipped through television channels and radio stations, scanning from conservative to liberal media, searching for any sign that the polarized nation had finally reached its tipping point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female motortaxi drivers on rise in Bangkok...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fast-lane-female-motortaxi-drivers-rise-bangkok-014703406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hair pulled back tightly as she lounges on her red scooter, Ar is a rare sight among the male-dominated ranks of Bangkok's motortaxi riders plying their trade on the Thai capital's treacherous roads. A veteran of seven years who works in the bustling On Nut district, Ar is among the thousands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipe bomb suspect was spinning records as FBI closed in...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fbi-uncovered-bomb-suspects-id-dna-fingerprint-clues-052108455--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the hours before his arrest, as federal authorities zeroed in and secretly accumulated evidence, Cesar Sayoc was in his element: spinning classic and Top 40 hits in a nightclub where he'd found work as a DJ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilians Head to Polls in Divisive Presidential Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/brazilians-head-to-polls-in-divisive-presidential-election-1540724400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilians began voting Sunday in a divisive presidential race expected to elect combative ex-army captain Jair Bolsonaro, shifting the country’s politics sharply to the right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 minutes of terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-synagogue-suffers-20-minutes-terror-233158762.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunman Robert Bowers only needed 20 minutes to sow terror at the Tree of Life synagogue in the US city of Pittsburgh, where congregants had gathered peacefully for Shabbat services marking a day of rest. Shortly before 10 am (1400 GMT) the 46-year-old Bowers -- who had penned virulent anti-Semitic messages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT CONDEMNS, CALLS FOR ARMED GUARDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-says-pittsburgh-attack-lays-bare-hate-us-181213687--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MURPHYSBORO, Ill. (AP) — President Donald Trump mourned the dead and forcefully condemned anti-Semitism Saturday after a mass shooting at a Pittsburgh synagogue that left 11 dead. But faced with another national tragedy, he did not long turn his focus away from the midterm elections or himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadliest anti-Semitic attack in US history...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apos-multiple-casualties-apos-shooting-150630876.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunman kills 11 at Pittsburgh synagogue He yelled "All Jews must die" Suspect, named Robert Bowers, charged with hate crimes Donald Trump condemns 'evil anti-Semitic attack' Shooting the 'deadliest anti-Semitic attack in recent US history' A gunman shouting "all Jews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NAZI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/10/report-pittsburgh-shooter-named-on-police-scanner-is-a-nazi-hated-donald-trump-thought-trump-controlled-by-jews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Cabinet exodus likely after midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/28/trump-cabinet-departures-midterms-943375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two years of already-high turnover, the president is expected to push out or accept the resignations of several more department chiefs by January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOODBATH DURING BRIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/active-shooter-reported-near-pittsburgh-synagogue-n925211</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s a very horrific crime scene. It’s one of the worst that I've seen," Pittsburgh Public Safety Director Wendell Hissrich said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RANTED ON SOCIALS BEFORE ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Suspected-synagogue-shooter-appears-to-have-13342102.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Bowers, who authorities said attacked a Pittsburgh synagogue during Saturday morning services, appears to have targeted Jewish people on a social media account rife with anti-refugee, anti-Semitic and white supremacist posts. The postings, which were listed under Bowers' name on the social media site Gab before the account was deactivated Saturday afternoon, could offer the clearest window into the mind-set of the 46-year-old, who police say stormed Tree of Life synagogue shouting anti-Semitic slurs and firing an assault rifle in an attack that left 11 people dead and six wounded, including one in critical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TRUMP HATER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/synagogue-shooter-disliked-trump-posted-i-did-not-vote-for-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunman was an anti-Semite who called Trump a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ALL JEWS MUST DIE'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6323781/Active-shooter-Pittsburgh-synagogue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman has been named by police sources as 46-year-old Robert Bowers.  He was infuriated by the Hebrew Immigrant Aids Society, according to social media profiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA: WE MUST UNITE AGAINST EVIL...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/IvankaTrump/status/1056238987336171520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“America is stronger than the acts of a depraved bigot and anti-semite. All good Americans stand with the Jewish people to oppose acts of terror &amp;amp; share the horror, disgust &amp;amp; outrage over the massacre in Pittsburgh. We must unite against hatred &amp;amp; evil. God bless those affected”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAUGHTER AT SYNAGOGUE; 11 SHOT DEAD</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/10/27/heavy-police-presence-near-synagogue-in-squirrel-hill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven people have been killed and a number of others injured after a shooting at The Tree of Life Synagogue in Squirrel Hill on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAID JEWS COMMITTING GENOCIDE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/017eca5511ec4834b4406ac8c6b5bb13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — The suspect in the mass shooting at a Pittsburgh synagogue told officers that Jews were committing genocide and that he wanted them all to die, according to a charging document made public early Sunday. Robert Gregory Bowers killed eight men and three women inside the Tree of Life Synagogue on Saturday during worship services before a tactical police team tracked him down and shot him, police said in the affidavit, which contained some previously unreported details on the shooting and the police response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLICE DEPLOY TO JEWISH HUBS...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/nypd-deploys-to-jewish-hubs-following-synagogue-shooting/4565353/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is deploying personnel to Jewish centers and houses of worship throughout New York City following an active shooter situation at a Pittsburgh synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSPECT CHARGED...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181027215337-oe0ot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENNSYLVANIA-SHOOTING/ (UPDATE 10, PIX, TV):UPDATE 10-Gunman targeting Jews kills 11 in Pittsburgh synagogue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETANYAHU 'HEARTBROKEN'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20181027172442-k6fsu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENNSYLVANIA-SHOOTING/ISRAEL (URGENT):Israeli prime minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's 'Tropical Trump' poised to win presidency in dramatic swing right...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/brazils-bolsonaro-poised-win-presidency-dramatic-swing-050850896--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilians fed up with corruption and rising crime are expected to elect former army captain turned politician Jair Bolsonaro as their president as voting begins on Sunday in a turbulent swing to the right in the world's fourth largest democracy. Bolsonaro's sudden rise was propelled by rejection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman stabs ex-husband -- takes SELFIE with him as he bleeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/739120/woman-stabs-ex-husband-selfies-bleeding-siberia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan halts after report of abducted child...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/oct/28/migrant-caravan-abducted-child-report-halts-journe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coordinators of a caravan of several thousand Central American migrants moving through southern Mexico urged its members to rest Sunday. At first the migrants vowed to press on anyway but later changed their minds amid reports that a child had been abducted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's first private rocket fails after launch...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/28/chinas-first-private-rocket-fails-after-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING — The first attempt by a private Chinese company to send a rocket into space has failed. Beijing-based Landspace said late Saturday that the first and second stage of its ZQ-1 rocket worked…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer cats: The invasive species in your backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cats-invasive-species-in-your-backyard-cbsn-originals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invasive species can be ruthless. Surprisingly, they can also be adorable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost and Angry...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article220730960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused mail bomber Cesar Sayoc, a pizza deliveryman and strip club floorman living out of his van, never found success at any of the roles he imagined for himself — until he became a Trump warrior and took center stage as perpetrator of a national crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron All In For Beto...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/lebron-james-wears-beto-orourke-for-senate-hat-to-lakers-game-in-san-antonio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'Rourke is running for U.S. Senate in Texas against Ted Cruz, and LeBron has previous praised the candidate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming dementia crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/opinion/article/We-re-not-prepared-for-the-coming-dementia-crisis-13339813.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of us played the lottery this week in hopes becoming an instant billionaire. The chance of winning was less than 1 in 300 million, yet we all believed we could be "the one." We like to believe that good things will come our way and tend to ignore real threats to our health as we age, even though the chances they will happen are high. Retired Supreme Court justice Sandra Day O'Connor recently disclosed that she has now been diagnosed with probable Alzheimer's disease. At 65, she had a 1 in 10 chance of developing dementia. At 85, her odds increased to 1 in 3. Now we acknowledge with great sadness that the 88-year-old's keen mind will fade away and that she, too, will succumb to the disease, just as her husband did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Decries 'Persecution' of Catholic Church Through Accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pope-decries-persecution-of-catholic-church-through-accusations-1540676324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis told a gathering of bishops from around the world that the Catholic Church is being persecuted through accusations—an apparent allusion to clerical sex-abuse scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Troops Deploy 'Overwhelming Force' Against Iceland's Beer Supplies...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/sailors-marines-beer-iceland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL IN LONDON:  4 JAGUARS arrested after brawl over $64,000 bar tab...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/7599437/nfl-team-bar-brawl-arrests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN football stars were involved in a nightclub brawl over a £50,000 bar bill. The four Jacksonville Jaguars players were arrested by cops at 4am. Trouble flared after they were accused of try…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
