<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Clinton question shadows Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Clinton-impeachment-question-shadows-Congress-in-13182287.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - At the outset of the 1998 impeachment hearings, Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., asked a memorable question that could resonate for some lawmakers today: "Is this Watergate or Peyton Place?" "Peyton Place" was a steamy soap opera from the 1960s, based on a 1950s novel of the same name. The final judgment, based on the outcome of that impeachment process, was that President Bill Clinton's affair with Monica Lewinsky was much more a soap opera than something close to the Watergate scandal that drove President Richard Nixon from the Oval Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French vegan fest off menu amid fears of butchers' revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-vegan-fest-off-menu-162822178.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French town of Calais has been no stranger to public disorder in recent years, with recurrent battles between police and migrants or striking ferry workers making headlines across the world. But now the port town is facing a bizarre new threat, according to its council: an alliance of hunters and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC protesters clash at rally for Confederate statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/counties/orange-county/article217286120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters gathered on the UNC-Chapel Hill campus Saturday morning, five days after the Silent Sam Confederate monument was toppled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE UNDER FIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/pope-francis-in-ireland/pope-francis-speech-was-disgraceful-and-contained-extraordinary-deflection-victims-claim-37251012.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clerical abuse survivor Colm O’Gorman has described the speech by Pope Francis at Dublin Castle as an “incredible missed opportunity”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo and Two Suicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/08/25/anthony-bourdain-jill-messick-metoo-two-suicides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the launch of #MeToo, two people connected to the movement have committed suicide - Anthony Bourdain and Jill Messick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court strikes down measures on firing federal workers...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/403593-court-strikes-down-trump-orders-on-firing-federal-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Saturday struck down several key provisions in President Trump's executive orders that he signed earlier this year that would have made it easier to fire federal workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Warns Staged 'Chemical Provocation' Coming In Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-25/us-says-assad-will-use-chemical-weapons-idlib-russia-warns-staged-provocation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May approach Harvey's US rainfall record...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/hawaii-may-face-direct-hit-serious-damage-from-hurricane-lane-to-end-this-week/70005829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires and Catastrophic Flooding: Lane's Wrath Continues in Hawaii ...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2018-08-23-hurricane-lane-forecast-hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest forecast for this dangerous, rare Hawaii tropical threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC: Body parts in trash bags on street...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/body-parts-found-trash-bags-side-bronx-street/story?id=57395983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Parks Department worker in New York City happened upon a grisly scene on a sidewalk outside Crotona Park on Friday when he found two black plastic bags with human body parts inside. The two trash bags were discovered Friday afternoon by the parks employee, who initially thought they might contain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former pastor claims sex abuse against televangelist...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/08/25/former-pastor-claims-sex-abuse-against-televangelist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit filed by a former associate pastor at an Ohio megachurch claims televangelist Ernest Angley sexually abused and harassed him over a 10-year period starting in 2004.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S.-Mexico trade deal could be imminent...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-says-u-mexico-trade-deal-could-imminent-134539518.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump tweeted on Saturday that the United States could reach a "big Trade Agreement" with Mexico imminently. "Our relationship with Mexico is getting closer by the hour. Some really good people within both the new and old government, and all working closely together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE UNDER FIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-francis-departs-1st-papal-trip-ireland-071909848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBLIN (AP) — The Latest on Pope Francis' trip to Ireland (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: UNC braces for rally over Confederate statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/25/us/unc-silent-sam-confederate-statue/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citing a volatile mood on its campus, the University of North Carolina is urging people not to participate in a "possible rally" on Saturday in Chapel Hill over the toppling this week of a Confederate monument.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolves helping war vets deal with PTSD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/24/wolves-are-helping-war-vets-deal-with-ptsd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being thrown to the wolves could be the best therapy session ever for the war vets featured on “Wolves and Warriors.” The Animal Planet series, premiering Saturday (Sept. 1), pairs veterans — many …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/24/politics/mike-pence-silent-cohen-manafort/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence is keeping quiet during yet another raucous news week for the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed Raises GDP Forecast to 4.6%...</title>
      <link>https://www.streetinsider.com/Fed/Atlanta+Fed+Raises+GDP+Forecast+to+4.6%25/14546182.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.streetinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GDPNow model estimate for real GDP growth (seasonally adjusted annual rate) in the third quarter of 2018 is 4.6 percent on August 24, up from 4.3 percent on August 16. After yesterdays releases on new-home sales and costs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates release demands amid 19-day prison strike across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/25/the-resistance-now-prison-strikes-demands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prisoners continue to protest while students target Smith &amp; Wesson in 50-mile gun control march and a survey reveals majority of Americans support Medicare for all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's Bullard warns of recession risk in raising rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-fed-bullard/feds-bullard-warns-of-recession-risk-in-raising-rates-idUSKCN1LA00B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Louis Federal Reserve Bank President James Bullard on Friday raised new alarm bells over the U.S. central bank's plan to keep raising interest rates, warning that even one more rate hike could set the stage for recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As surfers taste the perfect wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-storm-lane-surfing/hurricane-treats-hawaii-surfers-to-a-taste-of-the-perfect-wave-idUSKCN1LA00N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Rozier could not sleep on Thursday night, not because wind and rain from Hurricane Lane was lashing his Hawaii home, but because he was anxious to surf the huge waves rolling into one of his favorite beaches on the Big Island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's Tourism Boom Lifting All Boats, Including Tiny Montenegro...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/europes-tourism-boom-is-lifting-all-boats-including-tiny-montenegro-1535194800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many tourists are descending on Europe this summer and a growing number are looking beyond the continent’s famous destinations to places like Montenegro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of Burning Man...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/725605/burning-man-festival-worlds-wildest-orgy-pictures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyalty Tested as Closest Confidants Become Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/25/loyalty-tested-as-trump-s-closest-confidants-become-witnesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revelations that two of Donald Trump’s closest longtime allies have struck cooperation deals shows that federal prosecutors are chipping away at one of the president’s most cherished values: loyalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: UNC board member calls for Confederate statue to be reinstalled on campus after protesters tear down...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/403573-unc-board-member-calls-for-confederate-statue-to-be-reinstalled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A board member at the University of North Carolina is calling for a Confederate statue to be promptly reinstalled on the Chapel Hill campus after it was toppled by protesters earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Returns to a Country Transformed and a Church in Tatters...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/25/world/europe/pope-francis-ireland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholics are waiting to see whether the pope will use Ireland as a symbolic stage to announce measures to combat a crisis that threatens the future of his church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RECORD HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/24/us-stocks-china-trade-talks-end-powell-to-speak-at-jackson-hole.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Composite reached all-time highs on Friday as Netflix shares rose. The broader market also climbed after the top Federal Reserve official characterized the U.S. economy as "strong."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors inch closer to Trump...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/403546-trump-org-cfos-immunity-deal-is-new-problem-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors are edging closer and closer to President Trump’s business empire, a fact underlined by the news Friday of an immunity deal reportedly given to the Trump Organization’s longtime chief financial officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Narrow in scope'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/24/us/politics/allen-weisselberg-immunity-cohen-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deal for testimony in the case against President Trump’s former personal lawyer, Michael D. Cohen, did not extend a blanket immunity beyond the information shared, a person briefed on the arrangement said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors want rapper Pitbull to clean up trash at abandoned house...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/entertainment/article217137235.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pinecrest, Florida, home owned by Pitbull’s music empire is in disrepair and has received numerous code violations from the village government as an abandoned or unkempt structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems' midterm strategy: Stop talking about Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article217217600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are making a bet that with a wave of TV and digital ads they can finally make the upcoming midterm elections about health care and taxes. They just need to hope voters will tune out Donald Trump long enough to listen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo rides high in bid for re-election despite gaffe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/23/gaffe-aside-n-y-s-cuomo-rides-high-in-his-bid-for-re-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Cuomo Rides High in His Bid for Re-Election in New York Despite Gaffe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Jehovah's Witnesses to protest sex abuse scandals at convention...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/news/jehovahs-witnesses-child-sex-abuse-protest-reading-chessa-manion-20180824.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of ex-Jehovah's Witnesses plan to protest at the Reading Santander Arena on Sunday, hoping to convince Witnesses who are attending a convention to question the religion's response to child sex abuse scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh argued the president can be impeached for lies, cover-ups and refusing to testify...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-kavanaugh-obstruction-20180823-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a young lawyer, Brett Kavanaugh argued that President Clinton should be impeached for lying and obstruction of justice. Will the same standard be applied to Trump?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 weeks after 75 people were shot in Chicago's most violent weekend of year, only one alleged shooter has been charged!</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/opinion/editorials/ct-edit-clearance-chicago-violence-shootings-murder-20180824-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gun violence runs amok in Chicago. The Police Department solved just 17 percent of homicides in 2017. This is a disaster for the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  Sea lice outbreak causes discomfort in Ocean City...</title>
      <link>http://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/eastern-shore/bs-md-oc-sea-lice-20180823-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ocean City Beach Patrol said Thursday they’ve received numerous calls from beach goers about sea lice in the water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash Against Venezuelan Refugees Grows Across South America...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/backlash-against-venezuelan-refugees-grows-across-south-america-1535132655 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across swaths of South America, sympathy is giving way to resentment over the 2.3 million Venezuelans the U.N. estimates have fled to neighboring countries since 2014. We look at one Brazilian town along the border—the sole road crossing between the two nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money Really Does Lead to More Satisfying Life... </title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/money-really-does-lead-to-a-more-satisfying-life/17793260/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research suggests that more money really does lead to a more satisfying life. Surveys of thousands of Swedish lottery winners have provided persuasive evidence of this truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA reveals plans for permanent base on moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7097412/nasa-reveals-plans-for-permanent-moon-base-as-agency-declares-we-want-lots-of-humans-in-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA chief Jim Bridenstine has revealed hopes for a permanent base on the moon. At a meeting at the Johnson Space Center in Houston this week, Mr Bridenstine gave details on plans to build ‘Gateway…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCAFEE: I hold gun sitting on toilet...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weird/article/John-McAfee-guns-shower-toilet-Belize-SEC-13180721.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John McAfee wants you to know that he never goes anywhere unarmed. The controversial tech mogul, who claims to have been targeted by numerous bad actors in the past, is protected around the clock by his own security team, but should they be comprised, he'd be more than ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak now at 105 cases; Bordering countries on alert...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ebola-outbreak-now-at-105-cases-and-bordering-13181274.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MPONDWE, Uganda - On Tuesdays and Fridays, an estimated 19,000 people stream down the hill from Congo's North Kivu province to cross the border into this small town, many of them headed to a sprawling open-air market. In recent weeks, crossing the border has become more difficult as Ugandan health authorities have beefed up precautions against the spread of the Ebola virus. An outbreak centered in North Kivu is responsible for 105 confirmed or suspected cases, including 67 deaths, according to Robert Redfield, director of the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, who has just returned from the area. Uganda is determined to keep the deadly hemorrhagic fever from spreading to its side of the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LIFESTYLES' Leach Dead in Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/robin-leach-dies-host-of-lifestyles-of-the-rich-and-famous-celebrity-columnist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robin Leach, a celebrity columnist and television host who famously signed off each episode of “Lifestyles of the Rich and Famous” with his signature catchphrase of “Champagne wis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football participation declines for second consecutive year nationally...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressofatlanticcity.com/sports/local/highschool/football-participation-declines-for-the-second-consecutive-year-nationally/article_65d9d993-2fa9-5059-803f-b4879401fcd4.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressofatlanticcity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — For the second consecutive year, participation in 11-player high school football declined nationwide, according to the annual survey by the National Federation of State High School Associations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE star says 'Coming out as transgender was infinitely easier for me than coming out as conservative'...</title>
      <link>https://womenintheworld.com/2018/08/24/republican-transgender-youtuber-takes-on-notions-of-identity-both-political-and-sexual/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;womenintheworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial YouTube personality Blaire White, a transgender woman who has become famous for her contentious and heavily conservative views, says that the hate and vitriol she’s endured from both …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl Head Coach: Players 'Right' To Protest During Anthem...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/08/24/eagles-head-coach-doug-pederson-players-right-to-protest-during-national-anthem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia Eagles head coach Doug Pederson addressed the ongoing debate over whether NFL players should be allowed to protest during the national anthem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to join Russian nuclear war games for first time...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/chinese-military-joining-russians-nuclear-war-games/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and China will hold a large-scale military exercise next month that will include simulated nuclear weapons attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communist Party funding DC think tanks...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/chinese-communist-party-funds-washington-think-tanks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Communist Party is intensifying covert influence operations in the U.S. that include funding Washington think tanks and coercing Chinese Americans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC DOMINATES WHITE HOUSE HELL WEEK</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/rachel-maddow-wins-tv-ratings-night-3-donald-trump-david-pecker-michael-cohen-campaign-finance-violation-1202451961/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump’s really bad week has been a ratings bonanza for Rachel Maddow. For a third night in a row, Maddow’s MSNBC program was highest rated across all of cable TV Thursday night. He…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem rising?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/24/grandson-munich-terrorist-rises-in-race-against-indicted-rep-hunter-disavows-dark-family-past.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Democratic congressional candidate Ammar Campa-Najjar was barely on anyone’s radar until the indictment of his opponent. With his boosted chances, though, has come scrutiny of his dark family past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal spray flu vaccine gets green light from CDC...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-cdc-flu-recommendations-nasal-spray-20180823-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After advising the public to avoid the nasal spray version of the flu vaccine for the last two years, the Centers for Disease Control is now giving it the green light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents fight back after school drops Pledge of Allegiance for oath to 'global society'...</title>
      <link>http://eagnews.org/parents-fight-back-after-school-drops-pledge-of-allegiance-for-student-authored-oath-to-global-society/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eagnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta Neighborhood Charter School Principal Lara Zelski decided students will no longer recite the Pledge of Allegiance during the school’s morning meeting agenda, which she described to parents as “an effort to begin our day as a fully inclusive and connected community.” “Over the past couple of years it has become increasingly obvious that more and more of our community were choosing to not stand and/or recite the pledge,” she wrote, according to the Atlanta Journal Constitution. The statement, posted to the school website, promised parents students could recite the Pledge of Allegiance later in the day, if they felt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires and Catastrophic Flooding: Lane's Wrath Continues in Hawaii ...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Wildfires-and-Catastrophic-Flooding-Lanes-Wrath-Continues-Hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as its core was being pulled apart by strong wind shear, Hurricane Lane continued to trigger an array of havoc across the Hawaiian Islands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY TAKES SHOT AT PRESIDENT FOR 'FLIPPING' COMMENTS...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-news-rudy-trump-flipping-lawyer-20180824-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to flipping, Rudy Giuliani won’t budge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American sues Feds over seized iPhone data during airport search...</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2018/08/23/woman_iphone_border_patrol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theregister.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal action seeks info copied during airport search</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future elections swayed by weaponized chatbots?</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/611832/future-elections-may-be-swayed-by-intelligent-weaponized-chatbots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AI advances that brought you Alexa are teaching propaganda how to talk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bare-knuckle fighting poised for brand boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/bare-knuckle-fighting-could-poised-us-boom-215851932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — David Feldman staged a bare-knuckle boxing match on the undercard of a mixed martial arts show at a Yavapai Nation casino in Arizona in 2011. The promoter offered the fight on the internet as a paid streaming option, just to see if anybody would watch it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCain decides to discontinue cancer treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/arizona/2018/08/24/arizona-senator-john-mccain-legacy-national-security-hawk-gop-maverick/567264001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain prefers that he be remembered for his contributions to the national defense. But history likely will recall him as GOP "maverick."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE quietly purges user-generated reviews?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-might-hiding-fact-reviews-shoddy-135640955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's local reviews have disappeared from normal search results, which brings to the surface that they may not be the best out there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAK: Aides expect to go rogue on pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/24/trump-manafort-pardon-white-house-aides-795712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's comments are being read as a signal that he wants to ignore his lawyers and exonerate his former campaign chairman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Sovereign Calculator' Explains Invented Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/08/24/venezuela-debuts-sovereign-calculator-app-explain-invented-currency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's Central Bank introduced a "sovereign calculator" app this week to help people work out the value of the country's new currency denominations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia Argento 'sent unwanted topless vid' to recovering sex addict...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6095413/Asia-Argento-sent-unwanted-nude-video-comedian-freaked-got-upset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Leach was appearing on the Legion of Skanks podcast when he shared this story during a discussion about the arrest of Harvey Weinsetein just days prior on charges of rape and assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tc_graphics/2018/graphics/EP142018_3day_cone_no_line_41.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY: NO ONE HAS CONCEDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/columns/pop/8472093/sony-music-responds-claims-suit-michael-jackson-album-vocals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement released on Friday morning (Aug. 24), Sony Music did not concede that the three songs in question on the 2010 &amp;quot;Michael&amp;quot; album featured lead vocals by someone other than Jackson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting fraud charges filed against foreign nationals...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfmynews2.com/article/news/local/19-illegal-immigrants-in-nc-voted-in-2016-election-federal-officials-say/83-587333046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfmynews2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A news release from United States Attorney for the Eastern District of North Carolina also said several of those charged voted in more than one election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat rental industry taking off across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/articles/2018-08-24/rent-a-goat-companies-gain-traction-across-the-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona flirts with sliding red to purple...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/the-report/articles/2018-08-24/races-for-governor-senate-test-arizonas-deep-shade-of-red</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson 'may not have' sung lead vocals on posthumous tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/24/michael-jackson-may-not-have-sung-lead-vocals-posthumous-tracks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When an album of previously-unreleased songs from their hero Michael Jackson was released a year after his death it seemed, some astute fans feared, too good to be true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,478-HP BUGATTI Hypercar Unveiled; Costs $5.8 Million!</title>
      <link>http://www.thedrive.com/news/23123/the-1478-horsepower-bugatti-divo-costs-5-8-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And you can't have one, because they sold out months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plea Reveals Link to Qatari Royals...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-guilty-plea-reveals-link-to-qatari-royal-family-1535127732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $100,000 real-estate brokerage fee that was part of former Trump attorney Michael Cohen’s guilty plea came from representing a company owned by a member of the Qatar royal family, according to interviews and real estate documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Muzzles Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/mueller-is-already-taking-measures-to-stop-manafort-from-making-this-claim-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG plans investigation into Cohen's taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/24/politics/michael-cohen-new-york-state-attorney-general-tax-law/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York state Attorney General's office is poised to pursue a criminal probe of Michael Cohen's potential state tax law violations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept cuts aid to Palestinians by $200 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3149b034ef4a4b92a6dbb9c4aa1f5ca7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration has decided to cut more than $200 million in bilateral aid to the Palestinians, following a review of the funding for projects in the We</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
