<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Police digitally alter mugshot after witnesses said bank robber had no facial tattoos...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/crime/2019/08/the-case-of-the-missing-tattoos-altered-photo-lineup-by-portland-police-draws-objection.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A defense lawyer says police had manipulated his client's mugshot so it more closely resembled the face of the suspected serial bank robber, He's urging a judge to throw out any witness identifications based on the fabricated photo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies race to find key to eternal life...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/companies-race-to-find-the-key-to-eternal-life-2019-08-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fountain of eternal youth once sounded like pure science fiction, but now investors are pouring millions into start-ups searching for revolutionary ways...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans in Mexico watch uneasily as anti-Mexican rhetoric shows face in US...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/americans-in-mexico-watch-uneasily-as-anti-mexican-rhetoric-shows/article_cbbf9ab5-cf44-5c55-930c-bae2d5f0d63f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AJIJIC, Mexico — In this haven for foreigners tucked neatly in a placid, lakeside community with cobblestone streets and surrounded by striking green hills that seem to touch the sky,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Murphy's First NETFLIX Series About Gay Politician...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/08/19/the-politician-trailer-netflix-ryan-murphy-gwyneth-paltrow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you mashed up Election and Rushmore and then sprinkled some trademark Ryan Murphy sass on top, it might look a lot like Netflix’s upcoming comedy The Politician… and we like what we …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE RATTLED? Crucial decisions on economy, guns...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/457773-trump-faces-crucial-decisions-on-economy-guns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is facing one of the most crucial periods of his time at the White House as he returns to Washington from a 10-day sojourn to New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Bill Clinton See This Coming? Former MVP Sidelined...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/08/bill-clinton-legacy/596323/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On his 73rd birthday, the former MVP of the Democratic Party has been sidelined—perhaps for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'POLITICIAN' Trailer Teases High Society and Dirty Politics in Ryan Murphy's NETFLIX Debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/politician-tr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitbull fights off shark to save owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/pitbull-fights-shark-save-owner-18963030</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pitbull Darby lept out of a car window when he heard the fisherman's cries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mooch assembling team of former Cabinet members to speak out against president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/457923-scaramucci-assembling-team-of-former-cabinet-members-to-speak-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci said on Monday that he’s assembling a team of former Cabinet members to speak out against President Trump in an effort to find a Republican challenger to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MORNING SHOW' Trailer: APPLE Gives First Full Look At New Drama...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/the-morning-show-trailer-apple-tv-plus-jennifer-aniston-reese-witherspoon-steve-carell-billy-crudup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After last week’s teaser trailer for The Morning Show that featured voiceover dialogue and, well, not much else, Apple has released the first full trailer which gives us a full look at the dr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman Torched Man's Home After 4 AM Booty Call Fizzled...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/arson/booty-call-arson-609753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey woman set fire to a man’s home after accepting a booty call invitation only to discover when she arrived that he had fallen asleep, police charge. According to cops, Taija Russell, 29, t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan who signed with A's strikes out all batters in debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/athletics/2019/08/18/mlb-nathan-patterson-fans-three-oakland-as-minor-league-debut/2047016001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oakland Athletics minor league pitcher Nathan Patterson, who touched 96 mph on the radar gun to get signed, was excellent in his first pro outing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Police thwart 3 mass shooting plots around USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/19/mass-shooting-plots-thwarted-connecticut-florida-ohio-police-say/2048855001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tips from the public aided in the three arrests in Connecticut, Florida and Ohio, which occurred from Thursday and Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peddling unproven treatments, stem cell industry harms patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/business/health-care/article233635472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meditation to prevent Alzheimer's?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/19/meditation-can-help-prevent-alzheimers-disease-study/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mindfulness is more than good for the soul. According to a new study published in the Journal of Alzheimer’s Disease, it can also help prevent those with mild cognitive impairment from develo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More evacuations as Canary Islands fire out of control...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/more-evacuations-canary-islands-fire-control-091720122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montaña Alta (Spain) (AFP) - A wildfire raged out of control on the Spanish island of Gran Canaria Monday, forcing more evacuations as flames in some parts rose so high even water-dropping planes were unable to operate, authorities said. The fire, which is devouring the mountainous centre of the holiday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Senator Stages Mock Trump Assassination At Fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/08/18/sandoval-mock-trump-assassination-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Illinois state senator apologized Sunday night after controversial photos surfaced from a local fundraiser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida's iconic palm trees threatened by invasive disease...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0740468f94b4a2b9f2db8d2dc116df4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVIE, Fla. (AP) — Florida's iconic palm trees are under attack from a fatal disease that turns them to dried crisps in months, with no chance for recovery once they become ill. Spread by a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>34% of economists expect by 2021...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d77bbfda266497699554a754c124735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A number of U.S. business economists appear sufficiently concerned about the risks of some of President Donald Trump's economic policies that they expect a recession in the U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas, Oklahoma Hit By 65 Earthquakes In 7 Days...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/this-isnt-normal-kansas-and-oklahoma-have-been-hit-by-65-earthquakes-within-the-last-7-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are we supposed to think when rather large earthquakes start happening in places that aren't supposed to have large earthquakes?  2019 has been quite a year for seismic activity already, and I understand that we should expect to see earthquakes in diverse places, but if someone told me that the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President cuts off one of his closest friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/19/donald-trump-cuts-off-tom-barrack-1467191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the president's feud with Tom Barrack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech billionaires haven't killed Burning Man's anti-capitalist spirit -- but influencers might...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90378291/tech-billionaires-havent-killed-burning-mans-anti-capitalist-spirit-but-influencers-might</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual mecca for the experimental and weird has become one of the world’s most iconic arts events by keeping the forces of commercialization at bay. If only it weren’t so Instagrammable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed during exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailypioneer.com/2019/state-editions/woman-killed-during-exorcism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailypioneer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 55-year-old woman was murdered by witch doctors during the process of exorcism in Sapahi village under Ramana police station, around 35 kilometres away from the district headquarter, on Saturday night. The deceased has been identified as Rudani Devi, a native of Kon Mandra village under Ramana</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Iran warns US against tanker seizure as ship leaves Gibraltar...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190819075934-gqu70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-IRAN/TANKER (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Iran tanker heads to Greece after release, Iran warns U.S against seizure attempt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: High-School Students Sing Nazi Song, Give Hitler Salute...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pacifica-high-school-students-sang-nazi-song-and-gave-hitler-salute</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Athletes performed a homage to the Third Reich before an awards ceremony. Their school won’t say how they were disciplined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum revolution coming -- and Chinese at forefront...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/The-quantum-revolution-is-coming-and-Chinese-14342081.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHANGHAI - More than a decade ago, Chinese physicist Pan Jian-Wei returned home from Europe to help oversee research into some of the most important technology of the 21st century.  At a conference in Shanghai this summer, Pan and his team offered a rare peek at the work he described as a "revolution."  They spoke of the hacking-resistant communications networks they are building across China, the sensors they are designing to see through smog and around corners, and the prototype computers that may someday smash the computational power of any existing machine.  All the gear is based on quantum technology - an emerging field that could transform information processing and confer big economic and national-security advantages to countries that dominate it. To the dismay of some scientists and officials in the United States, China's formidable investment is helping it catch up with Western research in the field and, in a few areas, pull ahead.  Beijing is pouring billions into research and development and is offering Chinese scientists big perks to return home from Western labs. China's drive has sparked calls for more R&amp;D funding in the United States, and helped trigger concerns in the Trump administration that some types of scientific collaboration with China may be aiding the People's Liberation Army and hurting U.S. interests.  "The United States must be prepared for a future in which its traditional technological predominance faces new, perhaps unprecedented challenges," the Center for a New American Security wrote in a recent report about China's quantum ambitions.  Quantum technology seeks to harness the distinct properties of atoms, photons and electrons to build more powerful tools for processing information.  Last year, China had nearly twice as many patent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paging Big Brother: In AMAZON Bookstore, Orwell Gets Rewrite...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/08/19/paging-big-brother-in-amazons-bookstore-orwell-gets-a-rewrite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - SAN FRANCISCO — In George Orwell’s “1984,” the classics of literature are rewritten into Newspeak, a revision and reduction of the language meant to make</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Russia, After the Radiation Came the Rumors...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/08/17/in-russia-after-the-radiation-came-the-rumors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - ARKHANGELSK, Russia — From the promenade at the water’s edge in the city of Arkhangelsk, a view opens of the broad, fast-flowing Northern Dvina River and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F-bombs away: Lawmakers cursing more than ever...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/457732-f-bombs-away-why-lawmakers-are-cursing-now-more-than-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For lawmakers and political candidates, 2019 could be the year of not giving a f--- about cursing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rape rows risk taking sheen off starry Venice film festival...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rape-rows-risk-taking-sheen-off-starry-venice-020154001.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The star-studded Venice film festival opens Wednesday with a row raging about the inclusion of controversial directors Roman Polanski and Nate Parker. With only two women directors out of 21 in the running for its Golden Lion top prize, campaigners have lashed the festival -- now the launchpad for the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force tests droid pilot...</title>
      <link>https://newatlas.com/us-air-force-robopilot-flight/61105/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newatlas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new US Air Force kit that can turn a conventional aircraft into a robotic one has completed its maiden flight. The ROBOpilot made its first two-hour flight on August 9 at the Dugway Proving Ground in Utah after being installed in a 1968 Cessna 206 small aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gators caught climbing fences, swimming across roads in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/18/us/alligators-florida-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people know alligators get just about everywhere in Florida, but now they've really leveled up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forest therapy enthusiasts take nature's slow lane...</title>
      <link>https://www.toledoblade.com/a-e/living/2019/08/17/off-the-beaten-path-forest-therapy-enthusiasts-commune-with-nature/stories/20190818016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Stelzer was already a regular on the wooded trails of Oak Openings Preserve. A full-time retiree of about five years, he said he makes it a point to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's 26 years old but still sees pediatrician: Young adults don't move on...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/He-s-26-years-old-but-still-sees-a-pediatrician-14341430.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Joann Alfonzo, a pediatrician in Freehold, N.J., walked into her office recently she mentally rolled her eyes when she saw her next patient: a 26-year-old car salesman in a suit and tie.  "That's no longer a kid. That's a man," she recalls thinking.  Yet, Alfonzo wasn't that surprised. In the past five years, she has seen the age of her patients rise, as more young adults remain at home and, thanks to the Affordable Care Act, on their parents' health insurance until age 26.  "First it was 21, then 23 and now 26," Alfonzo says. "A lot of them can't afford to live on their own and get their own insurance, or even afford the co-pay. And if insurance is offered at work, there's generally a cost share involved, if insurance is provided at all."  The idea of young adults continuing to see their longtime pediatricians has been around for quite some time - it was a laugh line on "Friends" in its last TV season in 2004. Rachel takes her child to a pediatrician, she sees the child's father, Ross, in the waiting room and realizes he's still a patient.  But these days that's pretty realistic, Alfonzo says. "We have people who have had children, and they still see us, so we're seeing the parents and their children, concurrently," she says.  So when is it time to leave your pediatrician? Talon Manfredini, 22, says he only left his pediatrician, who is a woman, this year because he moved from his family home in New Jersey to begin a new job in Miami.  But he didn't think twice about continuing to see her, even though he'd finished college. "She just felt like a regular doctor," he says. "It didn't feel odd at all or different or weird or anything like that."  Debbie Weinberger DeFrancesco, 41, a regional sales manager for Tyson from Marlboro, N.J., says she continued to see her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demand grows for video game addiction clinics...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/aug/18/gap-in-nhs-provision-forcing-gaming-addicts-to-seek-help-abroad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Addicted teenagers travelling to overseas clinics as there are no NHS facilities to treat them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising trails off...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2019/joe-biden-online-fundraising-actblue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s online fundraising has tailed off since his campaign launch, suggesting problems generating grassroots enthusiasm, a POLITICO review of millions of digital donations shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TRASHES FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-trashes-fox-news-to-reporters-im-not-happy-with-fox-my-worst-polls-come-from-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump went on a tear against Fox News this afternoon and singled out two of the network's most notable Democratic pundits as he bemoaned what's happened to the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two mass murders world apart share common theme: 'Ecofascism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Two-mass-murders-a-world-apart-share-a-common-14341707.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the slaughter of dozens of people in Christchurch, New Zealand and El Paso, Texas this year, the accused gunmen took pains to explain their fury, including their hatred of immigrants. The statements that authorities think the men posted online share another obsession: overpopulation and environmental degradation.  The alleged Christchurch shooter, who is charged with targeting Muslims and killing 51 people in March, declared himself an "eco-fascist" and railed about immigrants' birthrates. The statement linked to the El Paso shooter, who is charged with killing 22 people in a shopping area earlier this month, bemoans water pollution, plastic waste and an American consumer culture that is "creating a massive burden for future generations."  The two mass shootings appear to be extreme examples of ecofascism - what Hampshire College professor emeriti Betsy Hartmann calls "the greening of hate."  Many white supremacists have latched onto environmental themes, drawing connections between the protection of nature and racial exclusion. These ideas have shown themselves to be particularly dangerous when adopted by unstable individuals prone to violence and convinced they must take drastic actions to stave off catastrophe.  The alleged El Paso shooter's document is full of existential despair: "My whole life I have been preparing for a future that currently doesn't exist."  In recent years, the mainstream environmental movement has moved strongly in the direction of social justice - the very opposite of what hate groups seek. Now the leaders of those organizations fear white nationalists are using green messages to lure young people to embrace racist and nativist agendas.  "Hate is always looking for an opportunity to grab hold of something," said Mustafa Santiago Ali, a vice president of the National Wildlife Federation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Williamson's presidential candidacy shines light on 'Course in Miracles'...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/politics/2019/08/18/marianne-williamson-course-miracles/39978445/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While some have labeled the practice as selfish and called Williamson wonky, there are more than 2,000 study groups around the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots with 'full AI' capable of 'replacing human intimacy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-full-ai-hit-18946556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI-AITech has launched its flagship Emma model equipped with 'full artificial intelligence'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever mandatory water cutbacks set to kick in along Colorado River...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona-environment/2019/08/15/colorado-river-water-drought-arizona-nevada-mexico-first-ever-reductions/2021147001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€˜An era of limitsâ€™ for the Colorado River: Mandatory cuts in water deliveries will take effect in 2020, reducing supplies for Arizona, Nevada, Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLY-EYED MACHINES TAKE OVER GROCERY STORES...</title>
      <link>https://wjbq.com/googly-eyed-robots-have-taken-over-new-england-grocery-stores/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjbq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this is indeed the first step of the robot takeover, it doesn't seem to be all that threatening just yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighter pilot vs. astronaut match-up in AZ could determine control of Senate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/457787-mcsally-kelly-race-in-arizona-may-determine-control-of-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2018 Arizona got a taste of what it was like to be a battleground state. Never before in modern senate campaigns had two candidates put up such an expensive and nasty fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Wallace becomes era's equal opportunity inquisitor...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/457777-chris-wallace-becomes-trump-eras-equal-opportunity-inquisitor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Wallace was nearing the end of a tense interview last year with Russian President Vladimir Putin in Helsinki, where the “Fox News Sunday” anchor had won the mercurial leader's attention by handing him an indictment implicating Russian agents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Biden has bigger problems than gaffes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/18/joe-biden-has-bigger-problems-than-just-gaffes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden, 76, has been getting heaps of attention for his verbal gaffes. Alas, voters should worry about a far bigger problem: It’s impossible to know what he stands for. Yes, some of his slip-ups…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Iran Ready to Escort Seized Tanker Back Home...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iran-ready-escort-seized-oil-114124729.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Government of Gibraltar says European Union regulations don’t allow it to seek a court order to seize a tanker which the U.S. accuses of breaching its sanctions by exporting Iranian oil.The U.S. issued a warrant to seize the supertanker, which has been detained by the U.K. and Gibraltar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRENGTH: HK PROTESTERS DEFY POLICE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/defiant-hong-kong-protesters-vow-huge-rally-despite-220012829.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sea of democracy activists flooded the streets of Hong Kong Sunday during torrential rain in a peaceful show to city leaders that their movement still pulls wide public support, despite mounting violence and increasingly stark warnings from Beijing. Hundreds of thousands of protesters carrying umbrellas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIG HEART TRANSPLANTS HOPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9745464/pig-heart-transplant-human-surgeon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIG hearts could be used for human transplants within just three YEARS, according to the surgeon who performed the first op in Britain 40 years ago. Sir Terence English said his protege from the UK…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv's Kosher Sex store seeks to give intimacy a spiritual revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-the-daughter-of-america-s-rabbi-just-opened-a-sex-shop-and-it-s-kosher-1.7683156</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THEY'RE BACK!  ISIS claims bombing at Kabul wedding that killed 63...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b5ceb0cfb33d4d73aaaadf5eee19fe9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The suicide bomber stood in the middle of the dancing, clapping crowd as hundreds of Afghan children and adults celebrated a wedding in a joyous release from Kabul's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kudlow dismisses fears of looming recession...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ffff50df5ad479e89156f31ab9d6044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERKELEY HEIGHTS, N.J. (AP) — President Donald Trump's top economic adviser is playing down fears of a looming recession after last week's sharp drop in the financial markets and predicting the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING WAITS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190818153055-vj4yj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-PROTESTS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Hong Kong protesters throng streets peacefully in pouring rain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland's ruling party condemns gay pride marches as election nears...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190818134014-q24uh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland's ruling party has used LGBT rights as a key campaign issue, depicting them as a dangerous Western idea that undermines traditional Catholic values</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy to build world's largest robot warship...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9747088/us-navy-robot-warship-unmanned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Navy wants to build a fleet of ten robot warships over the next five years. The huge ships referred to as Large Unmanned Surface Vehicle (LUSV) would function as scouts for the main battle f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 earthquakes in 5 days hit one Kansas county...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/state/kansas/article234125492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
