<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DECLARES AMERICA'S BIGGEST ENEMY IS 'FAKE NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/michael-w-chapman/trump-our-countrys-biggest-enemy-fake-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD: Serial Phone Bandit On Bike Snatches Devices Right From Pedestrians' Hands...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/nypd-search-on-for-bandit-on-bicycle-snatching-cell-phones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police believe the suspect first started the string of robberies on May 28.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is COMCASTFOX a done deal?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c0d533d459b94e29aed34b66ca4e7796/After-AT&amp;T-Time-Warner-win,-is-Comcast-Fox-a-done-deal?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Comcast will likely bid for Fox's entertainment business as early as Wednesday now that a federal judge has cleared AT&amp;T's $85 billion takeover of Time Warner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declares NKorea nuke threat over...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/31b82018ce384e1b99b300e3fbc40cad/Trump-declares-via-Twitter-the-NKorea-nuclear-threat-is-over</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump declared on Wednesday that there was "no longer a Nuclear Threat from North Korea," a dubious claim following his summit with leader Kim J</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raccoon reaches roof after scaling Minnesota skyscraper...</title>
      <link>https://www.kare11.com/article/news/climbing-mpr-raccoon-has-been-trapped/89-563763824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kare11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Public Radio news reporter Tim Nelson tweeted the news shortly after 7 a.m. saying building management had successfully captured the little raccoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Steps Up Hollywood Talent War With NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/new-amazon-chief-steps-up-talent-war-netflix-courts-a-list-creators-1119671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Salke's plan for the streamer includes "hands-on" development, 'Lord of the Rings' by 2021 and a strategy to use her deep relationships to build an "alternative to Netflix's volume."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Burton reveals live-action 'DUMBO' remake trailer...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/movies/2018/06/13/dumbo-trailer-tim-burton/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beloved big-eared baby elephant takes center stage in a film for a new generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  OBAMA FAILED TO BRING BACK GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2009/apr/14/barack-obama-world-cup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama has written to Fifa president Sepp Blatter to signal his support for the USA's bid to host either the 2018 or 2022 World Cup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN FLIPS?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-cooperate-attorneys-leave-case/story?id=55861988</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As attorneys for Michael Cohen rush to meet Judge Kimba Wood’s Friday deadline to complete a privilege review of over 3.7 million documents seized in the April 9 raids of Cohen’s New York properties and law office, a source representing this matter has disclosed to ABC News that the law firm...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anticipation surrounds Fed's rate forecasts after next hike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f953b4d3cae04ccfb189e06a6da612b9/Anticipation-surrounds-Fed's-rate-forecasts-after-next-hike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve is set Wednesday to modestly raise its key short-term interest rate for the second time this year. But attention will be focused mainly on an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: 50 worst cities to reside in...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/economy/2018/06/13/50-worst-cities-to-live-in/35909271/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall St. created an index with measures in eight categories -- crime, economy, education, environment, health, housing, infrastructure, and leisure -- to identify the 50 worst cities to live in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who shot cockfight ref? Secret arena outside Miami was packed but nobody's talking...</title>
      <link>http://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article212673589.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami-Dade police detectives are searching for the killers of Jose Garcia, a referee for cockfighting, an illegal sport that continues to draw crowds of gamblers to secret events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Stars Get Rich Making Bomb Threats and Streaming It...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/youtube-stars-get-rich-making-bomb-threats-and-streaming-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For just a few bucks, anyone can pay people like ‘Arab Andy’ to broadcast anything in public—and he makes hundred of dollars a day doing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'UFO' sighting on American west coast rogue missile?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/973702/UFO-sighting-alien-news-missile-launch-whidbey-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A STRANGE missile-shaped object blasted over the skies of western US, but military officials say that it was not a weapon, prompting confusion over what the UFO actually was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising rates, deficit spell big trouble for USA, warns bond king...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-us-is-on-a-suicide-mission-warns-bond-king-gundlach-2018-06-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Fed day and the central bank will need to fill the excitement gaps lacking after the North Korea summit. Our call of the day from Jeffrey Gundlach has a dreary forecast for the the U.S. fiscal situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria to Stage Border Defense War Games After Migrant Surge Warning...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/london/2018/06/13/austria-wargames-mass-migration-surge-border-closure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian troops will carry out war games preparing the nation’s border defence against a migration influx later this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department weighs appeal in AT&amp;T case...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/att-time-warner-what-happens-next-152884826-4be36e74-1b09-4301-b704-bc13c127bb61.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government has six days to decide whether to appeal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uruguay marijuana legalization leads to pot shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/uruguay-marijuana-legalization-pot-shortage-demand-outpaces-farmers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contrary to U.S., experts say Uruguay's licensed growers only have capacity to produce about a third of the marijuana consumed in the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thefts rise after California reduces criminal penalties...</title>
      <link>http://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/article213078369.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California researchers are linking a voter-backed reduction in criminal penalties for drug and property crimes to a jump in car burglaries, shoplifting and other theft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocks Under I-95 Present Odd, and Scary, Threat to Power Grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/13/rocks-under-i-95-present-odd-and-scary-threat-to-power-grid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocks Under I-95 Present Odd, and Scary, Threat to Power Grid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab states launch biggest assault of Yemen war with attack on main port...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180613090136-veud3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEMEN-SECURITY/ (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-Arab states launch biggest assault of Yemen war with attack on main port</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead' husband returns after police send wrong body...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/oddities/dead-husband-returns-after-japan-police-send-wrong-body/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A Japanese wife has told police the body she thought was of her missing husband belonged to a stranger after her spouse turned up alive a year later. Tokyo police acknowledged Wednesday that the body found in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55 illegals found in tractor-trailer in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/texas/article/Officials-55-people-found-in-tractor-trailer-in-12989913.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO (AP) - Dozens of people, including some children, were discovered in a tractor-trailer in San Antonio. KSAT-TV reports that authorities from several agencies were called to a North Side neighborhood around 8:30 p.m. on Tuesday and found 55 people suspected of entering the country illegally in and around a tractor-trailer. Homeland Security Investigations spokeswoman Nina Pruneda confirmed that the agency is investigating. San Antonio Fire Department chief Charles Hood says all the people appeared to be in good health. Hood said, "This truck was air-conditioned, thank God. This truck had water. So they were hydrated." Hood says five individuals were treated for minor injuries. They were transported to a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada's most famous pimp wins primary...</title>
      <link>https://lasvegassun.com/news/2018/jun/13/dennis-hof-nevadas-most-famous-pimp-wins-gop-prima/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lasvegassun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dennis Hof has dubbed himself "The Trump of Pahrump." He celebrated his win at a party in Pahrump with Hollywood Madam Heidi Fleiss ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rules man can sue GOOGLE for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/australian-court-rules-man-sue-103149548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — An Australian man who alleges Google defamed him on Wednesday won a court battle to sue the search engine giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT investigating reporter amid leak scandal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/13/new-york-times-investigating-reporter-amid-leak-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times said Tuesday that they are investigating a reporter whose information was seized amid a federal investigation of a Senate aide accused of leaking classified information. The Time…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN TROUBLE: Turkey's Election Too Close to Call, Poll Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2018-06-13/erdogan-fights-to-keep-power-as-bloomberg-poll-shows-tight-votes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey’s election this month could go down to the wire, with President Recep Tayyip Erdogan facing a tougher battle to cement power or even an upset, according to a poll commissioned by Bloomberg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NO LONGER NUKE THREAT'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180613101114-jxz9m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/TRUMP (URGENT):Trump says North Korea 'no longer a nuclear threat'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Surveillance State Will Soon Track Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-chip-in-the-windshield-chinas-surveillance-state-will-soon-track-cars-1528882203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is establishing a nationwide program to track cars using an electronic identification system, according to records and people briefed on the matter, adding to a growing array of its surveillance tools used to monitor its citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce and Jay-Z tickets 'given away for free' as stars struggle to fill seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/6513621/beyonce-jay-z-free-ticket-on-the-run-tour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEYONCE and Jay-Z gig tickets are being given away in a car park as they struggle to fill seats on their On The Run II tour. The superstar couple have thousands of unsold tickets for their UK dates…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anticipation builds for report on FBI's Clinton probe...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/391971-anticipation-builds-for-report-on-fbis-clinton-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservatives on Capitol Hill are anxiously awaiting the imminent release of a report from the Department of Justice (DOJ) inspector general scrutinizing the law enforcement agency’s handling of its investigation into Hillary Clinton’s private ema</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY: Calls for plug to be pulled on political talkshows; Fuel rise of right...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/13/populist-talkshows-fuel-rise-of-far-right-german-tv-bosses-told</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political shows’ negative focus on Islam erodes social cohesion, says cultural council</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Collect Record Taxes; Still Run $532.2B Deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/feds-collect-record-individual-income-taxes-through-may-still-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Screen Capture)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK BREXIT MESS ROLLS ON...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6514660/brexit-chaos-leavers-remainers-veto-no-deal-theresa-may/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DESPERATE Theresa May escaped a crippling defeat on Brexit yesterday in a Commons farce. The PM came through a crucial vote only after pro-EU Tories forced her to agree to boost Remainer MPs’ power…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One in three Americans take meds with depressive side effects... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/one-three-americans-meds-depressive-side-effects-study-163936830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One third of Americans are taking prescription and over-the-counter drugs, such as birth control pills, antacids and common heart medications, that may raise the risk of depression, researchers warned on Tuesday. Since the drugs are so common, people may be unaware of their potential depressive effects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Mansion Shoots for Record $135 Million!</title>
      <link>ttps://www.wsj.com/articles/los-angeles-mansion-shoots-for-a-record-135-million-1528813810 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streisand gives early nod of approval to Lady Gaga's 'STAR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/streisand-gives-early-nod-approval-lady-gagas-star-205827465.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Barbra Streisand's "A Star Is Born" is being reborn online with scenes she'd cut from the 1976 movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare type of tick inexplicably turns up in Arkansas...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rare-tick-inexplicably-turns-arkansas-204437893.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — A hardy, invasive species of tick that survived a New Jersey winter and subsequently traversed the mid-Atlantic has mysteriously arrived in Arkansas. No one is sure how the Longhorned tick, native to East Asia, arrived in the country, nor how it made its way to the middle of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAYLE KING: #MeToo Needs Due Process; Men Instantly Get Death Penalty...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/12/magazine/gayle-king-thinks-metoo-needs-due-process.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Collect Record Taxes; Still Run $532.2B Deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/feds-collect-record-individual-income-taxes-through-may-still-run https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Dfg8HF_WsAANzro.jpg </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art Basel:  $20 Million Impulse Buys Are New Normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/2018/06/12/at-art-basel-20-million-impulse-buys-are-the-new-normal </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Art Fair Where $20 Million Impulse Buys Are the New Normal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radical plan to split California into three states earns spot on ballot...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-pol-ca-california-split-three-states-20180612-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The history of California, admitted to the Union on Sept. 9, 1850, has been marked by more than 200 attempts to either reconfigure its boundaries, split it into pieces or even have the state secede and become an independent country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Stamp Enrollment Lowest in 8 Years...</title>
      <link> http://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/06/12/food-stamp-enrollment-dips-lowest-level-8-years/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  World Cup travelers' devices could be hacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-hackers-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-counterspy-warns-world-cup-travelers-devices-could-be-hacked-idUSKBN1J82YX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top U.S. counterintelligence official is advising Americans traveling to Russia for football's World Cup beginning this week that they should not take electronic devices because they are likely to be hacked by criminals or the Russian government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Keeps Meddling, Mueller Says in Bid to Guard Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/opinion/mueller-fearmongers-about-election-interference-to-try-to-hide-evidence-from-defendants-in-russian-trolls-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female judge in hot water over affair with cop who testified in murder case she presided over...</title>
      <link>https://www.livingstondaily.com/story/news/local/2018/06/12/tenure-commission-files-formal-complaint-against-judge-theresa-brennan/695384002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livingstondaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Michigan Judicial Tenure Commission has filed a formal complaint with the Michigan Supreme Court against District Court Judge Theresa Brennan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL GANGLAND: Platforms used to fan violence, protect turf...</title>
      <link>https://chicagotonight.wttw.com/2018/06/12/new-chicago-gang-book-highlights-rise-factions-social-media-use</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicagotonight.wttw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago Crime Commission on Tuesday published its first new Gang Book in six years. In it, they examine the new and changing trends and issues within gang culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How gangs use socials to fan violence, protect turf...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/social-media-fanning-chicago-gang-violence-study-225350603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media interactions are playing a "significant" role in fanning violence in Chicago, the American city with the highest murder rate, a study found Tuesday. The Chicago Crime Commission found that many of the more than 100,000 gang members in the Midwestern city are engaged in regular</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: Dem Identity Politics View Appears Cynical...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/06/12/the-democratic-partys-2018-view-of-identity-politics-is-confusing-and-thus-appears-cynical-and-opportunistic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given its rhetoric, how does the party justify supporting white male machine politicians over credible female challengers, LGBT people, and people of color?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bees -- understand the concept of zero...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1302703/bees-understand-the-concept-of-zero-or-nothingness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humans have flattered ourselves, thinking we're the only ones that understand the concept of zero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Backs Obamacare Coverage of Pre-Existing Illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-12/mcconnell-backs-obamacare-s-coverage-of-pre-existing-conditions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even after the Trump administration chose not to defend Obamacare’s protections for people with pre-existing medical conditions in court, Republican leaders are hoping the lawsuit doesn’t undo one of the most popular parts of the law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVACUATIONS ORDERED...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxla.com/news/local-news/crews-battling-brush-fire-near-beverly-glen-homes-threatened</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire crews are battling a brush fire in the Beverly Crest area, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealed: Senator Used Private Plane During 'RV Tour'...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/politics/claire-mccaskills-private-plane-used-on-campaigns-rv-tour-through-missouri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Claire McCaskill said her campaign was "hitting the road" in an RV, but public flight information indicates travel also occurred on her private plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVERLY HILLS FIRE THREATENS CELEB HOMES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/fire-homes-benedict-canyon-beverly-hills-celebrities-1202843597/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-burning brush fire is threatening the Beverly Crest area near Benedict Canyon, the location of numerous multi-million dollar mansions. KTTV reported that the fire was at 20 acres. LAFD spoke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVACUATIONS EXPECTED... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>http://ktla.com/2018/06/12/brush-fire-burning-in-beverly-crest-area-in-west-l-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 10-acre brush fire was threatening homes in the Beverly Crest area in West Los Angeles on Tuesday afternoon, officials said.  An unknown number of homes were under "immediate threat" on both flanks of the blaze, south of Yoakum Drive and north of Portal Drive, according to the L.A. Fire Department. The fire was moving toward Benedict Canyon Drive, the agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7,000 Tigers Living in USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-44444016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US has more captive tigers than the rest of the world has wild ones. Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sues NASA for ownership of space dust, claims gift fom Neil Armstrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.theregister.co.uk/2018/06/12/nasa_space_dust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theregister.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She claims it was gift from Apollo veteran Neil Armstrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to boost US Marines in Norway...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/06/12/the-corps-plans-to-boost-the-number-of-marines-in-norway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three hundred additional Marines currently in Romania will beef up the Corps' rotation in Norway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Member Calls Bernie Supporter Who Attended DNC Meetings 'Russian Plant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wvgazettemail.com/news/politics/dnc-member-calls-wv-sanders-supporter-a-russian-plant/article_52830d46-3ceb-53f0-8578-a155d74ce2b7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wvgazettemail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Selina Vickers' weekend trip to Rhode Island was as cheap as she could make it. She shelled out $143.60 for a train ticket from her home in West Virginia to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERGER MANIA INTENSIFIES</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/at-t-time-warner-merger-approval-opens-floodgates-big-media-deals-1119374</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Time Warner instantly rose 5 percent after the closing bell the moment the news broke, while shares of AT&amp;T fell 1 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;TTIMEWARNER!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/12/att-time-warner-ruling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Time Warner jumped roughly 5 percent in extended trading. Shares of AT&amp;T dropped as much as 2 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CONDITIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-12/at-t-cleared-by-judge-to-buy-time-warner-create-media-giant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T Inc. was cleared by a judge to take over Time Warner Inc. in an $85 billion deal that the mobile-phone giant says will fuel its evolution into a media powerhouse that can go head-to-head with Netflix Inc. and Amazon.com Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDDING WAR FOR FOX BEGINS; CBS NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-time-warner-m-a-at-t/att-wins-u-s-court-approval-to-buy-time-warner-for-85-billion-idUSKBN1J82QX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T Inc won approval from a U.S. court on Tuesday to buy Time Warner Inc for $85 billion, without conditions, allowing AT&amp;T to compete with internet companies that dominate digital advertising and providing new sources of revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOW TO JUSTICE DEPT...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/judge-is-set-to-decide-whether-at-t-and-time-warner-can-merge-1528832942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge ruled AT&amp;T can proceed with its planned acquisition of Time Warner Inc., rejecting the Justice Department’s allegations that the deal would suppress competition in the pay-TV industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Kim claim big summit success, but details are scant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2d80cb7d512c49978e69853a7daa4d5c/Trump,-Kim-claim-big-summit-success,-but-details-are-scant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — Claiming success at their whirlwind summit, President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un left Singapore Tuesday, praising their face-to-face progres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Michael Cohen expects to be arrested soon...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-news-trump-michael-cohen-arrested-any-day-20180612-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's legal bulldog expects to land behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Americans arming themselves to stay alive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/12/gay-americans-are-arming-themselves-to-stay-alive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t want to get beaten to death, stabbed and burnt alive,” a slight woman with long blond hair and a checked shirt says. “I want a gun to feel equal.” She is a member of one of the Unite…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charm offensive overshadows rights abuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kim-charm-offensive-overshadows-n-korea-rights-abuses-092137476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong Un's charm offensive and his historic summit with US President Donald Trump have overshadowed a more sinister side of his regime -- widespread human rights abuses, activists say. The meeting in Singapore offered a dramatic image makeover for Kim, previously known for his apocalyptic threats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;TTIMEWARNER?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/12/att-time-warner-decision-effects-on-telecoms-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entire U.S. telecommunications industry is anxiously awaiting Judge Richard Leon's decision on whether AT&amp;T can buy Time Warner. Here is how the major companies in the industry could be affected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller worries Russia could use case to spy on probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mueller-worries-russia-could-court-case-spy-probe-193320299--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller's team is worried that Russian intelligence services will use a criminal case in Washington to gather information about its investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Budget Deficit Widens; Weak Revenue...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-federal-budget-deficit-widened-in-first-eight-months-of-fiscal-2018-1528826767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government’s budget deficit widened in the first eight months of its fiscal year as spending rose faster than revenues compared with the same period a year earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada looks to ride out Trump trade storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/canada-looks-ride-trump-trade-storm-181639548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada moved to tamp down spiking tensions with the United States Tuesday, brushing aside a warning by US President Donald Trump that it will pay for Justin Trudeau's G7 summit remarks. "If the US decides to apply new tariffs, Canada will be ready," the official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless accused of having sex beneath Virgin Mary statue... </title>
      <link>https://www.app.com/story/news/crime/jersey-mayhem/2018/06/12/seaside-heights-homeless-woman-denies-church-sex/694671002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.app.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Noelle Smart, 48, pleaded not guilty to lewdness and three other charges on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alligator On Runway Stops Flights At Florida Airport...</title>
      <link>http://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/06/12/alligator-flight-stopped-alligator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customers on a Spirit Airlines flight probably weren't expecting to hear that an alligator was keeping them from getting to their destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO school nurses can dispense marijuana...</title>
      <link>http://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article213001539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Third-grade student Quintin Lovato uses medical marijuana to help with his seizures. He inspired Colorado lawmakers to sign a bill that allows school nurses to administer the medicine to students who qualify.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May offers rebels HUGE concession paving way for SOFT Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/973124/eu-withdrawal-bill-vote-live-updates-brexit-news-debate-latest-theresa-may-philip-lee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May's Brexit plans have been plunged into uncertainty after she offered Tory rebels a huge concession as MPs voted on the EU Withdrawal Bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Mistakenly Wires $93K To Cyberscammer...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/11/state-agency-wires-public-funds-to-cyberscammer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts Clean Energy Center mistakenly wired $93,679 in public funds to a criminal’s bank account, according to the state auditor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE PRAISES...</title>
      <link>https://www.vermontbiz.com/news/2018/june/12/sanders-statement-trump-kim-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vermontbiz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont Business Magazine Senator Bernie Sanders (I-Vermont) issued the following statement Tuesday following President Trump and Kim Jong Un's meeting in Singapore: "While very light on substance, the meeting between President Trump and Kim Jong Un in Singapore represents a positive step in de-escalating tensions between our countries..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS UNVEILS 'NORTHERN BORDER STRATEGY'...</title>
      <link>http://www.newsweek.com/dhs-announces-strengthened-northern-border-strategy-amid-growing-tensions-973115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The updated Northern Border Strategy’s release comes just days after President Donald Trump announced steel, aluminum and auto tariffs on its northern ally, citing a “national security” threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared to Israel, Egypt and Saudi for peace talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/kushner-travel-to-israel-egypt-saudi-arabia-for-peace-plan-talks-0c65acf3-aeb3-4aa7-9674-699de36168e5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's peace plan is almost ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force boosts nuke sniffer aircraft fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/air/2018/06/12/us-to-boost-nuke-sniffing-with-modified-c-130s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force doesn't have too many WC-135 Constant Phoenix. Enter the ever-versatile Hercules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass layoffs at TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/12/tesla-to-cut-about-9-percent-of-jobs-across-company-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt workers told to leave work, attend Stanley Cup parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.govexec.com/pay-benefits/2018/06/white-house-tells-agencies-give-dc-area-feds-time-during-capitals-stanley-cup-parade/148910/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.govexec.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPM also authorizes agencies to allow employees to telework or take other flexibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than half of Millennials expect to be millionaires...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5835419/More-half-Millennials-expect-millionaires-someday-according-new-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that 53 percent of Millennials (like multi-millionaire cosmetics mogul Kylie Jenner, pictured) believe they will one day be millionaires. Despite that, 25 percent say they'll never marry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation to change name to please neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/06/12/greece-reaches-deal-macedonia-name-dispute/694727002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Macedonia’s independence from Yugoslavia in 1991, Greece has argued that the young country’s name implied a claim to the territory and ancient heritage of Greece’s northern region of Macedonia – birthplace of ancient warrior king Alexander the Great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Confronted at Book Signing About Groping Women...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/biden-confronted-at-book-signing-about-groping-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charitable giving in USA tops $400 billion for first time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/84a9d91f4ff749398dd634dc10ff5938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fueled by a surging stock market and huge gifts from billionaires, charitable giving in the United States in 2017 topped the $400 billion mark for the first time,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flies home with lots to brag about...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0acd517d8f94b649c3d49bb17238235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — All North Korean leader Kim Jong Un really needed from his unprecedented summit with U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday was to keep his nuclear a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians fear for safety as threats skyrocket...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/11/politicians-fear-for-safety-as-threats-against-congress-skyrocket/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Rep. Barry Loudermilk of Georgia bought body armor. Rep. Gregg Harper hired armed security guards for events back home in Mississippi. And Rep. Dan Dovonan fortified his Brooklyn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia building 'laser cannon' death ray...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/11/russia-building-space-gun-laser-death-ray-terrifying-sounds-7621352/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Putin soon have the ability to wage space war using a massive new laser weapon?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's unlikely allies on  talks --  progressive Dems!</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article212960759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump found an unlikely source of support as he meets with North Korea leader Kim Jong-un: Democrats. Some of the same Democrats who complain that he stole the election and want to impeach him praise him for engaging in diplomacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Summit produced less than many analysts expected...</title>
      <link>http://www.courant.com/nation-world/ct-la-summit-assessment-20180612-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The much-hyped summit between President Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un produces little guidance for real de-nuclearization or other steps to pacify the Korean peninsula. Instead, it offers much of what failed in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-stakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/high-stakes-ruling-awaited-t-time-warner-merger-142911568.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high-stakes decision in a US court Tuesday will be significant for the future of Big Media, Big Tech and big business in general. A US federal judge was set to announce his verdict in the $85 billion merger of wireless and broadband giant AT&amp;T with media-entertainment conglomerate Time Warner. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch anti-Islam party to hold Prophet Mohammad cartoon competition...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/dutch-anti-islam-party-hold-prophet-mohammad-cartoon-151742746.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Freedom Party of Dutch anti-Islam politician Geert Wilders will hold a competition of cartoons depicting the Prophet Mohammad, it said on Tuesday. The party said the plan to hold the competition in the party's secure offices in Dutch Parliament had been approved by the Dutch Counter-terrorism</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
