<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NC county bans Coke machines over 'left wing' politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/3/surry-county-north-carolina-bans-coke-machines-ove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Carolina county commission has kicked Coca-Cola vending machines from government office buildings, accusing the soda giant of engaging in left-wing politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET RUSSIAN TECH?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3014192/uk-us-investigate-ufo-pentagon-report-hypersonic-aircraft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world must ramp up its investigations into UFOs as the Pentagon’s “disturbing” report appears unable to rule out that foreign hypersonic technology could be behind the sightings, an expert clai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK harvest of face scans...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3015362/tiktok-privacy-policy-face-voice-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIKTOK has updated its privacy policy in the US so it can collect things like “faceprints and voiceprints” from its users. The app said it “may collect biometric identifiers and biometric informati…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Puppies Born With Human-Like Social Skills, Wired To Communicate With People...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/puppies-human-like-social-skills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We found that there's definitely a strong genetic component, and they're definitely doing it from the get-go," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis star arrested for 'deliberately losing match'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/sport/other-sports/french-open-match-fixing-arrested-24248080?%3F%3F=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian tennis star Yana Sizikova was arrested on Thursday evening on suspicion of deliberately losing a match at the ongoing Roland Garros tournament in France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>151,620,000 Americans Employed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/national/susan-jones/bls-151620000-americans-employed-may-444000-more-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a disappointing employment report in April, the Labor Department's Bureau of Labor Statistics on Friday produced an improving picture as the nation continued to emerge from its COVID slump in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  $7 Gas In CA?</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/03/most-expensive-gas-in-the-us-mendocino/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is currently charging $6.73 a gallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK marketing user thoughts, prayers?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/facebook-wants-your-thoughts-and-prayers-1847028464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s found a new way to capitalize on the thoughts, prayers (and data) from the religious side of its user base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum protesters denounce Picasso's treatment of women...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210604131756-1fl24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPAIN-MUSEUM/PROTEST (PIX, TV):Museum protesters denounce Picasso's treatment of women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake patient reviews make it increasingly hard to find medical help on GOOGLE, YELP...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fake-patient-reviews-are-making-it-increasingly-hard-to-seek-medical-help-on-google-yelp-and-other-directory-sites/ar-AAKHtpN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia scrambles fighter jet to accompany U.S. military plane...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210604123153-5pygs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/MILITARY (URGENT):Russia scrambles fighter jet to accompany U.S. military plane</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrest erupts after man dies in Minneapolis arrest attempt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/death-of-george-floyd-minneapolis-business-death-of-daunte-wright-shootings-0c3907f72981ad591187d07a393e698d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Crowds vandalized buildings and stole from businesses in Minneapolis’ Uptown neighborhood after officials said a man wanted for illegally possessing a gun was fatally shot by authorities who were part of a task force trying to arrest him that included U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent cardinal offers to resign, citing 'catastrophe' of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/prominent-german-cardinal-offers-to-resign-citing-e2-80-98catastrophe-e2-80-99-of-sexual-abuse/ar-AAKHTds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reinhard Marx, the archbishop of Munich and Freising, is a close adviser to Pope Francis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear videos show Chinese weapons tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1445491/UFO-investigation-Pentagon-aliens-China-Russia-military-threat-hypersonic-weapons-news-vn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON'S highly-anticipated report into UFOs has been briefed by US intelligence officials ahead of its release, with suggestions that the mysterious objects and inexplicable technology captured on video could in fact be experiments from Chinese and Russian military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VT decriminalizes possession of opioid addiction drug...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vermont-opioids-health-0b9efd46f0eed0d765fc576a9d29139e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTPELIER, Vt. (AP) — Gov. Phil Scott has signed a bill into law decriminalizing possession of the opioid use disorder treatment drug buprenorphine. The measure decriminalizes possession of up to 224 milligrams of the drug by people without a prescription, WPTZ-TV reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIRING STRUGGLES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-bb295afe6ec8d8b88b1b944f3eba7931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. employers added a modest 559,000 jobs in May, an improvement from April’s sluggish gain but still evidence that many companies are struggling to find enough workers as the economy rapidly recovers from the pandemic recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She could hold keys to dismantling world's most dangerous cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/04/emma-coronel-el-chapo-wife-sinaloa-cartel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Chapo's wife, Emma Coronel Aispuro, could be the key to smashing the notorious Sinaloa drug cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY JOBS: +559K...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/04/jobs-report-may-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls in May were expected to increase by 671,000, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci calls on China to release medical records of Wuhan researchers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/556815-fauci-calls-on-china-to-release-medical-records-of-wuhan-researchers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci is calling on China to release medical records of researchers at a laboratory in Wuhan, China, that reportedly became sick with COVID-like symptoms prior to the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart reaction probed as possible vax link in teens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-vaccine-coronavirus-pandemic-health-0d56422a02293617feb211bb02587dcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health authorities are trying to determine whether heart inflammation that can occur along with many types of infections could also be a rare side effect in teens and young adults after the second dose of COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bottom 90% of Americans Borrowing From Top 1%...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-04/the-bottom-90-of-americans-are-borrowing-from-the-top-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The savings of the rich are recycled into household and government debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>East L.A., cradle of Mexican American culture, seeks greater independence...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210604085100-2wab9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-LATINOS/EAST LA (PIX):East L.A., the cradle of Mexican American culture, seeks greater independence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Rising: Hedge Funds, Big Tech Drive Lone Star Wealth Boom...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-rising-hedge-funds-big-090000238.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Big Tech is flocking to Austin. Big Finance is expanding in Dallas. Houston, the epicenter of the U.S. energy industry, is diversifying away from Big Oil.Florida may be the destination of choice for A-list money managers looking to flee Wall Street. But in the post-pandemic economy, Texas is rising, welcoming a rush of talented, wealthy people from California, New York and Illinois with the lure of lower taxes, luxury suburbs and opportunities to invest their cash -- even as state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU, UK Open First Antitrust Probe Into FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/eu-u-k-open-first-094534961.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- European scrutiny of U.S. tech giants reached a crescendo on Friday as antitrust watchdogs across the continent hit Facebook Inc. and Google with separate probes.The European Commission said it will investigate whether Facebook misuses a trove of data gathered from advertisers to compete against them in classified ads. It will also check if the company unfairly ties its Marketplace small ad service to the social network.At the same time, the U.K said it was opening probes into Fac</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report does not confirm, or rule out, UFOs in unexplained aerial events...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/report-does-not-confirm-or-rule-out-ufos-in-unexplained-aerial-events/ar-AAKH2JF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressionally mandated study comes as once-fringe discussion of UFOs gains mainstream traction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns of continent-wide third wave in Africa...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/556810-who-warns-of-continent-wide-third-wave-in-africa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization (WHO) on Thursday warned of a continentwide third wave of coronavirus cases in Africa as the continent's countries see major spikes in COVID-19 infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt for Clarity About van Gogh's Last Days Leads to Maine...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/04/the-hunt-for-clarity-about-van-goghs-last-days-leads-to-maine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 19th-century painter Edmund Walpole Brooke occupies a tiny, but durable place in art history. Not because of his own</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover Operative Says She Recruited 'Proud Boys'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/this-undercover-operative-says-she-recruited-the-proud-boys-for-the-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Just received this from the GOP. They are asking me to potentially gather the ’boys and all the patriots and lead a literal (non violent) charge on the County Elections office.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SO WHAT ARE THEY?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3011747/ufos-investigated-pentagons-report-rubio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SENATOR Marco Rubio said UFOs need to be “seriously investigated” before the bombshell Pentagon report drops later this month. On Thursday, a spokesperson for the Republican senator tol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Warns Companies to Act Now on Defenses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/white-house-warns-companies-step-up-cybersecurity-2021-06-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House warned corporate executives and business leaders on Thursday to step up security measures to protect against ransomware attacks after intrusions disrupted operations at a major meatpacking company and the biggest U.S. fuel pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court narrows anti-hacking law, worries about criminalizing common behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-narrows-anti-hacking-law-worries-about-criminalizing-common-behavior/ar-AAKGjCg?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Amy Coney Barrett writes for unusual majority of Trump nominees and liberals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach mayor to feds: Florida's gambling compact with tribe is corrupt, illegal and should be rejected!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/miami-beach-mayor-to-feds-florida-s-gambling-compact-with-tribe-is-corrupt-illegal-and-should-be-rejected/ar-AAKGnLp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — As Florida's historic sports gambling deal with the Seminole Tribe is being reviewed for approval by the federal government, Miami Beach Mayor Dan Gelber on Thursday sent a letter to the U.S. Department of the Interior urging it to reject what he calls a "tortured artifice," negotiated with the corrupt intent to expand gambling in Florida — in violation of both state and federal law. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memphis digging up remains of Confederate general who led early KKK...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/memphis-is-digging-up-the-remains-of-a-confederate-general-who-led-the-early-kkk/ar-AAKEib0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since 1904, the bodies of Forrest and his wife have laid in the city park that was named in his honor for more than a century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graffiti plague returns to Manhattan!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/graffiti-a-growing-problem-for-soho-store-owners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graffiti is now a growing problem in SoHo, as the neighborhood has been the target of vandals in recent weeks and local shop owners say the eyesores are keeping customers away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Covid collides with HIV, the pandemic may be taking an ominous turn</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-collides-hiv-aids-100051925.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in South Africa have documented an ominous development: the collision of the COVID-19 pandemic with HIV/AIDS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED leaker gets 6 months in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/03/treasury-official-sentenced-491781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natalie Mayflower Sours Edwards admitted to conspiring to violate the Bank Secrecy Act by disclosing what prosecutors said were more than 2,000 “suspicious activity reports.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVT FINDS NO EVIDENCE OF ALIEN SPACECRAFT</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/06/03/us/politics/ufos-sighting-alien-spacecraft-pentagon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strange objects witnessed by Navy pilots remain unexplained, but officials briefed on a new study say they are not secret technology from a classified American program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Dumps Dollar...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/russia-cuts-dollar-holdings-119-100449669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia said it will eliminate the dollar from its oil fund to reduce vulnerability to Western sanctions just two weeks before President Vladimir Putin holds his first summit meeting with U.S. leader Joe Biden.The National Wellbeing Fund will shift its dollar holdings into euros, yuan and gold, Finance Minister Anton Siluanov said.The dollar pared gains on the news Thursday before bouncing back as analysts said the immediate market impact is likely to be limited. The transfer will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA NIGHTMARE SUMMER</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/california-drought-summer-wildfire-a0e2c959-8d76-4c56-af5d-e13b1ee76e6f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Southwest is drying out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOES PUSH FOR QUICK VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-politics-netanyahu-lapid-bennett-e96cc15e2474658e271e373cd4d6aeda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s opponents pushed Thursday for a quick parliament vote to formally end his lengthy rule, hoping to head off any last-minute attempts to derail their newly announced coalition government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrinking giants: North Atlantic right whales getting tinier...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-climate-change-whales-science-environment-and-nature-e8478d8d6decf8a6cf4c9037f0c60f2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the giants of the deep is shrinking before our eyes, a new study says. The younger generation of critically endangered  North Atlantic right whales are on average about three feet (one meter) shorter than whales were 20 years, drone and aircraft data show in a study in Thursday’s journal Current Biology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-printed 'electric nose' can SNIFF out virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9648775/3D-printed-electric-nose-SNIFF-COVID-19-just-80-seconds-94-accuracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'electric nose' sits in the nostril and uses deep learning to sniff out the coronavirus, which emits specific smelling chemicals. The device produces results in just 80 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of elder care is here: Artificial intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jun/03/elder-care-artificial-intelligence-software</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Computers are increasingly guiding decisions about elder care – and tracking everything from toilet visits to whether someone has bathed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden offers to keep '17 tax cuts intact in infrastructure counteroffer ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-offers-to-keep-2017-trump-tax-cuts-intact-in-infrastructure-counteroffer-to-gop/ar-AAKFOS8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's new offer to pay for infrastructure would look to end tax loopholes for corporations but not raise the corporate tax rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity attorney F. Lee Bailey dead at 87...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ma-state-wire-f-lee-bailey-entertainment-celebrity-8cdd719dd3dbfa6c2ea30bc853f8b036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALTHAM, Mass. (AP) — F. Lee Bailey, the celebrity attorney who defended O.J. Simpson, Patricia Hearst and the alleged Boston Strangler, but whose legal career halted when he was disbarred in two states, has died, a former colleague said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Self-described 'Trump man' copped to serial pooping spree targeting home of Biden supporters...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/trump-fan-busted-for-serial-pooping-spree-547906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 3--A 70-year-old Ohio man who told cops he was a “Trump man” confessed to repeatedly urinating and defecating in front of a neighbor’s home because the residents "are Democrats and support Joe B</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation drugs track, kill cancer: 'Next big wave'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cancer-science-business-health-54e08ed1a440669a88932aba505d2e54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors are reporting improved survival in men with advanced prostate cancer from an experimental drug that delivers radiation directly to tumor cells. Few such drugs are approved now, but the approach may become a new way to treat patients with other hard-to-reach or inoperable cancers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booming Market for Woke Gurus...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/culture/what-wokes-worth-and-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early 2019, Ta-Nehisi Coates delivered the inaugural "Distinguished Diversity Lecture" at the Ohio State University. Coates’s hourlong engagement, which included a reading, a moderated conversation, and an audience Q&amp;A, cost OSU $41,500.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When Doctors Can't Tell the Truth?</title>
      <link>https://bariweiss.substack.com/p/what-happens-when-doctors-cant-speak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bariweiss.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whole areas of research are off-limits. Top physicians treat patients based on their race. An ideological 'purge' is underway in American medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bodycam Video Shows Deputies In Shootout With Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/volusia-county-florida-shootout-12-14-year-old-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Volusia County Sheriff's Office said the children shot at the deputies for more than half an hour Tuesday night, before the deputies returned fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic deaths soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210603180749-ydzgn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-TRAFFIC (URGENT):U.S. traffic deaths soar to 38,680 in 2020; highest yearly total since 2007</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quake at underwater Hawaii volcano shakes Big Island...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hi-state-wire-hawaii-earthquakes-science-75a58084ec1b72e92a917ac0d9c2df1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — An earthquake at an active deep sea volcano off Hawaii shook the Big Island but didn't appear to have any impact on other nearby volcanoes and no significant damage was reported. The U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90% of Sharks Were Mysteriously Wiped Out, Never Recovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvzj5m/90-of-sharks-were-mysteriously-wiped-out-and-never-recovered-scientists-find</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They made it through the asteroid impacts, they've made it through global warming, global cooling, and all sorts of things. And yet this event that we didn't know about wiped out 90 percent of them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY MAIL Published Nude Photos of Katie Hill. Now She Has to Pay Them $100k...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/katie-hill-daily-mail-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge decided today that the former Congresswoman is on the hook for the tabloid's legal fees in her revenge porn lawsuit against it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sly smuggler uses Border Patrol for free trips home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/3/sly-smuggler-uses-border-patrol-free-trips-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the category of not all crooks are stupid, one accused migrant smuggler figured out an ingenious way to cut in half the time it took him to get back to Mexico from the U.S. to prepare for his next load of people: He turned himself in to the Border Patrol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuated after anonymous threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/03/europe/air-france-flight-ecavuated-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers on an Air France flight were evacuated in Paris on Thursday after an anonymous threat, the company said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  No explosive device aboard the AIR FRANCE flight...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210603163813-jmh9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-CHAD/ (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-No explosive device aboard the Air France flight from Chad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Turmoil erupts at DAILYNEWS as owner pushes buyouts...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/03/union-turmoil-erupts-at-daily-news-owner-as-hedge-fund-pushes-buyouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tribune Publishing is asking all of its full-time editorial staffers to consider voluntary buyouts at all nine major metro dailies in the chain, which is now controlled by the cost-slashing hedge f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st cruise ship sails through Venice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-entertainment-music-health-coronavirus-pandemic-52e1150bd621486282a4d677aaaf29b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOAVE, Italy (AP) — Early risers in Venice were surprised Thursday to see a cruise ship nosing down the Giudecca canal for the first time since the start of the pandemic, despite repeated government pledges to reroute such huge vessels due to safety and environmental concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE BLUNDER! New iOS system 'draining battery life FAST'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3008745/ios-update-ruins-iphone-battery-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IPHONE users have been reporting battery issues after upgrading to the Apple’s latest iOS 14.6 software. Apple’s Community Forum is full of complaints about the issue and users have also take…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA-SHAM! Influencer 'brags about flying business class', is then snapped in economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/3008218/instagram-model-pretending-fly-business-class-selfie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FRENCH Instagrammer has been caught out by fans posting a picture of herself in business class but actually flying in economy. Model and reality TV star, Oceane El Himer, 27, uploaded the Instagr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pupil Size Marker of Intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/pupil-size-is-a-marker-of-intelligence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scientificamerican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a surprising correlation between baseline pupil size and several measures of cognitive ability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone wants to debate Bannon as traitor to movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/06/03/maga-throwdown-roger-stone-wants-to-debate-steve-bannon-as-traitor-to-trump-movement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will lumbering MAGAsaurs do battle? Stone throws down "gauntlet" to "sloppy Steve" in Infowars appearance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S trials artificial intelligence drive-through system to cut waiting times...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mcdonalds-trials-artificial-intelligence-drive-24244345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology is being tested 10 branches in the US, but it has so far proven to be only 85% accurate, with the remaining 15% of orders needing to be corrected by staff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FRIENDS' Producer Stands by All-White Casting Amid Scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/tv-shows/news/friends-producer-stands-by-all-white-casting-amidst-continued-scrutiny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following the Friends reunion, producers of the popular sitcom are facing a myriad of complaints [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Attributes Meat Industry Cyberattack To Russia-Linked Op...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/06/02/greeley-jbs-cyberattack-fbi-attributes-revil-ransomware-operation-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cyberattack that disrupted operations at JBS, the world's largest meat supplier, is now attributed to a Russia-linked ransomware operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI investigating Postmaster General Louis DeJoy in connection with his political fundraising...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/FBI-investigating-Postmaster-General-Louis-DeJoy-16222392.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The FBI is investigating Postmaster General Louis DeJoy in connection with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lab-Leak Theory: Inside Fight to Uncover Origins...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/the-lab-leak-theory-inside-the-fight-to-uncover-covid-19s-origins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout 2020, the notion that the novel coronavirus leaked from a lab was off-limits. Those who dared to push for transparency say toxic politics and hidden agendas kept us in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake rattles San Jose...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/california/article251864413.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It was so big and shook my whole bed, it was very scary. Scarier than most earthquakes.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Pushes Forward With Olympics Despite Covid Crisis, Public Doubts... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tokyo-olympics-2021-move-forward-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Tokyo marked 50 days until the start of the Olympics, most of Japan is still under a COVID-19​ state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://scedc.caltech.edu/recent/Maps/122-37.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scedc.caltech.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
