<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Could Be Most Powerful in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/07/joe-bidens-vice-president-powerful-history/614161/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’d need to maintain a healthy partnership with his deputy—without worrying that she’ll outshine him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters clash with police in violent encounter at Chicago's Columbus statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/07/18/chicago-protest-columbus-statue-18-police-wounded-12-arrested/5464162002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of protesters attempting to topple the city's Christopher Columbus statute faced off with dozens of Chicago police Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Creepy Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/its-spooky-right-now-inside-the-creepy-federal-crackdown-on-portland-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Customs and Border Protection joined the protest crackdown in D.C., they were made into U.S. Marshals. In Portland, they’re using new powers provided by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Low-Budget Horror Is Thriving This Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2020/07/why-low-budget-horror-thriving-summer/614344/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These dirt-cheap productions are making money, finding eager audiences, and garnering critical praise during a largely dead box-office season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lollapalooza co-founder predicts no concerts until 2022...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/507946-lollapalooza-co-founder-predicts-no-concerts-until-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lollapalooza co-founder Marc Geiger predicts there may not be concerts or festivals in the U.S. until 2022 due to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground parties continue to dismiss social distancing rules...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/18/underground-parties-continue-to-dismiss-social-distancing-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clubs continue to be called out for packed parties that don’t follow social distancing rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trusted employee arrested in grisly murder of tech CEO... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/17/tyrese-haspil-charged-with-murdering-tech-ceo-fahim-saleh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trusted employee of tech CEO and investor Fahim Saleh was arrested on Friday in his boss’ slaying and dismemberment on the Lower East Side — with sources saying the motive involved a broken promi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China city enters 'wartime mode'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200718112239-8lt36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/CHINA-CASES (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-China's western city Urumqi enters 'wartime mode' after reporting 16 coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising Opposition...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/18/federal-officers-in-portland-face-rising-opposition-on-streets-and-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. — An aggressive federal campaign to suppress unrest in Portland appears to have instead rejuvenated the city’s movement,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Star, Web Founder Team Up on Tech for Humans to Communicate With Animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/rock-star-and-internet-founder-team-up-on-dr-dolittle-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rock Star and Internet Founder Team Up on Dr Dolittle Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor who survived bewildered by public disregard...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3f548ec32bf6b7dd198f26c90b8cff2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIRMINGHAM, Ala. (AP) — Dr. Michael Saag spends much of his time treating patients fighting for their lives and working with colleagues who are overwhelmed and exhausted by the relentless battle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP senators sound alarm as cases surge in home states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/507924-gop-senators-sound-alarm-as-coronavirus-surges-in-home-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are raising the alarm over the country's rapidly growing number of coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistrust Could Imperil Widespread Immunity...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/18/mistrust-of-a-coronavirus-vaccine-could-imperil-widespread-immunity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost daily, President Trump and leaders worldwide say they are racing to develop a coronavirus vaccine, in perhaps the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathtaking virus numbers show normal life still far away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c0d1e01ffd786d510a37951d758a996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — South Africa was poised on Saturday to join the top five countries most affected by the coronavirus, while breathtaking numbers around the world were a reminder that a return...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to launch mini space station as military takes to stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/pentagon-launch-mini-space-station-22366865 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bermuda Pitches Island Life as Escape From Pandemic Madness...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/bermuda-pitches-island-life-as-escape-from-pandemic-madness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For anyone tired of dodging coronavirus Bermuda has an offer: a year at the beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal Case Launched After 15th Century Cathedral in Nantes Catches on Fire...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/europe/202007181079921473-cathedral-in-nantes-france-catches-on-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Roman Catholic church located in Nantes, Pays de la Loire, France has caught fire a year after a devastating blaze hit the Notre-Dame cathedral in Paris, partially...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surging Dems expand Senate targets to Republican states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/269c5a18f098ec93e8a63fc460a78e0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It's come to this for Republicans straining to defend their Senate majority in November's elections: They're air-dropping millions of dollars into races in Alabama, Kentucky and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rancor between scientists and allies threatens response... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/rancor-between-scientists-and-trump-allies-threatens-pandemic-response-as-cases-surge/ar-BB16SFa2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  FOXNEWS host fact-checks Trump claim -- to his face!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chris-wallace-calls-out-trump-in-new-interview-for-claim-biden-wants-to-defund-the-police-sir-he-does-not/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Chris Wallace spoke to President Donald Trump for the first time in a long while, and he shared a preview of the hour-long sit-down on Friday with Bill Hemmer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU files lawsuit over federal agents in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/507922-aclu-files-lawsuit-over-federal-agents-in-portland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) on Friday filed a lawsuit against the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) and U.S. Marshals Service after they deployed agents to quell demonstrations in Portland, Ore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parscale calls media 'criminal network'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/507897-trump-campaigns-brad-parscale-calls-media-criminal-network</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brad Parscale, who was recently demoted as the campaign manager of President Trump, called the media a "criminal network" and "America's biggest enemy" in a Friday tweet, drawing criticism from journalists on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden seizes book by Jewish comedian criticizing war-time collaboration...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/sweden-seizes-book-by-jewish-comedian-criticizing-war-time-collaboration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State claims cover of book violates a copyright, but Aron Flam says it's satire and authorities are using it as an excuse to suppress free speech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW PEAK NOW:  USA 77,638 INFECTIONS IN PAST 24 HOURS...</title>
      <link>https://www.macaubusiness.com/us-sets-another-virus-record-with-77638-new-cases-johns-hopkins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macaubusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International, MNA | The United States marked a record number of coronavirus cases Friday for the third consecutive day, notching 77,638 new infections in 24 hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man leaves hospital after 100 day fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/long-island-man-leaves-hospital-after-106-day-fight-with-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hafeez Yehman was released from Long Island Jewish Medical Center in New Hyde Park on Friday after a 106-day hospitalization due to coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Virus-deaths-rise-with-records-set-in-hard-hit-15416982.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For weeks this summer, it was a seeming paradox of the coronavirus pandemic: cases in the United States were rising but deaths were falling.  To the Trump administration, this was evidence that its strategy for combating covid-19 was working. To medical experts, it was only a matter of time before the trajectory changed.  And now it has. Nationwide, deaths have begun to rise again. In some of the worst-hit states, especially across the South and the West, new death records are being set daily. As a virus-scarred summer wears on, public health specialists say the numbers are almost certain to continue to climb.  "Even if we could magically lock everyone in their room and no one transmits to anyone, we would still be seeing an increase in deaths for the next several weeks," said Catherine Troisi, an epidemiologist with UTHealth School of Public Health in Houston.  That grim assessment came as the United States on Friday set another record for total cases, with more than 76,000 - including a new high of nearly 15,000 in Texas alone.  More than 900 people died, matching a death count of recent days that has consistently hovered just below 1,000. That is well beneath the toll during the virus's most devastating stretch, in April, when 2,000 or more people were dying daily nationwide. But it is also well above the totals earlier this month, when the average number of daily deaths dropped below 500.  More than 136,000 people in the United States have died of covid-19, the disease caused by the novel coronavirus.  The recent increase in fatalities follows a nationwide surge in cases that has brought the country record numbers of new infections. Public health experts have long said that the death count is a lagging indicator - with patients typically taking two to three weeks after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain tells millions stay home...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-passes-1-million-virus-cases-global-crisis-075359195.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four million residents of Spain's second city Barcelona were told to stay at home Friday, as virus cases rise, while EU leaders met in Brussels seeking to rescue Europe's economy from the ravages of the pandemic. "We must take a step back to avoid returning in coming weeks to a total lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil outbreak has 'plateaued'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-virus-outbreak-plateaued-172133726.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new coronavirus outbreak in hard-hit Brazil has plateaued, the World Health Organization said Friday, urging the country to seize the opportunity to drive down transmission. "The rise in Brazil is no longer exponential, it has plateaued," WHO health emergencies chief Michael Ryan told</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation divided over mask wearing and schools reopening...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200717181509-g9t4g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 5-U.S. divided over mask wearing and schools reopening as coronavirus cases surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans eye sweeping shield from liability...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/97196fa5f70f07a2e46cdd27b74f496d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A new plan from Senate Republicans to award businesses, schools, and universities sweeping exemptions from lawsuits arising from inadequate coronavirus safeguards is putting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Law Enforcement Use Unmarked Vehicles To Grab Protesters Off Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/It-was-like-being-preyed-upon-Federal-officers-15415096.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal customs officials said Friday that their agents had detained a demonstrator in Portland, Ore., who had described being "terrified" by an encounter with unidentified men in military fatigues, offering a defense amid intense criticism of accounts of federal officials circulating in the city in unmarked cars.  Mark Pettibone, a 29-year-old demonstrator, told The Washington Post he was scared when men in green military fatigues and generic "police" patches jumped out of an unmarked minivan early Wednesday. Reports of similar incidents have sparked condemnation from civil-rights activists and lawmakers.  Pettibone told The Washington Post in an interview he did not know who detained him. In a statement on Friday, U.S. Customs and Border Protection said its agents had taken the action and that they "had information indicating the person in the video was suspected of assaults against federal agents or destruction of federal property."  When the agents approached him, Customs said, "a large and violent mob moved towards their location. For everyone's safety, CBP agents quickly moved the suspect to a safer location for further questioning."  The agency also disputed his description of not knowing who detained him, saying: "The CBP agents identified themselves and were wearing CBP insignia during the encounter. The names of the agents were not displayed due to recent doxing incidents against law enforcement personnel who serve and protect our country."  In Pettibone's account, when several men in fatigues approached him, his first instinct was to run.  He did not know whether the men were police or far-right extremists, who frequently don militarylike outfits and harass left-leaning protesters in Portland. The 29-year-old resident said he made it about a half-block before he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House blocks director from testifying...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/507876-white-house-blocks-cdc-director-from-testifying-before-house-panel-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is rebuffing House Democrats' effort to hear testimony from Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) Director Robert Redfield on safely reopening schools during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SERVICES UNREACHABLE</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2020/07/17/cloudflare-dns-goes-down-taking-a-large-piece-of-the-internet-with-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many major websites and services were unreachable for a period Friday afternoon due to issues at Cloudflare’s 1.1.1.1 DNS service. The outage seems to have started at about 2:15 Pacific time and lasted for about 25 minutes before connections began to be restored. Google DNS may also have been…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNET SITES BUCKLE AFTER WEB OUTAGE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/internet-down-outage-cloudflare-hack-dns-google-1202988757/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE,3:31 PM: The Internet is actually not under siege and you can still watch Netflix over the weekend, it turns out – though it certainly felt like the digital world had collapsed to PONG…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov calls for 'Trump's federal officers to leave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/protesters-portland-oregon-clash-police-federal-officers-during-chaotic-night-n1234160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Videos on social media show federal officers in camouflage aiming weapons and using smoke to press protesters back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW Scores All-Time High With Interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/rachel-maddow-show-scores-all-time-high-mary-trump-interview-1303655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MSNBC anchor draws her biggest audience ever with an episode featuring the president's niece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTY'S OVER: 8 P.M. CURFEW IN SOUTH BEACH!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/17/new-curfew-partygoers-south-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party is over in Miami Beach’s entertainment district as the city issues a new 8 p.m. curfew in South Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Strike teams' to visit businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.wesh.com/article/orange-county-putting-together-coronavirus-strike-team-to-randomly-inspect-businesses/33342050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wesh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The county is looking to make sure businesses are complying with reopening guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists identify 6 types of coronavirus with increasing severity levels...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-identify-six-different-types-185531392.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six distinct types of coronavirus have been identified by scientists in a breakthrough that promises to save lives by flagging the highest-risk patients. Analysis of thousands of cases by artificial intelligence software has revealed different "clusters" of symptoms and ranked them in order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random abductions of citizens by 'Homeland'?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/07/17/dhs-border-patrol-agents-randomly-detain-protesters-portland-oregon-homeland-security-chad-wolf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security is not answering questions about Border Patrol agents allegedly detaining people in Portland, Oregon without cause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With antibodies fading fast, vaccine hopes fade, too...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/With-coronavirus-antibodies-fading-fast-focus-15414533.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent studies indicate that the human body does not retain the antibodies that build up when people are infected with the coronavirus, meaning there may be no lasting immunity to the virus, even with a vaccine. The news reinforces a decision by scientists at UCSF’s Quantitative Biosciences Institute to develop treatments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mo'Nique's NETFLIX Discrimination Case Moves Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/live-updates-protests-for-racial-justice/2020/07/17/892351564/monique-s-netflix-discrimination-case-moves-forward</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge says Oscar-winning actress's discrimination and retaliation suit against Netflix can move forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdered and dismembered by own employee?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8532799/Was-tech-millionaire-murdered-dismembered-employee-NYPD-hunts-person-interest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police sources say the person of interest worked for the victim and their business deal apparently went bad. Cops are not releasing the name of the person, who is not yet in custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders USA to accept new DACA applications...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/17/politics/daca-trump-judge/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration must begin accepting new applications for the Obama-era program that shields undocumented immigrants who came to the US as children from deportation, a federal judge ruled Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Orders Schools In Watch-Listed Counties To Stay Closed...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/17/newsom-orders-schools-counties-watch-list-stay-closed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty counties remain on the state’s watch list, including Los Angeles, Orange, Riverside, San Bernardino and Ventura.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,449,990,800% return on investment? Welcome to NFL owners club...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/sports/story/2020-07-17/nfl-billionaire-team-owners-who-rule-sports-united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team-by-team look at the NFL team owners who collectively control football and the richest sports league in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran air defense on high alert amid explosions...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iranian-air-defense-on-high-alert-amid-explosions-report-635370</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early 2020, Iran confirmed its air defense batteries mistakenly shot down a Ukrainian plane killing all 176 people on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations getting out of control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/17/health/us-coronavirus-friday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battles over wearing face coverings intensified even as the US shattered another daily coronavirus record and health officials warned hospitalizations are getting out of control in some areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Critic of Big Tech Has Side Gig Working for AMAZONAPPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-07-17/amazon-apple-hire-one-of-big-tech-s-most-prominent-u-s-critics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning: Italy's Mafias eye EU's billions in recovery funds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1a1766c2d285ae9677b8fd2b053bfe52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italy’s anti-Mafia investigators issued a dramatic warning Friday that mobsters will scheme to get some of hundreds of billions of euros in European Union recovery aid after the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida church's statue of Jesus beheaded...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/florida-churchs-statue-of-jesus-beheaded-similar-attacks-occur-across-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statue of Jesus Christ was decapitated and knocked off a pedestal at a Catholic church in Florida, another in a string of similar incidents nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floridians worry contact tracing calls are scams...</title>
      <link>https://www.bradenton.com/news/coronavirus/article244271002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bradenton.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Supreme Court's Ginsburg says she's being treated for liver cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/17/supreme-courts-ginsburg-says-shes-being-treated-for-liver-cancer-but-still-working-full-steam.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 87-year-old justice said she began a course of chemotherapy in May to treat a recurrence of cancer after a February scan revealed lesions on her liver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubba Wallace Booed at NASCAR Qualifier, Cheered After Crash...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/news/bubba-wallace-booed-nascar-all-star-race-qualifer-cheered-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bubba Wallace took some heat before he competed in the NASCAR All-Star Open, which was the race to [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank CEOs warn of tougher economic road ahead...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-bank-ceos-warn-tougher-110000679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The road to recovery for the U.S. economy will be uneven, unclear and uncertain as the coronavirus retains its hold on business and Americans’ everyday activities, according to the heads of the nation’s biggest banks.In the wake of brighter data on employment, retail sales and housing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body decapitated and dismembered in Manhattan condo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae17e405d2f7840f2c8b87ad03c33860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A person was taken into police custody Friday in the killing of a 33-year-old tech entrepreneur found dismembered inside his luxury Manhattan condo, two law enforcement officials...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
