<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to read Ukraine call transcript to American people...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/fireside-chat-on-live-television-trump-says-he-wants-to-read-transcript-of-ukraine-call-to-american-people  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A defiant President Trump signaled he will not cooperate with the Democratic Party's impeachment proceedings, insisting his telephone conversation with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky was "a good call" and that he might read it aloud to Americans so they can see his point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Days of terrifying darkness, cold and hunger amid PG&amp;E's sweeping power blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.omaha.com/news/national/days-of-terrifying-darkness-cold-and-hunger-amid-pg-e/article_2bf8fd0b-94a0-52e4-9b9a-087e98dc0541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEARLAKE, Calif. — For four nights, Eliana Rubin cared for her newborn son, James, by candlelight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER NO MORE!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-lifelong-new-yorker-declares-himself-a-resident-of-florida/ar-AAJFly0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  DEADSPIN Revolt Is Latest Clash as Private Equity Swallows Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/deadspin-revolt-is-latest-clash-as-private-equity-swallows-media/ar-AAJEWDC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake firefighters entering evacuated areas to loot homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7635979/California-police-warn-FAKE-firefighters-trying-loot-wildfire-devastated-areas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sonoma County Sheriff's Office announced they're investigating reports of fake firefighters in the area of the Kincade Fire in Northern California on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watchdog sues FBI over facial recognition secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/watchdog-sues-fbi-over-facial-recognition-secrecy-185123202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A civil liberties watchdog Thursday sued the FBI and other federal agencies claiming the government is improperly withholding information on how it uses a facial recognition database of millions of Americans. "Because of the FBI's secrecy, little is known about how the agency is supercharging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidency on Treacherous New Ground...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-presidency-treacherous-ground-house-182244439.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s presidency stands on its most treacherous ground after the House voted Thursday to approve and proceed with its impeachment inquiry.The resolution, passed on a largely party-line 232-196 vote, does not just lay out a road map for the public phase of the inquiry. It sends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inquiry Faces Critical Test...</title>
      <link>https://justrealnews.ca/2019/10/28/moving-closer-to-trump-impeachment-inquiry-faces-critical-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justrealnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYT &gt; U.S. &gt; Politics WASHINGTON — House impeachment investigators are speeding toward new White House barriers meant to block crucial testimony and evidence from the people who are closest to President Trump — obstacles that could soon test the limits of Democrats’ fact finding a month into their inquiry. What has been a rapidly …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt officials around globe targeted for hacking through WHATSAPP...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191031220251-c0v3i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK-CYBER/WHATSAPP-NSOGROUP (UPDATE 3, EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Government officials around the globe targeted for hacking through WhatsApp -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president dismisses report alleging military discontent...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191031205645-okprt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-MILITARY/:Mexican president dismisses report alleging military discontent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keystone pipeline shut after spilling 9,000 barrels of oil in NDakota...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191031180757-6lurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIPELINE SPILL/NDAKOTA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Keystone pipeline shut after spilling 9,000 barrels of oil in N. Dakota</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Trump aide confirms Biden probe linked to Ukraine aid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6b5c1b4adbc40dda0bb4f7fba8bae1d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A former top White House official confirmed Thursday that military aid to Ukraine was held up by President Donald Trump's demand for the ally to investigate Democrats and Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDS CALM IN CA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96b6eaacf3fa49d3be2575fdfc3c2caf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDSOR, Calif. (AP) — Lynn Darst and her husband were camped out in their motor home on the edge of their seats for four days wondering if their house would survive yet another wildfire menacing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists working on pill to edit memories...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/eternal-sunshine-of-the-spotless-mind</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are working on ways to edit memories — to make the intolerable bearable — by, say, blocking the synaptic changes needed for a memory to solidify</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING grounds 50 planes over cracks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boeing-says-50-planes-grounded-052100893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween asteroid flyby one of the closest near misses ever seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/spooky-halloween-asteroid-flyby-one-of-the-closest-near-misses-ever-seen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A big space boulder scopes out the trick-or-treating situation here on Earth. Fortunately, it doesn't knock on any doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The empty 'ghost' homes of Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20191023-what-will-japan-do-with-all-of-its-empty-ghost-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 20% of its population aged 70 and older and the birth rate declining, Japan has a property problem: there are more homes than people to live in them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Of Profanity: Swearing Can Reduce Pain During Workouts...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/10/30/researchers-using-curse-words-can-help-combat-pain-improve-your-workouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say, whether it is socially acceptable or not, cursing can actually improve fitness and endurance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasty floor fight sets baseline...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/nasty-house-floor-fight-sets-baseline-trump-impeachment-n1074791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: Mostly unified Democrats now know the challenge in front of them — and the bar starts high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Director Corroborates Quid Pro Quo...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-official-corroborates-diplomats-account-that-trump-appeared-to-seek-quid-pro-quo/ar-AAJC0dv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign to end child marriage in the USA runs into some surprising opposition...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/child-marriage-in-us-cbsn-originals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"In 38 states, what would otherwise be considered felony rape becomes completely legal once a marriage license is handed out," one activist said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists hail new cystic fibrosis treatment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-hail-cystic-fibrosis-treatment-184623585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new triple-drug therapy that tackles the genetic causes of cystic fibrosis has been shown to be highly effective in treating the rare life-threatening disorder, scientists reported Thursday following landmark clinical trials. The finding -- 30 years after the gene that causes the disease was identified</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Again Gives Iran Green Light to Conduct Sensitive Nuke Work...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/trump-admin-again-gives-iran-green-light-to-conduct-sensitive-nuclear-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has again approved a series of sanctions waivers on Iran that permit the Islamic Republic to engage in sensitive nuclear work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions over 'edits'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/401efdc06a334f4a87365eb9b3107af4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The question has long baffled lawmakers: What is missing from the White House's rough transcript of President Donald Trump phone call with Ukrainian President Volodymr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Bradleys, Army infantry roll into Syria to secure oil...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/2019/10/31/bradleys-and-army-infantry-roll-into-syria-to-help-secure-oil-wells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Army Col. Myles B. Caggins III, a spokesman for the U.S.-led mission to defeat ISIS in Iraq and Syria, said the mechanized forces moving in to Deir ez-Zor province, Syria, hailed from the 30th Armored Brigade Combat team, a National Guard unit from South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haunted houses -- property bargains!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/money/homeandproperty/haunted-house-ghostly-homes-are-property-bargains/ar-AAJCm1r?li=AA64tF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Reality TV Series: 'Man vs. Bear'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/discovery-channel-pits-man-bear-competition-series-1251267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Humans will be entering the bear's territory and take them on in a competition like never attempted," the network says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Depositors in Denmark May Be Facing Record Negative Rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/banking-finance/world-record-in-negative-rates-has-bankers-testing-no-mans-land</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businesstimes.com.sg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[COPENHAGEN] After more than seven years of negative rates, some of Denmark's biggest banks are resorting to uncharted territory in order to cope with the extreme monetary regime. Read more at The Business Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires 2 missiles amid stalled talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-10-31/north-korea-launches-missile-test-prompting-escalation-fears </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeping up with the Qardashians: New ISIS caliph is Sharia judge Abdullah Qardash...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10252802/isis-names-new-leader-as-the-professor-abdullah-qardash-in-message-confirming-baghdadis-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FORMER officer in Saddam Hussein’s army has today taken over as the new leader of ISIS after the terror group finally confirmed the death of Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi. Abdullah Qardash – known as the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 2 Dems Vote Against... </title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article236856433.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-Record Low Ratings Despite Game 7...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/world-series-game-7-tv-ratings-wednesday-oct-30-2019-1251424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Nationals' first-ever title delivers the biggest audience for baseball in two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAY TO PLAY:  APPLE laying groundwork for iPhone subscription!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/30/apple-lays-groundwork-for-iphone-or-apple-prime-subscription.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple could bundle hardware upgrades with services such as iCloud storage or Apple TV+ content and hardware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>96-year-old snowfall record smashed in Chicago after Halloween storm... </title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/halloween-snowstorm-wallops-the-midwest/611593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nats fan drops F-bomb on live TV, calls Trump '---hole' in White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/468286-fan-blasts-trump-on-live-tv-as-asshole-in-the-white-house-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Washington Nationals fan is going viral after footage showed him dropping the F-bomb on live television and blasting President Trump as an "asshole" shortly after his team’s World Series win on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters, police in Halloween standoff...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/080c53f88d7449a0964e42ea948c89a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Police and protesters engaged in a standoff in Hong Kong's nightlife district on Thursday after pro-democracy demonstrators urged people to celebrate Halloween by wearing masks in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same-sex love scene was cut from movie on DELTA flights. So was word 'lesbian'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-same-sex-love-scene-was-cut-from-a-movie-on-14637534.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Near the end of the 2019 film "Booksmart," a tense bathroom kiss between Amy, the film's timid, justice-minded lead, and Hope, her high school's "basic hot girl," turns into more: Hidden from a house party outside, they engage in a hookup that's been hailed as an unusually frank, on-screen portrayal of sex between two women.  But watch "Booksmart" on a Delta Air Lines flight, and the R-rated high school comedy will skip right through that scene. Reportedly, the in-flight cut also passes over the words "vagina" and "genitals," an exchange about a lesbian sex act, talk of a urinary tract infection, and a bit in which Amy and her friend watch porn in the back of a ride-share.  Amid calls of censorship, those edits - made by an outside company that works with the airline - are drawing the ire and confusion of passengers and Hollywood insiders alike, in what's at least the fourth instance when same-sex romance has been stripped from an in-flight Delta movie in recent years.  "If it's not X-rated, surely it's acceptable on an airplane," director Olivia Wilde said at an awards show on Sunday night. "There's insane violence of bodies being smashed in half [in other movies], and yet a love scene between two women is censored from the film. It's such an integral part of this character's journey. I don't understand it."  In a statement to The Washington Post early on Thursday, Delta said its "content parameters do not in any way ask for the removal of homosexual content from the film."  But it's not the first time the airline has come under fire for the situation - or, for that matter, even the only time this week. On Tuesday, other Delta passengers protested that the in-flight cut of "Rocketman," the Elton John biopic released this year, was missing sex scenes and even a chaste kiss between two men.  The same was true of "Carol,"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insanely humanlike androids enter workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/31/human-like-androids-have-entered-the-workplace-and-may-take-your-job.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian start-up Promobot recently unveiled what it calls the world's first android. It closely resembles a real person and can perform workplace tasks, such as accepting payments and answering customer questions. The android comes with an artificial intelligence system that has more than 100,000 speech modules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT HALLOWEEN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd2765706ced4eb29c8737348c64d55c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats pushed a package of ground rules for their impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump toward certain House passage on Thursday as the chamber neared the first formal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of Theaters? 'IRISHMAN' Opens in Less Than Half of Country...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/10/31/the-end-of-theaters-the-irishman-opens-tomorrow-in-less-than-half-the-us-one-theater-only-in-most-places-concentration-in-new-york-and-los-angeles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it the beginning of the end for movie theaters? Tomorrow, Netflix opens Martin Scorsese’s epic “The Irishman” — highly touted for the Academy Awards — in just a han…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mankind's belief in evil 'caused by disease'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/scientists-discover-mankinds-belief-evil-20762415</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A potentially-massive breakthrough in our understanding of evil may have been found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Live pigs used as crash-test dummies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7634193/Live-pigs-used-crash-test-dummies-killed-China.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifteen immature pigs (some of which are seen in their car seats) were strapped in for high-speed simulations in a study carried out in China which killed seven of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Fertility Crisis Has Govts Scrambling for Answer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2019-global-fertility-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS Manager Suing Company for Discrimination Against White People...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/10/31/former-center-city-starbucks-manager-suing-company-for-alleged-discrimination-against-white-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former regional manager of a Center City Starbucks where two black men were arrested last year for sitting inside the store is suing the company for allegedly discriminating against white people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The city preparing for collapse of capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/oct/31/us-city-preparing-itself-for-the-collapse-of-capitalism </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a festival that helps artists trade work for healthcare to a regional micro-currency, Kingston is trying to build an inclusive and self-sufficient local ecosystem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?465765-1/us-house-debates-impeachment-inquiry-resolution</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House debates and votes on a resolution that lays out the next steps in the impeachment investigation of President Trump, including public hearings, and rights for the president and minority…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Veteran Catherine Herridge Moves to CBS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/catherine-herridge-cbs-news-fox-news-channel-1203389192/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catherine Herridge, a Fox News Channel veteran who has been with that network since it was founded in 1996, is moving to rival CBS News. She will work as a senior investigative correspondent out of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In swing state Ohio, are workers still on President's side?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/swing-state-ohio-workers-still-trumps-side-022912827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Rust Belt state of Ohio, where Donald Trump unexpectedly earned significant support in 2016, some voters are wondering why the "greatest economy in American history" is passing them by. Workers for General Motors spent more than a month on the picket line here, carrying signs and huddling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants on Greek islands 'on edge of catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/migrants-greek-islands-edge-catastrophe-council-europe-110646687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The situation for migrants in camps on Greek islands is "explosive" and "on the edge of catastrophe", the Council of Europe's Commissioner for Human Rights said Thursday. Greece has once again become the main point of entry for people seeking asylum in Europe and it is struggling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUVRE in push to display 'missing' Da Vinci...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/louvre-push-display-missing-da-vinci-culture-expert-115742325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Louvre museum has made an "offer" to the owner of the world's most expensive painting to allow it to be displayed in a Leonardo da Vinci exhibition in Paris, a French cultural body chief said Thursday. The world-famous Salvator Mundi has not been seen in public since it was sold for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House to formalize Trump impeachment investigation... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-formalize-trump-impeachment-investigation-061523863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats laid out a formal roadmap for President Donald Trump's impeachment Thursday as they accumulated more evidence to support charges that he improperly pushed Ukraine to boost his own 2020 electoral prospects. One day after a decorated army officer told Congressional investigators he witnessed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists say quarter of all pigs could die of swine fever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4d525760e304520899eb10a7b084ea2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY (AP) — Around a quarter of the world's pigs are expected to die from African swine fever as authorities grapple with a complex disease spreading rapidly in the globalization era, the World...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires spare Reagan library but menace homes in SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a5c14ddf1dd4130bf02c5a33f21c379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIMI VALLEY, Calif. (AP) — Santa Ana winds were expected to linger for a final day Thursday after driving more than a dozen wildfires through California, sending thousands fleeing and burning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog helps police ID pedestrian hit by vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/dog-helps-police-id-pedestrian-hit-vehicle-66659341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in New Jersey say a dog helped officers find the home of a pedestrian who was struck by a vehicle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People always running late happier...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/study-people-always-running-late-are-happier-and-healthier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who usually run late also tend to be happier and live longer, this according to a new study from Harvard University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory loss set by age 8...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/10/30/memory-loss-mental-decline-old-age-largely-decided-age-eight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memory loss and mental decline in old age is largely decided by the age of eight, a new study has shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Harper trolled after NATS win without him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/world-series-bryce-harper-trolled-on-twitter-after-nationals-win-world-series-without-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nationals unlikely October run ended in a title</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Bans Online Material 'Inciting Violence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/h-k-court-bans-online-materials-inciting-violence-report-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;H.K. Court Bans Online Materials Inciting Violence, Report Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How Rudy May Cost President Dearly...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5714722/rudy-giuliani-transformation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is going on with Giuliani?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Vote to Open Intense Public Phase of Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-inquiry-vote-show-080000555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Democrats hold a historic vote on Thursday to kick off the public phase of an inquiry of President Donald Trump that moves significantly closer to a vote to impeach him.The vote, which is expected to break down mostly along party lines, doesn’t make his conviction and removal from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Boasts on Economy Undercut by Weak Pay Gains...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-boasts-economy-undercut-weak-080000204.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.President Donald Trump boasts that a robust economy will protect him from impeachment and ensure his re-election, but it’s an argument resting on a shaky foundation.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia set to disconnect from Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/russia-disconnect-internet-tomorrow-test-20763305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The test will see Russia revert to an internal version of the web called ‘RuNet’ which is isolated from the networks of other nations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORGET BUGS, PEOPLE NOW EATING 'HUMAN BLOOD SAUSAGE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/forget-bugs-some-people-are-now-eating-human-blood-sausage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, really.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divisive docket to test Supreme Court ahead of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/468224-divisive-docket-to-test-supreme-court-ahead-of-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court is poised to rule on a range of controversial political issues in its current term, potentially putting the high court's broad popularity with the public to the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Republicans shift tone on impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/468246-senate-gop-shifts-tone-on-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans are taking the House impeachment proceedings against President Trump more seriously as damaging revelations against the president mount and the possibility of a quick dismissal of the charges shrinks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires 2 missiles amid stalled talks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed0a113001fb40ff95a854bf3c176f49 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea on Thursday fired two projectiles into its eastern sea, an apparent resumption of weapons tests aimed at ramping up pressure on Washington over a stalemate in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2-HOUR WAITS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7633481/Chaos-LAX-ban-curbside-Uber-Lyft-pickups-leaves-thousands-passengers-stranded.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures were high into the seventies in LA yesterday afternoon, but the sizzling Autumnal heat did little to compare to the boiling tempers of the travelers stuck in heavy traffic in LAX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Campaign Holds 'Witch Hunt' Halloween Party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-campaign-holds-witch-hunt-021941396.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joyce Bollini, in a tall black witch hat, gestured at her yellow T-shirt when asked why she and her friend Cynthia Lane, attended a Trump campaign Halloween “Witch Hunt Party” in Lancaster County, Pennsylvania, on a drizzly Wednesday evening.The T-shirts worn by Bollini and Lane had the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX apologizes after UBER policy causes gridlock...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/oct/30/lax-uber-lyft-rideshare-pickup-shuttle-traffic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ban on curbside rideshare pickups leads passengers to report wait times longer than the flights themselves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton Fuels Rumors of Hillary 2020:  'She May or May Not'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/10/bill-clinton-fuels-rumors-of-a-hillary-2020-run-she-may-or-may-not-run-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House lawyer moved to classified server...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-lawyer-moved-transcript-of-trump-call-to-classified-server-after-ukraine-adviser-raised-alarms/ar-AAJC8D7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE DIVIDED ON PARTY LINES...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-hoped-theyd-win-over-republicans-on-impeachment-but-its-not-looking-that-way-so-far/ar-AAJC2PN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD SERIES TRIUMPH!</title>
      <link>https://www.mlb.com/news/nationals-win-2019-world-series</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Down Howie Kendrick reached and off it went. Carrying far, slicing right, pinging the yellow-coated steel screen of the foul pole in right field. The Washington Nationals were trailing until they weren’t. They were, true to form, down but not done.   The late-May misfits and National League Wild</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak feared in Bahamas as nation put on 'high alert'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ebola-outbreak-feared-bahamas-nation-20762175</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus has killed thousands of people in Africa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing club of very powerful countries steering away from dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/31/de-dollarization-russia-china-eu-are-motivated-to-shift-from-using-usd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The greenback's status as the world's major reserve currency could come under threat, as a group of countries seeks to undermine its importance, according to Anne Korin of the Institute for the Analysis of Global Security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent Crime, Robberies Surge in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2019/10/30/statistics-show-paris-violent-crime-robberies-surging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crime statistics in Paris show a continued surge in violent crime, with some areas seeing as much as a 70 per cent rise in violent incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keystone pipeline leaks oil in North Dakota...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/832aca2a059f471c993a55788a3fc719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BISMARCK, N.D. (AP) — A pipeline that carries tar sands oil from Canada through seven states has leaked an unknown amount of crude oil over more than quarter-mile swath in northeastern North...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
