<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>IDF chief orders plans to thwart Iran's nuke program...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/idf-chief-ive-instructed-military-to-prepare-plans-to-thwart-irans-nuke-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The only samurai colony ever attempted outside of Japan was in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/sfhistory/article/wakamatsu-farm-japanese-immigrants-california-15896619.php?IPID=SFGate-HP-CP-Spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first families from Japan arrived in California with fanfare, and most disappeared...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic Incidents Surge; 'Moving Into Dangerous Phase'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/anti-semitic-incidents-on-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Jewish leaders said the growth of crimes against Jews intensified under former President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Fueling Deaths Of Despair...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/01/26/960492035/deaths-of-despair-how-the-pandemic-may-be-fueling-lethal-drug-overdoses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As drug overdose deaths rise during the pandemic, a former White House economist says social isolation could be partly to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: AC Unit Falls On FDNY Firefighter While Battling Blaze...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/01/26/air-conditioning-unit-falls-on-firefighter-in-bensonhurst-brooklyn-fdny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrifying moments were caught on camera at the scene of a fire in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Scant spread in schools --  with precautions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-finds-with-precautions-in-place-scant-spread-of-coronavirus-in-schools/ar-BB1d7hsi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers warn that indoor athletics, without masks and with close contact, pose danger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERIZONGOOGLEZOOM stall out...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/east-coast-internet-outages-494451f9-73bb-4025-9730-36ab5a6ad5d6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet users in the Washington-to-Boston corridor reported widespread outages Tuesday affecting service for both broadband and internet content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Weighs Race-Based Preferences...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/01/26/oregon-weighs-race-based-vaccine-preferences/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of allowing people with chronic medical conditions to get a higher place in line, a pivotal Oregon committee leans into racial justice considerations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes to tongue, hands or feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/changes-to-tongue-hands-or-feet-may-flag-coronavirus-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AFP) - Changes to the tongue, the hands or the soles of the feet could give an early indication of Covid-19 infection, Spanish researchers found in a study presented on Tuesday (Jan 26).. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing lung cancer cases -- turning up in unexpected population...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/01/26/growing-share-of-lung-cancer-turning-up-in-never-smokers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists disagree whether the number of lung cancer patients who never smoked is increasing, but the proportion who never did clearly is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian Premier Resigns as Instability Grows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-pm-quit-tuesday-seeking-193455597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte resigned Tuesday in the hope of forming a new government after weeks of turmoil in his ruling coalition, leaving Italy rudderless as it battles the deadly coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany mulls cutting all international air traffic...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-01-germany-mulls-international-air-traffic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany is considering almost completely halting flights into the country to slow the spread of more infectious strains of the coronavirus, Interior Minister Horst Seehofer said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread internet outages hit northeast... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/widespread-internet-outages-hit-northeast-175129937.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Verizon reported a fiber cut in Brooklyn via Twitter, although it’s not clear if that issue is responsible for the entire outage. The internet service provider didn't have any estimate when the problem spot would be fixed. Neither Verizon nor Comcast, another major internet service provider, immediately responded to requests for comment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's pandemic policy: No police. No curfews. No fines. No regrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Mexico-s-pandemic-policy-No-police-No-curfews-15898157.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - As the coronavirus swept the globe early last year, Mexican officials made...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orders Gov't Agencies to Buy American-Made Products...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/policy/2021/01/biden-orders-agencies-buy-more-american-made-products-and-publicly-post-exemptions/171613/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The order seeks to close existing loopholes and creates a new oversight regime, including a GSA-hosted website to post waivers publicly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  Neighborhood cat mauled to death after owners sic dogs on NYC strays...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/neighborhood-cat-mauled-to-death-after-owners-sic-dogs-on-group-of-brooklyn-strays/2848290/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One woman said that the owners let the dogs go after the cats, and when one escaped up a tree, they forced it to go back down to be mauled by the canine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye to Hollywood? ALBUQUERQUE Named Best for Moviemakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/best-places-to-live-and-work-as-a-moviemaker-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s list of the Best Places to Live and Work as a Moviemaker is different than any we’ve done before, because never have so many moviemakers seriously considered changing their lives dramatically — starting with where they live. Best Places Hall of Famers Los Angeles and New York City will always be our greatest […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 in USA has STD...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/1-in-5-americans-have-sexually-transmitted-diseases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New federal data show that an estimated 1 in 5 people in the United States have had a sexually transmitted infection on any given day and half of them are in people under the age of 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST executive editor Baron announces retirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/26/media/marty-baron/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marty Baron, the editor who transformed the Washington Post into an international powerhouse and led the news organization to win 10 Pulitzer Prizes, is retiring next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon restricted commander of DC Guard before riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pentagon-restricted-commander-of-D-C-Guard-15899083.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The commander of the District of Columbia National Guard said the Pentagon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortion Drama Leads SPIRIT AWARD Nominations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/2021-independent-spirit-awards-nominations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indie Spirit nominations are here, and the 36th Annual Independent Spirit Awards will air on Thursday, April 22 on IFC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS TO ADDRESS NATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/13853311/uk-covid-deaths-pass-100000-boris-johnson-address-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE than 100,000 people have now died with Covid in the UK – as Boris Johnson prepares to mark a bleak day in the battle against the deadly virus with a national address. A further 1,631 peo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACKED!  OR DID SHE SET UP HER MOM?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2211974/claudia-conway-nude-picture-leak-kellyanne-hacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLAUDIA Conway said she thinks her mom Kellyanne was hacked after an alleged nude photo leak and urged “don’t incite violence.” “I have faith and I know that my mother would…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fonda to Receive Cecil B. DeMille at GLOBES...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/01/26/triumph-jane-fonda-to-receive-golden-globes-cecil-b-demille-lifetime-achievement-award-for-acting-activism-philanthropy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Triumph! Jane Fonda will receive the Cecil B. DeMille Lifetime Achievement Award from the Golden Globes on February 28th. The two time Oscar winner will be honored for her acting, activism, and phi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  Entire family, including baby, found dead in Michigan woods...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlive.com/news/saginaw-bay-city/2021/01/missing-bay-city-family-found-dead-in-northern-michigan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The three were found outside their vehicle in Ogemaw County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani wasn't just Trump partisan but shrewd marketer of vitamins, gold, lawsuit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Giuliani-wasn-t-just-a-Trump-partisan-but-a-15898262.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he outlined how</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Sarah Huckabee Sanders' shameless campaign for gov...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/962986/sarah-huckabee-sanders-shameless-campaign-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can the former White House spokesperson lie her way to the Arkansas governor's mansion?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEATH TOLL TOPS 100,000 IN UK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-tsunamis-united-kingdom-coronavirus-pandemic-leeds-76f125a9c79a766f4d8e84220a09804c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — For nine months, Gordon Bonner has been in the “hinterlands of despair and desolation” after losing his wife of 63 years to the coronavirus pandemic that has now taken the lives of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citing pandemic, Greece bans protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-greece-coronavirus-pandemic-2a2859442f65ded4f522eb5d7782cf10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Greece’s center-right government on Tuesday imposed a weeklong ban on public protests attended by more than 100 people, angering left-wing political opponents. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA LOOSENS UP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-sacramento-coronavirus-pandemic-california-gavin-newsom-fc0c15eb5e7359b4bae50602f79a2cfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California’s health department on Monday released to the public previously secret projections for future hospital intensive care unit capacity throughout the state, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All border wall construction stops TONIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/all-border-wall-construction-to-be-stopped-tuesday-night</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Construction workers on the U.S.-Mexico border were notified to stop all border wall projects by the end of Tuesday, according to a congressman whose district sits on the international boundary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCTV...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/13852432/quarantine-hotels-inside-room-rules-food/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL arrivals to the UK could be forced to quarantine at a hotel for 14 days as Boris Johnson is expected to announce the new travel restrictions later today. Australia and New Zealand already have …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 signs of 'new Covid' to watch for...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2211498/symptoms-new-covid-strains-6-signs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS the coronavirus continues to spread across the world it has also mutated and there are now three significant new variants of the virus. Experts have warned the UK variant, which was first discov…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE:  WE ARE ALL OK...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/01/26/george-conway-responds-to-family-scandal-posts-plea-from-daughter-claudia-i-am-okay-we-are-okay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, father of Claudia, posted this Tweet just now. Claudia says “I am okay, we are okay.” The Conways are America’s most visible dysfunctional family thanks to the abho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland mayor pepper sprays man after confrontation at restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2021/01/portland-mayor-ted-wheeler-contacts-police-after-unspecified-weekend-incident.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The encounter marks the latest incident where individuals have aggressively confronted Mayor Wheeler in public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Bombers Were Dress Rehearsal For War...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidaxe/2021/01/26/those-bombers-china-sent-toward-taiwan-they-were-a-dress-rehearsal-for-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;War, if and when it comes, could begin with Chinese bombers barreling toward Taiwan like they did on Saturday. Here's how it could play out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Undetermined'...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/breaking-news/hc-br-zappos-ceo-tony-hsieh-new-london-fire-report-20210126-lrxsk56nczcadokqoxldxnob6q-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New London fire officials released a report Tuesday that offered no definitive cause for the November blaze that killed former Zappos CEO Tony Hsieh, but pointed to candles, improperly discarded smoking materials, a propane heater or even a careless or intentional act sparking the fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who lived at church for 3 years goes home after Biden suspends deportations...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-francisca-lino-leaving-church-20210124-3wlphevu7zcodn2emclwg7vzs4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who has lived in a Humboldt Park church for three and a half years to avoid deportation returned home Saturday night to live with her family after President Joe Biden’s 100-day moratorium on deportations went into effect Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail billionaire slept with propane tank, candle before fire that killed him...</title>
      <link>https://www.8newsnow.com/news/i-team-tony-hsieh-death-investigation-fire-las-vegas-nevada-new-london-zappos-ceo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.8newsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I-Team: Tony Hsieh slept with propane tank, candle before fire that killed him, report says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shops boarded up as Dutch brace for fourth night of anti-lockdown riots...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210126145428-qs0kn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NETHERLANDS-PROTESTS (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Shops boarded up as Dutch brace for fourth night of coronavirus riots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Power Naps Recharge Brain, Improve Mental Sharpness, Lower Risk Of Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/afternoon-naps-better-mental-sharpness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study finds regular naps have a connection to better locational awareness, verbal fluency, and working memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the people paying $55 million each to fly to space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/meet-the-people-paying-2455-million-each-to-fly-to-the-space-station/ar-BB1d6LFc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first space crew composed entirely of private citizens includes two grandfathers and a father with three young children. All are extremely wealthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai had virus licked. Then flung open doors...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Dubai-seemed-to-have-the-coronavirus-licked-Then-15898768.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates - After a 12-hour shift in the Old Souk one day last week,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech companies could see blowout fourth quarters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/26/tech-companies-could-see-blowout-fourth-quarters-for-ad-revenue-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The setup couldn't be any better for the digital ad names," Bernstein analysts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Green juices, lots of CBD: Inside Martha Stewart wellness routine at 79...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/26/inside-martha-stewarts-wellness-routine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martha Stewart talks to CNBC Make It about her health and wellness routine, where she gets her drive, how she handles stress and getting the Covid vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to impose moratorium on new oil and gas leasing on federal lands and waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/2021/01/25/biden-drilling-moratorium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The planned moratorium would halt oil and gas auctions as the new administration reviews the program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Aims to Turn Small Town Into QAnon, USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mayor-aims-to-turn-small-town-into-qanon-usa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think we’re a little microcosm of what’s happening at the national level," said Marsha Maguire, a resident of Sequim, Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Suspends Two Executives Accused of Racist and Sexist Conduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cbs-executives-placed-on-leave-after-reports-of-racist-and-sexist-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A company statement said there would be an independent investigation into issues raised in a report in the Los Angeles Times that accused an executive of making "racist, sexist, homophopic and discriminatory comments."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONWAY SHOW: Kellyanne Accused Of Leaking Topless Photo Of Teen Daughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.unilad.co.uk/news/kellyanne-conway-accused-of-leaking-topless-photo-of-her-teen-daughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unilad.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump spokesperson Kellyanne Conway has been accused of leaking a nude photo of her teenage daughter. Conway, who served as Senior Counsellor to Donald Trump, has been the subject of abuse allegations from her 16-year-old daughter Claudia. In a number of TikTok videos, Claudia accused her mother of being &amp;#8216;physically, mentally, and emotionally abusive&amp;#8217;. &amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani wasn't just Trump partisan but shrewd marketer of vitamins, gold, lawsuit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/giuliani-wasn-e2-80-99t-just-a-trump-partisan-but-a-shrewd-marketer-of-vitamins-gold-lawsuit-says/ar-BB1d6vNJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s personal lawyer sought to turn unfounded conspiracy theories and voter fraud videos into online moneymakers, attorneys said in a lawsuit seeking more than $1.3 billion in damages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claudia Asks Followers To Report To Authorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.aceshowbiz.com/news/view/00165657.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aceshowbiz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 16-year-old avid TikTok user takes to the video sharing platform to ask her followers to report her mom to authorities after the former White House advisor allegedly posts the photo on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinaloa Cartel Setting up Front Operations to Hijack New Legal Pot Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-sinaloa-cartel-is-setting-up-front-operations-to-hijack-mexicos-new-legal-pot-market</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cartel farmers tell the Daily Beast they are importing stronger—more lucrative—strains of marijuana to sell in the legal market and maximize profits through front operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life inside quarantine hotel from locked windows to police guarding room...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/life-inside-covid-quarantine-hotel-23385949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the UK government is expected to announce mandatory quarantine for incoming travellers today, countries including New Zealand, Australia, Hong Kong and India have been making people quarantine for months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chic abayas on catwalk in rare Saudi fashion show...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210126-chic-abayas-on-the-catwalk-in-rare-saudi-fashion-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chic abayas on the catwalk in rare Saudi fashion show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air pollution linked to irreversible sight loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210126-air-pollution-linked-to-irreversible-sight-loss-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air pollution linked to irreversible sight loss: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to conduct military drills in South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210126031622-wd6my</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTHCHINASEA-CHINA/DRILLS:China to conduct military drills in S. China Sea amid tensions with U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER permanently bans MY PILLOW CEO...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-media-elections-presidential-elections-ac34de7cb5844d96589a10ea6e653d50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has permanently banned My Pillow CEO Mike Lindell’s account after he continued to perpetuate the baseless claim that Donald Trump won the 2020 U.S. presidential election. Twitter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THIS IS ME': Rioters flaunt involvement in Capitol siege...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-media-social-media-f9a4050fc3179c87e0c29b8872e020e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — These suspects weren't exactly in hiding. “THIS IS ME,” one man posted on Instagram with a hand emoji pointing to himself in a picture of the violent mob descending on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan air force flexes muscles after latest Chinese incursion...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-taiwan-security/taiwan-air-force-flexes-muscles-after-latest-chinese-incursion-idUSKBN29V0ID</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed and ready to go, Taiwan air force jets screamed into the sky on Tuesday in a drill to simulate a war scenario, showing its fleet's battle readiness after dozens of Chinese warplanes flew into the island's air defence zone over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian Premier Resigns as Instability Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/26/italys-prime-minister-giuseppe-conte-quits-amid-political-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy is facing more political turmoil after Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte resigned on Tuesday, just as the country faces a severe health and economic crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Alien Life-Form Do Drive-By of Our Solar System?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/26/did-an-alien-life-form-do-a-drive-by-of-our-solar-system-in-2017/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXTRATERRESTRIAL The First Sign of Intelligent Life Beyond Earth By Avi Loeb On Nov. 12, 2018, Avi Loeb, then the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy couple chartered plane to Yukon, took shots meant for Indigenous elders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/wealthy-couple-chartered-a-plane-to-the-yukon-took-vaccines-meant-for-indigenous-elders-authorities-said/ar-BB1d6rHW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I can’t believe I’ve ever seen or heard of such a despicable, disgusting sense of entitlement and lack of a moral compass,” British Columbia Solicitor-General Mike Farnworth said Monday, according to the Vancouver Sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil patients 'drop like flies' in oxygen shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/brazil-pandemic-like-medieval-plague-23384735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian medical volunteers in Manuas, which has been devastated by coronavirus, are having to deprive some Covid patients of oxygen so others can receive life-saving treatment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT BATTLE FOR JAB</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9184203/AstraZeneca-say-meet-EUs-Covid-19-vaccine-demands-blocs-supply-chain-problems.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU health chiefs last night demanded pharmaceutical firms give early warning to officials when exporting vaccines to countries outside the bloc - including Britain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States Ease Covid Restrictions Even as Variants Take Hold...</title>
      <link>https://tylerpaper.com/ap/national/us-states-ease-virus-restrictions-even-as-variants-take-hold/article_5b507f5b-85a9-582a-8916-b093e78434f0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tylerpaper.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California and other large states are loosening COVID-19 restrictions just as scientists warn that more-contagious variants of the virus are beginning to take hold in the U.S. and the vaccine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK News in UK to help 'sustain' local journalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/jan/26/facebook-news-launches-in-uk-following-deals-with-news-outlets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stories from the Guardian, Daily Mail, Economist and more will appear in a dedicated feed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin American newspapers bet on digital subscriptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com.au/latin-american-newspapers-bet-digital-subscriptions-1671948</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin American newspapers bet on digital subscriptions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States Ease Covid Restrictions Even as Variants Take Hold...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-01-26/u-s-states-ease-covid-restrictions-even-as-variants-take-hold</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood elites skipping vaccine line...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/covid-vaccine-hollywood-skipping-line-1234891647/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As coronavirus vaccines trickle out across the country and new infections and deaths rise at alarming rates in cities like Los Angeles, some power players in entertainment and media are leveraging …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA LOOSENS UP</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210126005444-60wxt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-California eases lockdowns as U.S. COVID-19 crisis ebbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president traveled on commercial flight hours before announcing infection...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210125212041-ps9tr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MEXICO (UPDATE 4, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 4-Mexican president's COVID-19 revelation fuels criticism of pandemic response</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA LOOSENS UP</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-expected-cancel-californias-regional-065415888.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The action by state officials means restaurants and gyms could soon reopen outdoor services. Counties will make the final call, however.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires thriving as poor suffer...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210124230112-e2cg3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10 richest men, including Amazon's Jeff Bezos, Tesla founder Elon Musk, Microsoft's Bill Gates and Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg, saw their net worth increase by $540 billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden continues to unpick Trump legacy as impeachment trial looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/25/joe-biden-transgender-military-ban-impeachment-trump-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New president has overturned Trump’s ban on transgender people serving in military as part of blitz of executive orders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the 'whites only' church sowing discord in a small Minnesota town...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9115263/Inside-whites-church-small-Minnesota-town.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On December 9, Murdock City Council granted the Asatru Folk Assembly (AFA) a permit to turn a run-down church it purchased in June into its 'gathering place'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida offers to host Olympics if Tokyo backs out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-offers-host-olympics-tokyo-231126044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's chief financial officer on Monday told the International Olympic Committee that the state would be happy to host the Olympics Games amid speculation that current hosts Japan may back out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-lockdown riots continue in Netherlands...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2208772/anti-lockdown-riots-loot-shops-netherlands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIOT cops fired tear gas and water canons as cars were torched and shops looted when anti-lockdown protesters went on the rampage across the Netherlands. Hundreds were arrested as police confronted…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Suffers Sharpest Rise in Poverty Rate in More Than 50 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-suffers-sharpest-rise-in-poverty-rate-in-more-than-50-years/ar-BB1d4QoE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The end of 2020 brought the sharpest rise in the U.S. poverty rate since the 1960s, according to a study released Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Slams Cancel Culture in Rare Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/rupert-murdoch-condemns-awful-woke-orthodoxy-and-social-media-censorship-in-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch, head of News Corp. and Fox Corporation said that media organizations, including social media, are facing widespread "censorship."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House send Trump Impeachment II to Senate, GOP opposes trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/senate-gop-oppose-trump-impeachment-f4b8bf18ce0e23b877ba945545c3e257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats marched the impeachment case against Donald Trump to the Senate Monday night for the start of his historic trial, but Republican senators were easing off their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle runs down 5 pedestrians in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2021/01/pedestrian-seriously-injured-in-southeast-portland-incident.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a developing story. Check back for updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE issues new warning: Keep iPhone away from pacemaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/25/tech/iphone-12-medical-device-interference/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An important heads-up for iPhone owners: Apple is warning customers that its smartphones could interfere with medical devices, including pacemakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota confirms first known U.S. case of Brazil-strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/25/minnesota-confirms-first-known-us-case-of-more-contagious-covid-variant-originally-found-in-brazil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON eyes treasure trove of health data in new vax push...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/23/amazon-covid-vaccine-distribution-461525</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon’s bid comes as Biden officials say they're trying to repair the vaccine distribution system they inherited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Slim recovering...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/telecoms-magnate-carlos-slim-recovering-well-from-covid-19-says-son/ar-BB1d5bMa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MEXICO-SLIM:Telecoms magnate Carlos Slim recovering well from COVID-19, says son</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley donors back recall to oust Newsom...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22245414/gavin-newsom-recall-silicon-valley-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech money could turn a quixotic recall attempt into a real threat to Gavin Newsom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How he could use small donors to bail him out...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/01/wall-street-looks-to-donald-trumps-next-con</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump doesn’t need a media empire to make bank—turning just a fraction of his supporters into paid subscribers could net him the cash he needs to pay off millions in debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Optimists Have Healthier Hearts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/optimism-positivity-heart-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoplel who report having both work-related stress and high stress in general have a 40-percent higher risk of dying from heart disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to 'make good' on climate finance pledges, Kerry tells leaders...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210125190249-rczj8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-CHANGE/SUMMIT-NETHERLANDS (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-U.S. to 'make good' on climate finance pledges, Kerry tells leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Decries 'Awful Woke Orthodoxy'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/25/rupert-murdoch-accepting-award-decries-awful-woke-orthodoxy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The media mogul Rupert Murdoch decried an “awful woke orthodoxy” and declared, “I’m far from done” while accepting a lifetime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers Jumped to Front of Vaccine Line -- But Still Refuse to Teach...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/01/25/fairfax-county-should-open-schools-or-stop-vaccinating-teachers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s time to open the schools full time or get new administrators. Really, we should do both.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leahy, not Roberts, to preside...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/25/politics/impeachment-article-senate-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The contours of former President Donald Trump's second impeachment trial are starting to take shape, with the Senate's longest-serving Democrat expected to preside over the trial and Democrats still weighing whether to pursue witnesses during proceedings that could take up a chunk of February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands died at nursing home chain. CEO got $5 million bonus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/genesis-healthcare-ceo-george-hager-bonus-exit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 claimed a heavy toll on residents at Genesis Healthcare facilities as top executive made a lucrative exit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
