<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>IS AMERICA HEADING FOR CIVIL WAR?</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/is-america-heading-for-civil-war-of-course-it-is_07072020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD IN HELL...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/can-summer-box-office-be-saved-hollywood-hinges-hopes-tenet-mulan-1302238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supervillain Hollywood never saw coming, the virus has already disrupted the summer movie season, forcing studios to push (and re-push) their lucrative tentpoles while leaving anxious theater owners hopeful for a third-act hero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN warns delayed election results could rock market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/08/goldman-warns-delayed-election-results-this-november-similar-to-bush-gore-could-rock-the-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs is warning that the upcoming presidential election could see delayed results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President threatens to cut funding for schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/08/coronavirus-trump-threatens-to-cut-school-funding-slams-cdc-reopening-guidelines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The threats came as the White House ramped up an administration-wide pressure campaign to schools to fully reopen this fall, despite the soaring rates of coronavirus infections around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cristina poised to become 1st hurricane of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/cristina-poised-to-become-1st-hurricane-of-2020/771328</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court allows religious exemption to birth control coverage...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200708133055-p4l6w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/CONTRACEPTION (URGENT):U.S. Supreme Court allows broader religious exemption to birth control coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St Fears Market Fragility in $23 Trillion Stock Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-fears-market-fragility-135920737.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s not your imagination: Stock markets are lurching from meltdown to melt-up like never before.After one of the swiftest corrections in history, the S&amp;P 500 is now back within a spitting distance of pre-crisis levels. Likewise the February 2018 crash was followed by a swift resurgence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Parched Southwest, Warm Spring Renews Threat of 'Megadrought'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/08/in-parched-southwest-warm-spring-renews-threat-of-megadrought/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOVELAND PASS, Colo. — Here at 12,000 feet on the Continental Divide, only vestiges of the winter snowpack remain, scattered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 61 million Hispanics in USA; Election impact looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/census-record-61-million-hispanics-in-us-election-impact-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hispanic population in America has reached a new record of nearly 61 million, making it the largest minority in the nation, according to a new analysis of U.S. Census Bureau data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students willing to give up free speech to avoid offending...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=15219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"That shouldn't be allowed"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does it pay to protect nature? New study weighs in...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200708121416-oobar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-CHANGE/BIODIVERSITY (PIX):Does it pay to protect nature? A new study weighs in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Series Of 'Mystery Explosions' Mean Next War About To Begin?</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/does-a-series-of-mystery-explosions-inside-iran-mean-that-the-next-big-middle-east-war-is-about-to-begin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past several weeks, a series of "mystery explosions" has happened at very strategically sensitive locations inside Iran, and it has become obvious that what we are witnessing is not just a bunch of random accidents.  For years, the Israeli government has pledged that the Iranians will never</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico border towns try to stop Americans crossing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jul/08/mexico-border-towns-stop-americans-crossing-covid-19-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Townspeople block road to beach resort popular with US tourists as cases surge in states including Arizona</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ to Require Outdoor Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/new-jersey-to-require-outdoor-face-masks-in-addition-to-indoor/2505387/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy says he will issue an executive order Wednesday requiring people to wear face masks outdoors when they can’t socially distance, in addition to the existing rules for indoor masks. “There’s no question that face coverings are game changers. I think we were the first state in America to require them indoors, they’ve been strongly recommended…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing's secret police get room with view in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Beijing-s-secret-police-get-a-room-with-a-view-in-15393411.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG - When China's state security officials came to town, they needed a home - and fast.  So they did what any newcomer would do: They sequestered a 33-story hotel with a rooftop pool and panoramic harbor views, then erected 7-foot-high barriers to limit public access to their new digs.  Early Wednesday, under a heavy police presence and before any public announcement about the matter, officials inaugurated the Office for Safeguarding National Security of the Central People's Government in the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region at a ceremony that took place behind water-filled barricades. They played the Chinese national anthem and raised the Chinese flag, though local media weren't invited. When the ceremony was over, reporters were finally able to photograph the building's front door.  The Metropark Hotel on the edge of the city's Causeway Bay district will be the initial base for the new agency, tasked with collecting intelligence and implementing a new law that sharply curtails political freedoms as Beijing takes fuller control of the territory after anti-government protests last year.  It's the first time the Chinese government's state security apparatus has been permitted to operate in Hong Kong, marking a milestone in officials' efforts to dismantle the firewall that separated the city from the authoritarian mainland.  The security law, which took effect July 1, specifies four broadly defined crimes against national security that can invite punishment of up to life imprisonment: subversion, secession, terrorism, and collusion with foreign forces. In practice, lawyers and other experts say, it effectively extends mainland legal provisions to Hong Kong, ending the autonomy that China promised the financial center would enjoy until 2047.  The new office is headed by Zheng Yanxiong, a senior Communist Party...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye Done With Trump; 'Taking Red Hat Off'...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/randalllane/2020/07/08/kanye-west-says-hes-done-with-trump-opens-up-about-white-house-bid-damaging-biden-and-everything-in-between/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across four hours of interviews, the rap billionaire says he’s never voted, has recovered from Covid but doubts vaccines and envisions running a presidency modeled on Wakanda in Black Panther.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROOKS BROTHERS Goes Bust...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/08/brooks-brothers-files-for-bankruptcy-as-it-seeks-buyer-closes-stores.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 202-year-old retailer has dressed U.S. presidents and countless investment bankers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCS coach says his players will 'all get sick' when NFL returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Buccaneers-coach-says-his-players-will-all-get-15393482.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When NFL teams reconvene for the 2020 season, Bruce Arians knows he has more reason than most to take precautions amid the novel coronavirus pandemic. Not only is his age, 67, a significant risk factor, but the Tampa Bay Buccaneers head coach has had procedures over the years to remove cancerous tumors.  Thus Arians plans to wear extra personal protective gear and have his staff adhere closely to safety protocols.  As for his players - now including soon-to-be-43-year-old Tom Brady - Arians appears to feel that there will be no avoiding illness. And not just for some of them, but as he put it Monday to the Tampa Bay Times, "all" of them.  "The players, they're going to all get sick, that's for sure," Arians said. "It's just a matter of how sick they get."  Buccaneers players are scheduled to report for training camp in two weeks, following the kind of virtual offseason all NFL teams have been conducting since March. That has meant participating in team-conducted training sessions via teleconferencing, not in meeting rooms and on practice fields.  Brady, though, has been organizing informal, in-person practice sessions in Tampa since May, when Florida loosened stay-at-home orders. While that has helped the former New England Patriots quarterback and six-time Super Bowl winner become more familiar with his new teammates, he has also been doing so in defiance of a recommendation last month by the NFL Players Association.  Florida is now one of the foremost coronavirus hotspots in a nation that has seen rates of new infections shoot upward since June, with at least 128,000 dead. That has complicated the plans to return to play not only of the NFL but several prominent sports leagues in the United States.  Major League Soccer chose to withdraw one of its teams, FC Dallas, from a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran mayor sees 'threat' in Iranians' dissatisfaction...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tehran-mayor-sees-threat-iranians-dissatisfaction-114441360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's low voter turnout reflects a wider malaise in a country long buckling under sanctions and more recently also hit hard by the coronavirus, spelling "a threat for everyone," Tehran's mayor Pirouz Hanachi told AFP. "The turnout at the ballot box is a sign of people's satisfaction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killing of Iraq expert stirs fear of new violent phase...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/killing-iraq-expert-stirs-fear-violent-phase-035122507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The killing of jihadism expert Hisham al-Hashemi has stirred fears Iraq is entering a dark and violent phase, as boiling tensions between pro-Iran factions and the government reach new heights. Hashemi, 47, was gunned down outside his home in east Baghdad late Monday by masked assailants on motorcycles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neurological problems linked to even mild infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brain-problems-linked-even-mild-virus-infections-study-102940044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Potentially fatal COVID-19 complications in the brain including delirium, nerve damage and stroke may be more common than initially thought, a team of British-based doctors warned Wednesday. Severe COVID-19 infections are known to put patients at risk of neurological complications, but research led</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump troubles in Arizona mount with surge...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200708091430-2tprl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/ARIZONA (PIX):Trump's troubles in Arizona mount with coronavirus surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain damage 'epidemic'?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12061825/coronavirus-brain-damage-epidemic-mild-cases-inflammation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE who have contracted the coronavirus could also suffer brain complications, experts have revealed. Conditions such as brain inflammation, strokes, nerve damage and delirium have all been name…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Rental Market Pushed to Breaking Point by Tenant Debts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/coronavirus-moves-nyc-affordable-housing-crisis-to-breaking-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Rental Market Pushed to Breaking Point by Tenant Debts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Paulson rips elite Manhattan school for 'anti-white indoctrination'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/07/billionaire-john-paulson-rips-elite-spence-school-for-anti-white-indoctrination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paulson is claiming an “alarming pattern” of “anti-white indoctrination” in the ultra-elite Manhattan school’s curriculum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Glitters; Rush to Safe Haven...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-rally-1-800-sees-084449978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Gold’s allure is only getting stronger as 2020 unfolds. Spot prices reached $1,800 an ounce and year-to-date inflows into bullion-backed exchange-traded funds topped the record full-year total set in 2009.Investors have favored havens this year as the coronavirus pandemic rips through</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INMATE #1: RISE OF TREJO': Prison, Recovery, Stardom...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/08/inmate-1-the-rise-of-danny-trejo-review-prison-recovery-stardom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor Danny Trejo, with more than 300 movies under his belt, doesn’t mind being what some people call “typecast.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY WORLD Draws Excitement and Incredulity as Reopening Nears...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/08/disney-world-draws-excitement-and-incredulity-as-reopening-nears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walt Disney World in Orlando, Fla., will reopen on Saturday, and Disney has been posting marketing videos online to highlight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches Now Major Source of Cases...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/08/churches-were-eager-to-reopen-now-they-are-a-major-source-of-coronavirus-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENDLETON, Ore. — Weeks after President Trump demanded that America’s shuttered houses of worship be allowed to reopen, new outbreaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhausted cities face another challenge: Surge in violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f84604913630146a6e4d174e581ae615</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Still reeling from the coronavirus pandemic and street protests over the police killing of George Floyd, exhausted cities around the nation are facing yet another challenge: a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Big Tech Testimony Will Be Bust...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/07/why-big-techs-congressional-testimony-will-be-a-bust.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Galloway and Kara Swisher discuss why they’re pessimistic about this month’s grilling of Zuckerberg, Bezos, Cook, and Pichai.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Desperation science' slows hunt for drugs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/db08697f6260038f196b1106fe574228</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desperate to solve the deadly conundrum of COVID-19, the world is clamoring for fast answers and solutions from a research system not built for haste. The ironic, and perhaps tragic,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE DESTRUCTION OF DEPP...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/07/everything-that-happened-on-day-1-of-johnny-depp-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood’s battle royale between Johnny Depp and Amber Heard exploded in a British courtroom Tuesday — with the star blasting his ex as “sociopathic’’ while denying claims he beat her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic-buying returns as Melbourne braces for lengthy lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/panic-buying-returns-melbourne-braces-lengthy-lockdown-032146627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shoppers in Australia's second-biggest city stripped supermarket shelves Wednesday as millions in Melbourne prepared for a return to virus lockdown, with warnings the new restrictions will cost the economy Aus$1 billion a week. Five million residents were ordered back into a six-week lockdown beginning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans split over whether to attend convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Republicans-split-over-whether-to-attend-the-15392709.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Republicans' determination to press ahead with a convention next month despite escalating covid-19 cases in the host city of Jacksonville, Fla., is prompting a growing split in the party, with some GOP leaders saying they'll stay home and others stressing the importance of attending to show support for President Donald Trump.  Politicians, donors and party officials, especially seniors at higher risk of complications from the disease, now face a difficult choice between a personal risk to their health and a potential backlash from the president and his supporters. Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., 78, indicated Tuesday he will attend the convention, but two other top Senate Republicans, Iowa's Charles Grassley, 86, and Tennessee's Lamar Alexander, 80, are taking a pass.  They are joined by two of the most senior Republican women in the Senate. Maine's Susan Collins, 67, said though a spokesman that she avoids attending the party convention in years when she is facing reelection. Alaska's Lisa Murkowski, 63, also has no plans to attend, according to a spokesperson, nor does Utah's Mitt Romney, 73.  Collins, Murkowski and Romney have criticized Trump on occasion, making their presence potentially uncomfortable at an event that will largely be a tribute to the president. But Grassley made it clear his decision is motivated solely by fear of contracting covid-19.  "I'm not going to go because of the virus situation," Grassley said Monday on a conference call with reporters.  Trump himself signaled Tuesday some flexibility regarding the convention. "When we signed a few weeks ago, it looked good. And now all of a sudden it's spiking up a little bit and that's going to go down," the president told television host Greta Van Susteren. "It really depends on the timing. . . . We can do a lot of things,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dehydration'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/506321-chief-justice-john-roberts-was-hospitalized-last-month-after-a-fall-supreme</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Chief Justice John Roberts was hospitalized last month after falling at a Maryland country club, the court confirmed Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents worry situation will get much worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Florida-invited-the-nation-to-its-reopening-15392818.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. - As the coronavirus savaged other parts of the country, Florida, buoyed by low infection rates, seemed an ideal location for a nation looking to emerge from isolation. The Republican National Convention moved from Charlotte to Jacksonville, the NBA eyed a season finale at a Disney sports complex near Orlando and millions packed onto once-empty beaches.  Weeks later, the Sunshine State has emerged as a coronavirus epicenter. Nearly 1 out of every 100 residents is infected with the virus, hospital intensive care units are full or filling up, and big-name visitors who chose Florida for their first post-isolation events are now mired in questions and controversies about safety.  Amid escalating infections, Florida, once held up by President Donald Trump as a model for how to manage the novel coronavirus, is faring poorly. Residents worry the situation will get much worse. Florida is now one of a handful of states whose spiking numbers are driving a major resurgence of the virus in the United States, which is approaching 3 million cases.  Gov. Ron DeSantis, a Republican, has downplayed the growing outbreak in Florida, saying expanded testing is responsible for more positive results and emphasizing that many new infections are among younger people less likely to experience the worst effects of the virus.  On Tuesday there were 213,794 cases of the coronavirus in Florida, according to Washington Post data. The state has tallied a record number of cases over the past week, averaging 8,766 a day, according to Post data.  In a sign of intensifying trouble, 52 intensive care units across more than a third of the state's counties had reached capacity by Tuesday, according to data released by the state's Agency for Health Care Administration. Another 17 hospitals had also run out of regular beds. The state has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY SHE DID IT</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-inside-story-of-why-mary-trump-wrote-a-tell-all-memoir/ar-BB16srWv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA PEAK VIRUS NOW:  New daily case record of 60,209...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/us-posts-new-daily-virus-case-record-of-60-209-johns-hopkins-01594169104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States, the country hardest hit by the coronavirus, on Tuesday posted 60,209 new cases, a record for a 24-hour period, according to a tally from Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California sheriff who mocked the state's stay-at-home order now has changed his tune...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-sheriff-mocked-states-stay-171219409.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merced County, where the sheriff questioned the pandemic and a town became a 'sanctuary city for business,' is now on the state watchlist after a surge in COVID-19 cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Brazil's skeptical president infected...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australia-locks-down-millions-us-struggles-contain-virus-132732039.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro, who has consistently downplayed the risks of coronavirus, announced Tuesday he has tested positive, as the United States -- the nation hardest hit by the pandemic -- formally launched its withdrawal from the World Health Organization (WHO). The UN health agency meanwhile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arraignment scheduled for next week...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200708004405-8qj98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-GHISLAINE MAXWELL/ (PIX):Ghislaine Maxwell's arraignment for luring underage girls scheduled for next week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA PEAK VIRUS:  New daily virus case record of 60,209...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/newsblogs/latest-news-live-updates-july-8/liveblog/76844758.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country was just shy of three million cases, at 2,991,351, the Baltimore-based university said in its latest data. The death toll stood at 131,362, with 1,114 additional deaths counted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SISTER CALLED HIM CLOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mary-trump-book-claims-trump-praised-her-breasts-and-his-own-sister-called-him-a-clown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump’s explosive tell-all about the president details her uncle’s comments about her breasts, his cheating on the SAT exam, and how his own sister called him a clown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIECE EXPOSES DYNASTY</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/trumps-worldview-forged-by-neglect-and-trauma-at-home-niece-mary-trump-says-in-new-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A tell-all book by President Donald Trump's niece describes a family riven by a series of traumas, exacerbated by a daunting patriarch who "destroyed" Donald Trump by short-circuiting his "ability to develop and experience the entire spectrum of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVER UP:  Florida still not reporting how many are hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-still-not-reporting-how-many-hospitalized-with-covid-desantis-wont-say-why/ar-BB16sfEO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I HAD TO TAKE DONALD DOWN'</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mary-trump-book-donald-trump-financials-c1635cb1-d1b0-48e0-b816-72d270170796.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was an effort to expose the president, whom she portrays as a dangerous sociopath.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banks Poised to Get Fee Windfall... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/banks-poised-fee-windfall-small-175710346.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Earlier this year, thousands of lenders rushed to arrange loans under the U.S. government’s Paycheck Protection Program. Now, some of them will be rewarded handsomely.More than 30 banks across the country, including dozens of community banks and some lenders with more than $1 billion in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Chairman Sets Goal Of 50% Diverse Workforce...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/nbc-news-diversity-1202979811/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cesar Conde, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest as Serbia reimposes virus curfew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/651b85a438d142858cefc2e1ab3640d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELGRADE, Serbia (AP) — Thousands of people protested the Serbian president's announcement that a lockdown will be reintroduced after the Balkan country reported its highest single-day death toll...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump donors among early recipients...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00a34243825661313f2cb6a0f6a21720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As much as $273 million in federal coronavirus aid was awarded to more than 100 companies that are owned or operated by major donors to President Donald Trump's election efforts,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple charged with hate crime for vandalizing Black Lives Matter mural outside California courthouse...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/black-lives-matter/blm-mural-defaced-275830</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; The couple recorded defacing a Black Lives Matter mural that was painted in front of a California courthouse have been charged with three misdemeanors, including a hate crime, prosecutors toda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of dead fish found in and around Hudson River...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-dead-fish-hudson-river-20200707-2swhsxxl75bixcvyvcsla4dhhq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a fishy situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida lawyer attends court in HAZMAT SUIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8498865/Florida-lawyer-attends-court-HAZMAT-SUIT-amid-COVID-19-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samuel J. Rabin Jr. donned the protective garb for a client's sentencing hearing which was held at Miami federal courthouse last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW MODEL: 208,000 deaths in USA by November...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/webview/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-07-07-20-intl/h_c5c9c0b1f6e8db4ffbd3dc5dcca35387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has brought countries to a standstill. In many places, as countries reopen, Covid-19 cases are on the rise. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Record: 10,028 New Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/texas-says-new-coronavirus-cases-jumped-by-more-than-10000-for-the-first-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas reported more than 10,000 additional Covid-19 cases Tuesday, a record-breaking daily surge in cases as the state responds to a growing outbreak and an increase in hospitalizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Defiant: Reopening on track for Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200707201123-t9d0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DISNEY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Disney says Walt Disney World reopening is on track for Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County to arrest positive residents who refuse to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/07/07/texas-county-to-arrest-covid-positive-residents-who-refuse-to-self-isolate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Texas county isn't taking any chances when it comes to the coronavirus, issuing a warning that anyone who tests positive and refuses to self-isolate could end up in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland protesters hit with federal charges in officer assaults, courthouse destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/7/portland-protesters-face-federal-charges-assaultin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Attorney in Oregon announced federal charges Tuesday against seven protesters who are accused in court papers of defacing a federal courthouse and assaulting federal officers during protests in Portland, Oregon against racial injustice and police brutality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors hit Black Lives Matter protesters with rare felony 'leak' charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/7/black-lives-matter-protesters-face-felony-leak-cha/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in Iowa have filed a rarely used leak charge against Black Lives Matter protesters accused of stealing a confidential police document and displaying it during a television news broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell eyes MORE virus aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.theledger.com/news/20200707/mcconnell-eyes-virus-aid-as-evictions-benefits-cuts-loom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — An eviction moratorium is lifting. Extra unemployment benefits are ending. Parents are being called to work, but schools are struggling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm Animals May Be Key To Forecasting Earthquakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/not-a-myth-after-all-farm-animals-may-be-key-to-forecasting-earthquakes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study by German scientists provides scientific evidence to support claims of odd animal behavior prior to earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS CORP CEO says 'digital denouement looming'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/news-corp-robert-thomson-digital-denouement-looming-journalism-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Corp CEO Robert Thomson discussed tech giants such as Amazon, Facebook and Google and their role in the journalism landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Sheriffs Refuse to Enforce Gov's Orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/texas-sheriffs-refuse-to-enforce-governor-greg-abbott-mask-executive-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least nine counties have publicly said they will not enforce the executive order requiring face masks in public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yet another blast reportedly damages factory in Iran, latest in series of blasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/explosion-reportedly-damages-factory-in-iran-the-latest-in-series-of-blasts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2 said killed and 3 injured at facility in Kahrizak, south of Tehran; local governor says explosion caused by human error as oxygen tanks were being filled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dangerous Vaccine Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/07/vaccine-race-covid-national-pride-348072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The international competition for a coronavirus vaccine harkens back to the golden age of Edison and the Wright Brothers. But excesses of national pride and one-upmanship are threatening to overwhelm the common good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.K. Rowling, Noam Chomsky Sign Open Letter Calling for End to Cancel Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/j-k-rowling-bari-weiss-and-noam-chomsky-among-dozens-to-sign-open-letter-calling-for-end-to-cancel-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.K. Rowling, Bari Weiss, Noam Chomsky, and more than 100 other writers, scholars, and academics signed an open letter calling for "open debate" and an end to cancel culture, sparking backla</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International investors bought bonds backed by Italian mafia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/international-investors-reportedly-bought-bonds-backed-by-the-italian-mafia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors around the globe were buying bonds backed by a notorious mafia in Italy for four years, The Financial Times reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Staffers Face Layoffs as Palaces Lose Millions in Tourism Income...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/royals/royal-staff-face-layoffs-as-palaces-lose-millions-of-dollars-in-tourism-income-amid-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal staff face layoffs as palaces lose millions of tourism dollars because of closures during coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Omar Calls For 'Dismantling' Of US Economy, Political System...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/07/07/ilhan-omar-calls-for-the-dismantling-of-us-economy-political-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Minnesota Rep. Ilhan Omar called for the &amp;quot;dismantling&amp;quot; of the U.S. economy and political system Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YAHOO engineer gets off with only probation after hacking 6,000 accounts to look for porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/yahoo-engineer-gets-no-jail-time-after-hacking-6000-accounts-to-look-for-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hacker sentenced to five years probation, with home confinement condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Office Delivery Trucks Keep Catching on Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/z3ezx4/post-office-delivery-trucks-keep-catching-on-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of the iconic Post Office delivery trucks have caught on fire in recent years, thanks to a 30-year-old fleet and a manufactured budget crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  DUNKIN closing 450 locations...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/food/2020/07/07/dunkin-closures-2020-speedway-gas-stations-convenience-stores/5389869002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the end of 2020, Dunkin' will close approximately 450 locations in Speedway gas station convenience stores, a move first announced in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY: 'Real headwinds' if election turns into 'referendum'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/07/mick-mulvaney-trump-general-election-350337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blunt acknowledgment from the president’s former top aide comes amid escalating anxiety among congressional Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Florida ICUs at full capacity...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200707154532-vlax5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FLORIDA (URGENT):Dozens of Florida hospitals at full ICU capacity -state data report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY  Heads Toward Hedge-Fund Ownership...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/06/mcclatchy-a-family-newspaper-business-heads-toward-hedge-fund-ownership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The McClatchy family has been in journalism since 1857, when its flagship publication, The Daily Bee, chronicled the latest for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch police uncover makeshift torture chamber...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bbe6743f42e5ab1dc6b06d2524fef32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — Dutch police arrested six men after discovering sea containers that had been converted into a makeshift prison and sound-proofed “torture chamber” complete with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy could 'section' people who refuse treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jul/07/italy-could-section-people-who-refuse-treatment-for-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minister proposes mandatory hospital care as country grapples with fresh outbreaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER, NEWSMAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumps-small-biz-rescue-bailed-out-kushners-family-obamas-aides-and-other-political-elite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PPP program was designed to help small businesses. And it has. But some of the most connected figures in politics also cashed in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grover Norquist's anti-government spending group took cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/nation/2020/07/06/grover-norquists-anti-spending-group-took-small-business-relief/112067360/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Americans for Tax Reform Foundation, a conservative group headed by anti-tax activist Grover Norquist, took Covid-19 small business relief funds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-sized giant bat leaves people convinced they've seen a demon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/giant-human-sized-bat-leaves-22313648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The golden-crowned flying fox in the Philippines is a huge bat with a 1.7m wing span that – but thankfully, the beast typically feasts on fruit rather than flesh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY, NJ expands list of quarantine states...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/new-york-and-new-jersey-expand-list-of-states-that-trigger-quarantine-orders-for-travelers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo and New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy added three more states to their travel advisory on Tuesday, requiring all individuals from the list of states to self-quarantine for 14 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herd immunity strategies called into question...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/herd-immunity-questioned-after-spanish-coronavirus-antibody-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 antibodies in Spain's population "are insufficient to provide herd immunity," a new study has claimed, despite the country being one of the worst-affected by the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Jogger Finds Human Head on Side of Road...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/crime/2020/07/07/police-florida-jogger-finds-human-head-on-side-of-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A human head was discovered Tuesday on the side of a road in St. Petersburg, Florida, according to authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI GOV: 'Not Going to Be Bullied' into Opening...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/07/07/michigan-gov-whitmer-on-reopening-im-not-going-to-be-bullied-into-moving-before-its-safe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dialing back reopening right before the July 4 holiday, Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer (D) affirmed Tuesday on CNN's "New Day" that she will not be "bullied" into reopening her state too quickly amid the ongoing coronavirus pandemic. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Pandemic accelerating, still short of peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/coronavirus-pandemic-accelerating-still-short-of-peak-who-01594137005?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 400,000 new cases of COVID-19 were reported over the weekend and the new coronavirus pandemic shows no sign of slowing down, the World Health Organization said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP worries Trump's divisive June imperils Senate control...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8e962577a52e4803c51f6761cf619da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's June began with his Bible-clutching photo op outside a church after authorities used chemicals and batons to scatter peaceful demonstrators. It never got...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIECE EXPOSES DYNASTY</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trumps-worldview-forged-by-neglect-and-trauma-at-home-his-niece-says-in-new-book/2020/07/07/b19b22f6-bf9d-11ea-864a-0dd31b9d6917_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump, who has a doctoral degree in clinical psychology, shares a history of family tragedy and division with President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded tourist begs to be rescued after being stuck in airport for 100 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1098646/tourist-stranded-coronavirus-real-life-terminal-tom-hanks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOURIST is pleading to be rescued after spending more than 100 days living in an airport in a real life echo of Tom Hanks film The Terminal. Roman Trofimov has been staying in the departures…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY expands list of quarantine states...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ny-nj-ct-add-three-more-states-added-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People arriving to New York, New Jersey and Connecticut from three more states will have to quarantine for 14-days due to concerns over the spread of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON On Track To Be First $2 Trillion Company...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90525091/how-high-can-amazon-stock-go-4-reasons-it-keeps-rising-during-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like the weather outside your window right now, Amazon is hot. The Seattle-based e-tail giant’s stock price keeps hitting all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY:  TRUMP ABUSED BY DAD</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8498179/Donald-Trump-suffered-child-abuse-hands-father-niece-claims-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump, Donald Trump's niece, will claim in her bombshell memoir he suffered 'child abuse' at the hands of his workaholic father Fred Trump Sr. The book will be released on July 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Brazil's Bolsonaro tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/07/americas/brazil-bolsonaro-positive-coronavirus-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro has tested positive for Covid-19, following months of downplaying the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires and country clubs receive 'small business loans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/the-billionaires-and-country-clubs-that-received-ppp-loans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaires, country clubs, private jet companies and Kanye West all received millions in government funding under the Paycheck Protection Program, according to filings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church of Scientology bailed out!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fresh-outrage-well-connected-firms-nab-us-loans-153140732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A centerpiece of US President Donald Trump's economic relief program was under renewed scrutiny Tuesday following revelations it aided white-shoe lobbying firms and businesses linked to Kanye West and other billionaires. The controversy is the latest to befall the PPP, which was launched in April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Televangelists, Dallas megachurch that hosted Pence approved for millions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200707021948-4ednx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PPP-RELIGIOUS:Televangelists, Dallas megachurch that hosted Pence approved for millions in pandemic aid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Stock Hits Record High Amid Ad Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/facebook-stock-hits-record-high-amid-ad-boycott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors don't appear to be too worried about advertisers boycotting Facebook, with the social network's stock price racing to a new all-time high</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why China Wants Trump to Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2020/07/why-china-wants-donald-trump-win/613864/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four more years might present tantalizing opportunities for Beijing to expand its influence around East Asia and the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Bolsonaro Positive? Awaiting Test After Showing Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/coronavirus-brazils-bolsonaro-tested-for-covid-19-after-feeling-ill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian media said Bolsonaro has canceled all his official activities until he gets the results of his test for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp, Amber Heard courtroom showdown off to explosive start...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/07/johnny-depp-and-amber-heards-domestic-violence-trial-gets-off-to-explosive-start/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp and ex-wife Amber Heard arrived at separate entrances to a London court for a showdown over mutual accusations of violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protective gear for medical workers begins to run low again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/481d933b0caa6f5fc61f466c86d4777b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The personal protective gear that was in dangerously short supply during the early weeks of the coronavirus crisis in the U.S. is running low again as the virus resumes its rapid spread and the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
