<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How man's death in Beverly Hills exposed sprawling Hollywood drug delivery business...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/how-a-mans-death-in-beverly-hills-exposed-a-sprawling-hollywood-drug-delivery-business/ar-AAUpSfR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guns, radicalization and father's alleged threat: First Jan. 6 trial set to begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/guns-radicalization-and-a-father-e2-80-99s-alleged-threat-first-jan-6-trial-set-to-begin/ar-AAUpvod</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil unrest?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4786894/russian-ruble-trouble-western-sanctions-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUN on Russian banks has begun as Western sanctions send the ruble into freefall, sparking hopes of civil unrest against Vladimir Putin. Pictures show long queues outside cash machines in St Pete…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, European allies freeze 'Vlad's war chest' as Russia careens toward economic crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-european-allies-freeze-putin-s-war-chest-as-russia-careens-toward-economic-crisis/ar-AAUpyWR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New UN report warns of deadly climate consequences...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/596056-new-un-report-warns-of-deadly-climate-change-consequences</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from a United Nations climate panel is warning of deadly impacts of climate change both now and in the future — finding that those impacts are currently worse than scientists had believed they woul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Foreign Policy U-turn, Germany Ups Military Spending, Arms Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/27/in-foreign-policy-u-turn-germany-ups-military-spending-arms-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — It took an invasion of a sovereign country nearby, threats of nuclear attack, images of civilians facing off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On cusp of Biden speech, state of disunity, funk and peril...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-state-of-the-union-address-joe-biden-coronavirus-pandemic-39fc55c088ac4b5101dbb217e838fafb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In good times or bad, American presidents come to Congress with a diagnosis that hardly differs over the decades. In their State of the Union speeches, they declare “the state of our union is strong" or words very much like it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas primary is George P. Bush's biggest test yet in GOP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elections-austin-texas-donald-trump-george-p-bush-175e56cb746a986417ec43bc757557b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKEWAY, Texas (AP) — Fighting to stay in office, George P. Bush — the last of the Bush family still on the ballot — greeted a small outdoor crowd at an Austin brewery sounding like most Republicans running in Texas' primary Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Capitol riot cases could hinge on 1st trial's outcome...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-texas-riots-donald-trump-f7c650caa88498c510d7275662ae650f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department launched one of the largest and most complex criminal investigations in its history after a mob of Donald Trump supporters stormed the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BISHOP: Vlad is 'anti-Christ of our time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/ukrainian-bishop-putin-is-the-anti-christ-of-our-current-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Ukrainian archbishop and spokesman for the Orthodox Church of Ukraine condemned Russian President Vladimir Putin as the “anti-Christ of our current time" as Russia invades Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Life on moon by 2040' with plan for humans to survive off rocks in 'lunar village'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/life-moon-2040-plan-humans-26345847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Space Agency has made an £840,000 deal to make a blueprint for a new machine which extracts oxygen from moon rocks meaning the resources would be in place to create 'lunar villages'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market shuttered as ruble crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/28/business/russia-ruble-banks-sanctions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's currency crashed to a record low against the US dollar Monday as the country's financial system reeled from crushing sanctions imposed by Western countries in response to the invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland and Sweden to join NATO?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-united-states-moscow-sweden-finland-38bc14feac1d35c4c86dcb710b44f60c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Finland and Sweden have brushed off warnings from neighboring Russia that their possible joining of NATO would trigger “serious military-political consequences” from Moscow for the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin sends militia into Kyiv to assassinate Zelensky...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10558749/Kremlin-sends-400-mercenaries-Kyiv-assassinate-President-Zelensky.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A private militia known as the Wagner Group 'has orders from Vladimir Putin to decapitate Zelensky's government to pave the way for Moscow to take over.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified, stronger Europe emerging...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putins-fears-unified-stronger-europe-210531046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin's assault on Ukraine is turning his fears of a more resolute Europe and NATO alliance into a self-fulfilling prophecy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe sends fighter jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/europe-stares-down-putins-nuclear-threat-everything-is-on-the-table-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin’s open threat to use nuclear weapons against NATO allies supporting Ukraine appears to European officials to be a watershed in high-stakes brinkmanship that could foreshadow a new level of carnage in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking scenes at Ukraine border sees thousands of kids separated from dads...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4785056/ukraine-border-heartbreaking-scenes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UKRAINIAN rail hub was swamped by desperate families fleeing to Poland yesterday — as brave fighters piled on to trains heading the other way to join the war against Russia. Refugees from all ove…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC plans to lift vax mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/new-york-city-lifts-vaccine-mandate-businesses-events-rcna17415</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mask rules for city schools were likely to end the same day, March 7, Mayor Eric Adams said. Masks are optional at Tuesday’s State of the Union address in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump praises Zelensky as 'brave man' two years after extorting him for political dirt on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/world/trump-praises-zelensky-as-a-brave-man-two-years-after-he-tried-to-extort-him-for-political-dirt-on-biden/ar-AAUlZPm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump praises Zelensky as a 'brave man' two years after he tried to extort him for political dirt on Biden -</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 'paranoid' Vlad has lost his mind!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/fears-paranoid-putin-lost-mind-26340870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears have been shared over the mental health of Russian President Vladimir Putin, with rumours the pandemic scrambled his mind, leading to the brutal invasion of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ominous signs BEFORE invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/7-ominous-warning-signs-world-26340795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin, 69, rose to power in Russia in 2000 and is the longest-serving Kremlin leader since Soviet dictator Joseph Stalin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney Excoriates 'Disgusting' Pro-Putin Republicans: 'Almost Treasonous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/mitt-romney-excoriates-disgusting-pro-putin-republicans-almost-treasonous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Mitt Romney tore into his fellow Republicans who've spoken positively about Vladimir Putin while Ukraine remains under attack from Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Licht to be next CNN president...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-chris-licht-to-replace-jeff-zucker-as-cnn-president-per-dylan-byers-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Licht is reportedly set to become the next president of CNN, replacing Jeff Zucker who resigned earlier this month shocking the cable news world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. embassy advises Americans in Russia to leave 'immediately'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-embassy-americans-russia-73cb348a-4598-4749-b974-b0fc76c25766.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came hours after the EU announced that it would ban all Russian aircraft from its airspace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite pics: Huge Russian convoy converges on Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/satellite-image-russian-troops-approach-kyiv-15cd8239-89a1-4c81-96fc-e433102643ba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convoy is 3.25 miles long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky emerges as global hero...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/596036-zelenskyy-emerges-as-global-hero-in-ukraine-battle-against-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has emerged as a hero to his nation's citizens and far beyond as the former actor and comedian first elected in 2019 remains in his country at great personal risk during its bombardment by Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lost his grip'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/596063-barr-says-trump-lost-his-grip-in-forthcoming-memoir</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Attorney General William Barr writes in his forthcoming memoir that former President Trump “lost his grip” after the 2020 Presidential election, also urging the Republican party to find a different candidate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUKE CRAZY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-business-europe-moscow-2e4e1cf784f22b6afbe5a2f936725550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — President Vladimir Putin dramatically escalated East-West tensions by ordering Russian nuclear forces put on high alert Sunday, while Ukraine's embattled leader agreed to talks with Moscow as Putin's troops and tanks drove deeper into the country, closing in around the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Multiple Sclerosis Linked To Eating Meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/eating-meat-multiple-sclerosis-ms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several genetic and environmental factors cause multiple sclerosis and a new report suggests these may include eating meat and having a less diverse gut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.1 mag quake shakes Ventura...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/preliminary-magnitude-4-1-earthquake-shakes-ventura-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A preliminary magnitude 4.1 earthquake struck Saturday evening in Ventura County. There were no immediate reports of damage or injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy seizes 2 boats as war goes to seas...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1572681/russian-navy-seize-two-ukraine-boats-war-black-sea-seize-hijacked-border-guards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE RUSSIAN NAVY has captured two Ukrainian civilian ships, as the war between the countries continues.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
