<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Michael Moore warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/aug/29/michael-moore-donald-trump-repeat-2016-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film-maker says enthusiasm for president in swing states is ‘off the charts’ and urges everyone to commit to getting 100 people to vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey launches new military drills as East Med tensions mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200829-turkey-stages-new-military-exercises-in-eastern-med</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey stages new military exercises in eastern Med</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Collins faces battle of lifetime in Maine...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/514111-susan-collins-faces-battle-of-lifetime-in-maine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORONO, Maine — Maine lawns may not yet be overwhelmed by campaign signs, but their airwaves have been taken over by the heated rhetoric of the hottest Senate race in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President goes after niece who wrote critical book: 'Unstable' and 'shunned' entire life...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/514267-trump-goes-after-niece-who-wrote-critical-book-unstable-and-shunned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Saturday lambasted his niece, who recently wrote a critical book about the him and released recordings of family members talking about him, with the president calling her “unstable.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kastellorizo, idyllic island at heart of Greece-Turkey row...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200829-kastellorizo-idyllic-island-at-heart-of-greece-turkey-row</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kastellorizo, idyllic island at heart of Greece-Turkey row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midwest cases climb...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/29/coronavirus-cases-climb-in-the-midwest-as-more-states-report-growing-outbreaks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases in the Midwest are beginning to emerge following warnings from top U.S. health officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, drugs, start-ups: Inside Silicon Valley's doomed creative culture...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/29/sex-drugs-start-ups-inside-silicon-valleys-doomed-creative-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2014, John Roa was at a professional high point. His company, Chicago-based ÄKTA, a high-end mobile design and development consultancy, had just been included in the latest Inc. 500 list of fast…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian aircraft make 'unsafe' intercept of US Air Force B-52 bomber...</title>
      <link>http://cnn.com/2020/08/29/politics/russian-aircraft-us-bomber-black-sea/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Russian aircraft made an "unsafe, unprofessional" intercept of a US Air Force B-52 bomber on Friday over the Black Sea and in international waters, according to a statement from US Air Forces in Europe and Air Forces Africa Public Affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Falwell departure, LIBERTY U faces questions about faith, power, accountability...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/After-Jerry-Falwell-Jr-s-departure-Liberty-15524296.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberty University students watched their first all-school convocation of the semester one day after their high-profile president, Jerry Falwell Jr., resigned amid personal scandals.  Falwell has been "an inspiration," said Jerry Prevo, a powerful, fundamentalist pastor from Alaska serving as acting president. He told students that Liberty's leaders are committed to the spiritual mission of the university. He also said Falwell had been the "builder of this great campus, which all of us can be proud of."  Then Jonathan Falwell, pastor of the Liberty-affiliated Thomas Road Baptist Church, spoke. He did not mention his brother by name. But he told his audience, in Lynchburg, Va., and around the globe: "So many times we see Christians that are more focused on building their own brand than they are about building the kingdom of God."  There are a lot of universities out there, Jonathan Falwell said, but Liberty is different: It was built to change the world with the gospel. He urged students to be faithful, trust God and avoid temptation.  Some students who heard the two men said the convocation highlighted a key tension at their school. They felt that Prevo was elevating the former president because of his transformation of the university and that Jonathan Falwell was elevating the Christian values they shared.  "I thought Jonathan Falwell, without being too explicit about it . . . he definitely kind of took Jerry to task," said Eli Best, a junior from Alexandria, Va. "But he did it in a way that took us all to task. It was very relevant."  Fallwell Jr.'s departure leaves Liberty at a turning point: Will the school continue its huge success as measured by the school's size, assets and political clout? Or will it return to the more rigorously religious priority of its revered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Outside Trump Rally Threatens Media: 'You Mother F*ckers Are Gonna Pay, Someone Is Gonna Bomb You'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/man-outside-trump-rally-threatens-media-on-camera-you-mother-fkers-are-gonna-pay-someone-is-gonna-bomb-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man approached a local news reporter outside President Donald Trump's New Hampshire rally and launched into an angry tirade that included telling him "You mother f**kers are gonna pay, someone is gonna bomb you, might even be tonight."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage After French Magazine Depicts Black MP As Slave...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/outrage-after-french-magazine-depicts-black-mp-as-a-slave-01598715605</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron led nationwide outrage Saturday after an ultra-conservative magazine portrayed a black lawmaker as a slave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Humans Take Step Closer to 'Flying Cars'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/29/humans-take-a-step-closer-to-flying-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1880s, the first automobile was developed and about two decades later, the Wright brothers in North Carolina invented</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-maskers march on London...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12532373/coronavirus-conspiracy-theorists-pandemic-hoax-march-london/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of coronavirus conspiracy theorists who believe the pandemic is a HOAX have marched on London today. Crowds of Covid-deniers swarmed the capital demanding an end to face masks, social dis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Weapon For Dieters: Consuming Capsules Made From Own Feces...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/secret-weapon-dieting-fecal-microbiome/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that taking frozen microbiome capsules created using one's own feces while dieting may help limit weight regain in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-cutting uncertainty mires Postal Service in more delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Cost-cutting-uncertainty-mires-Postal-Service-in-15524127.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Confusion over Postmaster General Louis DeJoy's planned cost-cutting changes has gripped the nation's mail service and threatened to bring even more delivery delays, say postal workers and union officials.  Days after DeJoy testified before Senate and House committees, vowing to prioritize election mail, postal workers disputed his assertions that pandemic-related challenges were to blame for widespread mail slowdowns. They say the holdups are tied to the postal leader's crackdown - since partially suspended - on overtime and other operational changes, as well as the lack of clarity about which of his proposals will ultimately stick.  In Philadelphia, some letter carriers have gone two weeks without a day off, said one postal worker who, like 11 others interviewed for this piece, spoke on the condition of anonymity because of fears of reprisal from their superiors. Processing facilities in other parts of Pennsylvania - Scranton, Harrisburg, Lancaster, the Lehigh Valley - have week-long package backlogs. In Florida, some workers are being instructed not to log mail that arrives after carriers have left on their routes, an anathema to long-serving agency employees.  In the Great Lakes region, which includes parts of Michigan, Wisconsin, Indiana, Illinois and Missouri, managers are unsure whether DeJoy's realignment of the agency will continue, further slowing the daily movement of hundreds of millions of mail items.  "Everyone's clueless," said one region mid-level manager.  In other areas, including California, Iowa, Minnesota and Wisconsin, postal workers say previous delays have been resolved, but employees are bracing for the election and holiday season, and additional changes DeJoy could institute after the Nov. 3 vote. The plans under consideration, described by four people familiar with Postal Service...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin protesters rally vs pandemic restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53959552</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters who say Germany's restrictions are "anti-freedom" are told to disperse for violating distancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Cartel Now Assassinates Enemies With Bomb-Toting Drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/36013/mexican-drug-cartel-now-assassinating-its-enemies-with-improvised-explosive-toting-drones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tactic has become widespread on battlefields overseas and now appears to be proliferating to organized crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: World's Richest Smash Wealth Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-28/world-s-richest-people-smashed-wealth-records-this-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History Suggests Post-Pandemic Peace Is Rare...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2020-08-29/history-suggests-post-pandemic-peace-is-rare-kefm52jx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will we even know by Inauguration Day who won?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/514162-will-we-even-know-by-inauguration-day-who-won-the-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this year’s election turns out to be an embarrassing, destabilizing and disruptive fiasco, it won’t require a succession threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JFK grandson may be last hope for Kennedy political dynasty...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/29/jfks-grandson-may-be-last-hope-for-kennedy-dynasty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Jack Schlossberg’s brief appearance at the 2020 Democratic National Convention, insiders are speculating about the possible political aspirations of JFK’s only grandson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Who Organized BLM Rally Hit With Bill For Police Overtime...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/08/28/new-jersey-teen-who-organized-rally-supporting-black-lives-matter-and-affordable-housing-billed-for-police-overtime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After watching thousands of Americans show support for the Black Lives Matter movement, Emily Gil, 18, was inspired to hold her own rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French police probe wave of horse killings; Satanic rituals suspected...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-police-investigate-wave-horse-184931026.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police on Friday issued an identikit picture of a suspect wanted over a wave of gruesome horse killings as they stepped up the investigation into what they believe may be satanic rituals. In the latest of at least 19 killings and savage mutilations this year, a mare was found eviscerated and a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President still faces skepticism in suburbs following convention...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf1e83c457046e248f7f095ee9460bd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pat Newell backed Donald Trump in 2016. But after Trump’s speech at the Republican National Convention this week included no mention of the police shooting of Jacob Blake...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin protesters rally vs pandemic restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0c7669902d01c346e365e7cb15644e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON — The U.S. government has detained children at several major hotel chains during the coronavirus pandemic instead of transferring them to government-funded shelters. The data...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riots in Sweden after Quran burning by far-right activists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/578834d58fa236ae2fcfaf6c979b3e55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM (AP) — Far-right activists burned a Quran in the southern Swedish city of Malmo, sparking riots and unrest after more than 300 people gathered to protest, police said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Trump appointees flout Hatch Act, civil servants who get caught get punished...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/To-punished-workers-Hatch-Act-not-a-joke-15523350.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A Defense Logistics Agency employee was suspended for 30 days without pay last fall after giving his office colleagues a PowerPoint presentation that displayed the words, "Vote Republican."  An Energy Department worker was forced to resign in January after admitting she gave a woman running for Congress a tour of a federal waste treatment plant so the candidate could show her expertise to potential voters.  Another civil servant began a 120-day suspension without pay from the Food and Drug Administration in July after creating a Facebook page with his name and photograph to solicit political donations and then co-hosting a fundraiser.  These were some of the recent consequences for federal workers who illegally mixed government employment with partisan politics in violation of the Hatch Act, the anti-corruption law Congress passed in 1939.  The New Deal-era law applies, on paper at least, to civil servants and political appointees alike. But the top Trump administration officials showcased in prime-time appearances and speaking slots at the Republican National Convention this week serve as a reminder that when it comes to flouting the separation between governing and politicking, there appears to be a two-tiered system of consequences.  Watchdog groups complained that acting homeland security secretary Chad Wolf and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo violated the Hatch Act this week when Wolf led a taped naturalization ceremony for newly minted citizens on White House grounds and Pompeo gave a speech from Israel.  "Convention events were planned and executed by the Trump Campaign and RNC," White House spokesman Judd Deere said in a statement. "Any government employees who participated did so in their personal capacities and in compliance with the Hatch Act."  The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASE NUMBERS RISE AGAIN IN EUROPE </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Case-numbers-rise-again-in-Europe-15522078.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases are surging again in Europe after months of relative calm, but the second wave looks different from the first: Fewer people are dying, and the newest and mostly younger victims of the pandemic need less medical treatment.  Unlike the initial hit of the pandemic this spring, which overwhelmed hospitals and turned nursing homes into grim mortuaries, the European resurgence of recent weeks has not forced as many people into medical wards.  But the increase is widespread, and it is unsettling societies that had hoped the worst was behind them. Paris on Friday joined some other French jurisdictions in imposing a citywide mask requirement, with cases spiking. France, Germany, Spain and others posted caseloads in recent days that had not been seen since April and early May. Spain has been hit particularly hard, with per capita cases now worse than in the United States - a notable marker in Europe, which after the initial springtime spike had generally controlled the virus more successfully than America.  And with almost every European country planning a return to in-person schooling, many starting next week, public health officials are holding their breath for the impact.  The surge is a first test of the efforts Europe has made to improve its resilience in the half-year since the pandemic unleashed a wave of suffering across the world. Most European countries have improved their testing capacity. They have hired contact tracers to combat big outbreaks. They have masks and gloves for their doctors and nurses.  Many countries, including Italy, endured grinding lockdowns this spring. Now citizens are exhausted, and economies are still flagging.  "I don't think the country can survive another lockdown. And to be frank, there is no reason to," said Ranieri Guerra, a World Health Organization assistant director...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE makes 'privacy' change, and advertising companies cry foul... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Apple-makes-a-privacy-change-and-Facebook-and-15522035.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the coming weeks, Apple plans to change its iPhone software to make it more difficult for advertisers to track Apple customers, an effort that will help further one of the company's long-standing goals: Protecting the privacy of its customers.  But with Apple under the antitrust spotlight, its privacy move has also been called a power move by an advertising industry that is scrambling to adjust to the changes, expected to be included in iOS 14, the company's latest mobile operating system expected to go live next month.  On Wednesday, Facebook became the latest organization to speak openly about the changes, telling investors and users that Apple's move will hurt the social network's bottom line because it will limit the kind of personalized targeting that makes Facebook's ads so valuable to advertisers. "This is not a change we want to make, but unfortunately Apple's updates to iOS14 have forced this decision," the company said in a blog post.  Some in the advertising industry see the moves as part privacy, part self-interest on the part of Apple. Apple also offers advertising, and by limiting the amount of data outside marketers collect, Apple's access to the data becomes more valuable.  "I think there's probably 30 percent truth in that they're doing it for privacy reasons and it's 70 percent that they're doing it because it's what's good for Apple," said Nick Jordan, founder of Narrative I/O, which helps companies gather data for advertising. "It's a question for regulators and courts whether they should be able to wield the power they do over this ecosystem," he said. "They created it, but can they rule it with an iron fist?"  In an interview with The Washington Post, Apple director of privacy engineering Erik Neuenschwander said the changes were part of Apple's privacy road map. When asked whether Apple...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEURALINK PUTS COMPUTER CHIPS IN ANIMAL BRAINS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828231238-ikq23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECH-NEURALINK/MUSK (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-'Three little pigs': Musk's Neuralink puts computer chips in animal brains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin CAN sue NYT for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828224738-q2qkg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK TIMES-PALIN/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Sarah Palin can sue New York Times for defamation -court ruling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTOR BOSEMAN DEAD AT 43...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5f4352111fdead278da3651b44d311b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Actor Chadwick Boseman, who played Black icons Jackie Robinson and James Brown with searing intensity before finding fame as the regal Black Panther in the Marvel cinematic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests providing results in 20 seconds trialled at Heathrow...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1387642/covid-19-tests-heathrow-eplace-quarantine-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 tests that produce results in just 20 seconds are being trialled at Heathrow airport to replace the current quarantine system. The airport plans to mass-screen the 78 million travellers th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSKENSTEIN!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/28/elon-musk-unveils-working-prototype-of-brain-implant-device/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney for accused Kenosha protest gunman says teen acted in self-defense...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828234039-68iot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-RACE/USA (WRAPUP 9, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 9-Attorney for accused Kenosha protest gunman says teen acted in self-defense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOKING FOR VOLUNTEERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aacbb0ff7a66b64faa375e22694425ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk isn't content with electric cars, shooting people into orbit, populating Mars and building underground tunnels to solve traffic problems. He also wants to get inside your...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College towns growing alarmed over outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d36c40584bc1c9730654b589f672f79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — As waves of schools and businesses around the country are cleared to reopen, college towns are moving toward renewed shutdowns because of too many parties and too many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, at NH rally, sows fears about 'thugs,' 'anarchists'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ca2a7999c107d682dc21b8a0dfad4f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDONDERRY, N.H. (AP) — Fresh off accepting the Republican Party’s nomination, President Donald Trump said Friday he was the only thing standing between “democracy and the mob,” as he lashed out...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  GOP portrayal of urban mayhem doesn't always match reality...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6a983b159cb0a20468e0c0a19dd93a31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At almost every turn at the Republican National Convention, speakers from the president on down portrayed American cities like Portland, Oregon, New York and Chicago as lawless Democratic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's charts slower course on reopening...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/253ce3fcdc81b2b7960cd3ab40b208ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — With the hope of preventing another virus surge, California Gov. Gavin Newsom announced a new process Friday for reopening businesses that's more gradual than the first...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Regrets Maskless Night...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gop-senator-thom-tillis-says-he-regrets-maskless-night-at-trumps-white-house-rnc-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I fell short of my own standard,” Sen. Thom Tillis (R-NC) said in a statement after he was photographed without a mask during Trump’s RNC speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service copes with infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-Trump-travels-Secret-Service-copes-with-15523103.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - When President Donald Trump gave a speech to a group of sheriffs in Tampa late last month, his decision to travel forced a large contingent of Secret Service agents to head to a state that was then battling one of the worst coronavirus surges in the nation.  Even before Air Force One touched down on July 31, the fallout was apparent: Five Secret Service agents already on the ground had to be replaced after one tested positive for the coronavirus and the others working in proximity were presumed to be infected, according to people familiar with the situation.  The previously unreported episode is one of a series of examples of how Trump's insistence on traveling and holding campaign-style events amid the pandemic has heightened the risks for the people who safeguard his life, intensifying the strain on the Secret Service.  In the past two months, dozens of Secret Service agents who worked to ensure the security of the president and Vice President Mike Pence at public events have been sickened or sidelined because they were in direct contact with infected people, according to multiple people familiar with the episodes, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe the incidents.  Despite that, Trump has continued to hold large gatherings - most dramatically at the White House on Thursday night, when he delivered his acceptance speech at the Republican National Convention before a crowd of 1,500 people seated closely together on the South Lawn, with few masks in sight. The vast majority were not tested for the coronavirus ahead of time.  Trump's actions rebuff the scientific consensus that the best way tamp down the spread of the virus is to avoid large gatherings and close quarters. Critics say his refusal to abide by those guidelines is imposing unnecessary risk on the Secret Service staff, who have no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Republicans weaponized impeachment and Dems ignored it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/28/democratic-republican-conventions-trump-impeachment-404342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It seems like history,” said House Judiciary Chairman Jerry Nadler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC suspended from App Store...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/28/apple-suspends-fortnite-maker-epic-games-app-store-account.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are disappointed that we have had to terminate the Epic Games account on the App Store. We have worked with the team at Epic Games for many years on their launches and releases," Apple said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems will try to repeal ban on federal money for abortions...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-democrats-try-repeal-longstanding-190200300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats say they will put up a fight in 2021 to end a long-standing ban on federal funding of abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BEATS TRUMP IN TV AUDIENCE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828204832-lodex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/TV RATINGS (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Trump convention speech attracts smaller TV audience than Biden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart Disease Detected From Selfies...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/selfies-help-diagnose-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists using a computer algorithm can detect coronary artery disease (CAD) using four pictures of a person’s face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg slams APPLE 'monopoly' in leaked comments...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/28/zuckerberg-slams-apples-app-store-monopoly-in-leaked-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg poured gasoline on his simmering feud with Apple on Friday, slamming the company’s “stranglehold” on the iPhone’s App Store, saying it charges “monopol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9.9 Million Watch on FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/republican-convention-tv-viewership-donald-trump-joe-biden-1203026084/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s acceptance speech on the final night of the Republican National Convention drew 19.9 million TV viewers across six networks, falling short of the 21.8 million who watched Joe B…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP GENERAL: MILITARY WON'T RESOLVE DISPUTE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a979ad8beceacd77c692e42448cf7b82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. armed forces will have no role in carrying out the election process or resolving a disputed vote, the top U.S. military officer told Congress in comments released...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divorce rates in America soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8674001/Divorce-rates-America-soar-34-percent-COVID-19-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data collected by Legal Templates found that there has been a 34% increase in sales for divorce agreements during the coronavirus pandemic - indicating soaring divorce rates in the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American jets intercept military aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/28/politics/us-jets-intercept-russians-alaska/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US F-22 fighter jets intercepted Russian military aircraft in international airspace off the coast of Alaska late Thursday, according to North American Aerospace Defense Command.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
