<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Obama at 60: Feet on dance floor, eyes on future...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/article/Obama-at-60-Feet-on-the-dance-floor-eyes-on-the-16374027.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday Barack Obama celebrated his 60th birthday on Martha's Vineyard, at his $11.75...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ leaks pics of bday bash...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/08/dj-posts-pics-of-obamas-birthday-party-before-being-forced-to-delete-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manager TJ Chapman gave his Instagram followers an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at President Barack Obama’s 60th birthday party at Martha’s Vineyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin warns of 'catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/09/austin-catastrophe-epicenter-again-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City implores residents to stay home, mask up and get vaccinated as ICU capacity in hospitals dwindles to single digits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican megadonors flock to Tim Scott, building 2024 buzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/09/tim-scott-mega-millions-fundraising-502764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oracle's Larry Ellison is the biggest name in a group of major Republican donors sending big money to South Carolina's Scott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia contends with Confederate names on side streets...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/virginia-9206a44094a86f8b212bc9b4aff5fe5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McLEAN, Va. (AP) — It came as a surprise to Mottrom Drive resident Beau Fitzpatrick that he lives on a street named for a Confederate soldier. “Really? I always assumed it was named for an apple, or apple juice,” he said, referring to the Mott's brand of apple products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILDREN'S HOSPITALS FILL UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/kids-sick-covid-are-filling-children-s-hospitals-areas-seeing-n1276238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Absolutely household infections are the beginning of this pandemic, that is a major driving force in the spread of infections. We see it often within households, parents to children,” a pediatrician said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge says Florida can't ban cruise ship's 'vaccine passport'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210809020408-gvbyl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NRWN CRS LN HLDG-COURT/FLORIDA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-U.S. judge says Florida can't ban cruise ship's 'vaccine passport' program</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-Generation Battery Pioneer Sees Breakthroughs Coming...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/next-generation-battery-pioneer-sees-breakthroughs-coming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Attacks on Diplomats Leave Scores of Victims but Still Little Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/08/mystery-attacks-on-diplomats-leave-scores-of-victims-but-still-little-evidence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s top aides were told on Friday that experts studying the mysterious illnesses affecting scores of diplomats, spies and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RESPECT' Review: Jennifer Hudson Brings Soul to Aretha Franklin Biopic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/respect-film-review-jennifer-hudson-aretha-franklin-biopic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Respect" film review: Jennifer Hudson shines as Aretha Franklin in a biopic that's more effective as a jukebox musical than a character piece</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In sudden bout of racial killings, S African sees dark history repeating self...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-a-sudden-bout-of-racial-killings-a-south-african-suburb-sees-a-dark-history-repeating-itself/ar-AAN3lLu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa may have christened itself the “Rainbow Nation,” but high walls of income and opportunity still divide its communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How crypto became powerful force in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-cryptocurrency-became-a-powerful-force-in-washington/ar-AAN3M8O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nascent cryptocurrency industry — eager to shed a reputation for being lawless and anti-regulation — is looking to influence ongoing political and regulatory debates that could alter cryptocurrency’s future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal U.S. marijuana pouring into Mexico. It's pricey, popular and has names like 'Bubba Kush'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Legal-U-S-marijuana-is-pouring-into-Mexico-It-s-16372703.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY - The most sought after marijuana being trafficked across the U.S.-Mexico...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL tensions rise over vax rules...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/566707-nfl-tensions-rise-over-vaccine-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions are running high in the NFL over COVID-19 vaccinations, with a vocal minority of players and coaches criticizing rules mandated by the league that is intended to raise the vaccination rate of team players and staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has pandemic put property rights in crosshairs?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/566784-has-the-pandemic-put-property-rights-in-the-crosshairs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent spate of policies goes too far in restricting homeowners’ ability to do as they wish with the properties they own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez doesn't rule out challenging Schumer...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/566914-ocasio-cortez-doesnt-rule-out-challenging-schumer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) did not rule out challenging Senate Majority Leader Charles Schumer (D-N.Y.) when asked during a recent interview if she will launch a primary bid for his seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House grapples with resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/566788-white-house-grapples-with-covid-19-resurgence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is grappling with a resurgence of coronavirus cases that Democrats see as a real political threat given the central role getting the pandemic under control plays for President Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of fish killed by toxic red tide wash ashore on Florida beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/09/red-tide-florida-beaches-fish-kill-phosphate-pollution</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A devastating wastewater dump may have contributed to a deadly algal bloom, residents say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roller coasters fight migraines?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3434400/roller-coasters-fight-migraines-sufferers-motion-sickness-differently-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIDING roller coasters could help combat migraines after new research discovered that sufferers experience motion sickness differently. Fresh findings from the pioneering German study could be key …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church reeling after six members die in 10 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/florida-church-reeling-after-six-members-die-within-10-days-amid-spike-in-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For George Davis, a bishop at Impact Church in Jacksonville, getting vaccinated against the coronavirus was an act of faith. He says that he believes in divine creation, and that the shot is a miracle - a sign of God...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban seizes cities across Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/taliban-seizes-cities-across-afghanistan-u-s-readies-final-withdrawal-n1276312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapid fall of provincial capitals deals a heavy blow to the crumbling Afghan government forces, which have struggled to contain the group's offensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta vanquishes all rivals as scientists race to understand its tricks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98goldilocks-virus-e2-80-99-delta-vanquishes-all-variant-rivals-as-scientists-race-to-understand-its-tricks/ar-AAN58B4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mutations ramp up transmissibility and raise new challenges for ending the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HE BROKE LAW'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/brittany-commisso-cuomo-groping-allegation-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The executive assistant says she never wants her daughter "to be afraid of any person in power."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/cuomo-s-fate-rests-with-n-y-lawmakers-considering-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuomo’s Fate Rests With N.Y. Lawmakers Considering Impeachment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows people trapped in elevator as floodwaters rise...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/08/video-shows-man-trapped-in-elevator-as-floodwaters-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nebraska man Tony Luu and two others nearly drowned as neck-high floodwaters engulfed the elevator of his downtown Omaha apartment building, video shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Top Aide Resigns...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/08/cuomos-top-aide-melissa-derosa-resigns-as-he-fights-to-survive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. — Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo’s top aide, Melissa DeRosa, said late Sunday that she had resigned, less than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN: CODE RED FOR HUMANITY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-science-climate-environment-and-nature-united-nations-1d89d5183583718ad4ad311fa2ee7d83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earth’s climate is getting so hot that temperatures in about a decade will probably blow past a level of warming that world leaders have sought to prevent, according to a report released Monday that the United Nations called a “code red for humanity.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire-friendly weather to return to Northern California...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-science-fires-environment-and-nature-california-754ad7ca2c6297e2327627d8688e714b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thick smoke that held down winds and temperatures began to clear Sunday from the scenic forestlands of Northern California as firefighters battling the largest single wildfire in state history braced for a return of fire-friendly weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO ACCUSER SPEAKS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-joe-biden-176b964414bc083081c39e737c0c0a59</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo faces another day under fire Monday as a key legislative committee meets to discuss possible impeachment proceedings and a woman who has accused him of groping her speaks in her first TV interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pitcher's 31 MPH strike is slowest recorded...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlb.com/news/brock-holt-throws-31-mph-eephus-pitch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Josh Harrison had seen veteran utility man Brock Holt pitch when they were teammates on the Nationals last season. But he still had no idea what was coming when Holt took the mound in the eighth inning to mop up for the Rangers in their 12-3 loss to the A's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most successful squatter' has lived in home 20 years without paying mortgage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9872937/Long-Island-squatter-52-not-paid-mortgage-20-years-claims-contracted-COVID-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York man has reportedly claimed he has COVID-19 and can't be evicted from the Long Island home where he has not paid his mortgage for more than 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestor carrying sign of aborted fetuses arrested at school...</title>
      <link>https://nbc-2.com/news/crime/2021/08/07/punta-gorda-protestor-carrying-sign-of-aborted-fetuses-arrested-for-disrupting-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nbc-2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A protestor carrying a sign showing aborted fetuses outside an elementary school was arrested disrupting traffic and school operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter of million rally in France against new restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/quarter-of-a-million-rally-in-france-against-countrys-new-covid-restrictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants argue that health pass now needed to enter cafes or travel on inter-city trains encroaches on civil liberties in country where individual freedom is highly prized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Apocalyptic' scenes hit Greece as Athens besieged by flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/07/apocalyptic-scenes-hit-greece-as-athens-besieged-by-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Athens is a city under siege. On the ground there are tales of heroism and fear for the future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City With 2.4 Million Population Has 6 ICU Beds Left...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/u-s-city-with-2-4-million-population-has-just-six-icu-beds-left/ar-AAN4aaD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With ICU beds down to a single digit, Austin sounded the alarm Saturday, using its emergency alert system to let residents in the Texas capital city know that the local state of the pandemic is “dire.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden speeds ahead on installing judges...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/566789-biden-speeds-ahead-on-installing-judges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden is ahead of any president in the past 40 years at this point for installing judges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic set off deadly rise in speeding that hasn't stopped...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-30a26b82eeab5880abab5f2b30952725</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Motorists put the pedal to the metal during the pandemic and police are worried as roads get busy with the final stretch of summer travel. The latest data shows the number of highway deaths in 2020 was the greatest in more than a decade even though cars and trucks drove fewer miles during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
