<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>State confronts its energy, politics and culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/02/20/they-were-not-prepared-after-winter-crisis-texas-will-have-to-confront-its-energy-politics-and-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the snow and ice melts, the Lone Star State faces a host of questions — technical, political and cultural. What went wrong? Who is responsible? How do...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea's concentration camps reviewed on GOOGLE Maps...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/google-maps-users-find-reviews-23540461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People have been leaving largely positive reviews for the Yodok Concentration Camp on Google, which has previously been reported by one ex-detainee as being "worse than Auschwitz"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black, female and high-profile, Kamala Harris is top target in online fever swamps...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/black-female-high-profile-kamala-155005192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president's high profile, race and gender have made her a target of some of the worst internet smears. The problem is only getting worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed with camera, an ER doctor captures faces of virus war...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/armed-camera-young-er-doctor-130004840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the COVID-19 pandemic began last spring, Dr. Scott Kobner knew history was unfolding. Soon he began showing up at the hospital on his days off with his Leica M6 and M10 cameras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY WARNS</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-02-virologist-italy-virus-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases in Italy are on the rise again, in large part due to the more infectious British variant, a top virologist warned in a newspaper interview published Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFECTIONS IN GERMANY RISE AGAIN</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-02-germany-urges-caution-covid-infections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Health Minister Jens Spahn urged caution on Sunday in the face of rising coronavirus infection numbers, just as schools across the country prepare to reopen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People who wear glasses are three times LESS likely to catch Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2376949/glasses-wearers-less-likely-catch-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEARING glasses makes you up to three times less likely to catch Covid, a study has found. Researchers found people with spectacles rub and touch their eyes less, which is a “significant route of i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION PASSES 500,000 COVID DEATHS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/u-s-reaches-500-000-deaths-coronavirus-n1257992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of dead rivals the population of Atlanta or Sacramento, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm X's family releases letter alleging FBI, police role in his death...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221151255-tedkj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil rights leader's family urge investigation into letter suggesting security forces behind his death in a 1965 shooting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  MASKS ANOTHER YEAR</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221143523-j7r4j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 1, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 1-Americans may still need masks to fight COVID in 2022, Fauci says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French city of Nice asks tourists to stay away...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221110647-2nxex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are mulling a weekend lockdown to put off visitors as it battles a spike in coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snubbed as Obama high court pick, Garland in line to be AG...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-biden-cabinet-merrick-garland-judiciary-coronavirus-pandemic-12978c008b81f1cc59e0d650cd4c7cb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The last time Merrick Garland was nominated by the White House for a job, Republicans wouldn't even meet with him. Now, the once-snubbed Supreme Court pick will finally...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How  winter storm pushed Texas into crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/houston-football-storms-coronavirus-pandemic-hurricanes-5fd491ed5bfd9aa0ae08426c6078539e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Two days before the storm began, Houston’s chief elected official warned her constituents to prepare as they would for a major hurricane. Many took heed: Texans who could stocked up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists clone endangered ferret!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/1st-cloned-endagered-species-ferret-23cde3908e496692648dc28d4b8121ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHEYENNE, Wyo. (AP) — Scientists have cloned the first U.S. endangered species, a black-footed ferret duplicated from the genes of an animal that died over 30 years ago. The slinky predator...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes voters in tumult...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/golden-globes-voters-tumult-members-130023140.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Times investigation finds that the nonprofit HFPA regularly issues substantial payments to its members in ways that some experts say could skirt IRS guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental health burden heaviest among young adults...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/pandemics-mental-health-burden-heaviest-young-adults/story?id=75811308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a recent survey, almost two-thirds of 18- to-24-year-olds reported symptoms of anxiety or depression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel re-opens further with 'green pass'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-re-opens-further-with-green-pass-for-vaccinated/ar-BB1dSlf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel took a step towards normalcy Sunday, re-opening a raft of businesses and services following its third national lockdown, with some sites only available to those who have been vaccinated. At the family-owned Katalina shoe store in central Tel Aviv, Mordechai Nazarian said his business had been closed for eight of the last 12 months, with "little openings here and there" as Israel lifted restrictions between lockdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5% have had near-death experience -- and say it made life worth living...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/five-percent-have-had-near-death-experiences-research/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five percent of the population has had a near-death experience — and they say it made life worth living.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coroner Accused of Running Funeral Home From Hell...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/grieving-mom-fears-coroner-grisly-215230261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summit County Sheriff's OfficeChantal Reh never got to know her daughter Christie, who had been diagnosed in the womb with Turner’s Syndrome, a rare chromosomal disorder, and was stillborn.Nearly three years later, Reh still doesn’t know if Christie’s ashes, which she keeps at home in a small urn, are actually Christie’s.Shortly after she delivered her baby at a Colorado hospital in August 2018, Reh says she was given a list of funeral homes in the area that would cremate such a small body. The only ones willing to provide the service were owned by a local couple, Shannon and Staci Kent. There was no reason for doubt—after all, Shannon Kent had been appointed Lake County coroner in 2012. He was subsequently elected to a four-year term in 2014, and re-elected in 2018. Chantal Reh never got to know her daughter, Christie. Chantal Reh However, on Thursday, Colorado police arrested Shannon and Staci Kent after finding a decaying corpse in a funeral home they previously operated. The body was identified as that of 42-year-old Victor Akubuo, a trucker who was killed in a semi-trailer crash last July, after which Akubuo’s family hired the Kents for funeral services. The corpse was reportedly discovered by a new funeral business that was moving into the building.Since 2012, Shannon Kent, 45, has served as the Lake County coroner alongside running a private funeral home business. A search warrant affidavit filed by Lake County Sheriff Amy Reyes reveals a spate of disturbing details about the couple, whose operating license was permanently revoked in December. Among other chilling anecdotes, a former deputy coroner in Colorado who planned on buying the Kents’ funeral homes describes backing out of the deal after discovering an unidentified infant found in a tiny casket that appeared to have been sitting in a freezer since at least last October.Reh, who had not heard about the arrests until being contacted by The Daily Beast on Saturday, wonders if the body might have been Christie’s.Reh and her partner took their first and last photos with Christie back in 2018, and the hospital released the body to Staci Kent—who promptly went dark.“We were calling her and calling her, and she wasn’t answering for days and days,” Reh told The Daily Beast, explaining that she wanted to go to the funeral home so she could “see my baby one last time,” before the body was cremated.Eventually, Staci texted Reh and scheduled an appointment for her to come in the next day. But when she got there, Reh says, Staci refused to let her see Christie’s body, which she claimed had been moved to another location. Besides, Staci said, Christie’s remains had been “sitting so long, the remains would be discolored and dismembered,” Reh recalls Staci telling her.Ten days later, Staci finally handed over Christie’s ashes to Reh in a sealed urn. Immediately, something seemed off. The remains were not in the urn Reh had chosen, nor was there any paperwork identifying them as Christie’s. Reh tried to confirm that the plastic baggie filled with ashes in fact contained her daughter’s remains, calling Staci weekly, then monthly, until finally giving up. The ashes “looked like pencil shavings or something,” said Reh, who said she never even got confirmation that the ashes were indeed human.“Still to this day, she has never gotten back to us,” she said. Staci Kent finally handed over Christie’s ashes to Reh in a plastic baggie and sealed urn. Chantal Reh The Kents were unable to be reached for comment. John Scott, a defense attorney who has represented the Kents in the past but has not yet been retained in the latest case, expressed cautious doubt about the charges.“A lot of the allegations that this District Attorney’s office has been making are very questionable, as far as I’m concerned,” Scott told The Daily Beast. “Based on my history with them, I’m a little bit skeptical.”The latest investigation into the couple began in February 2020, when a grieving mom called the Lake County Sheriff’s Office and left a voicemail. The unidentified woman explained that her baby son had been stillborn in December 2019. Like Reh, she was not getting straight answers from the Kents about taking possession of her son’s remains, and said dealing with them had been a “nightmare.”According to the search warrant affidavit, Staci Kent promised the woman and her fiancé that their child would be cremated in time for a Christmas service. The price for an adult cremation was normally $400, but since the body was so small, Staci said she’d only charge $200. The couple would get their child’s remains by Dec. 20, Staci assured them. A week went by, then 10 days, and the two hadn’t heard from Staci. On Dec. 23, they were finally able to reach her, the filing says.Something “seemed off and fishy,” they told Staci, who “apologized profusely and [said]...she would waive the cremation charge,” it continues. Staci explained that the body had been transferred to another location to be cremated, something to which the parents had not agreed. They asked Staci how they could be sure the ashes were indeed those of their child, it says. Staci told them not to worry.When a funeral home employee dropped off the ashes at the couple’s home that evening, they grew even more suspicious. The worker handed over a “black plastic urn of ashes...affixed with a zip tie.” The ashes were delivered with no paperwork—no death certificate, no chain of custody, and no name attached. They also weighed almost a full pound, the mom said, which was far more than it should have been for a premature infant. Had their baby’s remains been mixed up with someone else’s? Did the container they were given contain more than one person’s ashes? Staci told the couple that they’d just have to take her word for it, the affidavit says. Shannon also explained that the excessive weight could be due the body being cremated while wearing “excessive clothes,” or perhaps the “extremely heavy” cardboard box in which the body was transported.A subsequent investigation by two experts found shards of metal that looked like pieces of jewelry that had melted in the heat of the crematorium. Further, the remains were those of a “minimum of two people”—an infant along with a “larger individual.”Although the affidavit does not include the mother’s name, the details and dates appear to describe David Roemer and Elizabeth Witthoeft, a Colorado couple who filed a civil lawsuit against Kent alleging he mishandled their stillborn son’s remains. According to Remington Fang, the attorney representing Roemer and Witthoeft, one of the funeral homes operated by the Kents kept bodies not in a refrigerator but in a garage.“What happened to my clients was just horrific,” Fang told The Daily Beast. “They took away the last bit of comfort that these parents had.”Ashes from a stillborn baby should fit inside a baggie 1 inch wide by 2 inches tall, said Fang. The bag of remains Roemer and Witthoeft received weighed 3/4 pound, and didn’t come close to fitting inside the infant-sized urn they bought. When they asked the Kents for a larger urn, Fang says, Shannon replied, “Now you’re just asking for a handout.”“You trust these funeral homes to take care of and show respect to a deceased person,” he said. “You’re going through a painful time, and these people are treating their loved one like a sack of radishes.”The Kents have long been under suspicion by authorities for what they say are sloppy, even criminal, business practices.In September 2019, Shannon was indicted for dispatching Staci to “numerous death scenes” without being licensed to practice as a coroner. In one instance, she showed up to collect a body without bringing a body bag. After being charged with second degree official misconduct, a petty offense, Shannon confronted the district attorney in a courthouse hallway and told him to “pull his head out of his ass,” according to court filings.A year later, the Colorado Department of Regulatory Agencies (DORA) shuttered two funeral homes operated by the Kents after police found abhorrent conditions there.This Is How Horribly They’re Treating the Dead in BrooklynDeputies serving a search warrant at one “encountered a strong odor of decomposition and discovered the following: used body bags, medical gloves, and other surgical equipment with dried bodily fluid on them piled on the floor; dried bodily fluids on the metal preparation table and the floor; bodily fluids leaking out of a blue body bag containing a decedent that was not refrigerated; numerous bags of unlabeled cremains; a container of animal remains leaking fluids; a sealed casket with dirt on the exterior containing the remains of John Doe that had been exhumed; several bodies in refrigeration wrapped in sheets or blankets without identifying tags or paperwork; a small unmarked casket containing a stillborn infant that was ‘abandoned’ according to Respondent; and paperwork scattered several feet deep on the floor of what appeared to be the business office,” says the DORA report.Chantal Reh wonders if the stillborn baby noted in the report might have been Christie.“I have been begging for testing to be done on this body and from what the sheriff and detective told me they couldn't get permits or approval to do so,” she says. “I am devastated to think that body might be my little girl and now will never know.”Reh, who circulated a petition trying to get Shannon recalled from his position as county coroner, says she had just about given up on him or Staci ever facing any consequences when she heard of the arrests.“They’ve been in trouble multiple times and nothing has ever come of it,” Reh said, describing a sensation of “immediate butterflies and relief” upon getting the news. “I felt kind of helpless in achieving anything...At this point I'm so mad, I don't have any tears left.”Shannon and Staci Kent were released on $10,000 bail, and are due back in court March 9. A judge forbade Shannon Kent from handling any coroner duties for the county until further notice.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel shuts all beaches along Mediterranean due to oil spill...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-february-21-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu discusses oil spill with Tarek el-Molla, suggests regional alliance to keep Mediterranean clean</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypothermia deaths in homes mount...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/houston-hypothermia-weather-conroe-texas-8323ab5f5c1612e632f7f2e6c2c20358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — With the snow and ice clearing in Texas after days of unusually cold temperatures, bodies are being found of people who likely froze to death as they struggled to stay warm after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Women Can Join Military in Latest Widening of Rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/saudi-women-can-join-military-in-latest-widening-of-rights/ar-BB1dS5z7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Women in Saudi Arabia can now take up arms and enter the military, the latest profession in the kingdom to open up to female recruits. Saudi Arabian women can be employed as soldiers, lance corporals, corporals, sergeants, and staff sergeants, according to the Saudi-based Arab News. Jobs have been gradually opening up for Saudi women, whose increased participation in the workforce is part of Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the closet, under the mattress: Partygoers hide from police...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210221114319-43uvf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN-RAID (TV):In the closet, under the mattress: pandemic partygoers hide from Madrid police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like Hunger Games': Vax hunters chase elusive doses...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/it-was-like-the-hunger-games-minnesota-vaccine-hunters-use-social-media-to-chase-elusive-doses/600025495/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Vaccine chasers" pool their intel on Facebook, with tips on where to get the shots on short notice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Entire school board resigns over comments bashing parents...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/california-districts-school-board-resigns-comments-bashing-parents/story?id=76020108</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All members of a California school district's board of trustees have resigned after several were heard making disparaging comments about parents during a meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of kids skip kindergarten...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/education/2021/02/21/millions-kindergartners-skip-public-school-covid-redshirting/6759277002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With parents desperate for alternatives to distance learning, kindergarten enrollment has plummeted in districts across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans flock to food banks as recovery begins
...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/story/news/2021/02/20/austin-searches-bottled-water-distribution-as-recovery-begins/4522646001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We check in on the status of water and power as Austin digs itself out of a winter storm crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant smugglers take advantage of Texas deep freeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/20/migrant-smugglers-take-advantage-texas-deep-freeze/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One consequence of the cold snap that’s engulfed much of Texas is that some migrant smugglers are figuring it’s the right time to try to sneak people north out of the border areas, figuring the Border Patrol has its hands full with other duties. Customs and Border Protection says it has recorded 15 migrant deaths in Texas so far this month, and seven of those have been blamed on exposure to the cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly shooting at Gun Outlet: 3 killed, 2 hurt and questions about why...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/crime_police/article_a897bee4-73ca-11eb-bbcb-df381460932f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Everybody’s strapped in there,' customer says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor NHL game turns into nightmare for players...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/20/outdoor-nhl-game-turns-into-a-nightmare-for-players/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STATELINE, Nev. — The setting was spectacular but the ice conditions were far from it, leading to an extended delay between the first and second period of the outdoor game between the Golden Knight…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy risks in tech-infused post-Covid workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210221-privacy-faces-risks-in-tech-infused-post-covid-workplace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Privacy faces risks in tech-infused post-Covid workplace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are streaming algorithms really damaging film?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-56085924</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Martin Scorsese says streaming algorithms demean cinema and treat viewers as consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combat experiences like ambushes or killing civilian more linked to suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/02/19/some-combat-experiences-like-ambushes-or-killing-a-civilian-more-closely-linked-to-suicide-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A years-long study of Iraq and Afghanistan veterans found three combat experiences most closely linked with suicidal behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50% of mild patients still have symptoms after 6 months...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/50-percent-of-mild-moderate-covid-patients-still-have-symptoms-after-6-months-study-659657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants were interviewed up to four times over the course of the study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How sluggish covid vaccination program could delay return to normal and invite resistant variants to emerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/How-a-sluggish-vaccination-program-could-delay-a-15966897.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president-elect's pledge had a certain ring to it:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second-shot crunch leaves many without immunizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/coronavirus/2021/02/second-shot-crunch-leaves-many-without-complete-covid-19-immunizations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As President Joe Biden accelerates purchases and distribution in an effort to get protection for almost all Americans by the end of the summer, critical weaknesses in the system are starting to show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon thought Donald had dementia?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2373046/bannon-trump-dementia-plot-oust-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STEVE Bannon secretly plotted to remove Donald Trump from office claiming he had dementia – and believed HE could personally succeed him as president, a bombshell new book claims. In a memoir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rained debris at least a mile wide!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/United-flight-returns-to-airport-after-engine-15966746.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kieran Cain was at the playground with his two children when he heard what sounded like...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drama on flight from Denver to Honolulu...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/local/airplane-parts-fall-broomfield/73-298bbbf8-637a-42a5-8bd0-5ca9b03c0f19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been no injuries, but parts have fallen in at least three locations, Broomfield Police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach Covid Compliance Team Investigating DeSantis Event For Maskless Crowd...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/02/19/palm-beach-covid-compliance-team-investigating-desantis-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach County's COVID Compliance Team is investigating an event Governor Ron DeSantis held at a West Palm Beach hotel Friday morning for violating the county's masking and social distancing rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loud Explosion...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/02/20/united-airlines-flight-328-passenger-plane-shuddering-explosion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Vena was traveling to Hawaii for a getaway when the unthinkable happened. The engine on his plane apparently failed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effort gets 1.1 million signatures...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Newsom-recall-effort-moves-closer-toward-making-15965131.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Almost 1.1 million signatures have been submitted in support of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA ramping up: To hire 6,000 new airport screeners...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/tsa-hiring-summer-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration is working to hire more than 6,000 airport security screening officers ahead of the traditionally busy summer travel season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds OK'd Export of Millions of Masks as U.S. Workers Cried for More...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/feds-okd-export-of-millions-of-n95-masks-as-u-s-workers-cried-for-more/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the hours before President Joe Biden was inaugurated, the Federal Emergency Management Agency allowed a Texas mask maker to ship the high-quality masks overseas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM GOVS SEE STARS DIMMED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-new-york-andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-pandemic-california-8351591b02e965a250f8b04139f7f37d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — At the outset of the coronavirus pandemic, two Democratic governors on opposite ends of the country were hailed as heroes for their leadership in a crisis. Now they're leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS THAWS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-austin-power-outages-tennessee-weather-e79196af45d3af529eda1af8f8293db7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Warmer temperatures spread across the southern United States on Saturday, bringing some relief to a winter weary region that faces a challenging clean-up and expensive repairs from...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
