<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed in Rhode Island...</title>
      <link>https://www.providencejournal.com/news/20200301/first-positive-coronavirus-case-confirmed-in-ri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rhode Island Department of Health has announced the state’s first "presumptive positive" case of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New case in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hhs-sec-azar-says-new-coronavirus-case-appears-in-chicago</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Alex Azar said on Sunday that a new case of the coronavirus appeared in Chicago overnight, marking the latest spread of the outbreak in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE:  More Deaths Coming...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/videos/politics/2020/02/29/mike-pence-coronavirus-sotu-tapper-vpx.cnn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence said there could be more deaths in the US from coronavirus, despite the fact most Americans face a low risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election officials scrambling to address...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-officials-scrambling-address-coronavirus-concerns-ahead-super/story?id=69255531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerns have sprouted for election officials, as a potential coronavirus outbreak in the United States could influence how votes are cast on Super Tuesday and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Australian to die...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/health/health-problems/australias-first-coronavirus-fatality-as-man-dies-in-perth/news-story/d3a2e6dfdcb81eb1da7181100aa87b39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first person to die from the coronavirus in Australia has been named as James Kwan, a retired travel agent from Perth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcgis.com/apps/opsdashboard/index.html#/bda7594740fd40299423467b48e9ecf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcgis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears close down France's Louvre Museum...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/29cc5b26f3620a2bbd6c8444f4f12e42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The spreading coronavirus epidemic shut down France's Louvre Museum on Sunday, with workers who guard its trove of artworks fearful of being contaminated by the museum's flow of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to free 5,000 Taliban fighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/1/us-free-5000-taliban-fighters-lift-sanctions-leade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. will free up to 5,000 Taliban prisoners and begin to remove economic sanctions on top Taliban leaders under the terms of a deal signed Saturday between the two sides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hand Sanitizer Hard to Find...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/where-do-i-find-your-hand-sanitizer-sorry-we-have-none/ar-BB10ywvD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthews absent from MSNBC after sexism allegations, on-air slip-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/chris-matthews-absent-from-msnbcs-primary-coverage-after-sexism-allegations-on-air-slip-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC’s Chris Matthews was noticebaly absent from the network’s South Carolina primary coverage Saturday evening, one day after being accused of “sexist” behavior by a former network contributor -- and then later misidentifying a politician while on the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coughing pope cancels retreat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c857823e5212f4da2bf6ed3b451ba3c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — A coughing Pope Francis told pilgrims gathered for the traditional Sunday blessing that he is canceling his participation at a week-long spiritual retreat in the Roman...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to remove iconic payphones off streets...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/york-city-set-remove-iconic-payphones-off-streets/story?id=69318328</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City is reportedly planning to remove all of the last remaining public payphones from the city’s streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coughing pope cancels Lenten retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattlepi.com/news/world/article/Coughing-pope-cancels-participating-in-Lenten-15096422.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattlepi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) - A coughing Pope Francis told pilgrims gathered for the traditional Sunday blessing that he is canceling his participation at a week-long spiritual retreat in the Roman countryside because of a cold.  It is the first time in his seven-year papacy that he has missed the spiritual exercises that he initiated early in his pontificate to mark the start of each Lenten season. Such retreats are typical Jesuits, an order to which he belongs.  The 83-year-old pontiff, who lost part of a lung to a respiratory illness as a young man, has canceled several official engagements this week as he battled an apparent cold.  His weekly appearance Sunday to pilgrims from a window high above St. Peter's Square was the first time he has been seen publicly since Ash Wednesday, when he was seen coughing and blowing his nose during Mass.  Francis paused twice to cough Sunday while addressing the faithful. At the end, he asked for prayers for the spiritual retreat, adding "unfortunately a cold prevents me from participating this year. I will be following the meditation from here."  Earlier this week, the pope canceled two planned official audiences - formal affairs in the Apostolic Palace where Francis would have delivered a speech and greeted a great number of people at the end. Those were to include an audience with an international bioethics organization and with members of the scandal-marred Legion of Christ religious order.  Francis has never previously canceled so many official audiences or events in his papacy. He was, however, continuing to work from his residence at the Vatican's Santa Marta hotel and was receiving people in private, the Vatican press office said. On Saturday, those private meetings were with the head of the Vatican's bishops' office, Francis'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases jump to 71...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/01/us-coronavirus-cases-jumps-to-71-west-coast-is-hardest-hit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of coronavirus cases in the US stood at 71 early Sunday, according to the Center for Disease Control officials. The majority of those cases — 44 — were patients who caught th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie raises impressive $46.5M in February...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/53069b074d706a7d7228cf4ec6fb0311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. (AP) — Bernie Sanders' presidential campaign said it raised more than $46.5 million in February, a show of financial strength announced Sunday, after the Vermont senator...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon General: 'STOP BUYING MASKS!'</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/surgeon-general-urges-the-public-to-stop-buying-face-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surgeon general on Saturday urged the public to stop buying masks, warning that it won’t help against the spread of the novel coronavirus but will take away important resources from health care professionals. “Seriously people — STOP BUYING MASKS!”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's crowdless sport: Prelude to virus-hit Olympics?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health-japan-sports-idUSKBN20O1ED</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A line of masked spectators raises muffled cheers for elite marathon runners, an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA TO ENDORSE?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/29/o-how-obama-could-alter-2020-presidential-race-for-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two days after the South Carolina primary in 2008, Ted and Caroline Kennedy endorsed Barack Obama after he beat Hillary Clinton there by 30 points. Obama spokesman Robert Gibbs said on Saturday tha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVIGORATED BY VICTORY!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/biden-wins-in-south-carolina-adding-new-life-to-his-candidacy/ar-BB10zCu5?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What did Jeffrey Epstein own? Here's a list, including islands, cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/investigations/article240750631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is El Salvador's millennial president a reformer or an autocrat?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/is-el-salvador-s-millennial-president-a-reformer-or-an/article_d2565548-82a0-5e0e-acf7-fd3d0bad98ba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador — The media in El Salvador quickly dubbed it “9F.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Scarlet letter statute': LA's adult performers strike back against state registry bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/entertainment/entertainmenttoday/s-2332893?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES -- Adult film actress Riley Reyes was preparing for a "particularly physical" scene last week when she received word of a proposed state measure that would impose strict new rules on her industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BIG IN SC</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9872b58b495fd17044f359338ab3f2a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — Joe Biden scored a thundering victory in South Carolina’s Democratic primary on Saturday, riding a wave of African American support and ending progressive rival Bernie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside White House's frantic attempts to minimize crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Inside-Trump-s-frantic-attempts-to-minimize-the-15095593.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Minutes before President Donald Trump was preparing Wednesday to reassure a skittish nation about the coronavirus threat, he received a piece of crucial information: The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention had identified in California the first U.S. case of the illness not tied to foreign travel, a sign that the virus' spread in the United States was likely to explode.  But when Trump took to the lectern for a news conference intended to bring transparency to the spiraling global crisis, he made no explicit mention of the California case and its implications - and falsely suggested the virus might soon be eradicated in the United States.  "And again, when you have 15 people - and the 15 within a couple of days is going to be down to close to zero - that's a pretty good job we've done," he said.  Trump's playing down of the California patient at his news conference underscores the administration's slapdash and often misleading attempts to contain not just the virus, but also potential political damage from the outbreak - which has tanked financial markets, slowed global commerce and killed some 3,000 people worldwide, including the first U.S. death, announced Saturday.  Since Trump touched down from a two-day trip to India early Wednesday morning, the administration struggled to cope with the fallout from the crisis - shaking up and centralizing its coronavirus response team under the leadership of Vice President Mike Pence, floating plans to stabilize the markets and publicly seeking to minimize the threat posed by the potential pandemic.  Interviews with nearly two dozen administration officials, former White House aides, public health experts and lawmakers - many speaking on the condition of anonymity to share candid assessments and details - portray a White House scrambling to gain control of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST COAST ON ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Virus-reported-in-wider-region-of-the-West-Coast-15095236.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California reported its second case of community transmission of the coronavirus Friday, and Oregon and Washington announced others just hours later, providing fresh evidence that the deadly virus is circulating in the United States.  Authorities in Santa Clara County, Calif., said a 65-year-old woman had come down with the covid-19 disease without traveling to any countries hit hard by the outbreak or coming in contact with anyone known to have the infection.  In Oregon, officials said a person from Washington County, in the northwest part of the state, had tested positive under similar circumstances. The positive test was conducted by the state's laboratory and is considered "presumptive" until it is confirmed by the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.  In Oregon, officials said a person from Washington County, in the northwest part of the state, had tested positive under similar circumstances. The positive test was conducted by the state's laboratory and is considered "presumptive" until it is confirmed by the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.  The unnamed Oregon individual is an employee of Forest Hills Elementary School outside Portland but has a job that "does not typically come into contact with students," the Lake Oswego School District wrote to parents in an email obtained by local news. The "few individuals" who did have close contact with the infected person were asked to stay home from work or school for two weeks.  The school will remain close through Wednesday as it is cleaned, the district told parents.  In Washington, state health officials said a high school student in Snohomish County, just north of Seattle, received a "presumptive" positive test in another case of unknown origin.  The Jackson High School student was not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Urged to Stop Cheek-to-Cheek Kisses...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/fight-coronavirus-france-urges-no-more-greetings-kisses-bans-large-n1145906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French health minister said he is recommending people cut back on "la bise," the custom of giving greetings with kisses, or air kisses, on the cheeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans canceling domestic travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/americans-are-canceling-their-domestic-travel-over-coronavirus-fears/ar-BB10xnbr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANDERS STALLS?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/joe-biden-looks-past-expected-south-carolina-win-to-super-tuesday/ar-BB10zvhl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.instagram.com/p/B9KWKfZg0Sg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.instagram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1,762 Likes, 909 Comments - Los Angeles Times en Español (@latimesespanol) on Instagram: “Empieza el show de #Oprah en L.A. con una inesperada caída que, sin embargo, no interrumpió la…”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street preps for possible shutdown of trading floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyse-could-close-trading-floor-in-coronavirus-contingency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Business reported that the NYSE is exploring a contingency that would including closing the trading floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPRAH TAKES HARD FALL DURING SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/02/29/oprah-takes-a-tumble-onstage-during-2020-vision-tour/?_ga=2.209183826.1364536535.1582908664-640973686.1582908664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After gathering herself on the floor, she called out “wrong shoes!” into the microphone, letting fans know exactly what caused the unexpected crash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEATH IN WASHINGTON STATE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/29/trump-misidentifies-first-us-coronavirus-fatality-calling-man-a-wonderful-woman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump misidentified the nation’s first coronavirus fatality as a “wonderful woman” on Saturday — the victim, in fact, was a man who died in a Seattle-area hospital…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China officials knew of coronavirus, ordered cover-up...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/29/china-officials-knew-of-coronavirus-in-december-ordered-cover-up-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese scientists knew about the coronavirus and its deadly effects as early as December — but were ordered by government officials to suppress the evidence, according to a report. In late D…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Psychosis' in Milan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sick-italys-virus-shutdown-milan-itches-back-204904436.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deserted cafes and restaurants. Milan, Italy's usually bustling economic and fashion capital, has been twiddling its thumbs since Monday, paralysed by a virus that has killed 29 and infected more than 1,000 people in Italy since breaking out just 60 kilometre (37 miles) south of the city a week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear at nursing facility; 50 sick...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f175d89567a26d59cab27725c9e8a0d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor of Washington declared a state of emergency Saturday after a man died there of COVID-19, the first such reported death in the United States. More than 50 people in a nursing facility...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  DON'T PANIC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ad97746163f019c576837838f8a6d267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Seeking to reassure the American public, President Donald Trump said Saturday there was "no reason to panic" as the new coronavirus claimed its first victim inside the U.S. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty streets, economic turmoil as virus alters daily life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00d9680372ff4945449f670c10a88fe9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The coronavirus claimed its first victim in the U.S. Saturday as the number of cases shot up in Iran, Italy and South Korea and the spreading outbreak continued to shake the global...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELEGATE COUNT</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-primary-elections/delegate-count</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/live-blog/south-carolina-primary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest updates and results from the 2020 South Carolina primary on Saturday, Feb. 29.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WINS SC</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2aeccf2e45dc8a0b955ceba9531efbe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — The Latest on the Democratic presidential primary contest (all times local): 7:10 p.m. Former Vice President Joe Biden is thanking South Carolina voters after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump considering travel restrictions at southern border...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/29/trump-considering-travel-restrictions-at-us-southern-border-over-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT'S ALREADY OUT OF THE BAG'</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-02-29/coronavirus-california-spread-health-officials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person who was not among the previously reported coronavirus cases in the U.S. has died of COVID-19, say Washington health officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Prototype Spacecraft Blows Up During Testing In Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.geekwire.com/2020/spacexs-starship-sn1-prototype-blows-pressure-test-texas-pad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geekwire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 100-foot-tall prototype for SpaceX’s Starship super-rocket was destroyed tonight during a cryogenic pressure test on its pad at the company’s South Texas facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LIVE</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?469892-1/president-trump-holds-news-conference-coronavirus&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump holds a news conference to provide an update on the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local spread of coronavirus marks turning point in USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200229163324-v735v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/USA (PIX, GRAPHICS):Local spread of coronavirus marks turning point in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2020/2/29/21157885/south-carolina-primary-live-results-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is critical for former Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious glowing object suddenly appears in Earth's orbit leaving scientists baffled...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/11069093/mysterious-glowing-object-appears-in-earths-orbit-scientists-baffled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS glowing object which suddenly appeared in the Earth’s orbit has left scientists baffled. Images of the puzzling object have been released after some speculated it appeared to be …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty stadiums and no more selfie lines? Coronavirus becomes 2020 X-factor...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/29/coronavirus-threatens-to-disrupt-2020-campaign-118238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the virus does spread, the mechanical implications for campaigns could be profound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic scenes on beach as walkers stumble across pig heads on spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dublinlive.ie/news/dublin-news/satanic-like-scenes-portmarnock-beach-17833423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dublinlive.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One walker even rang gardai out of concern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/south-carolina-primary-results-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Carolinians head to the polls today to vote in the Democratic primary. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna left in tears, struggling to walk after fall during Paris concert...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/02/29/madonna-left-in-tears-struggling-to-walk-after-fall-during-paris-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna took a hard fall during her Thursday night Madame X show in Paris, leaving the singer in tears as she struggled to walk off stage after the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Republican mega-donor buys stake in TWITTER and seeks to oust Dorsey...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/feb/29/paul-singer-elliott-management-twitter-jack-dorsey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Paul Singer’s Elliott Management has taken a ‘sizable state’ and intends to ‘push for changes’, reports Bloomberg News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Marine becomes first woman to lead Howitzer team...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/california-marine-becomes-first-woman-to-lead-howitzer-team/article_300e2327-0bb6-56ef-ae4a-09f47e943fc1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMP PENDLETON, Calif. — A Marine stationed at Camp Pendleton became the first woman to graduate from the Corps’ Howitzer Section Chief Course this month, taking on a combat artillery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney receives standing ovation in Denver for impeachment vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2020/02/28/mitt-romney-impeachment-denver-jason-crow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP senator, weeks after historic vote, talks democracy at DU</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu, Gantz neck and neck as campaign reaches climax...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-gantz-neck-neck-campaign-reaches-climax-154111486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and rival Benny Gantz were wrapping up another bitter election campaign on Saturday as voters prepared to cast their ballots for the third time in 12 months. Netanyahu, Israel's longest-serving leader, has been charged on several counts of corruption but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders look-alike enjoying the ride...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-sanders-look-alike-enjoying-ride-040809634.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up until a few years ago, Jeff Jones was going about his life, minding his own business and enjoying his passion for music. Then Bernie Sanders burst onto the national political stage, prompting many to do double takes on seeing Jones, who bears a striking resemblance to the Democratic presidential</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
