<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>White House Knew of Whistleblower Allegations Soon After Trump Call With Ukraine Leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-knew-of-whistle-blowers-allegations-soon-after-trumps-call-with-ukraine-leader/ar-AAHToDz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani engaged parade of Ukrainian prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Giuliani-engaged-parade-of-Ukrainian-prosecutors-14471702.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rudy Giuliani spent months cultivating current and former prosecutors in Ukraine with a particular goal: Help President Donald Trump in next year's election by ensuring that Ukrainian authorities pursued allegations that could damage his Democratic rivals.  But the effort hit a snag. A political neophyte and comedian named Volodymyr Zelensky - who had once played a Ukrainian president on television in a sitcom - swooped in last spring and became the president of Ukraine for real. Some of Giuliani's efforts were thrown in doubt. One of the prosecutors Giuliani initially saw as an ally made public comments undermining his claims against former vice president Joe Biden. How Zelensky would act was unknown.  "New Pres of Ukraine still silent on investigation of Ukrainian interference in 2016 election and alleged Biden bribery of Pres Poroshenko," Giuliani tweeted on June 21, without evidence of the allegations, referring to the former president, Petro Poroshenko, whom Zelensky defeated. "Time for leadership and investigate both if you want to purge how Ukraine was abused by Hillary and Obama people."  The frustration helps explain why Trump, ahead of a July 25 phone call that is now the subject of a whistleblower complaint and a congressional impeachment inquiry, turned up the heat.  Amid uncertainty about Zelensky's willingness to work with Giuliani, Trump suspended military aid to Ukraine on July 18. Days later, Zelensky's party swept Ukraine's parliamentary elections, ushering in a wave of political newcomers and upping the uncertainty about whether Giuliani's efforts would come undone.  In the meantime, Trump had been withholding a date for a coveted bilateral summit with Zelensky. A call with the comedian was on the books - a chance for Trump to make his desires clear.  "I would like you to do us a favor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part of broader secrecy effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/effort-to-shield-trumps-call-with-ukrainian-leader-was-part-of-broader-secrecy-effort/ar-AAHUnST</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only the ballot box can deliver a final verdict!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/463164-only-the-ballot-box-can-deliver-a-final-verdict-on-president-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The history of impeachment can inform us but the ultimate decision remains with the voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Attacks Whistleblower's Sources, Alludes to Punishment for Spies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-branding-whistle-blower-spy-230248704.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump appeared to threaten a government whistle-blower who is protected under federal law, adding to the list of accusations that could fuel the impeachment inquiry in Congress.Trump said the unidentified whistle-blower had no direct knowledge of the president’s actions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson allies warn UK faces riots if Brexit fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10015632/boris-johnsons-britain-faces-la-riots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson’s allies have warned Britain faces LA-style riots if Brexit is reversed. A senior cabinet minister last night said the country risked a “violent, popular uprising” i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURN:  2 Republican governors support impeachment....</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Two-Republican-governors-say-they-support-14471605.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, two Republican governors have publicly supported the impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump, a new development in an intensifying political fracas that has so far been largely partisan.  Vermont Gov. Phil Scott and Massachusetts Gov. Charlie Baker, both outspoken critics of Trump, said Thursday that they favored the investigation, but Scott added that he would wait for more information before calling for further action against the president.  In a statement to The Washington Post, Scott called the inquiry "appropriate" and said it is a key part of Congress's duty as a co-equal branch of government.  "I think we have much more to learn and need to understand all the facts as this serious allegation is considered," he said. "Congress has a solemn responsibility to every American to fulfill its role in our government system of checks and balances."  But impeachment, he cautioned, "is a very serious issue and should not be taken lightly or abused."  At a Thursday event, Baker told reporters that, "It's a deeply disturbing situation and circumstance and I think the proper role and responsibility for Congress at this point is to investigate it and get to the bottom of it."  As governors, however, Scott and Baker have no role in the formal process, so their break from the Republican ranks is largely symbolic.  So far, two Senate Republicans have publicly expressed serious concern over revelations that Trump repeatedly urged the Ukrainian president to investigate former vice president Joe Biden, one of his foremost political rivals.  "There's obviously a lot that's very troubling there," said Sen. Ben Sasse, R-Neb., on Wednesday, adding that Democrats should still be careful when using the word "impeach."  Sasse opposed Trump's 2016 candidacy, but he has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCORCHED EARTH DEFENSE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-writes-the-gop-impeachment-playbook-scorched-earth-but-will-it-work/ar-AAHTPr2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America filled with anger and animosity digs in...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/impeach-trump-an-america-filled-with-anger-and-animosity-digs-in/ar-AAHTDK9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Pence-again-in-spotlight-despite-attempts-to-14471582.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As President Donald Trump fumed Thursday about a whistleblower complaint that accused him of abusing his power and endangering national security, Vice President Mike Pence was in his home state, sticking to the script.  "I came to Indiana to say it's time for Congress to pass the U.S.-Mexico-Canada Agreement, and pass it this year," Pence said at an Indianapolis machinery plant, where he touted a trade deal that has been put on the congressional back burner amid an impeachment inquiry into alleged misconduct by Trump.  Even as Pence distanced himself from the impeachment saga playing out in Washington, his penchant for sidestepping the Trump administration's most controversial episodes is perhaps facing its greatest test thus far. Congress is preparing to mount an aggressive probe into allegations that Trump pressured Ukraine to interfere in the 2020 elections and that the White House sought to cover it up - and Pence's dealings with Ukraine have already become part of the focus.  Pence did not participate in a controversial July 25 phone call in which Trump pushed Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky to investigate former vice president Joe Biden and his son, according to a senior administration official, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal deliberations.  But Pence's name has emerged in several other contexts - including as a potential successor should Trump be ousted from office - since Democrats announced this week that they were launching a formal impeachment inquiry.  The whistleblower complaint, released Thursday, said Pence canceled a planned trip to Ukraine at the direction of Trump, who was seeking to pressure the Ukrainians to help him politically.  Three people familiar with the matter confirmed that Pence's attendance had been requested at Zelensky's inauguration and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST WING 'SHELL-SHOCKED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/total-panic-shell-shocked-white-house-struggles-find-impeachment-footing-n1059251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many in the Trump White House are battle-tested from the Mueller investigation, this is starting to feel different, aides and advisers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House officials acted to 'lock down' record of call...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/whistleblower-complaint-reveals-witnesses-concern-over-handling-trump-ukraine-call-n1058941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official concluded that the president was "using the power of his office to solicit interference from a foreign country."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower Is CIA Officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/whistle-blower-is-a-cia-officer-who-was-detailed-to-the-white-house/ar-AAHToDz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Attacks Whistleblower's Sources; Punishment for Spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-attacks-whistle-blowers-sources-and-alludes-to-punishment-for-spies/ar-AAHTvMV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORED ON SEPARATE COMPUTER NETWORK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/26/biggest-bombshells-in-trump-whistleblower-complaint-cover-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whistleblower says senior White House officials intervened to "lock down" records of the call with Zelensky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are great white sharks swimming so close to beaches?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/why-are-sharks-swimming-so-close-to-north-atlantic-beaches-60-minutes-2019-09-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More sharks are showing up near coastlines in the North Atlantic Ocean. "60 Minutes" reports on what's bringing them there, Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA deploys air defense systems, troops to Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.baynews9.com/fl/tampa/ap-top-news/2019/09/26/us-deploys-air-defense-systems-troops-to-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baynews9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon says it will send one Patriot missile battery and four radar systems to Saudi Arabia, in what officials describe as the first steps to help the kingdom protect itself against Iranian attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATORS FRET TRUMP TRIAL</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/463113-senators-fret-over-prospect-of-trump-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launching of a House impeachment inquiry against President Trump is raising the prospect of a Senate trial — unnerving senators already anxious about an election-year battle where the Senate majority could be up for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' producer defends movie for holding 'mirror to our society'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/26/joker-producer-defends-movie-for-holding-mirror-to-our-society/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The executive producer of “Joker” has defended the movie over fears it may incite mass shooters — insisting people cannot “run” from the ugliest sides of society. “Loo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems accuse him of witness intimidation!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2f662aa7aa64030bed2dd496dfc3b0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on testimony by the acting director of national intelligence and a whistleblower complaint (all times local): 7 p.m. House Democrats are condemning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 2020 rivals avoid rush to defend him...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/68f19fffdbdf4638ab94117b83f5c8f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidates are united in condemning President Donald Trump for seeking a foreign country's help to trash a domestic political rival. But when it comes to defending the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman put meth in bean dip served to co-workers...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/bean-dip-meth-508216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 26--An Oregon felon allegedly placed methamphetamine into bean dip that she served to co-workers at a Thriftway supermarket, according to cops who arrested the woman on multiple criminal cou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First let me take a selfie, El Salvador's president tells UN...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-let-selfie-el-salvadors-president-tells-un-211735780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Salvador's President Nayib Bukele, whose social media savvy helped win him power earlier this year, took a selfie before his maiden speech at the UN General Assembly, which he called "obsolete" and suggested scrapping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots could be headed to circus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/business/technology/article/Robots-made-famous-on-YouTube-could-be-headed-to-14471022.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) - Animal-like robots that started out as a military-funded research project might be shipped off to the circus instead of the battlefield.  Cirque du Soleil says it's in talks with robot maker Boston Dynamics about using the four-legged Spot robot in its live shows.  The agile robots walk, gallop and jump. They have become famous on YouTube but haven't been applied commercially since the company was founded in 1992.  That's changing this fall. The Waltham, Massachusetts, robotics firm revealed in a YouTube post this week that Spot is now in mass production and shipping to select customers for such uses as monitoring construction sites or inspecting energy facilities.  Cirque du Soleil says it's still in the "ideation" stage and evaluating Spot's potential in live entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas signs ex-MICROSOFT lawyer, others to aid in GOOGLE antitrust probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tech-antitrust-google-exclusive/exclusive-texas-signs-ex-microsoft-lawyer-others-to-aid-in-google-antitrust-probe-idUSKBN1WB14N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas attorney general's office has hired three consultants for a multi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Rouhani backs moving UN out of NYC to 'better' country...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/irans-rouhani-backs-moving-un-out-of-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani said Thursday that his country's delegation would vote for the United Nations headquarters to be moved out of New York if given the chance, in the latest sign of escalating tensions with the United States on the sidelines of the U.N. General Assembly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Republican governor comes out in support...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republican-vermont-governor-impeachment-inquiry-92b9ff2d-f64e-4913-832e-ea066efb08f1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His position is a departure from the party norm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owners seek expansion to 17-game NFL seasons...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/owners-seek-expansion-17-game-nfl-seasons-reports-191611325--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL owners are pushing to expand the regular season from 16 to 17 games, while reducing the number of pre-season contests, in talks with the players union, according to multiple reports Thursday. ESPN and The Athletic websites, citing unnamed sources, said team owners were making the pitch after NFL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Phones, Computers Creating Generation Of Porn Addicts...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/smart-phones-computers-generation-porn-addicts-public-health-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studies show children are typically first exposed to pornography at age 13.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Tlaib Leads Crowd In Profanity-Laced Chant...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/09/26/rashida-tlaib-leads-profanity-laced-impeachment-chant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan Democratic Rep. Rashida Tlaib on Thursday copied her viral video from earlier this year where she called President Trump a &amp;quot;motherf****r.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTING DNI TESTIFIES</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/09/26/whistleblower-complaint-top-moments-joseph-maguire-testimony/3774069002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph Maguire, the acting director of national intelligence, faced scrutiny Wednesday from lawmakers investigating the whistleblower complaint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 part costing nearly $1B for nuke modernization...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/smr/nuclear-arsenal/2019/09/25/nuclear-warhead-programs-need-850m-fix-heres-how-the-government-plans-to-cover-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delays to the B61-12 and W88 Alt 370 could cost taxpayers a lot of money, but the National Nuclear Security Administration has a plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY: 'These morons -- when this is over, I will be the hero'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/09/giuliani-ukraine-trump-biden/598879/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s personal attorney unleashes in a new phone call with The Atlantic while Trump allies turn on him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA hits Cuba's Raul Castro, family with travel ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article235508202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters react with joy, fury, ambivalence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/-as-trump-impeachment-inquiry-looms-voters-react-with-joy-fury-ambivalence/ar-AAHSXYd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt blames homeless for water woes in California...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-govt-blames-homeless-water-woes-california-173732520.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration picked another fight with California Thursday, accusing the liberal state of being lax on water pollution and linking the problem in part to feces from homeless people. "Based on data and reports, the EPA is concerned that California's implementation of federal environmental</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'OK' hand gesture, 'Bowlcut' added to hate symbols database...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48ae1303568b4b21813adb3bd6d592e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLLEGE PARK, Md. (AP) — The "OK" hand gesture, a mass killer's bowl-style haircut and an anthropomorphic moon wearing sunglasses are among 36 new entries in a Jewish civil rights group's online...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTING DNI TESTIFIES</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?464509-1/acting-director-national-intelligence-maguire-testifies-whistleblower-complaint&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting Director of National Intelligence Joseph Maguire testifies before the House Intelligence Committee on the process &amp; handling of a whistleblower complaint involving President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Flight Diverted After Passenger Gets Stuck Inside Bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/09/26/locked-in-bathroom-diverted-flight-san-francisco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have all experienced airline delays, but Jennifer Gettman and her fellow passengers on United Airlines Flight 1554 have quite a doozy to tell after their flight to San Francisco was diverted because someone got locked in the plane's bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50,000 Apples Stolen From Orchard...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/50000-apples-stolen-from-northwest-indiana-orchard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty thousand apples were recently stolen from an apple orchard in Northwest Indiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli politics remain in chaos after deadlocked election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b9a16d777554487b66fef59fd2a5feb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Benjamin Netanyahu has been tasked by Israel's president to form a new government for the sixth time in his lengthy political career. This time it's no mere formality, but rather...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS SPEED IT UP</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-deflects-and-defies-as-Democrats-speed-up-14468600.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump struck a stance of defiance Wednesday, proclaiming his innocence and leveling distortions and falsehoods after the publicly released notes of his phone call with his Ukrainian counterpart turbocharged the push on Capitol Hill for his impeachment.  The five pages of a rough transcript of Trump's call asking Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky to work with Attorney General William Barr and personal attorney Rudy Giuliani to investigate Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden landed like a hand grenade on Capitol Hill and led House Democrats to recalibrate their strategy.  House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., and her fellow Democratic leaders agreed to speed up their impeachment investigation and significantly narrow it to Trump's dealings with Ukraine, according to five Democrats familiar with their discussions during a closed-door emergency meeting Wednesday in Pelosi's office.  Democratic leaders see the evidence from the Zelensky call as damning enough to impeach - and easy enough for the public to digest - in isolation, without drawing in allegations of obstruction of justice, self-dealing and other wrongdoing. Leaders began discussing a swift timeline to, in the words of one member, "strike while the iron's hot" and possibly vote on articles of impeachment before the end of the year.  "It's very understandable," said House Majority Leader Steny Hoyer, D-Md. "It's a betrayal of the presidency of the United States, which is now making deals to affect an election, to go after an opponent with a foreign leader who is relying on the United States."  Trump presented himself as an aggrieved victim of "viciousness" from Democrats and the media during a meandering and uncharacteristically muted news conference late Wednesday in New York. He defended his conduct in the July 25 call...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of House members now support impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/majority-house-members-now-back-some-type-impeachment-action-against-n1058596</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats reached the milestone following claims Trump might have withheld aid to Ukraine to pressure officials there to investigate Joe Biden and his son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWEETS DOZENS AND DOZENS AND DOZENS OF TIMES IN MORNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-has-done-38-retweets-and-counting-ahead-of-intelligence-officials-testimony/ar-AAHSWkf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKPLACES TURN TOXIC AS POLARIZATION INTENSIFIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-the-impeachment-inquiry-into-president-trump-and-a-brutal-2020-election-could-cost-american-companies-billions-2019-09-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Society for Human Resource Management’s CEO Johnny Taylor Jr. tells MarketWatch that companies should brace for a higher turnover in this heated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sgt. charged with manslaughter in Army cadet training death...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/army-staff-sergeant-charged-in-west-point-cadets-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staff sergeant is facing charges in a rollover accident that killed a U.S. Military Academy cadet during training exercises this summer, Army officials confirmed Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel general warns Iran situation reaching 'level of war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/israel-general-warns-approaching-level-20254197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brigadier General Dror Shalom said 'we are starting to approach the level of war' and its "only a matter of time"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump warns  stock market will crash if impeached...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/26/trump-warns-again-that-the-stock-market-would-crash-if-he-is-impeached.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Do you think it was luck that got us to the best Stock Market and Economy in our history. It wasn't," President Donald Trump tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: Border Wall Progress Remains Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/09/26/coulter-very-suspicious-we-cant-get-a-straight-answer-new-border-wall-construction-warns-of-2020-election-consequences/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The border wall remains a crucial concern for Republican voters, especially as it pertains the 2020 presidential election according to conservative commentator Ann Coulter. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unique and unprecedented'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/maguire-intelligence-committee-whistleblower-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting DNI says he didn’t forward a whistleblower complaint regarding Trump pressuring Ukraine because he needed clarification on executive privilege.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley goes to Vatican to talk tech ethics...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vatican-technology-ethics/silicon-valley-goes-to-the-vatican-to-talk-tech-ethics-idUSKBN1WB1RP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican brought together Silicon Valley heavyweights, Nobel laureates and cy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Civil War: How 'SNL' Firing Exposed Growing Rift in Stand-Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/shane-gillis-snl-firing-comics-mixed-reactions-exposes-growing-rift-stand-up-world-1242739</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many cheered Shane Gillis' NBC dismissal four days after he was hired, a slice of the community sneered, revealing an increasing divide over what's legitimate envelope-pushing and what’s "just plain racist."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Percentage of foreign-born U.S. residents highest in century...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-census-finds-22-1-100000352.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The percentage of foreign-born U.S. residents has reached its highest level in more than a century, according to estimates from the 2018 American Community Survey released today.A record 44.7 million people are foreign-born, or about 13.7% of the U.S. population. That’s the highest rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramedics Save Man Suffering Heart Attack -- After Shocking Him 34 Times!</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/man-shocked-34-times-after-heart-attack-tells-his-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio man who had to be shocked 34 times to stabilize his failing heart is now sharing his near-death experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khashoggi murder 'happened under my watch,' Saudi crown prince tells PBS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190926050919-u090r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-KHASHOGGI/:Khashoggi murder 'happened under my watch,' Saudi crown prince tells PBS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fjrzu37-ljI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon presents this exclusive trailer for Martin Scorsese's The Irishman, starring Robert De Niro, Al Pacino, and Joe Pesci....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year after Moonves ouster, CBS seeks new programming direction...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/entertainment/article/A-year-after-Les-Moonves-ouster-CBS-seeks-a-new-14469665.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - The veteran producer looked at the priest in disbelief.  "Look, I agreed to give you 20 minutes so (a colleague) doesn't drop a Me Too bomb on me," said the producer.  "So you think you're vulnerable to Me Too?" said the priest.  The producer shook his head. "There's a reason Weinstein went down. I don't use sex. And I'm much more talented."  Then the director yelled cut.  The moment was part of a shoot on the much-anticipated new CBS show "Evil" - the priest was part of a trio investigating a slick entertainment boss for fostering a toxic work culture.  If that last part sounds familiar, it should. "Evil" debuts on a network that spent much of last year dogged by sexual-misconduct allegations against former chief executive Leslie Moonves along with accusations of sexual harassment on multiple sets.  That a CBS primetime series is willing to tackle an incisively modern issue - this incisively modern issue - offers a telling snapshot of just how new a moment the network is looking to create.  CBS launches its fall schedule this week - Thursday's "Evil" premiere is one of a half-dozen new series on the network with blockbuster dreams. But amid the traditional rollout of broadcast hopefuls is one of the trickier balances in modern TV. CBS must advance a diverse and socially conscious post-Moonves form of storytelling without abandoning the middle-of-the-road formula he rode to great success.  "Our goal is to figure out the next generation of shows and make some unexpected moves while still appealing to the core CBS audience," said David Nevins, CBS' chief creative officer and Moonves' programming successor. "We can broaden and we can be more surprising, but without alienating people."  CBS has been the most-watched broadcast network every year for the past 11 - meaning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Franco 'ZEROVILLE' worst film of year?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/sep/26/james-franco-zeroville-review-worst-film-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor-writer-director’s adaptation of Steve Erickson’s 2007 book on 70s Hollywood is a film of staggering incompetence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters react with joy, fury, ambivalence...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-09-25/what-do-voters-think-of-the-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do voters around the country think of the impeachment inquiry into President Trump?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Outrage is a commodity': Director Todd Phillips bashes 'far left' criticism of 'JOKER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Outrage-is-a-commodity-Director-Todd-Phillips-14469623.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since debuting at the Venice International Film Festival earlier this month, "Joker," an R-rated supervillain origin story, has drawn both rave reviews and concerns over its realistic portrayal of a character sliding into a psychosis that leads him to kill.  The film's director, though, fiercely defended his film in a newly published interview, arguing that those worries are little more than the complaints of people looking for something to be angry about.  "I think it's because outrage is a commodity, I think it's something that has been a commodity for a while," director Todd Phillips told the Wrap in a Sept. 20 interview first published Wednesday. "What's outstanding to me in this discourse in this movie is how easily the far left can sound like the far right when it suits their agenda. It's really been eye-opening for me."  Though the film won the top prize in Venice and has been well reviewed before its Oct. 4 release in the United States, it has also stirred fears of gun violence and criticisms that the film glorifies the bloody action at the center of its plot. Some of that uproar has emerged after Phillips originally spoke to the Wrap.  This week, the families of those killed in a mass shooting at a Colorado movie theater in 2012 asked Warner Bros. to donate proceeds to groups supporting victims and urged Congress to pass bipartisan gun-control legislation. The theater in Aurora where the massacre took place during a screening of "The Dark Knight Rises" is refusing to show "Joker," a manager told The Washington Post.  On Sept. 18, a U.S. Army base in Oklahoma warned its service members that online threats had been made to target an unspecified theater during the "Joker" release, Christopher Grey, an Army Criminal Investigation Command spokesman, told The Post in a statement. A second memo sent Monday reiterated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first trans pro boxer face of iconic boxing brand EVERLAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/26/patricio-manuel-the-first-transgender-pro-boxer-represents-everlast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Dec. 12, 2018, Patricio Manuel made history, becoming the first transgender boxer to have a professional fight. On Sept. 26, he made history again when he was named the face of the iconic boxing brand Everlast. But the road to getting there wasn't easy, and Manuel had to risk everything he knew in order to achieve his dream of competing as a male boxer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPLAINT ALLEGES COVER-UP</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cce1f1146f924609912a032c61fd067c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A secret whistleblower complaint at the center of an impeachment inquiry alleges that President Donald Trump abused the power of his office to "solicit interference from a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: 13% trust media 'a great deal'...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/267047/americans-trust-mass-media-edges-down.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-one percent of Americans trust the mass media to report the news "fully, accurately and fairly," marking a four-percentage-point dip since last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO END IN SIGHT FOR 'RETAIL APOCALYPSE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/theres-no-end-in-sight-for-the-retail-apocalypse_09252019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers say Boris rhetoric stirs hate as rancor over Brexit intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Lawmakers-say-Johnson-s-rhetoric-stirs-hate-as-14469414.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON -A raw, noxious session of Parliament that left lawmakers expressing fears for their safety amid death threats has intensified Britain's national rancor over Brexit, while drawing from Prime Minister Boris Johnson a dismissive "humbug."  Johnson was rebuked by lawmakers on all sides for his language in a bombastic performance in the House of Commons on Wednesday night, when the prime minister used terms such as "betray" and "surrender" to describe opponents blocking his path for exiting the European Union.  Long-serving members, veteran journalists and British historians said they had never seen a more toxic session of Parliament than the one that unfolded after Johnson's return to the House of Commons, just a day after the Supreme Court ruled that the new prime minister's suspension of Parliament had been "unlawful."  After cutting short a trip to New York, where he attended the U.N. General Assembly and met with President Donald Trump, the prime minister delivered a statement to the House in which he apparently tried to goad opposition lawmakers into granting him an early election. Johnson called them "cowards." His opponents called him "unfit to serve" and shouted for his resignation.  But it wasn't just the jeering and sneering and clapping that prompted many observers to say it was one of the most extraordinary parliamentary sessions ever witnessed. It was Johnson's choice of words.  Several women lawmakers stood up in Parliament and pleaded with Johnson to moderate his language. Some pointed out the death threats they have received.  Opening Parliament on Thursday, Speaker John Bercow said that the atmosphere on Wednesday was "toxic" and "worse than any I have known in my 22 years in the House."  Bercow urged lawmakers to "treat each other as opponents, not as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second-quarter GDP left at 2%; Slower growth seen persisting...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/second-quarter-us-gdp-left-at-2-downshifting-economy-unlikely-to-rev-up-soon-2019-09-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy grew more slowly in the second quarter, updated figures confirm, and is slow growth is expected to persist through the end of the year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARPER: NATIONALS Fans Crossed Line Heckling Me In Loss...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/09/26/bryce-harper-nationals-fans-crossed-line-while-heckling-him-in-phillies-loss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harper spurned the Nationals and signed a 13-year deal with the Phillies last offseason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Prices In CA Expected To Soar Past $4 Following Saudi Refinery Attack...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/09/25/gas-saudi-refinery-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average price of gas in Los Angeles jumped three cents Wednesday to $3.85 per gallon and was expected to pass the $4 mark in the next few days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAYS OUT OTHER DOCUMENTS AND WITNESSES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4204c450b9542058f0d7764e982dcb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats who reviewed a secret whistleblower complaint involving President Donald Trump Wednesday called it "deeply disturbing" and said it gives them new leads to pursue as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV cure? Scientists discover 'kill switch'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10008045/hiv-cure-kill-switch-cells-reproducing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN HIV cure is a step closer after scientists found a molecular “kill switch” that stops infected cells reproducing. Lifelong drug treatment can prevent the virus leading to Aids — but it remains d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No drones, drinking or dissent: Beijing lays down law ahead of 70th anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/sep/26/no-drones-drinking-or-dissent-china-lays-down-law-ahead-of-70th-anniversary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Beijing prepares to mark founding of PRC with a massive military parade, the Chinese leadership faces its most difficult chapter since 1989</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to Face Dems... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spy-chief-face-democrats-disturbing-080000957.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The nation’s spy chief who delayed giving Congress a whistle-blower complaint about President Donald Trump will face tough questions from House Democrats on Thursday, an early glimpse of their newly intensified impeachment focus.Acting Director of National Intelligence Joseph Maguire will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap between haves and have-nots highest in 50 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bfa51032ee27470c9f908914328eea99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — The gap between the haves and have-nots in the United States grew last year to its highest level in more than 50 years of tracking income inequality, according to Census...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face masks to decoy t-shirts: The rise of anti-surveillance fashion...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190926043446-h9egt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artists and fashion designers are coming up with novel ways to stay private in public</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacques Chirac, giant of French politics, dies at 86...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/jacques-chirac-giant-french-politics-101635410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former French President Jacques Chirac, a major force in French politics who opposed the 2003 US-led invasion of Iraq, died in Paris on Thursday at the age of 86. A seasoned politician, Chirac’s career included two presidential terms, two stints as prime minister and nearly two decades as mayor of Paris.Charming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECLASSIFIED -- HOW LONG SECRET?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/463135-whistleblower-complaint-declassified-on-eve-of-high-stakes-maguire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whistleblower complaint at the center of the political firestorm involving President Trump's contacts with Ukraine's leader has been declassified, a member of the House Intelligence Committee announced late Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese 'IRISHMAN' Images De-Age De Niro -- And It's Weird...</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/irishman-movie-images-de-niro-de-aged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it only cost $159 million to do it!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
