<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The lives upended around $20 cheeseburger...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/dc-md-va/2020/07/07/le-diplomate-burger-beef-supply-chain-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cash-strapped rancher, a virus-stricken meatpacker, an underpaid chef, a hungry engineer: All their lives have been upended</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duckworth condemns Tucker for questioning patriotism: 'Walk mile in my legs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/walk-a-mile-in-my-legs-tammy-duckworth-condemns-tucker-carlson-for-questioning-her-patriotism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Tammy Duckworth criticized Fox News host Tucker Carlson for questioning her love for the United States after she said she would consider removing statues of George Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highest-ever security team monitoring Ghislaine every move in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1096649/ghislaine-maxwell-security-monitoring-epstein-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell’s every move will be monitored behind bars following the jail cell death of her former lover. The Brit socialite has been transferred to New York’s tough Metropolitan …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK hit with $150 million penalty for Epstein relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/jeffrey-epstein-case-deutsche-bank-fined-150-million-penalty-for-relationship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused child sex trafficker Jeffrey Epstein was a former friend of Presidents Donald Trump and Bill Clinton, as well as of Prince Andrew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Germany Fell Back in Love With Merkel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/07/how-germany-fell-back-in-love-with-angela-merkel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Angela Merkel of Germany is on her way out. After almost 15 years in office, the pandemic is likely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors say experimental treatment may have rid man of HIV...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/32171d5b5edb3babe25ba6edc4b505d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian man infected with the AIDS virus has shown no sign of it for more than a year since he stopped HIV medicines after an intense experimental drug therapy aimed at purging hidden, dormant...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Porn Star Accused of Sexual Abuse; 'Blood Everywhere'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ryan-madison-accused-of-sexual-abuse-by-10-women-there-was-blood-everywhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten women allege that the porn star violently abused them in the middle of shooting scenes—often after his wife lured them in with promises of a safe, female-fronted environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINCOLN PROJECT Mocks Raft of Leaks and Disloyalty: 'They Expect You to Lose'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/new-lincoln-project-ad-mocks-white-house-for-raft-of-anti-trump-leaks-and-disloyalty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lincoln Project went after President Donald Trump's paranoia on Tuesday by claiming "everyone" is disloyal to him, and that's the reason why his administration has so many leak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires risk turning nation into 'powder keg' as wealth surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-richest-billionaires-risk-turning-22288193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wealth of the top 1% has soared during lockdown, but the booming fortunes of tech billionaires like Facebook boss Mark Zuckerberg and Amazon's Jeff Bezos reveal deep faultlines in society</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot 'replicant' of real person; Unable to tell difference... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-replicant-pornhub-star-22312814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pornhub chart-topped Asa Akira has been pictured with a sex robot produced by RealDoll that was based on her. Amazed fans said they could barely tell the difference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN claims Trump broke international law with killing of Soleimani...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8495837/U-N-expert-deems-U-S-drone-strike-Irans-Soleimani-unlawful-killing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The January U.S. drone strike in Iraq that killed top Iranian general Qassem Soleimani and nine others represented a violation of international law, a U.N. human rights investigator said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KOREAN AIR!?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/07/among-companies-getting-millions-in-ppp-loans-korean-air.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Seoul-based airline has about 500 employees in the U.S. and says it is using most of the funds to pay staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt's boxed food aid promise falls short...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-food-aid-exclusive-idUSKBN248184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government delivered far less food aid than it had pledged by the end of June, according to food bank managers and data from the agriculture department sent to Reuters, after it hired inexperienced companies to box food during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations jump 50% in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-california/hospitalizations-jump-50-in-california-as-coronavirus-infections-soar-idUSKBN2472UL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New coronavirus cases soared in California over the July Fourth weekend, stressing some hospital systems and leading to the temporary closure of the state capitol building in Sacramento for deep cleaning, officials said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singles having kids with strangers in co-parenting trend...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/06/singles-are-having-kids-with-strangers-as-part-of-the-co-parenting-trend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No need for love and marriage — just the baby carriage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View mask refusers like drunk drivers: leading scientist...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/view-mask-refusers-drink-drivers-leading-scientist-084912790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who refuse to wear face masks during the coronavirus pandemic should be stigmatised the same as drink drivers, the head of the prestigious Royal Society science journal said Tuesday. The comments from Venki Ramakrishnan come as two new peer-reviewed studies showed how wearing face coverings may</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli sabotage? Mysterious damage to Iran nuke site...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mysterious-damage-iran-nuclear-know-100512867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious incident in the early hours of Thursday, July 2, badly damaged a building at Iran's Natanz nuclear complex and sparked speculation over the cause. The incident came at the end of a week marked by two explosions in Tehran, including one near a military site. Israel and the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil shocked by woman held as slave for years at family mansion...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200706195032-xuzb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former executive at Avon was found to have kept a domestic worker in slavery-like conditions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Focus Starts to Turn Toward Biden Victory...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/market-focus-starts-turn-toward-175908724.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A number of analysts are highlighting fresh investor interest in the implications of Joe Biden beating Donald Trump in November.Conversations with clients have begun to slowly shift toward what a Democratic sweep may mean, Compass Point’s managing director for policy research Isaac Boltansky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX dogged by claims of racism, sexual abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b32900c7a2e838dfe471f60daeea8f69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Last month, when former Major League All-star Torii Hunter said he’d been called the N-word “a hundred times” at Boston’s storied Fenway Park, the Red Sox were quick to back him up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How risky is dining out?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab7c92bcaa55ccbf4ff01b69daf0204e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How risky is dining out during the COVID-19 pandemic? There is some risk, but health officials say there are precautions you can take to minimize the chances you'll be exposed to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can United States pull itself together? Troubles cleave nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ff1254f0017af3aa02f0311bb2c67ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAGINAW, Mich. (AP) — It was difficult to celebrate America in Saginaw this year. The deadly coronavirus had torn through the county. Unemployment had surged five-fold. Weeks of protest over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black activist says he was victim of 'attempted lynching' by white group in incident partially caught on video...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/i-was-almost-the-victim-of-an-attempted-lynching-black-man-says-group-of-white-men-assaulted-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bloomington, Indiana civil rights activist says he was assaulted by a group of white men at a lake. Two people were hit by a car at a protest over the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Internet Fight Begins...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/07/hong-kong-security-law-sets-stage-for-global-internet-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Hong Kong grapples with a draconian new security law, the tiny territory is emerging as the front line in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferson's descendant wants memorial pulled down...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1095610/thomas-jeffersons-descendant-washington-dc-memorial-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DESCENDANT of Thomas Jefferson wants the Washington DC memorial to be removed because the Founding Father “owned more than 600 slaves”. In an opinion piece published in the New York T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music icon Charlie Daniels dead at 83...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/entertainment/music/2020/07/06/charlie-daniels-country-music-dies/5384087002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlie Daniels, a member of the Country Music Hall of Fame best known for "The Devil Went Down to Georgia," has died at age 83.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Bolsonaro Undergoing Test After Showing Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bolsonaro-undergoing-covid-19-test-after-showing-symptoms/ar-BB16pILd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrested Under New Law, Hong Kong Protesters Get Swabbed for DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/arrested-under-new-law-hong-kong-protesters-get-swabbed-for-dna/ar-BB16pF3E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States mandate masks, begin to shut down again, as coronavirus cases soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/states-mandate-masks-begin-to-shut-down-again-as-coronavirus-cases-soar-and-hospitalizations-rise/ar-BB16pmw8?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi's husband among lawmaker-linked recipients...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/06/nancy-pelosis-husband-among-lawmaker-linked-loan-recipients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A firm partially owned by House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s husband was among the lawmaker-linked businesses that got Paycheck Protection Program loans, according to data released Monday. Companies owne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governors' companies grabbed bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9544ec851527b8712ff63adf9180b47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Governors who ordered shutdowns as their states responded to the coronavirus pandemic were among millions of beneficiaries of the loan program created to help small...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Support Withering in Hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-support-withering-in-areas-where-virus-cases-are-rising/ar-BB16nPCi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Camp Sees 'Desperation' in Ever-Changing Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-camp-sees-desperation-in-trumps-ever-changing-attacks/ar-BB16nYnH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA: July 4 weekend air travel down 70%t compared to last year...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/506094-tsa-july-4-weekend-air-travel-down-70-percent-compared-to-last</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. air travel over the July Fourth weekend dropped significantly this year over last year as Americans remain wary of mass transit amid the ongoing coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom, coming under fire, ramps up enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-coming-under-fire-ramps-214430011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom vows to crack down on restaurants and bars that ignored restrictions over the July 4 weekend. Some critics say it is too little, too late.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE WEST'S CLOTHING LINE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8798e58a0ddc490ad549329b343e551c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The government's small business lending program has benefited millions of companies, with the goal of minimizing the number of layoffs Americans have suffered in the face of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music icon Charlie Daniels dead at 83...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1093709/country-star-charlie-daniels-dead-stroke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COUNTRY Hall of Fame star Charlie Daniels passed away Monday morning at the age of 83. His death was confirmed in a statement by his publicist Don Murry Grubbs, the Tennessean reported. Doctors det…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquor store employee scooped everyone with news...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/sports/spt-columns-blogs/for-petes-sake/article244030892.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small business bailouts went beyond hard-hit companies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2c79abd6acb08843b13f8a5be877b7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The government on Monday identified roughly 650,000 mostly small businesses and nonprofits that received taxpayer money through a federal program that was designed to soften job...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals approaching capacity as Miami closes restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edb298e959d070aea5851d3bd1d8ffbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Hospitals rapidly approached capacity across the Sunbelt, and the Miami area closed restaurants and gyms again because of the surging coronavirus Monday, as the U.S. emerged from a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Mayor infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e758a52a3e5a275549f1a4e426021a65</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Atlanta mayor Keisha Lance Bottoms announced Monday that she had tested positive for COVID-19. The 50-year-old Democrat is among the women named as a potential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Mayor infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/atlanta-mayor-keisha-lance-bottoms-tests-positive-for-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"COVID-19 has literally hit home," Bottoms said in a tweet. "I have had NO symptoms and have tested positive."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania's former right hand coming out with another tell all...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/07/stephanie-winston-wolkoff-book-melania</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melania’s former right hand will write, among other things, about her “abrupt and very public” departure from the East Wing after inauguration chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Capitol shutters after lawmaker tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/california-capitol-closes-after-l-a-lawmaker-tests-positive-for-covid-19/ar-BB16pl2Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West company...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8494965/U-S-Treasury-small-businesses-took-pandemic-aid-says-51-1-mln-jobs-supported.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Monday revealed how a firehose of $521.4 billion in taxpayer cash washed across the landscape of America's small businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent researcher of jihadi groups shot dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/06/middleeast/baghdad-iraq-hisham-al-hashimi-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prominent Iraqi expert on jihadi groups in the Middle East, including ISIS, was shot dead by unknown gunmen late Monday in front of his home in central Baghdad, media director of the Iraqi Ministry of Interior, Major General Saad Maan, told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign pupils must leave USA if classes go online...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/768c2bf5c9615a15a1397f4cd1c32500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International students will be forced to leave the U.S. or transfer to another college if their schools offer classes entirely online this fall, under new guidelines issued Monday by federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White woman charged after racist Central Park confrontation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/White-woman-charged-after-racist-Central-Park-15389218.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A white woman who called the police during a videotaped dispute with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's intel briefer breaks her silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/06/trump-intelligence-briefer-breaks-silence-349936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In rare public remarks, the veteran intelligence officer tip-toed around the complexities of her job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit council staffer killed in apparent murder-suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2020/07/06/deandree-watson-detroit-policy-staffer-apparent-murder-suicide/5384803002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeAndree Watson, 30, was found shot to death in his vehicle on Sunday in Westland, the victim of what police called a murder-suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors warn country in 'free fall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/06/health/us-coronavirus-monday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With rates of infection soaring in most states, "we can't really keep going at this rate," one doctor says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia gov to deploy 1,000 National Guard troops after bloody weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/kemp-deploy-000-national-guard-troops-after-violent-weekend/nuGXOOMNsj0zkkoO9GLNPL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Of Investment Advisors, Portfolio Managers Received Bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/here-are-thousands-investment-advisors-and-portfolio-managers-who-received-bailout-grants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-year commitment!</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29418825/sources-chiefs-patrick-mahomes-agree-10-year-extension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chiefs and quarterback Patrick Mahomes have reached agreement on a 10-year contract extension that ties him to Kansas City through the 2031 season, league sources tell ESPN's Adam Schefter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech start-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/ppp-loans-to-tech-start-ups-bird-mixpanel-grindr-on-the-list.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several tech start-ups were among the companies that received loans under a program intended to blunt the economic damage from Covid-19, according to a list released Monday by the Trump Administration. Bird, Mixpanel, Grindr and Zendrive were on the list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political orgs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/coronavirus-stimulus-list-of-ppp-small-business-loan-recipients-released.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Paycheck Protection Program was set up as part of the CARES Act relief law to help companies retain employees during coronavirus lockdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick, DISNEY announce partnership deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29417850/colin-kaepernick-disney-announce-partnership-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick will be featured in an exclusive docuseries produced by ESPN Films as part of a first-look deal with The Walt Disney Co. The deal between Kaepernick's production arm, Ra Vision Media, and Disney was announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit strip club linked to outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/wayne-county/2020/07/05/romulus-strip-club-linked-13-covid-19-cases/5381144002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virus cases of 12 patrons or staff at the Playhouse Club in Romulus and one Checkers employee have been linked to club, health department says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth management firms got bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/wealth-management-firms-have-taken-ppp-loans-amid-coronavirus-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many businesses, the government's PPP loans offered terms that were too good to pass up. That includes many wealth management firms across the country, according to government data. But whether those firms should have taken those loans is the subject of controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formula One drivers take knee, wear 'End Racism' shirts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/506038-formula-one-drivers-take-a-knee-wear-end-racism-shirts-at</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Formula One drivers wore shirts that said “End Racism” and took a knee ahead of Sunday's season-opening Austrian Grand Prix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids suffer mysterious brain damage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/06/some-kids-suffer-mysterious-brain-damage-from-coronavirus-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus may be causing scary neurological issues in some children. Youth may help beat the novel virus itself, but kids may be more vulnerable to a secondary, brain damage-causing ailment w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals reserve tickets to NH rally to make venue look empty...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/liberals-reserve-tickets-trumps-nh-rally-try-making-venue-look-empty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group Blue Revolution is sharing an RSVP link to Trump's rally in Portsmouth, N.H. Saturday on social media telling followers to reserve spots and not show up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Camp Vows to Protect Brazil Iconic Statue From Left Wing Mobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-camp-vows-to-protect-brazils-most-iconic-statue-from-left-wing-mobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new ad warns that the famous Christ the Redeemer statue in Rio de Janeiro is under threat. It’s unclear if this is even true or how the president would actually save it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 million gig workers getting unemployment, 41% of the total...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/pua-unemployment-benefits-being-paid-to-about-13-million-americans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are about 13 million people getting unemployment benefits through a program meant for previously ineligible groups of workers, and the share is rising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Announces Kaepernick Docuseries Deal...</title>
      <link>https://espnpressroom.com/us/press-releases/2020/07/the-walt-disney-company-announces-overall-first-look-deal-with-colin-kaepernick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;espnpressroom.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR 'TRUMP 2020' WRECK...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/07/06/corey-lajoie-nascar-trump-2020-brickyard-400-race-pit-road-wreck/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corey LaJoie's "Trump 2020" car barely made it out of the garage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. COVID DEATHS PASS 130,000... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2020/jul/06/coronavirus-live-news-india-sees-record-new-cases-as-texas-warns-of-overwhelmed-hospitals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s handling of US crisis under microscope; Israel reimposes restrictions after infections spike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters boycott WHOLE FOODS over BLM masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1093168/boycott-whole-foods-black-lives-matter-masks-massachusetts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROTESTERS are boycotting a Cambridge Whole Foods after workers wearing Black Lives Matter masks were sent home, reports say. People have picketed outside the Massachusetts store every day since Ju…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami restaurants, gyms closing AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article244024192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Noose' made of bread dough gets JIMMY JOHN'S workers fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/nation-world/national/article244022002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel blamed for explosion at Iran nuclear site...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/israel-blamed-for-explosion-at-iran-nuclear-site-report-634013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRGC member told the 'NYT' that the possibility a cyberattack was behind the incident at Natanz has been ruled out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Expert Offer Grim Outlook:  'We'll Be Living With Masks For Years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/living-with-masks-for-years-covid-19-through-the-eyes-of-a-pandemic-expert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the summer of 2019, I've been speaking with one of the world's leading pandemic experts about what a global outbreak could look like. Now, as the world enters a grim new phase, he says we're in a whole new ball game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick Signs First-Look Deal With DISNEY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/colin-kaepernick-walt-disney-first-look-deal-espn-1234698911/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick’s journey from San Francisco 49ers quarterback to civil-rights activist will be chronicled in a documentary series developed by ESPN Films as part of a first-look deal betwee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House hopes Americans will grow numb to toll...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/923821/white-house-reportedly-hoping-americans-grow-numb-covid19-death-toll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As new COVID-19 cases and deaths continue to rise in the United States, White House officials are reportedly crossing their fingers that Americans will simply get used to it. President Trump's advisers are looking to 'reframe' his coronavirus pandemic response, and they want to 'convince Americans that they can live with the virus,' with White House officials hoping 'Americans will grow numb to the escalating death toll and learn to accept tens of thousands of new cases a day,' The Washington Post reports. One senior administration official said Americans will have to 'live with the virus being a threat,' while a former official told the Post, 'They're of the belief that people will get over it or if we stop highlighting it, the base will move on and the public will learn to accept 50,000 to 100,000 new cases a day.' Dr. Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, recently said the U.S. could soon reach this shockingly high number of 100,000 new cases a day while also warning that the final death toll will be 'very disturbing.' The U.S. has reported almost 130,000 deaths from COVID-19 and has been setting records for the number of new cases per day. NBC News similarly reports the White House is preparing a new message on COVID-19 that the country must 'learn to live with it.' Trump has faced a declining approval rating during the pandemic, with Bloomberg reporting on Monday that support for Trump 'is slipping fastest in the 500 counties where the number of cases have been more than 28 coronavirus deaths per 100,000 people.' Meanwhile, the Post reports that presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden's campaign plans to keep attacking Trump for his COVID-19 response, arguing that, as one adviser put it to the Post, 'the country would be in a much different place today ... if Joe Biden had been the president in January.' Brendan Morrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President slams Bubba Wallace over 'hoax'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/77f320f49331e17ca4ddce5ee4b3bed0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — After a weekend spent stoking division, President Donald Trump on Monday blasted NASCAR for banning the Confederate flag and wrongly accused the sport's only Black driver, Bubba...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Struggles to Resume Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/as-pandemic-worsens-hollywood-struggles-to-salvage-reopening-plans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"For a big-budget studio film, COVID testing and safety could increase a budget by 15-20%," producer Shaun MacGillivray says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY'S BOOK NEXT WEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/publisher-of-mary-trumps-book-pulls-release-date-forward-to-july-14-after-extraordinary-interest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Due to high demand and extraordinary interest in this book” by Trump’s niece it will now be published on July 14, the publisher says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West Used His 'Presidential Announcement' as Lure to Sell Merchandise Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/06/kanye-west-used-his-presidential-announcement-as-a-lure-to-sell-merchandise-online-this-afternoon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West’s “presidential announcement” wasn’t followed up on Instagram with more information about his important campaign to make America great again. No, the next Instagr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SURVIVAL CONDO': Inside The Luxury Nuclear Bunker Protecting The Mega-Rich From Apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/features/inside-the-survival-condo-nuclear-bunker-protecting-the-ultrarich-hacking-the-apocalypse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A climbing wall, a waterslide, a gun range... preparing for nuclear war just got deluxe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Employees More Trouble Than Worth...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/coronavirus/employers-find-testing-employees-more-trouble-than-its-worth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From nursing homes in New York and a landfill in Utah to Disney World and the Las Vegas Strip, employers are wrestling with workplace safety in the age of Covid-19 and making fraught calculations about how to safeguard both their businesses and their employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If She Tells All, Will Fallout Be Too Much Even For U.S. Government?</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@dylanhoward/ghislaines-last-stand-if-epstein-s-accomplice-tells-all-will-the-fallout-be-too-much-even-for-u-s-8fc87089da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sensational arrest of Ghislaine Maxwell, alleged madam for sex fiend Jeffrey Epstein, is the end game in The Justice Department’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120 DAYS UNTIL VOTE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8513ec966d26d1c850e7cab0b269997c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Not long after noon on Feb. 6, President Donald Trump strode into the elegant East Room of the White House. The night before, his impeachment trial had ended with acquittal in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Anyone Watching QUIBI?</title>
      <link>https://www.vulture.com/2020/07/is-anyone-watching-quibi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vulture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming platform raised $1.75 billion and secured a roster of A-list talent, but it can’t get audiences to notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticking Time Bomb of HIV in Plagued South...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-ticking-time-bomb-of-hiv-in-covid-plagued-mississippi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dire situation in Mississippi—where disease surveillance for HIV has succumbed to coronavirus chaos—could send the larger region into a death spiral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How second half of 2020 could be even 'messier' than first...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-second-half-2020-pandemic-unemployment-election-20200706-nk6ji4s5x5buxozcj7ixwt7qea-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The year 2020 hasn't been great, but here's how the rest of it could shape up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump attacks Bubba Wallace...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8494303/Trump-launches-attack-Bubba-Wallace-demanding-NASCAR-star-apologize-noose-hoax.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump launched an attack on Bubba Wallace, demanding the only Black NASCAR driver apologize to those who supported him when it was reported a noose had been found in his garage stall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions believe allergic to modern life...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/04/millions-of-americans-believe-they-are-allergic-to-modern-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Welsh was a respiratory therapist living in Muskegon, Michigan, when, in the space of a few years, his life began to fall apart. It started when he developed an allergic reaction to certain f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: TRUMP APPROVAL 38%; RECORD PARTISAN GAP...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/313454/trump-job-approval-rating-steady-lower-level.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval rating remains lower than his earlier 2020 readings, with 38% currently approving of the job he is doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How LINCOLN PROJECT got into his head...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/how-lincoln-project-anti-trump-republicans-got-his-head-spoiler-n1232669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With clever ads and searing social media attacks, the group has drawn notice. But what that means for the election is up in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Crops Trump Out of Epstein, Maxwell Pic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-crops-trump-out-of-jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-photo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News appeared to scrub President Donald Trump out of a photograph with Jeffrey Epstein on Sunday during the network's coverage on the arrest of Ghislane Maxwell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Camp Sees 'Desperation' in Trump's Ever-Changing Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/biden-camp-sees-desperation-in-trump-s-ever-changing-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden Camp Sees â€˜Desperationâ€™ in Trumpâ€™s Ever-Changing Attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case for fewer laws...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/894138/case-fewer-laws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Americans regard America as 'a nation of laws.' But, more and more, the United States is becoming a nation of too many laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo drags British royal family into scandal once again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/04/ghislaine-maxwell-kevin-spacey-once-sat-on-buckingham-palace-thrones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a newly surfaced 2002 photo, the just-captured accused Jeffrey Epstein madam sits on Queen Elizabeth II’s throne during a private Buckingham Palace tour — with actor Kevin Spacey at her side.…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
