<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Did FBI go too far questioning Chinese researchers without reading them rights?</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/did-the-fbi-go-too-far-questioning-chinese-researchers-without-reading-them-their-rights/article_582dda8a-cbc1-52c3-83ba-2eca3458809e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — As federal prosecutors press forward with cases against Chinese researchers accused of lying about their ties to China's military to gain access to prestigious American universities, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euro 2020 match suspended after Danish star collapses on field...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/soccer/denmark-den/story/4406805/denmarks-christian-eriksen-collapsesreceives-cpr-as-euro-2020-game-with-finland-postponed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark's Euro 2020 Group B game with Finland was suspended just before half-time after Christian Eriksen collapsed on the field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 13 people wounded in Austin, Texas shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/12/us/austin-texas-shooting-downtown/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 13 people were injured early Saturday in a mass shooting in downtown Austin, Texas, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sighs of relief among world leaders even as divisions linger...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/12/politics/g7-leaders-biden-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Donald Trump used his elbows at international summits, it was to throw them -- on trade, on Russia and, once, to help remove the Montenegrin prime minister from his path to a photo-op.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner, once 'American hero,' struggles to win support from voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/caitlyn-jenner-once-an-american-hero-struggles-to-win-support-from-california-voters/article_4185fc38-65d2-5fcb-8dd4-5f3af2d626fb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Caitlyn Jenner's initial ascent into American social strata was astronomical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Private Equity Avoids Paying...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/12/private-inequity-how-a-powerful-industry-conquered-the-tax-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were two weeks left in the Trump administration when the Treasury Department handed down a set of rules governing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across West, drought arriving dangerously early...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210612-across-us-west-drought-arriving-dangerously-early</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across US West, drought arriving dangerously early</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN Auctions Seat on Bezos Rocket for $28 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/12/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-auctions-spaceflight-seat-for-28-million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The winning bidder will fly to the edge of space with the Amazon founder on Blue Origin's New Shepard rocket scheduled to launch on July 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road rage shootings kill or injure someone every 18 hours...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/automobiles/558141-road-rage-shootings-kill-or-injure-someone-every-18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person is killed or injured in a road rage shooting every 18 hours in 2021, an analysis done by Everytown for Gun Safety, a group that works to stop gun violence, found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept to probe secret subpoena for Schiff's records on Trump's watch...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/justice-dept-probe-secret-subpoena-200803613.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Dept.'s internal watchdog will investigate secret subpoenas to obtain records on Adam Schiff and others during Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus-ravaged Brazil doesn't want Copa America. But Bolsonaro hosting anyway...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/virus-ravaged-brazil-doesn-t-want-copa-america-but-bolsonaro-says-it-s-hosting-it-anyway/ar-AAKYsL9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana, the sold-out state New Yorkers can't get enough of...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/12/montana-the-sold-out-state-new-yorkers-cant-get-enough-of/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flathead Lake Lodge, in Bigfork, Montana, near Whitefish, lies at the foothills of the Swan Mountains where the Swan River feeds into the northern edge of Flathead Lake. In the mornings, guests rid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge great white sharks lurking off NY, NJ, Cape Cod...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/12/huge-great-white-sharks-lurking-off-ny-and-cape-cod-coasts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professional shark taggers warn there are at least four great whites lurking off Long Island en route to Cape Cod  – with a 600-pounder named Rose right behind them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star who posed nude at George Floyd mural found dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9679609/Porn-star-trolled-online-posing-nude-George-Floyd-mural-dead.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Kaye Scott, 27, who is known in the porn industry as Dakota Skye, was discovered by her boyfriend on Wednesday at their motorhome in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Fat Cats on Hot Tin Roof...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/12/fat-cats-on-a-hot-tin-roof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — I find this all quite taxing. Infrastructure talks just collapsed, with Republicans scratching their heads, wondering where on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed explores 'once in century bid to remake dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/12/fed-remake-us-dollar-493548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of private cryptocurrencies motivated the Fed to start considering a digital dollar to be used alongside the traditional paper currency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware's suspected Russian roots point to long detente between Kremlin, hackers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ransomware-e2-80-99s-suspected-russian-roots-point-to-a-long-detente-between-the-kremlin-and-hackers/ar-AAKY1M8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One apparent cybercrime rule still applies: Don’t target Russia or its friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden asks G-7 to take tougher line on China, but not all allies enthusiastic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-asks-g-7-to-take-a-tougher-line-on-china-but-not-all-allies-are-enthusiastic/ar-AAKYeRg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany is among the members of the economic club with reservations about confrontation with a major trading partner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to hold solo press conference after Putin meeting...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/558119-biden-to-hold-solo-press-conference-after-putin-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will hold a solo press conference next week following his first in-person meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin since taking office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile shuts capital as vaccines fail to quell rampant cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610214438-1gzip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHILE (PIX):Chile shuts capital Santiago once more as vaccines fail to quell rampant cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday names replaced with 'Day Off' on NJ school calendars...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-holiday-name-day-off-new-jersey-school-calendar-20210611-oraqdhe6ebhntfa2mibbzg4isa-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'What did you just do?' asked one confused attendee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 13 people wounded in Austin, Texas shooting...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210612092109-wos3p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEXAS-SHOOTING/ (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-At least 13 people wounded in Austin, Texas shooting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of Traffic? 10-Year Quest to Build Flying Car...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/12/what-is-a-flying-car/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was sleek, cone-shaped, a little confusing — like something Hollywood would give a sci-fi villain for a quick getaway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian cases spike 47% in week...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-coronavirus-pandemic-health-73f9ea558bd9e5fe276ee33e28691067</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia’s national coronavirus taskforce on Saturday reported that the country’s tally of daily new infections has risen by nearly 50% over the past week and more than doubled in Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST HOURS OF 'THE KING'... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/last-ditch-effort-netanyahu-offered-to-resign-let-gantz-serve-as-pm-670783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last offer came a little after midnight on Thursday, with Netanyahu's team reportedly telling Gantz that Netanyahu is "ready to resign this morning."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man killed by angry residents after urinating in middle of street...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-urinating-in-middle-of-north-houston-street-shot-and-killed-by-confronting-residents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary information from HPD suggests the unidentified man first arrived at the location to buy drugs from someone. However, at some point, the man began urinating in the middle of the roadway, resulting in a large confrontation with the area residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMORGAN Staff Irked Over Order to Save Texts on Personal Phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/banking-finance/jpmorgan-staff-irked-over-order-to-save-texts-on-personal-phones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businesstimes.com.sg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Judy Suffers Another Court Loss; Trial Certain In Big Battle Over CBS Deal...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/judge-judy-lawsuit-loss-cbs-rebel-library-sale-1234773722/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Judge Judy concluded shooting her long-running syndicated series earlier this year, but her efforts to shut down a $5 million lawsuit against her and CBS over profits from the lucrative …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un: K-pop 'vicious cancer' that merits execution...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/06/11/kim-jong-un-k-pop-fans-north-korea-culture-bts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BTS vs. The Dictator ... that's the new battlefront for Kim Jong-un, who reportedly sees the rise of K-Pop and its fans as a serious threat to North Korean socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US tourist hit by stray bullet in Cancun by jet-skiing cartel!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3064457/us-tourist-hit-by-stray-bullet-in-cancun-attack/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO’S TOURIST mecca Cancun became a crime scene after assassins on jet skis shot and killed two men as a stray bullet struck an American tourist.  The brazen hydro hitmen reportedly were ri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr doesn't recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/11/barr-distances-democratic-subpoenas-493491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comments come as Democratic congressional leaders demand the former attorney general testify about the leak probes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandmother killed at Florida grocery store fought gunman, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/grandmother-killed-at-florida-grocery-store-fought-gunman-police-say/ar-AAKX9rh?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROYAL PALM BEACH, Fla. – A grandmother who was killed with her grandson in a South Florida Publix fought with the gunman, police said Friday. The gunman shot the toddler first. His grandmother grabbed the gun, jamming it in the process, said Palm Beach County Sheriff Maj. Talal Masri. As the gunman tried to reload, he pushed the grandmother to the ground. Then he shot her before turning the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cocaine washes ashore at Space Force base...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/1-2-million-worth-of-cocaine-washes-ashore-at-cape-canaveral-space-force-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Space Force says 24 packages of cocaine washed ashore on a Cape Canaveral beach. The drugs have an estimated street value of approximately $1.2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demanded Data on 73 Phone Numbers, 36 Email Addresses from APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/11/politics/justice-department-apple-congress-leak-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice sent a broad request in February 2018 to Apple as part of its investigation that collected data on members of Congress, staffers and their families. The department demanded metadata on 73 phone numbers and 36 email addresses from Apple, the company said Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violators of Olympic Games virus rules to face fines...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Violators-of-Summer-Games-virus-rules-to-face-16242277.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - Athletes and others involved in the Tokyo Olympics who violate rules to prevent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines see unprecedented rise in disruptive passengers. It could get even worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Airlines-have-seen-an-unprecedented-rise-in-16241877.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The headlines had barely faded after a Southwest passenger reportedly knocked out a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  White boys who grew up with Black neighbors more likely to become Dems...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-boys-grew-black-neighbors-180023073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White men who had a Black neighbor in 1940 are more likely to be registered with the Democratic Party 70 years later, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro booed on plane, tells critics to 'take a donkey'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-booed-plane-tells-critics-211231009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say Brazil is polarized under far-right President Jair Bolsonaro, but the divide was literal Friday, when he boarded a commercial plane to greet supporters in the front -- as opponents booed him at the top of their lungs from the back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe's first foreign trip as VP was a breeze: Harris's was into the lion's den...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bidens-first-foreign-trip-vp-182712451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contrasting inaugural vice presidential trips — Biden's to Europe in 2009 and Harris' to Latin America — show their different roles in the No. 2 job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN PRAISES TRUMP; SLAMS 'FAKE NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/nbc-interview-putin-calls-trump-colorful-says-he-can-work-n1270561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin told NBC's Keir Simmons that accusations that he is a "killer" are "Hollywood macho."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Abuse of power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/justice-dept-watchdog-to-probe-trump-era-leak-investigations-including-secret-subpoenas-for-data-from-congress-journalists/ar-AAKWXvm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats on Capitol Hill called on former attorneys general Jeff Sessions and William Barr to testify over the subpoenas of Democratic Reps. Adam Schiff and Eric Swalwell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sh-t Show: 'ULTIMATE SLIP 'N SLIDE' Production Shut Down Over Explosive Diarrhea Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/slip-n-slide-show-nbc-diarrhea-shut-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC's upcoming series "Ultimate Slip 'N Slide" has halted production after dozens of crew members fell ill with "awful explosive diarrhea" on set</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gore pressed Biden to stick with climate plans as liberals fear White House softening agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/gore-pressed-biden-to-stick-with-climate-plans-as-liberals-fear-white-house-is-softening-its-agenda/ar-AAKVgkY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president and former vice president had a private phone call amid concerns the White House might strip climate measures from infrastructure deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Tax Leak Referred to FBI as Probe Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/billionaire-tax-leak-referred-to-fbi-as-probe-grows-irs-says/ar-AAKV0rD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disclosure of the personal income and tax data of some of the wealthiest Americans has been referred to additional federal investigators to probe the leak of confidential information, an Internal Revenue Service official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Geophysicist Who Stormed Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/06/11/jeffrey-sabol-capitol-riot-jan-6-radicalization-491975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Sabol lived in a quiet Colorado town and had some doubts about government spending. On January 6, he was photographed with a baton in his hand on the Capitol terrace. How does someone cross the threshold from belief to action?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweeping Overhaul...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/lawmakers-taking-aim-at-big-tech-push-sweeping-overhaul-of-antitrust/ar-AAKX5QY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — House lawmakers on Friday introduced sweeping antitrust legislation aimed at restraining the power of Big Tech and staving off corporate consolidation. If passed, the bills would be the most ambitious update to monopoly laws in decades. The bills — five in total — take direct aim at Amazon, Apple, Facebook and Google and their grip on online commerce, information and entertainment. The proposals would make it easier to break up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago cop broke in,bragged he 'knocked out a commie'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-chicago-police-officer-broke-into-the-capitol-in-january-and-bragged-in-a-text-that-he-knocked-out-a-commie-new-court-filings-show/ar-AAKXgZ1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karol Chwiesiuk, 29, has been a member of the Chicago Police Department since December 2018. He also worked for the Cook County Sheriff's Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland 'legally required' to spend wall money...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/11/dhs-legally-required-spend-trumps-border-wall-mone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security officials said Friday they are “legally required” to spend billions of dollars Congress allocated to Mexican border wall construction, but said they will focus on projects that “mitigate” damage from previous construction rather than on finishing the wall President Trump had planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: Soak the Rich!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnbcs-jim-cramer-calls-for-billionaire-tax-after-propublica-report-these-revelations-make-me-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC's Jim Cramer is calling for a billionaire's tax following the release of a stunning ProPublica report earlier this week exposing the IRS returns of the mega-rich, and showing how little they pay in taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Big-Donor Lobbying for Plum Ambassadorships...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/inside-the-big-donor-scramble-for-a-biden-ambassadorship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They are the closest things we have to somebody being declared a lord or a lady.” But the White House might be changing the rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE suspends Senator for touting unproven Covid treatments...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/558056-youtube-suspends-ron-johnson-for-7-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube suspended Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The scandals we don't know about...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/donald-trump/1001454/doj-subpoenas-scandals-we-dont-know-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest revelation of administration abuses won't be the last</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists demanding more action against online harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-journalists-racial-injustice-business-race-and-ethnicity-d986426b7211a67fffb621f0a2414001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Associated Press' recent firing of a young reporter for what she said on Twitter has somewhat unexpectedly turned company and industry attention to the flip side of social media engagement — the online abuse that many journalists face routinely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers hit Teamsters -- but they refused to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/ransomware-attack-hit-teamsters-2019-they-refused-pay-n1270461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI advised the union to "just pay" the ransom, according to sources. Union officials chose to rebuild their computer network instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobster Diver Survives After Nearly Swallowed Off Cape Cod...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/06/11/lobster-diver-swallowed-by-whale-cape-cod-michael-packard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lobster diver says he was nearly swallowed by a whale in a terrifying encounter off Cape Cod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star who posed nude pic at George Floyd mural found dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/11/porn-star-who-posed-nude-pic-at-george-floyd-mural-found-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 27-year-old was discovered dead in her Los Angeles motorhome by her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaders agree to keep money taps open...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210611180646-8xykl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G7-SUMMIT/ECONOMY (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-G7 leaders agreed to keep the money taps open -source</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gives Biden framed Frederick Douglass photo printed from WIKIPEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/newsletter/london-playbook/politico-g7-playbook-carbis-bay-fitness-regime-hug-and-walk-turbot-charged-dinner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's driving the day in Westminster. Politics and policymaking in the UK capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress, Justice Dept. probing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-donald-trump-ca-state-wire-europe-business-76af370a04c6d80613c9e9ba1e54c8c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department's internal watchdog launched an investigation Friday after revelations that former President Donald Trump's administration secretly seized phone data from at least two House Democrats as part of an aggressive leaks probe.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
