<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>American Fighters Flying Dozens of Daily Deterrence Missions from Carrier...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2022/03/19/video-navy-pilots-flying-dozens-of-daily-russian-deterrence-missions-from-uss-harry-s-truman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABOARD AIRCRAFT CARRIER USS HARRY S. TRUMAN IN THE IONIAN SEA – For the longest stretch in decades, the Mediterranean Sea has played host to the deafening roar of U.S. carrier aircraft launching into Europe. Since December, the Harry S. Truman Carrier Strike Group, Carrier Air Wing 1 and its escorts have been operating in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space missions to Venus could find evidence of life...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4928072/space-mission-venus-ancient-alien-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVIDENCE of ancient alien life could be lurking on one of our nearest space neighbours: Venus. These days, it seems like everyone is talking about celebrities going to space on private shuttles or …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More mercenaries hunt Zelensky...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-701782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia accused of expelling Ukrainian civilians from Mariupol • At least 902 civilians killed in Ukraine, UN says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MAURY' Canceled After Three Decade Run...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/maury-canceled-syndicated-talk-show-1234982475/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another syndicated daytime talk show is coming to an end: NBCUniversal’s veteran tabloid talker Maury, hosted and executive produced by Maury Povich. The show will end original productions at…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rift looms over DISNEY's future...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/20/disney-ceo-chapek-iger-falling-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Disney CEO Bob Iger chose Bob Chapek to succeed him, but their relationship soured quickly, and the pressure is on Chapek to show he's right for Disney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INITIAL CAMPAIGN 'DEFEATED'</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-am-e17389c4-1797-4245-8ebc-981689d54fa4.html?chunk=1&amp;utm_term=emshare#story1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China making new billionaires much faster than USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-new-billionaires-faster-us-5ab941fc-e8f8-42af-a249-bb7901d05081.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But American billionaires still control more money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAUDI ARAMCO profit doubles on soaring oil prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/20/saudi-aramco-full-year-profit-more-than-doubles-on-soaring-oil-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabian oil giant Aramco reported blowout full-year earnings on Sunday, posting a more than doubling in year-on-year net profit to $110 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine war backdrop in US push for hypersonic weapons...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-technology-business-maine-us-navy-9f344a7a73f5767de3520fe7bc53fc6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Lagging behind Russia in developing hypersonic weapons, the U.S. Navy is rushing to field its first, with installation on a warship starting as soon as late next year. The United States is in a race with Russia and China to develop these weapons, which travel at speeds akin to ballistic missiles but are difficult to shoot down because of their maneuverability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan's last finance minister, now DC UBER driver...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/middle_east/2022-03-19/afghanistan-last-finance-minister-uber-driver-ponders-what-went-wrong-5400789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Until last summer, Khalid Payenda was Afghanistan's finance minister, overseeing a $6 billion budget. Now, seven months after Kabul fell to the Taliban, Payenda is an Uber driver in the Washington, D.C., metro region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage Over Vlad's $13,000 jacket, $12,000 watch, $800 sneakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10631441/Putin-shows-designer-wear.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Russia feeling the impact of sanctions, it is unclear which of Putin's aides thought it wise for him to don a coat costing 25 times the nation's average monthly wage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIH Awarded 56,000 Grants in '20. Just 2% for Studying COVID...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/03/18/nih-awarded-more-than-56000-grants-in-2020-just-2-percent-were-for-studying-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More evidence that the public health bureaucracy dropped the ball when a once-in-a-generation pandemic hit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run for lives as gunshots ring out: Students trampled, hide in alleys...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10632035/Spring-breakers-run-lives-gunshots-ring-Miami.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flocks of panicked college students fled the area surrounding Kantina Restaurant on Ocean Drive, after multiple gunshots were fired early Sunday morning. At least two people were injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring breakers flash the flesh at raucous beachside parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10626409/Wet-T-shirt-contests-bikinis-beach-plenty-twerking-display-spring-break.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;College students headed south to Texas and Florida like they'd been locked away for two years, shedding their winter coats and inhibitions for a little sun, sand and skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims women, children forcibly sent to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/mar/20/ukraine-crisis-claims-mariupol-women-and-children-forcibly-sent-to-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of resident illegally taken across border, says Mariupol council, as reports emerge its art school has been bombed while 400 were sheltering inside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia loses ANOTHER top commander...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10632485/Putin-loses-commander-Black-Sea-Fleet-captain-51-shot-dead-near-Mariupol.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine claimed today that its forces had shot dead the deputy commander of Russia's Black Sea Fleet, first rank captain Andrey Paliy, 51, (pictured) in another significant blow to Vladimir Putin's forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Prince of Crypto Has Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6158182/vitalik-buterin-ethereum-profile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vitalik Buterin dreamed up the blockchain technology for uses beyond currency. Now he's fighting to fix the industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at SXSW festival in Austin; 4 injured...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/20/south-by-southwest-festival-shooting-leaves-4-injured/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All four victims’ gunshot wounds from South By Southwest 2022 are not expected to be life-threatening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 injured, 1 dead in shooting outside Arkansas car show...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnct.com/top-stories/dumas-pd-chief-20-injured-1-dead-in-shooting-outside-arkansas-car-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnct.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Keith Finch with the Dumas Police Department said one person was killed and at least 20 others were injured in the shooting incident outside of a car show Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's 'cursed presidency': Gas prices latest headache as midterms loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/20/joe-biden-cursed-presidency-gas-prices-covid-inflation-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his 14 months in office, the US president has grappled with Covid, inflation, the Russia-Ukraine war and energy prices – and seemingly can’t catch a break</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marriage on the rocks in China, total hits record low...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/3171165/marriage-rocks-china-women-rethink-their-options-and-covid-19-limits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A range of factors at play, from coronavirus restrictions to the legacy of the one-child policy, observers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside secret drug culture at West Point...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/19/inside-secret-drug-culture-at-west-point-other-military-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the spring break overdoses of five West Point cadets, insiders expose the shocking drug culture at the country’s most elite military academies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Korea's next leader to abandon Blue House for new office...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seoul-south-korea-666c4751dab0bc6fac9b1bf748c8bf32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — South Korea’s incoming president said Sunday he will abandon the mountainside presidential palace of Blue House and establish his office at the Defense Ministry compound in central Seoul to better communicate with the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK:  People will riot if another full lockdown is enforced, top doctor warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10631269/People-riot-lockdown-enforced-doctor-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Roger Kirby, president of the Royal Society of Medicine, said the public would not tolerate being deprived of their liberty on such a scale again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye  pulled from Grammys lineup over 'concerning online behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/music/news/kanye-west-grammys-concerning-online-behavior-1235209759/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West has been barred from performing at the Grammy Awards due to his “concerning online behavior,” a rep for the artist confirms to Variety. Reps for the Recording Academy and CBS, which pres…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN GOES HYPERSONIC</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/zelensky-calls-fresh-talks-russia-052632840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine called on China on Saturday to join the West in condemning "Russian barbarism", as Moscow claimed it had struck a Ukrainian arms depot with hypersonic missiles in what would be the first use in combat of the next-generation weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official invites Biden to Kyiv next week 'if he is brave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10631455/Ukrainian-official-invites-Biden-Kyiv-week-brave.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zelensky's chief diplomatic adviser Ihor Zhovka said 'one should not be afraid to [travel to Kyiv] if you are brave'. He said Zelensky is seeking Biden's help with facilitiating Ukraine's weapons acquisiton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House considered sending gas cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-democrats-gas-prices-inflation-russia-sanctions-2e647ba7-116d-4a49-b3a4-3cad156c1148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea died quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Transgender swimmer finishes last in final college race...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/transgender-swimmer-makes-final-bid-182804467.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transgender swimmer Lia Thomas ended her controversial college swimming career with a last place finish in the final of the 100-yard freestyle at the US collegiate champsionships on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow ridicules idea that cosmonauts wore yellow in support of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-ridicules-idea-cosmonauts-wore-151014565.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Sometimes yellow is just yellow," Roscosmos's press service said on its Telegram channel. "The flight suits of the new crew are made in the colours of the emblem of the Bauman Moscow State Technical University, which all three cosmonauts graduated from ... To see the Ukrainian flag everywhere and in everything is crazy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlike Trump, Biden Has Stock Market Far Down His Priority List...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unlike-trump-biden-stock-market-170000174.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Even investors with a lot at stake tend to agree: The stock market shouldn’t be a president’s top priority, especially when issues like war, blistering inflation and a pandemic are in play. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Russia Denies Cosmonauts’ Colors Signal SupportRussia Says It Used Hypersonic ‘Kinzhal’ Missiles to AttackBiden Warned Xi of ‘Consequences’ for Backing Russia in WarUkraine Update: Zelenskiy Says Talks Are Russia’s ‘Only Chance’Biden Team Hardens View of</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
