<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump leaves White House as he came in: Isolated and unpredictable...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article248535105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his final days in office, Donald Trump found friends and political allies in short supply following the deadly Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next TESLA? Investors Bet Big on RIVIAN...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/19/rivian-has-been-a-tortoise-to-teslas-hare-can-it-catch-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLYMOUTH, Mich. — It’s hard to imagine any company matching Tesla’s rocket-like rise. But if any electric car start-up could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, GOP leaders will attend church before inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-gop-leaders-will-attend-church-before-inauguration/ar-BB1cTrsx?ocid=Peregrine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President-elect Joe Biden has invited top Republican and Democratic congressional leaders to a bipartisan prayer session at church early Wednesday hours before his inauguration, people familiar with the plans said. "Yes I can confirm" that top Senate Republican Mitch McConnell will join Biden, who was a longtime colleague in the US Senate, at the church, a person knowledgeable of McConnell's plans told AFP Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON discussed posing as troops to infiltrate National Guard...</title>
      <link>ttps://www.adn.com/nation-world/2021/01/19/qanon-adherents-discussed-posing-as-troops-to-infiltrate-inauguration-fbi-briefing-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Hottest Housing Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.zillow.com/research/zillow-hottest-markets-2021-28667/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zillow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austin and a lineup of sunny, affordable metro areas are most likely to outperform the nation in home value growth in 2021, according to experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence 'man without a home'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2021/01/19/mike-pences-future-chances-running-president-hurt-trump/6640990002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After four years of steadfast loyalty to Trump, Pence is said to be open to a 2024 run, but his rift with the president may close off that option.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revving up electric car industry, firm develops 5-min-charge battery...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/revving-up-electric-car-industry-israeli-firm-develops-5-minute-charge-battery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herzliya-based startup StoreDot unveils solution for main obstacle to widespread use of electric vehicles, but it requires major upgrades to charging stations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to hold Covid rule breakers in refugee camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/13773701/germany-covid-rule-breakers-refugee-camps-mutant-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY’S worst Covid rule breakers will be held in detention centres under new proposals being drawn up by a number of state governments. The move forms part of the country’s efforts t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Was Fired From TACO BELL for Being in Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lonna-wells-was-fired-from-taco-bell-for-being-in-porn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With her sex work on pause during the pandemic, Lonna Wells was earning money for her family at Taco Bell. But she was fired when a customer complained. Now she’s speaking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service Bracing for Dangerous Times...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/01/how-secret-service-plans-protect-joe-biden-now/617726/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any chance of a normal security environment for the president-elect evaporated during the Capitol siege.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 HOURS</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-era-s-battles-over-truth-will-outlast-his-15879674.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump stands as a singular figure in American history for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to propose major immigration legislation this week...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Biden-to-propose-major-immigration-legislation-15880225.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President-elect Joe Biden propose major changes to the nation's immigration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican support for convicting Trump in Senate growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/19/republican-support-convicting-trump-growing-460247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 20 percent of Republicans said they “strongly” or “somewhat” approved of a Senate conviction in the latest poll, conducted between Jan. 15-17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon deploys hundreds of active-duty soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/18/pentagon-deploys-troops-inauguration-security-460203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The personnel will support enhanced security measures related to the event, as local law enforcement continues to track threats of violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds file conspiracy charge against Oath Keeper leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-files-conspiracy-charge-against-oath-keeper-leader-in-alleged-plot-against-the-capitol/ar-BB1cT81o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI says Thomas Caldwell of Virginia scouted lodging and recruited self-styled militia members before “storming the castle.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many paths ahead for ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/citizen-trump-the-many-paths-ahead-for-the-ex-president/ar-BB1cR7gW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump leaves the White House as the most controversial president in modern history. So what now?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FOR SELF, FAMILY?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/breaking-trump-reportedly-will-not-pardon-himself-or-his-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is set to issue a slew of pardons in the final hours of his term. But none, reportedly, will go to his family. And he will not pardon himself either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Going to Church with Biden Ahead of Inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/just-in-mitch-mcconnell-going-to-church-with-joe-biden-ahead-of-inauguration-at-bidens-invitation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has learned that Joe Biden's outreach to Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell will begin with the two of them attending church before inauguration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcast, Trailed by Pandemic, Joblessness...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/trump-leaves-town-an-outcast-trailed-by-covid-19-pandemic-joblessness-101611047742915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last president who chose not to attend his successor’s inauguration was Andrew Johnson in 1869, another impeached leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletproof vests and gas masks: Journalists prep...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/18/media/journalists-inauguration-preparation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of December, Los Angeles Times Washington Bureau Chief Kimbriell Kelly was looking at getting Moleskine notebooks as gifts for her staff. A couple weeks later, she was procuring goods of a decidedly different kind: gas masks, helmets and body armor for LA Times staff members who will be attending Wednesday's inauguration of President-elect Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St has new top cop. And Elizabeth Warren is big fan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/18/economy/biden-wall-street-gensler-sec-elizabeth-warren/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new sheriff is coming to Wall Street -- and, for a change, he's not a friendly face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAND FINALE:  100 PARDONS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/17/politics/trump-pardons-expected/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is preparing to issue around 100 pardons and commutations on his final full day in office Tuesday, according to three people familiar with the matter, a major batch of clemency actions that includes white collar criminals, high-profile rappers and others but -- as of now -- is not expected to include Trump himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie mural defaced in DC; Cops investigating as hate crime...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/01/bernie-sanders-mural-defaced-in-dc-police-investigating-as-hate-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mural of Independent Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders was defaced near Navy Yard in Southeast D.C., and it’s being investigated as a hate crime, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman accused of trying to sell Pelosi laptop to Russians arrested...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/534727-woman-accused-of-trying-to-sell-pelosi-laptop-to-russians-arrested</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who the FBI says took a laptop belonging to Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) during the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol and tried to sell it to Russians has been arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  Give me something. Give me hope. Give me Xanax...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/topic/trumpism-toxic-debate-matt-labash-chris-buskirk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if I told you I disliked the ‘uniparty’ and Trump? In the binary world that is Trumpism (us vs them typifies all cults), it’s impossible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemalan security forces break up US-bound migrant caravan ...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/guatemalan-security-forces-break-us-194807999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guatemalan security forces on Monday broke up a caravan of some 4,000 Honduran migrants trying to reach the United States on a journey of thousands of kilometers through Central America on foot, AFP reporters witnessed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An inauguration like no other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-concerns-razor-wire-no-014358732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With war-zone-like security, no crowds and coronavirus distancing for guests, Joe Biden's swearing-in as the 46th US president will be a muted affair unlike any previous inauguration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cinderella story for a dog': Joe's shelter pet gives adoption trend boost...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cinderella-story-dog-bidens-shelter-130045525.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major, a German shepherd, will become the first White House shelter dog. The pandemic has fueled pet adoptions, "one of the few silver linings to COVID," one animal rescue official says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Field of Flags'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-inaugurated-amid-high-security-052251407.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers for President-elect Joe Biden's inauguration on Wednesday finished setting up about 200,000 flags on Monday, representing the American people who cannot travel to the inauguration amid a worsening coronavirus pandemic and extraordinary security precautions. The flags represent all of the states and U.S. territories, and they also are meant to honor the 400,000 Americans who will have officially died from COVID-19 by the time Biden is sworn in.Embed from Getty ImagesEmbed from Getty ImagesEmbed from Getty ImagesThe Presidential Inaugural Committee highlighted the "Field of Flags" on Monday night, with 56 pillars of light — one for each of the 50 states and six U.S. territories — beamed into the air for 46 second, a reference to Biden becoming the 46th U.S. president.Embed from Getty ImagesBiden arrives in Washington for his inauguration on Tuesday, and he and incoming first lady Jill Biden will spend Tuesday night at Blair House, near the White House. Outgoing President Trump plans to leave the White House on Wednesday morning, making him the first president since Andrew Johnson — the first impeached president — to skip the inauguration of his successor. Trump has made no public appearances in six days.Biden and Vice President-elect Kamala Harris, who resigned as a U.S. senator on Monday, volunteered in service events to honor Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. on Monday. They will take part in a memorial at the reflecting pool near the Lincoln Memorial on Tuesday to honor the Americans who lost their lives to COVID-19.More stories from theweek.com 5 more scathing cartoons about Trump's 2nd impeachment Melania Trump released a farewell video. So did Colbert's Late Show Melania Trump. Stephen Colbert has theories about Trump's conspiratorial 'pillow talk' with MyPillow's Mike Lindell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After allergic reactions, CA pauses use of MODERNA doses...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/after-allergic-reactions-at-1-clinic-california-pauses-use-of-more-than-330k-doses-of-moderna-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After several people had apparent allergic reactions at one California clinic, state health officials on Sunday told providers across the state to pause administering doses from one COVID-19 vaccin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army working on Frankenbots with living tissue...</title>
      <link>https://federalnewsnetwork.com/defense-main/2021/01/army-is-working-on-frankenbots-with-living-tissue-to-better-robot-capabilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;federalnewsnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The robots may have better stability and flexibility by taking advantage of living muscles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cremation limits lifted in LA...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/health/as-bodies-pile-up-cremation-limits-lifted-in-los-angeles-county/9762002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death rate during the COVID-19 pandemic is so high in LA County that officials are lifting environmental limits on cremations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police recover 500-year-old stolen copy of da Vinci's 'MUNDI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/salvator-mundi-leonardo-da-vinci-copy-found/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under concussion protocols, decision on Mahomes' status out of CHIEFS' hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Under-NFL-s-concussion-protocols-decision-on-15881157.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major betting implications...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/19/patrick-mahomes-mystery-has-major-nfl-betting-implications/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland House speaker to unveil 'Black agenda'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Maryland-House-speaker-to-unveil-Black-agenda-15880918.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do People 'Hear Dead'? Scientists Reveal 'Sixth Sense'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/how-do-people-hear-dead-scientists-reveal-why-some-have-sixth-sense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe selects trans doctor as assistant health secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-selects-transgender-doctor-rachel-levine-as-assistant-health-secretary/ar-BB1cT1Vv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Transition Approval Remains High at 68%...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/328640/biden-transition-approval-remains-high.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy man's 'miracle' potion turns sour...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210119-sri-lanka-holy-man-s-miracle-coronavirus-potion-turns-sour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrican Strain 50% More Infectious...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/carlieporterfield/2021/01/18/south-african-coronavirus-strain-is-50-more-infectious-scientists-say/?sh=6080777a4475</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: COVID has shown what happens when we destroy nature...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210119081114-l50qc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny calls for street protests after being jailed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210118201406-swgr8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New challenge: Mutations rise along with cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-genetics-coronavirus-pandemic-united-kingdom-f471eca388965ee95cd1e324c4e239d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai, party haven amid pandemic, faces biggest surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-dubai-united-arab-emirates-coronavirus-pandemic-financial-markets-6edff7b2ecc2a94b1ca0cbeea0de1b32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo clings to Trump's legacy with eye toward inheriting MAGA base...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Pompeo-clings-to-Trump-s-legacy-with-eye-toward-15880192.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will halt Keystone XL pipeline...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-to-kill-Keystone-XL-pipeline-in-fight-on-15879538.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make America California Again? State takes center stage as Biden sets his agenda...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/america-california-again-thats-bidens-110050453.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARLER reappears with support from Russia...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210118224444-0t0va</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid covid, lonely big dogs remain stuck in adoption shelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/amid-covid-19-lonely-big-dogs-remain-stuck-in-adoption-shelters-655796</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump lifting virus travel restrictions on Europe, UK, Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-usa-travel/exclusive-trump-lifting-covid-19-travel-restrictions-on-europe-uk-brazil-sources-idUSKBN29N20Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy voted with affidavit ballot, which he bashed in failed effort to overturn election...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/18/politics/rudy-giuliani-affidavit-ballot-vote-kfile/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thief threatens to call cops on mom who left child in back seat of car he stole...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/news/2021/01/thief-threatens-to-call-police-on-mom-who-left-her-child-in-the-back-seat-of-the-car-he-stole.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census Director Quits After Trying To Rush Out 'Indefensible' Report...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/01/18/957302276/trumps-census-director-to-quit-after-trying-to-rush-out-indefensible-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes' concussion headache for NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/30736432/patrick-mahomes-nfl-concussion-protocol-needs-happen-chiefs-star-play-bills</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania says 'violence never the answer' in farewell address...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9160983/Melania-Trump-says-violence-never-answer-farewell-video-touting-Best-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman ruled dead in '17 fights to be declared alive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lyon-2256556e1c682d8ca561cc14b58b0228</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINION sends cease and desist letter to MYPILLOW CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/dominion-mike-lindell-my-pillow-ceo-trump-meeting-df5ec714-0528-4d7a-b70d-5c7a5a012a7e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garth Brooks joins lineup of entertainers at inaugural...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-donald-trump-lady-gaga-barack-obama-16fbd38c05b304a924132fa5d6732390</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINION threatens to sue MYPILLOW CEO over false claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/01/18/us/mike-lindell-mypillow-dominion-voting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eerie video shows warning message tested in desolate streets...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/18/video-shows-capitol-warning-tested-in-desolate-dc-streets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving trucks arrive at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.wptv.com/news/region-c-palm-beach-county/palm-beach/moving-trucks-arrive-at-president-donald-trumps-mar-a-lago-club-on-palm-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wptv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea's Kim could be planning fireworks to welcome Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/north-korea-s-kim-could-be-planning-fireworks-to-welcome-biden-administration/ar-BB1cRQCv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Accelerates Vaccine Plan as Popularity Takes Hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bolsonaro-accelerates-vaccine-plan-as-popularity-a-takes-hit/ar-BB1cRulq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police command structure crumbled fast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-riots-only-on-ap-michael-pence-a27921d08ca949c0b1e64c33628dd80e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unlocks more secrets in Saqqara...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/egypt-unlocks-secrets-saqqara-discovery-temple-sarcophagi/story?id=75322551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricketts launching national news outlet based in Omaha...</title>
      <link>https://omaha.com/business/local/joe-ricketts-is-launching-a-national-news-outlet-based-in-omaha/article_117fe584-55e5-11eb-9f6b-9349abea2fd7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convicted Killer Fought at Jan. 6 Rally in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.wweek.com/news/2021/01/17/kyle-brewster-convicted-in-1988-killing-of-mulugeta-seraw-fought-at-jan-6-pro-trump-rally-in-salem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's test: Engineering economic boom in partisan divide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-28d953d9c624573ef44f1c229211f2e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inauguration rehearsal evacuated after fire in homeless camp...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-fires-5e8a266ac54cc7205498a24c9972008a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of children hospitalized in AZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/hundreds-of-children-being-admitted-to-arizona-hospitals-for-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Minting Money in Pandemic Like Never Before...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/business/economy/rich-in-us-minting-money-in-pandemic-like-never-before</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETWORK DODGED DEPOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/01/17/business/media/fox-news-seth-rich-settlement.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Doesn't Rule Out Quarantine Hotels, GPS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-k-doesn-t-rule-out-quarantine-hotels-gps-to-fight-virus/ar-BB1cPkSD?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Migrants Head for USA After Clash in Guatemala...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/migrants-honduras-moving-guatemala-hoping-reach-us/story?id=75311138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incoming CDC director expects 500,000 COVID deaths by mid-Feb...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-biden-cdc-pick-expects-half-million-covid-deaths-mid-february-20210118-vxhzjtcwvzfgbdkni3f6x4b5xu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight to detention: On plane with Moscow's most wanted...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/flight-to-detention-on-the-plane-with-russia-e2-80-99s-most-wanted/ar-BB1cRbVN?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax groups received PPP loans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-trump-administration-bailed-out-prominent-anti-vaccine-groups-during-a-pandemic/ar-BB1cRo69?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Proud Boys and others found refuge on Christian fundraising site...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98a-place-to-fund-hope-e2-80-99-how-proud-boys-and-other-fringe-groups-found-refuge-on-a-christian-fundraising-website/ar-BB1cRxU0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Discovered After Living Inside O'Hare Airport for 3 Months in Fear of Virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-ohare-trespasser-arrest-20210117-aad2craysvehzmk5rm6l23p3l4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JITS: CAPITOL LOCKDOWN FALSE ALARM...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/biden-inauguration-preparation-2021-01-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California warns against using batch of Moderna jabs after allergic reactions...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-warns-doctors-avoid-batch-130055139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
