<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Russian lawmaker wants to ban 'mockery' of soccer team...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-lawmaker-wants-ban-mockery-soccer-team-172505377--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Russia (AP) — A conservative legislator in Russia says he wants to ban "mockery" of the national soccer team because the players are "fighting for the honor of our country."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia: Marines beefed-up presence in Norway an attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/06/18/russia-argues-the-corps-beefed-up-presence-in-norway-is-an-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week Russia warned there would be consequences following Norway's decision to invite 700 Marines for training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY UNDER INVESTIGATION...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/18/comey-under-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEVELOPING...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Tractor Strikes Roadside Explosive, Linked To Mysterious PA Booms...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/06/15/police-tractor-mowing-grass-strikes-device-related-to-mysterious-explosions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating another mysterious explosion in Bucks County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: WENDY'S Employee Finds Mouse, Feces In Burger Bun Bag...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/06/18/video-mouse-found-crawling-in-bag-of-wendys-hamburger-buns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It shows a mouse among the hamburger buns and feces throughout the packaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: TRUMP APPROVAL TIES HIGHEST OF PRESIDENCY...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/203207/trump-job-approval-weekly.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gallup tracks daily the percentage of Americans who approve or disapprove of the job Donald Trump is doing as president. Weekly results are based on telephone interviews with approximately 1,500 national adults, with a margin of error is ±3 percentage points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian mobster jailed for vicious attack on journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/italian-mobster-jailed-vicious-attack-journalist-172136279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A notorious Italian mobster, Roberto Spada, was sentenced Monday to six years in jail for violently assaulting a journalist during an interview in 2017, the video of which immediately went viral. The assault, which shocked Italy, occurred last November in the seaside town of Ostia, near Rome. Daniele</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia cuts Treasury holdings in half as foreigners start losing appetite for US debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/russia-cuts-treasury-holdings-in-half-as-foreigners-start-losing-appetite-for-us-debt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign governments pulled back their purchase of U.S. debt as trade tensions escalated. One of the most glaring declines has come from Russia, which sliced its holdings nearly in half from March to April, from $96.1 billion to $48.7 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Obama Immigration Agencies Separated Children From Families...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/immigration/obamas-immigration-agencies-separated-children-from-their-families-too-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President orders Pentagon to create 'space force' branch of military...</title>
      <link>https://www.13wmaz.com/article/news/nation-world/trump-announces-hes-directing-pentagon-to-create-space-force-branch-of-military/507-565332483</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.13wmaz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump announced the plans during a meeting with the National Space Council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Call me Mr President': Macron dresses down cheeky teen...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/call-mr-president-macron-dresses-down-cheeky-teen-161211452.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like most politicians, French President Emmanuel Macron seems to enjoy pressing the flesh and posing for selfies when on public outings. A cheeky teen who dared greet him with a breezy "How's it going, Manu" during an official outing near Paris on Monday was left red-faced after receiving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House aims to reduce satellite clutter in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/white-house-aims-reduce-satellite-clutter-space-145854437--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The White House is establishing a new policy for reducing satellite clutter in space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER Pays Settlement After Wrongly Labeled 'Anti-Muslim Extremist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/maajid-nawaz-splc-apologizes-settles-extremist-label/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group’s ‘Field Guide to Anti-Muslim Extremists’ was widely criticized before Maajid Nawaz’s lawsuit prompted its retraction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel arrests former govt minister for Iran spying...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1f70c51ab91b46e08e4a3c0d34805acf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — A former Israeli government minister, once imprisoned for trying to smuggle drugs, is back behind bars after being charged with spying for archenemy Iran, the cou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court takes APPLE antitrust case...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/u-top-court-mulls-apples-app-store-commissions-133902621--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday agreed to take up Apple Inc's bid to escape a lawsuit accusing it of breaking federal antitrust laws by monopolizing the market for iPhone software applications and causing consumers to pay more than they should. The justices said they would hear Apple's appeal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDI boss arrested in diesel probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/audi-boss-arrested-diesel-probe-110012059.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Audi chief executive Rupert Stadler was arrested Monday in connection with parent company Volkswagen's "dieselgate" emissions cheating scandal, with prosecutors saying they feared he might try to suppress evidence. The dramatic development comes a week after Munich prosecutors raided Stadler</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foods that fatty and sweet hijack brain...</title>
      <link>http://www.heraldcourier.com/news/national/foods-that-are-both-fatty-and-sweet-can-hijack-the/article_17af3321-b686-594f-b23b-54ffbd362244.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may have taken thousands of generations of hunting, gathering, farming and cooking to get here. But in the end, the genius of humankind has combined fats and carbohydrates to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive swarms of bugs invading World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/soccer/2018/06/18/england-tunisia-volgograd-world-cup-bugs/709816002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Helicopters have been deployed to spray insecticide on the Volgograd Arena, which will host four games over the course of the tournament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers at WASH POST demand raise...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5852193/Over-400-Washington-Post-employees-signed-petition-asking-Jeff-Bezos-share-wealth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 400 employees of The Washington Post have signed on to a public letter to owner Jeff Bezos asking him to remedy working conditions at the newspaper, after unsuccessful negotiation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Media Mistakes in the Trump Era: The Definitive List... </title>
      <link>https://sharylattkisson.com/2018/06/10/50-media-mistakes-in-the-trump-era-the-definitive-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sharylattkisson.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll: Kim Jong-Un More Popular Than Pelosi!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kim-jong-un-more-popular-than-pelosi-among-republicans-exclusive-poll-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And yet Pelosi isn’t the most unpopular member of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wait times at California DMVs top 5 hours!</title>
      <link>http://www.sacbee.com/news/local/transportation/back-seat-driver/article213205334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unwary motorists are finding themselves spending entire mornings or afternoons trapped in crowded Department of Motor Vehicles field offices in California. Here are several tips on how to avoid long waits at the DMV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE: USA TAKING IN 250 KIDS PER DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/us-could-be-holding-30-000-border-kids-by-august-officials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration could be holding 30,000 illegal immigrant children by the end of August as a result of its push to enforce federal immigration laws, which has led to the separation of children from their parents and guardians as those adults are prosecuted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  Americans grapple with recognizing facts in news stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/americans-grapple-recognizing-facts-news-stories-pew-survey-140456645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Angela Moon NEW YORK (Reuters) - Only a quarter of U.S. adults in a recent survey could fully identify factual statements - as opposed to opinion - in news stories, the Pew Research Center found in a study released on Monday. The survey comes amid growing concerns about so-called fake news spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Govt's creepy obsession with your face...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/779196/governments-creepy-obsession-face</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uncle Sam wants you(r face data and DNA)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Gets Ultimatum on Immigration Challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/merkel-gets-ultimatum-on-immigration-challenge-1529324605</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Angela Merkel was handed a two-week ultimatum by her coalition partners to secure a European deal allowing German police to turn back some migrants at the border, a senior lawmaker said, potentially buying time to settle a standoff that has threatened to topple her government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RIPS BORDER CRITICS, ATTACKS MERKEL</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-ex-trump-adviser-questions-border-talking-points-125706085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and immigration (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant that can cause burns and blindness found in Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/06/18/giant-hogweed-burns-blindness-found-virginia/709415002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in Isle of Wight County, near Norfolk and Newport News, posted a warning on Facebook about the plant, which can grow to almost 15 feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security chief slams 'irresponsible' reports on separation of migrant families...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/homeland-security-chief-slams-irresponsible-reports-separation-migrant/story?id=55968436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration fired back at criticism of its immigration policy on Sunday with tweets by both the president himself and his head of the Department of Homeland Security. Trump deflected mounting criticism over the government's separation of parents and children of illegal immigrants in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of DACA recipients with arrest records, including 10 accused murderers, allowed to stay in USA...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/18/thousands-daca-recipients-with-arrest-records-including-10-accused-murderers-allowed-to-stay-in-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 60,000 immigrants with arrest records have been permitted to remain in the United States under the Obama-era Deferred Action for Childhood Arrivals (DACA) program, the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) revealed Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Holding U.S. Citizens 'Hostage' in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/beijing-is-holding-us-citizens-hostage-in-china </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exit bans are a new tool in China’s global coercion campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAST COAST SIZZLE; HEAT RECORD?</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5854467/New-Yorkers-warned-stay-inside-temperatures-expected-reach-95-degrees.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers are preparing for near record-breaking weather on Monday as temperatures are predicted to be well into the 90s. The temperature could reach a scorching high of 95 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party dips can give HERPES...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/food/article-5848667/How-party-dips-Norovirus-HERPES.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microbiologists reveal on Channel 4's Food Unwrapped how double dipping can spread bacteria very quickly as even a small amount of someone's saliva in a dip will allow germs to multiply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONSANTO Squares Off With Man Dying of Cancer in Roundup Trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/18/monsanto-squares-off-with-man-dying-of-cancer-in-roundup-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monsanto Squares Off With Man Dying of Cancer in Roundup Trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're seeing greatest asset inflation bubble in 20 years, fund manager warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/were-seeing-the-greatest-asset-inflation-bubble-in-20-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it could pop sooner than many expect, Centricus Asset Management Fund Manager Ralph Jainz said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four in 10 people have deleted social media account in past year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/18/people-are-deleting-social-media-accounts-due-to-privacy-worries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a serious lack of trust in social media such as Facebook and Twitter and consumers expect brands that advertise on such platforms to urgently find solutions, according to research published Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too frail for death row? Texas inmate seeks execution reprieve...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/too-frail-death-row-texas-inmate-seeks-execution-114557643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two recent botched U.S. executions of inmates with compromised veins, a convicted murderer and rapist is arguing he is too ill to be put to death by lethal injection in Texas later this month. Lawyers for Danny Bible, a 66-year-old inmate set to be executed on June 27, said in a federal court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL FOLDS; ACCEPTS BORDER CONTROL DEADLINE...</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/topic/merkel-accepts-minister-end-june-deadline-border-control-180618-99-771324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Stories from around the globe brought to you by dpa International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Satisfaction with US direction highest since '05...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/235739/satisfaction-direction-reaches-year-high.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' satisfaction with the way things are going in the country has reached a 12-year high of 38%, one point above last month's satisfaction rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN human rights head calls 'zero-tolerance' policy abuse...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/international/un-treaties/392722-un-human-rights-head-trump-policy-separating-migrant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Nation’s top human rights official on Monday called on the Trump administration to end its "zero-tolerance" policy, which has resulted in the separation of migrant families at the southern border, calling the practice abusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insecure millennials set for unhealthy middle age...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/why-insecure-millennials-are-set-for-an-unhealthy-middle-age-825mjshs5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials are on track to become the first generation to suffer worse health than their parents when they reach middle age, a study has warned. People in their 20s and 30s will have a higher risk...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry told Meghan's dad to 'give Trump a chance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/prince-harry-told-meghans-dad-trump-chance-interview-112244319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan Markle's father Thomas on Monday said that new son-in-law Prince Harry had urged him to give President US Donald Trump "a chance" in comments likely to cause discomfort for the royal family. Markle also said that during a "loose conversation" with Harry, the prince had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theaters Post Warnings After Strobe-Light Scene Causes Moviegoers To Become Nauseous...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/06/17/incredibles-2-is-huge-hit-but-now-comes-with-a-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I walked out of the theater with a migraine," said blogger Veronica Lewis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Slim could profit from election of Mexican leftist...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-election-slim/billionaire-slim-america-movil-could-profit-from-election-of-mexican-leftist-idUSKBN1JE0B1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Carlos Slim has had harsh words for Mexico's presidential frontrunner, saying recently he is "concerned and afraid" about what leftist Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador might do if elected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaming addiction classified as mental health disorder by WHO...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-06-compulsive-video-game-mental-health-problem.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization says compulsively playing video games now qualifies as a new mental health condition—a move that some critics warn may risk stigmatizing its young players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Erdogan Heartland, Lira Crisis Taking Toll on Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/06/18/in-erdogan-heartland-lira-crisis-is-taking-toll-on-businesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Anatolian Tigers’ are roaring less these days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin RUTHLESS crackdown on hooligans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/710377/russia-vladimir-putin-ultras-world-cup-hooligans-england-tunisia-volgograd-marseille-euros</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Machines Predict When Will Die...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/18/google-is-training-machines-to-predict-when-a-patient-will-die</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Is Training Machines to Predict When a Patient Will Die</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mergers to Make AT&amp;T, COMCAST World's Most Indebted Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mergers-to-make-at-t-comcast-worlds-most-indebted-companies-1529314201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent mergers could transform AT&amp;T and Comcast into the two most indebted companies in the world, a standing that carries uncharted risks for investors in the firms’ bonds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barricades and Empty Streets: Nicaragua's Leader Loses Control...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/barricades-and-empty-streets-nicaraguas-leader-loses-control-1529314200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since a revolt broke out two months ago, President Daniel Ortega, the former Marxist guerrilla leader, has lost control over most of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Nashville Rapidly Expands, Residents Worry Metropolis Growing Too Fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-nashville-rapidly-expands-residents-worry-the-metropolis-is-growing-too-fast-1529314200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anxiety about rapid growth is widespread in Nashville, as a city known for country music and honky-tonks also becomes known for a skyline full of cranes and traffic congestion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro musical disrupted with 'Keep America Great' flag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/18/trump-supporter-disrupts-de-niros-play-with-keep-america-great-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Trump supporter tried disrupting a performance of the Robert De Niro directed musical “A Bronx Tale” on Saturday — standing up during the curtain call and displaying a “Keep Ame…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
'Terrified' San Francisco Tourists Shocked By Aggressive Vagrants, Discarded Needles, Dead Bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-06-17/terrified-san-francisco-tourists-shocked-aggressive-vagrants-discarded-needles-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local billionaire takes control of LA TIMES...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-latimes-owners-20180617-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With its newspaper, the Chandler dynasty shaped Los Angeles, only to sell it and fade into history. A new owner plans to use it to build his own legacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human toes stolen from dead body exhibition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1&amp;objectid=12072908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is accused of stealing two toes from a famous travelling exhibition of dead bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photog captures bears vs. eagles brawl in Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/outdoors-adventure/2018/06/16/katmai-national-park-drama-bear-vs-eagles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eagles face off with a Katmai brown bear sow to defend the eagle's nest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUV FLEEING BORDER PATROL FLIPS AT 100MPH!</title>
      <link>http://news4sanantonio.com/news/local/12-immigrants-ejected-4-die-after-car-being-chased-by-border-patrol-crashes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news4sanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIG WELLS, Texas (KABB/WOAI) - Authorities said five undocumented immigrants are dead following a chase involving Border Patrol agents Sunday afternoon. Dimmit County Sheriff Marion Boyd said the crash happened off Highway 85 in Big Wells at about noon. Bo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Eminem keeps 'gunshot' effects, tells fans 'easily freightened shouldn't be here'...</title>
      <link>https://www.delawareonline.com/story/entertainment/firefly/2018/06/17/eminem-ignores-criticism-firefly-its-kind-what-he-does/708388002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delawareonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eminem's manager has defended the sound effect, calling it "pyrotechnic concussion," not a "gunshot" as some have called it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Most Psychopathic States USA...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1307670/us-states-with-the-most-psychopaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Connecticut wins the dubious award of most psychopathic state in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Egos get bigger after meditation, yoga...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1307380/yoga-and-meditation-boost-your-ego-say-psychology-researchers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So much for quieting your inner narcissist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative wins presidency in Colombia, stops leftist rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/D-C-Colombian-squares-off-against-former-13001753.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTA, Colombia - Conservative Ivan Duque captured Colombia's presidency on Sunday, bringing to power a U.S.-educated 41-year old whose victory promises an aggressive new era in the drug war and could upend a historic peace deal that ended Latin America's longest running insurgency. With nearly all the votes counted, Duque held a commanding 54-42 lead. Turnout was 53 percent of voters, higher than in other recent Colombian elections. By winning Sunday's vote, Duque - who spent years studying and working in Washington -- stopped the rise of his leftist opponent, Gustavo Petro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasure-hunters warned to keep pickaxes away after claim lost masterpiece hidden beneath Belgian street...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/ghent-altarpiece-code-solved-gino-marchal-belgium-treasure-dig-holes-kalandeberg-mystic-lamb-a8402156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Do not go to the shopping street with a shovel or spade,’ says Ghent’s mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman shoots husband in testicles after he tries to take air conditioner...</title>
      <link>https://www.actionnewsjax.com/news/local/report-woman-shoots-husband-in-testicles-after-he-tries-to-take-her-air-conditioner/770435073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.actionnewsjax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In October of last year, Kimberly Dunn, 35, shot her ex-husband in the testicles after he tried to take an AC unit, according to an arrest report. Story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Domain jacker' jailed over armed website heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/17/internet-domain-jacker-jailed-20-years-armed-website-heist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has been jailed for 20 years over the first known instance of armed &amp;quot;domain hijacking&amp;quot; in which he sought to gain control of a website at gunpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret rainforest at heart of African volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/17/mozambique-mount-lico-rainforest-new-species</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ‘dream team’ of scientists scaled Mount Lico and found a wealth of new species</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanctions on Russia spotlight threat posed to undersea cables...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/392577-spotlight-falls-on-russian-threat-to-undersea-cables</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New sanctions are highlighting fears Russia could target the telecom cables for espionage or sabotage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Puts Cyberwarriors on Offensive, Increasing Conflict Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/pentagon-puts-cyberwarriors-on-the-offensive-increasing-the-risk-of-conflict/17634489/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Pentagon has quietly empowered the United States Cyber Command to take a far more aggressive approach to defending the nation against cyberattacks, a shift in strategy that could increase the risk of conflict with the foreign states that sponsor malicious hacking groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landon Donovan Blasted By USA Team Members, Fans Over Mexico Support...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2781516-landon-donovan-criticized-by-past-present-usmnt-members-for-supporting-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former U.S. men's national soccer team players have been critical of Landon Donovan , who suggested in a video for Wells Fargo that American soccer fans should support ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUV fleeing Border Patrol crashes; 5 dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.kens5.com/article/news/5-people-die-in-south-texas-pursuit-crash-involving-undocumented-immigrants/273-565118086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kens5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Suburban was being chased by a Dimmit County deputy prior to the crash, the sheriff said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FATHER'S DAY: Bill Clinton 'son' calls for 'dad' to take paternity test...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/fathers-day-bill-clinton-son-calls-for-dad-to-take-paternity-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danney Williams still wants to have a relationship with the man he calls his “dad.” This Father’s Day, Williams, who says Bill Clinton is his father, is backing calls for Clinton to undergo a paternity test to prove — or disprove — his assertion. Retweet! https://t.co/tTArv8DjPM — Danney Williams (@danney_williams) June 17, 2018 “Retweet!” Williams …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
