<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>No school, no trains, no Eiffel Tower: France on strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20191217/france-strikes-flights-trains-and-buses-cancelled-as-another-day-of-protest-planned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French transport strikes enter their 13th day on Tuesday with another round of street protests planned, including a major demo in Paris. Trains, flights and the Paris Metro are all facing disruption on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair together 70 years die minutes apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlive.com/news/jackson/2019/12/after-70-years-of-marriage-couple-dies-minutes-and-inches-apart.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their skills and hobbies complemented one another like the jigsaw puzzles they'd piece together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' grips Hollywood with 'SKYWALKER' premiere...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/star-wars-grips-hollywood-rise-skywalker-premiere-045614863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final film in the epic "Star Wars" trilogy of trilogies brought Hollywood to a standstill, as a galaxy of VIPs from the space saga that began four decades ago descended on a glittering world premiere. Veterans Mark Hamill (Luke Skywalker) and Harrison Ford (Han Solo) arrived Monday to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Set Up Senate Trial Strategy Ahead of Impeachment Vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-set-senate-trial-strategy-090000365.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Democrats are nearing one of the most important decisions in their effort to impeach Donald Trump: Who will bear the historic duty of prosecuting the president in next year’s Senate trial.With the House planning to vote Wednesday on two articles of impeachment against the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brees sets NFL all-time TD mark...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e7755ed40dc1d117c4b37c9752e9e946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Drew Brees trotted along the sideline holding his helmet and a Hall of Fame-bound ball in his left hand while using his right hand to wave and blow kisses to an adoring...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: George launches PAC to fight reelection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/513cab63a1b3317f6342daf888a10763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A small group of President Donald Trump's fiercest conservative critics, including the husband of the president's own chief adviser, is launching a super PAC designed to fight...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope abolishes 'pontifical secret' in clergy sex abuse cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f8380a98bd76c839c7f056088039727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis has abolished the “pontifical secret” used in clergy sexual abuse cases, after mounting criticism that the high degree of confidentiality has been used to protect...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those UFO sightings -- govt believes phenomena might be threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/the-real-reasons-the-us-government-is-so-secretive-about-ufos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years ago Sunday, the New York Times broke the stunning story of a secret Pentagon program to study unidentified flying objects. That story led me to delve into this strange world. I've learned some interesting stuff about UFOs ("unidentified aerial phenomena," or "UAP," as the Pentagon refers…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SMASH NEW RECORDS!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/16/us-futures-point-to-higher-open-on-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks hit record highs as a so-called phase one trade deal between China and the U.S. clears the path higher for Wall Street to end 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Wants Penalties for Social Media 'Hate Speech'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/12/16/justin-trudeau-wants-significant-penalties-for-social-media-hate-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, recently made infamous over resurfaced blackface photos, has instructed his ministers to create new legislation aimed at tackling "hate speech" on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell takes heat from all sides...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/474817-mcconnell-takes-heat-from-all-sides-on-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is under pressure from Senate Democrats, House Republicans and President Trump when it comes to the fraught impeachment trial that is about to take over life in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: The decade of division...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/474764-on-the-trail-the-decade-of-division</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at a decade of decoupling, as generational, economic and racial strife rends the post-Cold War fabric of liberal democracy and an increasingly interconnected world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP THRIVES</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/impeachment-hurts-teflon-trump-thrives-021126355.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment is about the worst thing that can happen to a president -- unless that president is Donald Trump. More than any other occupant of the White House, the real estate developer and reality TV performer obsesses over his image. Trump's name and patina of glitzy success is literally a brand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest married couple celebrate 80th wedding anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtrf.com/news/worlds-oldest-married-couple-celebrate-their-80th-wedding-anniversary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtrf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family and friends of the oldest married couple in the world helped them celebrate yet another major milestone on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tweet gave journalist a seizure. His case brings new meaning to idea of 'online assault'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-tweet-gave-a-journalist-a-seizure-His-case-14911397.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kurt Eichenwald sat down at the desk in his Dallas home office and logged onto Twitter. The prominent journalist and author was used to Internet invective - especially then, in the weeks after he posted a particularly inflammatory tweet about President Donald Trump.  More than 170 notifications awaited him when he signed on that evening, Dec. 15, 2016. But he didn't make it past the first one: A GIF that strobed violently across his computer screen, flashing a red, yellow and blue geometric pattern behind the words "YOU DESERVE A SEIZURE FOR YOUR POSTS."  Within seconds, Eichenwald, who has epilepsy, suffered a seizure. He would have died, he has said, if his wife hadn't walked into the study and found him.  The GIF set off a highly unusual court battle that is expected to equip those in similar circumstances with a new tool for battling threatening trolls and cyberbullies. On Monday, the man who sent Eichenwald the moving image, John Rayne Rivello, was set to appear in a Dallas County district court. A last-minute rescheduling delayed the proceeding until Jan. 31, but Rivello is still expected to plead guilty to aggravated assault. And he may be the first of many.  The Epilepsy Foundation announced on Monday it lodged a sweeping slate of criminal complaints against a legion of copycats who targeted people with epilepsy and sent them an onslaught of strobe GIFs - a frightening phenomenon that unfolded in a short period of time during the organization's marking of National Epilepsy Awareness Month in November.  With Rivello's expected guilty plea, the foundation has a legal road map for fighting back.  "These kinds of attacks need to be taken seriously," Allison Nichol, Epilepsy Foundation's director of legal advocacy told The Washington Post. "There needs to be a very...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Eating chilies cuts risk of heart attack, stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/16/health/eating-chili-pepper-study-scli-intl-scn-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many years, chili has been hailed for its therapeutic properties, and now researchers have found that eating chili peppers regularly can cut the risk of death from heart disease and stroke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor complains his penis was digitally edited out of 'CATS'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/16/jason-derulo-complains-his-anaconda-was-edited-out-of-cats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Andy Cohen's Radio Andy, Jason Derulo and Cohen discussed his large penis being cut out of the movie “Cats.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller's Top Lieutenant Believes Trump Committed Federal Crimes...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/impeachment/robert-muellers-top-lieutenant-trump-committed-federal-crimes-while-in-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian spy ship operating in 'unsafe manner' near U.S. base...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/16/viktor-leonov-russian-spy-ship-operating-unsafe-ma/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian spy ship is conducting operations off the coast of the Eastern United States and has been engaged in unsafe activities near a U.S. nuclear missile submarine base, according to the Coast Guard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEDNESDAY I-DAY?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7799449/Rules-Committee-prepares-bipartisan-warfare-decide-impeachment-vote.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The articles of impeachment have one more stop in the House of Representatives before ending up on the floor: the House Rules Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group of more than 100 doctors warn Assange will die in jail... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7799431/Group-100-doctors-warn-Julian-Assange-die-jail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group has written an open letter to Foreign Minister Marise Payne calling for the 48-year-old to be returned to Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM says will fight misinformation with expanded fact-check...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/instagram-says-fight-misinformation-fact-check-allies-002837134.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instagram on Monday went global in its fight against misinformation, making alliances with fact-checkers around the world to expose deception in shared photos or videos. The Facebook-owned social platform launched a fact-checking program in the US early this year. "Today's expansion is an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screenplay about Barron Trump sabotaging dad's campaign makes 'Black List'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/barron-trump-sabotaging-dad-campaign-screenplay-1203440203/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barron Trump could be coming to the big screen soon, in a wild scripted ride that imagines President Donald Trump’s 10-year-old son attempting to thwart his presidential ambitions. “Bar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPPORT GROWS TO 7%...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2020-democratic-primary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a daily basis, Morning Consult is surveying over 5,000 registered voters on the 2020 presidential election. Each week, we'll update this page with the latest survey data, offering an in-depth guide to how the race for the Democratic nomination is shaping up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurfacing of past sexism claims rocks Bloomberg's bid...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bloomberg-answer-sexist-comments-women-released-ndas-elizabeth/story?id=67764371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren says Michael Bloomberg 'has to answer' for sexist comments and women should be released from their NDAs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for lewd act in WALMART toy section...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/another-vile-walmart-patron-285930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 16--A Florida Man is behind bars on a pair of criminal charges after allegedly committing a lewd act in the toy section of a Walmart, police report. According to investigators, Elias Flor, 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERROR QUEUE: Internet moderators suffer from PTSD...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/12/16/21021005/google-youtube-moderators-ptsd-accenture-violent-disturbing-content-interviews-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They scrub the internet of violent and disturbing content, and it haunts them forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Explore Drug-Free Idea To Relieve Chronic Pain: Green Light...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/12/15/787138928/researchers-explore-a-drug-free-idea-to-relieve-chronic-pain-green-light</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are looking into a surprisingly simple technique that shows promise in easing certain kinds of chronic pain, including migraine headaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Green Burial': Colorado Mulls Legalizing Turning Human Remains Into Soil...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/12/16/green-burial-legalize-turning-human-remains-soil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"'Natural Organic Reduction' involves placing bodies in individual vessels and gently decomposing them into a nutrient-dense soil that can then be returned to families," officials explained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisis extends...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/shutdown-likely-at-boeing-renton-as-737-max-crisis-extends/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boeing board is considering a proposal by management to stop 737 MAX production this week or next and keep the assembly lines closed until the FAA clears the jet to return to commercial service. That is likely to mean...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING suspends MAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/boeing-will-halt-renton-assembly-lines-but-no-layoffs-for-employees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing won't announce any timeline for the production stoppage because it has no control over the jet's return to service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  VOX cuts hundreds of freelance jobs ahead of CA gig economy laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/16/vox-media-to-cut-hundreds-of-freelance-jobs-ahead-of-californias-ab5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vox, which owns the sports site SB Nation, is informing freelancers that they'll be losing their jobs when AB5 kicks in next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders surges ahead of Iowa caucuses...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/474777-sanders-surges-ahead-of-iowa-caucuses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) is rising in the polls ahead of Thursday’s pivotal debate in Los Angeles, reestablishing his standing in the top tier of Democratic contenders with the Iowa caucuses less than 50 days away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-DISNEY star: Porn pays better...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/16/boy-meets-world-star-maitland-ward-i-make-more-money-doing-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porn pays better than Disney, a former actress-turned-adult film star says. Maitland Ward, who rose to fame on ABC/Disney Channel’s “Boy Meets World,” says she makes more money in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Kodak Black Claims He's Being Drugged, Beaten In Prison...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/12/16/south-florida-rapper-kodak-black-claims-drugged-beaten-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Florida rapper Kodak Black is apparently having a tough time in prison and is posting about it on his Instagram account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Giant Tortoises Highly Intelligent, Have Strong Memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/turtle-power-study-finds-giant-tortoises-have-strong-memories-high-intelligence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study suggests that both the overall brain power and memory skills of giant tortoises have been greatly underestimated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurfacing of past sexism claims rocks Bloomberg's bid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/resurfacing-past-sexism-claims-rocks-184855787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bloomberg’s presidential campaign has been rocked by the resurfacing of historic claims that he made sexist and derogatory comments to women, including allegedly urging one to get an abortion. The billionaire was accused in a past lawsuit of telling a female employee who said she was pregnant to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once affordable, Phoenix rents among fastest rising in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae1aed4b8c1303e57fe1ef6b148af222</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Aspen Day-Flynn and her boyfriend, Travis Tolin, were thinking of moving back to her native Washington state this fall when their Phoenix landlord helped give them the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feral Pigs Roam the South. Now Even Northern States Aren't Safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/feral-pigs-roam-the-south-now-even-northern-states-arent-safe/ar-BBY3kGw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY STUNS: 'I needed Yovanovitch out of the way'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/884544/rudy-giuliani-stunningly-admits-needed-yovanovitch-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, that wasn't subtle. In a sweeping article in The New Yorker, focused on Ukraine's former General Prosecutor Yuriy Lutsenko, President's Trump personal lawyer and former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani was pretty open about his plan to get rid of Marie Yovanovitch, the former U.S. ambassador to Ukraine. Lutsenko reportedly wasn't fond of Yovanovitch, whom he felt favored his rival, the head of Ukraine's new anti-corruption bureau. That seemingly made him a good partner for Giuliani, who was launching a campaign to get Kyiv to investigate the actions of some of President Trump's domestic political rivals in Ukraine. Giuliani has widely been viewed as the leading force behind the movement to drive Yovanovitch out of her role because she was seen as an obstacle to his investigation-related plans, and he admitted as much to The New Yorker. This seems quite problematic to Trumpâ€™s defense about ousting Yovanovitch.â€œI believed that I needed Yovanovitch out of the way,â€� Giuliani said. â€œShe was going to make the investigations difficult for everybody.â€�https://t.co/u7IFgGg8jD â€” Andrew Desiderio (@AndrewDesiderio) December 16, 2019 Giuliani then compiled a dossier on Yovanovitch and former Vice President Joe Biden and his son, Hunter, who once served on the board of a Burisma, a Ukrainian gas company at the center of corruption allegations. He went on to coordinate with journalist John Solomon, who interviewed Lutsenko for The Hill, to push the story and force out Yovanovitch. 'I said, 'John, let's make this as prominent as possible,'' Giuliani told The New Yorker. Read more at The New Yorker. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Officials Warn Of 3 Measles Cases At LAX...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/12/16/3-new-measles-cases-reported-at-lax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far in 2019, there have been 34 total measles cases in L.A. County: 20 among residents and another 14 from non-residents who were just passing through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare tax repeal added to $1.4T spending bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/05565ff1986720c70c66c9dd9e23310d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Retired coal miners and longtime opponents of Obama-era taxes on high-cost health plans are eyeing big wins as top congressional leaders and the Trump White House close in on a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN:  Arms sales dramatically up...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/16/putin-russias-arms-sales-increased-dramatically-ye/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economic sanctions haven’t slowed Moscow’s foreign arms sales, Russian President Vladimir Putin said Monday, boasting that his nation’s weapons exports actually increased dramatically in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete raises money from Silicon Valley billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2019/12/13/21021008/pete-buttigieg-reed-hastings-laurene-powell-jobs-sergey-brin-eric-schmidt-fundraiser-palo-alto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The families of Eric Schmidt, Reed Hastings, and Sergey Brin are hosting a fundraiser for Buttigieg on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiorina Calls for Impeaching -- But Doesn't Rule Out 2020 Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/16/carly-fiorina-impeach-trump-vote-2020-086170</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think it is vital that he be impeached," the former Republican presidential candidate told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy Ally Says $1 Million From Russia Was Loan to Wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-12-16/giuliani-ally-says-1-million-moved-from-russia-was-loan-to-wife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone welcome? Gay soccer fans prepare for Qatar...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/everyone-welcome-gay-football-fans-prepare-qatar-024610417--sow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Cup 2022 host Qatar has given the clearest indication yet that LGBT fans will be welcome, engaging with gay supporters as it hosts the Club World Cup -- despite criminalising homosexuality. Organisers of the 2022 soccer spectacle travelled to Britain in recent months to meet Liverpool fan clubs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Poll Stuns 'FOX &amp; FRIENDS' Host...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/foxs-brian-kilmeade-says-hes-stunned-by-fox-news-poll-showing-majority-support-for-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox &amp; Friends co-host Brian Kilmeade told viewers he was "stunned" by a Fox News poll that shows 54 percent support for impeachment, which is all the more stunning considering he misstat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop Denounces NETFLIX as 'Blasphemous' over Gay Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/faith/2019/12/16/bishop-denounces-netflix-as-blasphemous-over-gay-jesus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catholic bishop of Tyler, Texas, denounced Netflix over its Christmas Special The First Temptation of Christ portraying a gay Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  West Point investigating 'white power' hand signs by cadets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/west-point-investigating-white-power-hand-signs-cadets-154144894.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Military Academy at West point said Monday it is investigating the apparent display of "white power" hand gestures by cadets this weekend during the nationally televised annual Army-Navy football game. "The US Military Academy is fully committed to developing leaders of character</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Activist Greta Goes Hollywood With New Movie: Was Her Rise Planned?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/greta-thunberg-documentary-hulu-greta-climate-crisis-b-reel-films-nathan-grossman-1202810111/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Sixteen-year-old Swedish climate activist Greta Thunberg is the subject of Greta (working title), an original documentary, which will premiere on Hulu in 2020. The  documentary is produc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  President's supporters in full revolt against media...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/15/trump-supporters-revolt-against-media-pew-research/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has broken the press in America, according to an analysis by the Pew Research Center, that found that while Democrats continue to have faith in American media, Mr. Trump’s followers are quite done with it all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy shakes free of recession fears in striking turnaround...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/u-s-economy-shakes-free-of-recession-fears-in-striking-turnaround-since-august/ar-AAK9ByW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court:  Homeless can sleep on sidewalks!</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-12-16/supreme-court-lets-stand-ruling-that-protects-homeless-who-sleep-on-sidewalk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court lets stand a ruling that says homeless people have a right to sleep on the streets if a city doesn't have enough shelters to house them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man faces seventh trial on same murder charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bond-hearing-for-man-tried-6-times-in-killings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge was being asked to set bond Monday for a Mississippi man waiting to hear whether prosecutors will try him a seventh time in a quadruple slaying 23 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homebuilder confidence best in 20 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/16/homebuilder-confidence-jumps-to-highest-level-in-20-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Builder confidence in the newly built, single-family home market jumped 5 points in December to 76, the highest reading since June 1999.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Escalates Showdown With U.S. Over Trade Rules Enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-12-16/mexico-escalates-showdown-with-u-s-over-trade-rules-enforcement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds bust illegal streaming site that boasts more content than NETFLIX, AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/474692-fbi-busts-illegal-streaming-site-with-more-content-than-netflix-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two programmers pleaded guilty to copyright charges in association with two illegal streaming services, including one site that had more content than Netflix, Hulu and Amazon Prime, according to the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress poised to ban tobacco sales to anyone under 21...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/474711-congress-set-to-ban-tobacco-sales-to-anyone-under-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress appears poised to permanently prohibit the sale of tobacco to anyone under the age of 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREGG:  Trump is conservative in name only...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/474661-judd-gregg-trump-is-a-conservative-in-name-only</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPINION: The president does not care about ideology, only loyalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's 199 wildest lines of 2019!</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2019/12/16/politics/trump-top-lines-2019/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man, what a decade!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remain in Mexico has 0.1% asylum grant rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2019-12-15/remain-in-mexico-has-a-0-01-percent-asylum-grant-rate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been almost a year since the government began sending asylum seekers back to Mexico and only 11 people have been granted asylum. That accounts for a grant rate of less than one percent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FBI Chief Assails Trump 'Slur' on Bureau...</title>
      <link>https://thecrimereport.org/2019/12/16/ex-fbi-chief-webster-assails-trumps-slur-on-bureau/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thecrimereport.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI's integrity is "tragically, under assault from too many people whose job it should be to protect" it, says former FBI and CIA director William Webster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India protests rage over 'anti-Muslim' law...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-protests-rage-over-anti-muslim-law-082940594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh protests rocked India on Monday as anger grew over new citizenship legislation slammed as anti-Muslim, after six people died in the northeast and up to 200 were injured in New Delhi. Critics say it is part of Prime Minister Narendra Modi's Hindu nationalist agenda to marginalise the 200-million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, GOOGLE Named in Lawsuit Over Child-Mining Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2019/dec/16/apple-and-google-named-in-us-lawsuit-over-congolese-child-cobalt-mining-deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dell, Microsoft and Tesla also among tech firms named in case brought by families of children killed or injured while mining in DRC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What would Sanders presidency really look like?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/12/16/bernie-sanders-first-100-days-president-white-house-administration-084447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could happen, really. Vice President Warren is being considered, and plans are in the works to de-Trumpify immigration and climate. Much less likely: Medicare for All.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JEWELL' Disaster at Boxoffice...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/clint-eastwoods-richard-jewell-jailed-by-fan-apathy-not-controversy-1262856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biographical drama marks a near-worst career opening for the prolific director.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots with facial recognition pick customers out of crowd...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-recognise-humans-using-21102122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: RealDoll revealed at an event attended by Daily Star Online that it is producing models with facial recognition allowing them to pick out customers in a crowded room</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: HALLMARK Channel Reinstates Ads Featuring Lesbian Wedding After Outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hallmark-channel-same-sex-couple-ad-reinstate-commercials-after-outcry-2019-12-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unclear whether Zola will continue airing ads on the The Hallmark Channel, but they noted they are "relieved" by these recent updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump slams debate commission, raising questions about his participation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/474693-trump-slams-debate-commission-raising-questions-about-his</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday hammered the Commission on Presidential Debates, raising questions about his participation in debates next year with the eventual Democratic presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year-end legislative blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/not-just-impeachment-democrats-plan-year-end-legislative-blitz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wary of polls showing battleground state voters are frowning on the impeachment effort in Congress, House Democrats plan a legislative blitz this week they’ll be able to tout when they return home for the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bribery, Wire Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/16/judiciary-committee-impeachment-report-trump-committed-multiple-federal-crimes-086096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 169-page report makes the case for Trump's removal from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>658-page impeachment report...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/house-judiciary-committee-publishes-full-impeachment-report-n1102531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In making its case that President Donald Trump abused his power and obstructed Congress, the committee concludes, "President Trump has realized the Framers' worst nightmare."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 99% of biggest firms paid no federal tax at all...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/2018-corporate-tax-rate-plunged-to-11-3-under-14909295.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 400 of America's largest corporations paid an average federal tax rate of about 11 percent on their profits last year, about half the official rate established under President Donald Trump's tax law of 2017, according to a report released Monday.  The 2017 GOP tax law lowered the U.S. corporate tax rate to 21 percent from 35 percent, but in practice large companies often pay far less than that due to deductions, tax breaks, and other loopholes.  In the first year Trump's tax law was in effect, the actual amount corporations paid in federal taxes on their incomes - their so-called "effective rate" - was an average of 11.3 percent, likely its lowest level in more than three decades, according to a report by the Institute of Taxation and Economic Policy, a left-leaning think tank.  From 2008 to 2015, under the previous tax code, corporations paid on average an effective rate of about 21 percent, according to ITEP's prior research.  The report also found that 91 corporations in the Fortune 500, many worth billions of dollars, paid no federal taxes at all last year.  "When drafting the tax law, lawmakers could have eliminated special breaks and loopholes in the corporate tax to offset the cost of reducing the statutory rate," the report says. "Instead, the new law introduced many new breaks and loopholes, though it eliminated some old ones."  ITEP looked at the 379 companies in the Fortune 500 that were profitable in 2018 and provided enough information to calculate their tax rates. Researchers excluded taxes incurred by corporations under a one-time "repatriation tax" on money they brought back from overseas due to the tax law, according to Matt Gardner, an analyst at ITEP.  The findings come amid an explosion in the federal deficit, which this year rose to close to $1...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC BRACED FOR BATTLE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-braces-historic-impeachment-clouding-090000374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s likely impeachment this week adds a permanent stain to a presidency plagued by unrelenting turmoil and partisan rancor, while aggravating U.S. political divisions as he starts his fight for re-election.The House is all but certain to deliver the formal rebuke in a vote on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust architect's grave dug up in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/holocaust-architects-grave-dug-berlin-134240972.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grave of a top Nazi who helped plan the Holocaust and was assassinated by British-trained agents during World War II has been dug up in Berlin, German police said on Monday. The grave of Reinhard Heydrich was "dug up in the night between Wednesday and Thursday" and an investigation has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person Found Dead Inside Port-A-Potty At RAVENS Stadium...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/12/15/body-found-m-t-bank-stadium-ravens-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating after a person was found dead inside a porta-potty near M&amp;T Bank Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolstering case, Dems say Trump betrayed nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cebb308b1c7bd81e715da5d2bd51a47a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Bolstering its case for impeaching President Donald Trump, a House panel released a lengthy report Monday detailing its rationale for the charges and accusing Trump of betraying...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
