<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Top intel officials say Al Qaeda rebuilding for USA attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/sep/14/al-qaeda-rebuilding-us-attacks-one-two-years-cia-d/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defeat of the American-backed government in Afghanistan has increased the danger that the al Qaeda terrorist group will launch another attack on the United States very quickly, the director of the Defense Intelligence Agency said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Jassy: 'Still early days for us in media'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/amazon-ceo-andy-jassy-its-still-early-days-for-us-in-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one of his first interviews since ascending to the CEO role, Amazon's Andy Jassy said the company has big ambitions in media and entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  General Milley thought Trump had declined mentally in aftermath of election... MORE</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/14/fears-that-trump-might-launch-a-strike-prompted-general-to-reassure-china-book-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff twice called his Chinese counterpart in the final months of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers in CO Could Face Criminal Charges If Don't Enforce Mask Mandate; Punishable By Prison...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/09/14/tri-county-health-teachers-could-face-criminal-charges-if-they-dont-enforce-school-mask-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some parents are planning to sue Tri-County Health Department over its mask mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarborough Hits Republicans Crying Fraud:  What whiners...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/scarborough-msnbc-larry-elder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC morning host says claiming fraud and being "losers" is now just part of Republicans' election "strategy"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spyware firm targeted APPLE devices via iMessage, researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/sep/13/nso-group-iphones-apple-devices-hack-patch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discovery was shared with Apple, which on Monday released a patch to fix the vulnerability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNET KILLED THE VIDEO STAR:  MTV Music Awards Draws Less Than Million Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/14/mtvs-video-music-awards-scored-less-than-a-million-viewers-on-mtv-and-not-much-more-anywhere-else</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know things are bad when MTV’s Video Music Awards barely score ratings on MTV. Sunday’s show had 900,000 viewers on the main channel, and a smattering elsewhere on channels like VH1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Senate Dems strike deal with Manchin on voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-senate-democrats-get-deal-with-manchin-on-voting-rights/ar-AAOqKLZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Senior Senate Democrats have reached agreement with moderate Senator Joe Manchin on a broad overhaul of U.S. voting rights law, a development that should unify all Democrats in the chamber behind a single plan for the first time. The measure would create an automatic voter registration system through each state’s motor vehicle agency, make Election Day a public holiday and provide voters with at least 15 days of early voting for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAVED BY ELDER?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/14/politics/larry-elder-covid-newsom-recall/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this year, when California Gov. Gavin Newsom was searching for the right message to convince disengaged Democrats to vote against the effort to oust him in Tuesday's recall election, it would have been impossible to imagine a more perfect foil than conservative talk radio host Larry Elder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 BODIES FOUND IN CREEPY WISCONSIN CORN FIELD; SITTING IN BLACK SUV...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnd.com/news/nation-world/national/article254229133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s like something out of a horror movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hand Sanitizer Poisoning In Children On Rise; Kids Getting Drunk...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/09/13/moon-township-elementary-school-hand-sanitizer-poisoning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Moon Township mother has a warning for every parent out there about hand sanitizer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why TV Producers Are STILL Betting on Broadcast in Streaming Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/can-broadcast-tv-survive-in-the-streaming-era-these-shows-are-betting-on-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of another fall TV season, showrunners tell TheWrap what it's like to launch a new broadcast series in a world dominated by Netflix</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANDSLIDE?</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/newsom-is-up-big-in-california-heres-why-pundits-got-fooled-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In today’s climate, motivating the base isn’t enough to win on enemy turf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reputed Colombo crime family boss among a dozen mobsters snared in bust... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/investigations/reputed-nyc-mob-boss-among-a-dozen-snared-in-fraud-corruption-bust-sources/3270937/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD and FBI arrested a dozen alleged mobsters, including a reputed Colombo crime family boss, early Tuesday on charges connected to healthcare fraud allegations and union-related corruption, law enforcement sources said. The arrests, which sources say include reputed 87-year-old Colombo street boss Andrew Russo, also known as “Mush,” and an underboss, 83-year-old Benjamin “Benji” Castellazzo, were conducted in the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man pulled from BMW in Manhattan carjacking...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/driver-pulled-from-bmw-assaulted-and-robbed-in-manhattan-carjacking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police were searching for a group of motorcyclists who carjacked and assaulted a man driving a BMW in Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm leaves Texas town underwater...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/live-news/live-tropical-storm-nicholas-updates-texas-louisiana-flooding/1016769</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic drone images show the town of Seabrook, Texas, surrounded by storm surge after Nicholas made landfall early Tuesday. Plus, hundreds of thousands were without power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecution witness in Netanyahu trial killed in plane crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/prosecution-witness-in-netanyahu-trial-and-his-wife-killed-in-greek-plane-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haim Geron was a former deputy director of the Communication Ministry; light plane he was piloting went down after apparent technical fault</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poverty Rate Rose From 60-Year Low, Incomes Fell Amid Virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-poverty-rate-rose-from-60-year-low-incomes-fell-amid-virus/ar-AAOqYyk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. household income fell in 2020 while the national poverty rate rose from a 60-year low as the Covid-19 pandemic upended the U.S. economy and threw millions out of work. Median, inflation-adjusted household income decreased 2.9% last year to $67,521 according to annual data released Tuesday by the U.S. Census Bureau. The poverty rate rose one percentage point to 11.4% after having dropped for five straight years and reaching...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada's 'Mad Max' stokes anti-vax rage -- and could help Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914141144-0bh3k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANADA-ELECTION/BERNIER (PIX):Canada's 'Mad Max' stokes anti-vax rage - and could help Trudeau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists Smoking Toad Venom in Mexico Hipster Town Tulum...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx53e5/tourists-are-now-smoking-toad-venom-in-mexicos-hipster-town-tulum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Observers are split on the consequences of “speed-toading” using the venom, called bufo, as a cure for the ills of the modern world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Enyart, Anti-Vax 'Real Science Radio' Host, Dies of COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bob-enyart-anti-vax-real-science-radio-host-dies-of-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Denver radio personality was also known for "gleefully" mocking those who died from AIDS on his defunct TV show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Unmanned Vessel Spotted In San Diego Bay...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42358/this-mysterious-unmanned-vessel-was-just-spotted-in-san-diego-bay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The low-slung drone-ship catamaran is equipped with solar panels, various antennae, and camera systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Warships Sailing Near Alaska; Shadowed By Coast Guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42352/chinese-warships-sailing-near-alaskas-aleutian-islands-shadowed-by-u-s-coast-guard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pictures of the Chinese vessels off Alaska emerged after criticism of similar American naval activity from one of China's main state media outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAY OR GO?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-california-climate-elections-a590782877be099d44f1766b2d138394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONG BEACH, Calif. (AP) — After a year of debate that laid bare divisions in America's most populous state, Californians on Tuesday will be deciding whether Gov. Gavin Newsom keeps his job, or if the state goes in a more conservative direction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving biggest name for last, Biden joins Newsom to campaign on eve of recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/saving-the-biggest-name-for-last-biden-joins-newsom-to-campaign-on-eve-of-recall/ar-AAOpbpt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two campaigned on covid-19 restrictions as the key to ending the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gavin team: No scenario where we lose...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/newsom-team-no-scenario-where-we-lose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom's team seems to be striking a confident tone just a day before Tuesday's California recall election, and said that there's no "scenario where we lose."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian Jim Breuer won't perform at venues requiring vax...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/572113-comedian-jim-breuer-wont-perform-at-venues-requiring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Jim Breuer says he's "absolutely not" performing shows at venues that require proof of COVID-19 vaccinations, calling the public health measures "segregation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overeating doesn't cause obesity? Scientists claim all about what you're eating...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/overeating-doesnt-cause-obesity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team adds that despite years of public health messaging about eating less and exercising more, cases of obesity continue to rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Order Sparks Price-Gouging for Fake Vax Cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/joe-biden-mandate-sparks-price-gouging-for-fake-vax-cards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s clear to us they’re using current events to galvanize the market,” researchers at cybersecurity firm Check Point found, said spokesperson Ekram Ahmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran could build nuke in month?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3657650/iran-month-away-from-building-first-nuclear-bomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN is a “month away” from having enough lethal uranium to build a nuclear bomb in a chilling threat to the West, experts claim. Tehran is closer than ever to reaching bomb-grade level…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrifying tale of prostitute orangutan chained to bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3657105/prostitute-orangutan-pony-tragic-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHAINED to a wall and lying on a dirty mattress with a full face of make-up, Pony the orangutan waited for her next client. Men working in the nearby palm oil farm in Borneo would come into the bro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$3,586,456,000,000: Federal Tax Collections Set Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/3586456000000-federal-tax-collections-set-record-through</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government collected a record $3,586,456,000,000 in total taxes through first eleven months of fiscal 2021 (September through August), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer price index rises 5.3% in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/consumer-price-index-august-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consumer price index was expected to increase 5.4% from a year ago in August, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fence back up...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/571981-capitol-fence-is-going-back-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fence surrounding the U.S. Capitol is set to return ahead of the pro-Trump rally on Sept. 18, the head of the Capitol Police confirmed Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400,000 without power...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914103355-vgwdg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-NICHOLAS/CENTERPOINT-POWER (URGENT):Storm Nicholas knocks out power to over 400,000 customers in Texas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians to decide gov's fate... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914095923-0szuz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-RECALL/ (PIX, TV):Californians to decide governor's fate in Republican-backed recall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Thirds of Businesses Around World Struggling to Hire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/two-thirds-of-businesses-around-the-world-are-struggling-to-hire/ar-AAOpHcP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Businesses around the world want to hire but face a similar dilemma: attracting workers. A survey of nearly 45,000 employers across 43 countries showed 69% of employers reported difficulty filling roles, a 15-year high, according to employment-services provider ManpowerGroup Inc. At the same time, 15 countries -- focused in Europe and North America -- reported their highest hiring intentions since the survey began in 1962....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man roams Galveston beach dressed as 'HALLOWEEN' Michael Myers...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/halloween-michael-myers-tropical-storm-nicholas-galveston-beach-costume/11018578/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh, you know, no big deal. Just Michael Myers roaming Galveston beach as a hurricane heads toward Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human remains found inside 504-pound gator suspected in Ida attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sunherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article254213953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sunherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities captured the animal early Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deaths of despair' worsen among Americans lacking college degrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/deaths-of-despair-worsen-among-americans-lacking-college-degrees/ar-AAOoWKl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the U.S., a four-year degree is increasingly a “talisman” against deaths related to suicide and economic hardship, according to a new research paper that offers a stark verdict on the current economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin self-isolates after Covid cases in inner circle...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210914-putin-self-isolates-after-covid-cases-in-inner-circle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin self-isolates after Covid cases in inner circle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Palm Reader Launches at Ampitheatre in Sneak Peek of Biometric Future...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/amazons-palm-reader-launches-at-first-non-amazon-venue-1847670790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Red Rocks Amphitheatre in Denver will use the new tech for ticketed events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving biggest name for last, Biden joins Newsom to campaign on eve of recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/saving-the-biggest-name-for-last-biden-joins-newsom-to-campaign-on-eve-of-recall/ar-AAOpbpt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two campaigned on covid-19 restrictions as the key to ending the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch rebuilding entertainment empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/fox-chief-charlie-collier-revamps-the-murdochs-empire-adds-tmz/ar-AAOoXQL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the big sale to Disney, Fox is adding pieces for a new mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT THE PUCK?  New Media Startup Treats Reporters Like Social Media Influencers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-09-13/a-new-media-startup-treats-reporters-like-social-media-influencers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Puck was founded by four media veterans in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicki Minaj Bolts Met Gala Over Vaxx Requirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/nicki-minaj-not-vaxxed-met-gala-1225492/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If I get vaccinated it won’t [be] for the Met. It’ll be once I feel I’ve done enough research. I’m working on that now,” she wrote on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Too Much Screen Time Not So Bad For Kids After All...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/screen-time-not-bad-for-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;School-aged children who spend lots of time staring at digital screens tend to have more close friends, the study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-ROLLING STONES Manager Dies In Freak Accident Digging Grave For Pet Dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/former-rolling-stones-tour-manager-dies-after-accident-while-digging-grave-for-dog-in-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mick Brigden has been mourned by many in the music industry, including his longtime client Joe Satriani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers May Be a Force...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/farmers-may-be-a-force-in-california-recall-election/ar-AAOoAnQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Craig Gordon, the owner of several dairy farms near Los Angeles, is a lifelong Democrat. He supported Senator Bernie Sanders for president, he doesn’t like former President Donald J. Trump and he voted for Gov. Gavin Newsom in 2018. But lately, he said, high taxes on milk, coronavirus shutdowns that have cut into his sales and state-imposed limitations on water for agriculture have made him so angry at Mr. Newsom that he has paid for seven...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pool of water near Dead Sea turns blood red...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/pool-of-water-near-dead-sea-turns-blood-red-authorities-investigating-679278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geologists believe the red color of the pool near the Dead Sea may be caused by algae, iron oxide or added chemicals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington ramps up security...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/572033-washington-ramps-up-security-ahead-of-sept-18-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking no chances, Capitol Police and other law enforcement officials are ramping up security measures ahead of Saturday’s rally in Washington to support the pro-Trump insurrectionists who attacked the Capitol earlier in the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA experts oppose...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-coronavirus-pandemic-science--38544e89b9dba06d49a800189c3ed42d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average person doesn’t need a COVID-19 booster yet, an international group of scientists — including two top U.S. regulators — wrote Monday in a scientific journal. The experts reviewed studies of the vaccines' performance and concluded the shots are working well despite the extra-contagious delta variant, especially against severe disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once inmates, Taliban now in charge in Kabul prison...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prisons-afghanistan-kabul-taliban-a3de341dd61a335f4d6d711c38d71e4b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL (AP) — Once, Kabul’s main prison was crowded with thousands of Taliban captured and arrested by the government. On Monday, a Taliban commander strolled through its empty halls and cell blocks, showing his friends where he had once been imprisoned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ sold to FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/13/media/tmz-sold-fox-entertainment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TMZ will now be a part of Fox Entertainment, the companies announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US budget deficit rises to $2.71 trillion through August...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-7a2fc48cf977988d3cd580ac84a51de5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. budget deficit rose to $2.71 trillion through August, on track to be the second largest shortfall in history due to trillions of dollars in COVID relief. In its monthly budget report, the Treasury Department said Monday that the deficit for the first 11 months of this budget year is 9.9% less than the imbalance during the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharon Osbourne reveals months of ketamine therapy after 'constant death threats'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9978409/Sharon-Osbourne-betrayed-hosts-following-secret-pact-underwent-ketamine-therapy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharon Osbourne sat down exclusively with DailyMailTV for her first in-depth interview since her shock exit from The Talk this year amid controversy over purported racist comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC broadens antitrust suit against AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/572008-dc-broadens-antitrust-lawsuit-against-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;District of Columbia Attorney General Karl Racine (D) on Monday expanded the antitrust lawsuit he filed against Amazon in May, accusing the e-commerce giant of locking first-party sellers into anti-competitive agreements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS' test data left on open web...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22623871/walgreens-covid-test-site-data-vulnerability</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people got Covid-19 tests through Walgreens. Their information wasn’t adequately protected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French far-right pundit edges closer to presidential bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210913-french-far-right-pundit-edges-closer-to-presidential-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French far-right pundit edges closer to presidential bid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban scientists reject 'Havana Syndrome' claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210913-cuban-scientists-reject-havana-syndrome-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban scientists reject 'Havana Syndrome' claims</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani denies being drunk during rambling 9/11 speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9985471/Rudy-Giuliani-says-NOT-drunk-rambling-September-11th-speech-Cipriani.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Mayor Rudy Giuliani denied accusations he was drunk during a speech at Cipriani on the anniversary of 9/11 where he mimicked the British accent of the Queen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Keefe says hackers scammed PROJECT VERITAS out of $165,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/project-of-veritas-says-hackers-scammed-it-out-of-165000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project Veritas announced on Monday that it was scammed out of $165,000 after being targeted by hackers who impersonated lawyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Sign of Presidency Becoming Monarchy...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/13/bidens-vaccine-mandate-is-the-latest-sign-of-the-presidency-becoming-a-monarchy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidency has always been inclined to unilateral power—and many Americans like it that way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA National Guard Activated -- Over School Bus Driver Shortage!</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/13/massachusetts-national-guard-activated-school-bus-driver-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts National Guard has been activated to help with the state's shortage of school bus drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected Reason AZ Mask Mandate Ban May Be Unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/13/1036455622/the-unexpected-reason-arizonas-mask-mandate-ban-may-be-unconstitutional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaf through the most recent Arizona budget, and you'll find everything from a mask mandate ban to voting restrictions. A new lawsuit says those aren't budget items; they are political horse-trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Syrian War Criminal, Double Agent Disappeared in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/09/20/how-a-syrian-war-criminal-and-double-agent-disappeared-in-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the bloody civil war, Khaled al-Halabi switched sides. But what country does he really serve?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
