<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians Won't Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9507317/The-Kardashians-NOT-hit-campaign-trail-Caitlyn-Jenner-announced-bid-Governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not a single member of the Kardashian klan has spoken out about Jenner's run over a day after she formally announced her campaign Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran fuel tanker attacked off Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210424-iran-fuel-tanker-attacked-off-syria</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran fuel tanker attacked off Syria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early front-runners like Yang usually win NYC mayoral primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/24/politics/nyc-mayoral-race-analysis/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York City Democratic mayoral primary is now less than two months away, on June 22. The polls indicate that businessman and former 2020 presidential candidate Andrew Yang continues to hold a clear lead in the first New York City mayoral election being held under ranked choice voting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala skillfully running silent and deep...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/549369-kamala-harris-skillfully-running-silent-and-deep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When immersed in turbulent political waters, experienced politicians know to hold their cards to their chests and consider all obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world isolates. A New Zealand band plays to 50,000 fans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-health-music-sports-arts-and-entertainment-13fbb155e4796d07c239030af7a7c6c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand (AP) — Singer Matiu Walters grinned as he gazed out over 50,000 damp but delirious fans and said those magic words: “So, what’s up Eden Park?” While much of the world remains hunkered down, the band Six60 has been playing to huge crowds in New Zealand, where social distancing isn't required after the nation stamped out the coronavirus. The band’s tour finale on Saturday night was billed as the largest concert in the world since the pandemic began. Equally momentous for a band which met while playing rugby at university was getting to play the first concert ever held at the storied Eden Park rugby stadium. And finding themselves at the apex of world music came as a twist for Six60, which has enjoyed unparalleled success in New Zealand but whose forays abroad have ended without the breakthroughs they sought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden will close first chapter of presidency before sparse crowd - and with historic backdrop...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Biden-will-close-the-first-chapter-of-his-16125959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - For eight years, Joe Biden was a fixture at President Barack Obama's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling to stay afloat, people turn to strangers online for help...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/Struggling-to-stay-afloat-during-the-pandemic-16126025.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - It took Josh Mitchell weeks to convince his sister to let him set up a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes before Trump left office, millions of Pentagon's dormant IP addresses sprang to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Minutes-before-Trump-left-office-millions-of-the-16126007.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - While the world was distracted with President Donald Trump leaving office on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornadoes, hail and stunning skies make for unforgettable Texas storm chase...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Tornadoes-hail-and-stunning-skies-make-for-16126049.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WICHITA FALLS, Texas - I've stalked tornadoes, floods, solar eclipses and hurricanes; my...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIA SOS</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-56870410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients are dying because of a lack of medical oxygen supplies, doctors warn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest space station crowd in decade after SPACEX arrival...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-53d48c39d1dfaa941dea519a9199aa3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The International Space Station's population swelled to 11 on Saturday with the jubilant arrival of SpaceX's third crew capsule in less than a year. It's the biggest crowd up there in more than a decade. All of the astronauts — representing the U.S., Russia, Japan and France — managed to squeeze into camera view for a congratulatory call from the leaders of their space agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volatile and Vengeful: How Scott Rudin Wielded Power in Show Business...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/volatile-and-vengeful-how-scott-rudin-wielded-power-in-show-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Rudin has long been one of the most celebrated and powerful producers in Hollywood and, especially, on Broadway —</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrorism Fears Feed Rise of France's Extreme Right...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/terrorism-fears-feed-the-rise-of-frances-extreme-right/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — “Marine Le Pen does not have to say anything,” said Alain Frachon, a former editor of the French</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Arms Merchant in  Sights of Russia's Elite Assassination Squad...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/the-arms-merchant-in-the-sights-of-russias-elite-assassination-squad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a major arms merchant, Emilian Gebrev cuts the modest figure of a bemused grandfather, preferring soccer jerseys and polo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London protest: Thousands march in fury over lockdown and vaccine passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1427536/london-news-protest-oxford-street-vaccine-passport-lockdown-police-breaking-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of protestors have gathered in central London this afternoon to object to the continued lockdown measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists probe mysterious melting of Earth's crust...</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-04/uow-spm042221.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unusual belt of igneous rocks stretches for over 2,000 miles from British Columbia, Canada, to Sonora, Mexico, running through Idaho, Montana, Nevada, southeast California and Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk warns 'people will probably die' during SPACEX mission to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-warns-people-probably-23974161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk told Peter Diamandis people will "probably die" during Space X's Mars mission but claimed that it will be "an amazing experience" for voyagers, calling the trip a "glorious adventure"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash Over 'Gov Jenner'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9506971/Caitlyn-Jenner-faces-backlash-LGBTQ-community-bid-Californias-governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jenner, 71, announced her run on social media Friday under the slogan 'Caitlyn For California' sparking an instant backlash on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Investor Reveals Secret to Success: Shrooms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/billionaire-investor-reveals-secret-success-184839538.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/Andreas Rentz/GettyGerman investor Christian Angermayer—a 42-year-old billionaire who bears a not-negligible resemblance to Jared Leto in Blade Runner 2049—has made a fortune betting on a host of sci-fi-sounding finance fads. Among them: space travel, crypto, psychedelics, movies, weed, SPACs, and “life extension.”Those ventures have done pretty well for him. In the past year alone, seven companies Angermayer’s family office funded went public, raising a combined $1 billion; another 10 companies are slated to issue IPOs this year, according to Bloomberg Wealth. But in a recent profile, Angermayer cited a single experience as having paved the way for his billions: doing hallucinogenic mushrooms.When the investor Zoomed with Bloomberg last month, he called in from his home in London, where he’d hung an “ancient statue of Hecate, the Greek goddess of witchcraft, in the background.” From there, Angermayer detailed his conversion from life-long straight-edge to something out of a Phish festival, after a revelatory chat with a neuroscientist eight years prior.Sean Hannity Drops $5 Million on Mansion Near Mar-a-LagoAngermayer said the doctor confirmed his instinct to avoid hard drugs, but suggested psilocybin mushrooms were less dangerous than other vices, like alcohol. British researcher David Nutt, for example, published a chart of drugs ranked by harmfulness, which lists alcohol at the top and shrooms dead last.When Angermayer went on a trip to the Caribbean with some close friends in 2015, he gave shrooms a try. The experience, the billionaire said, “was the single most meaningful thing I’ve done in my whole life.”In the ego death of his hallucinations, Angermayer “finally understood Bitcoin.”The Bloomberg piece describes Angermayer as “a German version of Chamath Palihapitiya, the serial SPAC-dealmaker who views himself as the Warren Buffett of the Reddit era.” And like Palihapitiya, the billionaire has been bullish on SPACs or “special purpose acquisition companies”—the blank-check companies that soared in popularity early this year, drawing warnings from the SEC and financial advisers. One of Angermayer’s is looking to raise some $200 million.Investigators to Elon Musk: Instead of Tweeting, Give Us Crash DataHe has also gotten involved in some murky corporate deals. Last summer, Angermayer collected multimillion-dollar fees for brokering a Softbank deal with the German financial company Wirecard, not long after the latter collapsed and was accused of widespread fraud. A friend whom Angermayer had helped get a board position at Deutsche Bank AG was later served with a criminal complaint for charges related to the Wirecard scandal.On Tuesday, one of Angermayer’s investments filed for an IPO. It was a company called Atai Life Sciences–a biotech company backed by Palantir co-founder Peter Thiel, the guy who paid for Hulk Hogan to sue Gawker into non-existence. The firm, valued at $2 billion, focuses on psychedelics.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARLEY Unleashes the Silent E-Hogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/harley-unleashes-the-silent-e-hogs/ar-BB1g04yW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company is all-in on electric motorcycles, though the financial gearing still isn’t great.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani, Lindell win Razzies for worst film performances...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/trump-supporters-giuliani-lindell-win-razzies-for-worst-film-performances-666196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Mayor Rudy Giuliani's unwitting appearance in "Borat Subsequent Moviefilm" was named one of the year's worst performances by voters for the annual Razzie prizes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Hunt for Ways Around Tax Hikes They Were Warned About...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-04-24/rich-americans-hunt-for-ways-around-tax-hikes-they-were-warned-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Joe Biden and state lawmakers target millionaires and billionaires, wealth advisers are trying to help their clients adapt to the new rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn after being misgendered on 'THE VIEW': 'Bigger issues than pronouns'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/550093-caitlyn-jenner-on-being-misgendered-by-the-view-co-host-california-has-bigger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner responded to "The View" co-host Joy Behar after the daytime talk show figure repeatedly misgendered her on Friday, telling her not to "sweat it" and focusing instead on her gubernatorial bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro says military would follow his orders to take streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210424011831-g1ikl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/BOLSONARO:Brazil's Bolsonaro says military would follow his orders to take the streets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Approval Rating Has Fallen. He Could Still Win Re-Election...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/cuomos-approval-rating-has-fallen-he-could-still-win-re-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo of New York has not had much good news over the past few months. His poll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of the cave: French isolation study ends after 40 days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-health-science-environment-and-nature-caves-82c18f720f0e08962191ddb68e2eeb39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOMBRIVES CAVE, France (AP) — Ever wonder what it would feel like to unplug from a hyperconnected world and hide away in a cave for a few weeks? Fifteen people in France found out. After 40 days in voluntary isolation in a dark, damp and vast cave, eight men and seven women who took part in a scientific experiment emerged Saturday from their self-segregation in the Pyrenees. With big smiles on their pale faces, the 15 participants exited the Lombrives cave to a round of applause and basked in the light of day while wearing special glasses to protect their eyes after so long in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza militants fire rockets after clashes flare in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/24/gaza-militants-fire-rockets-after-clashes-flare-in-jerusalem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rockets seen as response to unrest in mostly Palestinian east Jerusalem, including far-right Jewish groups chanting ‘death to Arabs’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those who got covid between doses urge caution: 'We were so close'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Those-who-got-covid-between-vaccine-doses-urge-16125805.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abbey Quinn regrets the Easter dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia may label Navalny opposition networks extremists groups. Even T-shirts outlawed?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Russia-may-label-Navalny-s-opposition-networks-as-16125797.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - A closed-door Moscow court hearing Monday is expected to officially ban the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As pandemic surges anew, global envy and anger over U.S. vax abundance...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/As-pandemic-surges-anew-global-envy-and-anger-16125800.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As India announced a grim records - the highest daily coronavirus infection tallies in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon UFO report: They 'acknowledged the reality,' whistleblower says...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/24/pentagon-ufo-report-its-a-reality-whistleblower-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US government is gearing up to share the “reality” of UFOs with the public — and not a moment too soon, says the man who claims to have run the Pentagon’s UFO program for 9 ye…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacKenzie Scott Gave Away Billions. The Scam Artists Followed...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/24/mackenzie-scott-gave-away-billions-the-scam-artists-followed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danielle Churchill needed help. She was raising five children in Wollongong, on the Australian coast south of Sydney, and had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With most adults now vaccinated, Israelis are busting loose...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/with-most-adults-now-vaccinated-israelis-are-busting-loose/ar-BB1fSzTN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People are having a ball. People at the beaches … it’s like, wow!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA weighs ban on menthol cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fda-weighs-ban-on-menthol-cigarettes-which-disproportionately-addict-e2-80-94-and-kill-e2-80-94-black-americans/ar-BB1fQIa3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Menthol cigarettes are more addictive and 85 percent of Black smokers smoke menthol. The FDA will decide later this month whether to ban them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs new law that makes sesame major food allergen...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-signs-new-law-that-makes-sesame-the-ninth-major-food-allergen/ar-BB1fZrc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA mandate expires soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-tsas-mask-mandate-expires-soon-airline-industry-leaders-and-politicians-are-calling-for-an-extension/ar-BB1fZoBq?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Transportation Security Administration announced in January that it would require people to wear a mask at airports and on planes, trains and other forms of public transportation, the announcement included a sunset date: May 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUNT OR SERIOUS?  Jenner officially running for CA gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/caitlyn-jenner-california-governor-run-710153ef-7a89-460d-b9ec-9efed2a9399f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She will officially announce her bid later today, her campaign tells Axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian hospitals plead for oxygen, country sets virus record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-hospitals-oxygen-tanks-coronavirus-surge-eeed59f1a8574e34353c046ca80419b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — India put oxygen tankers on special express trains as major hospitals in New Delhi begged on social media on Friday for more supplies to save COVID-19 patients who are struggling to breathe. More than a dozen people died when an oxygen-fed fire ripped through a coronavirus ward in a populous western state. India’s underfunded health system is tattering as the world’s worst coronavirus surge wears out the nation, which set a global record in daily infections for a second straight day with 332,730. India has confirmed 16 million cases so far, second only to the United States in a country of nearly 1.4 billion people. India has recorded 2,263 deaths in the past 24 hours for a total of 186,920.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ activists shun...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/23/lgbtq-activists-shun-caitlyn-jenner-over-trump-sup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though Caitlyn Jenner is one of the most famous transgender people in America, the announcement of her candidacy for California governor was greeted hostilely by one of the state’s largest LGBTQ-rights groups and by many trans activists around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGER LIVES!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/uncategorized/2763088/golf-tiger-woods-leg-brace-dog/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIGER WOODS has revealed he is on the mend as he posted a picture in a leg brace while stood next to his dog. The golf legend sustained serious injuries in a horror car accident in February with fe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City of Albuquerque refers $211K Trump campaign bill to collection agency...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/city-of-albuquerque-refers-211k-trump-reelection-campaign-bill-to-collection-agency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Albuquerque, New Mexico, has sent an unpaid bill for former President Donald Trump’s reelection campaign to a debt collection agency, officials said. The bill stems from an event in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Styles to perform 'realistic' gay sex scenes in new film...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/23/harry-styles-gay-sex-scenes-to-look-as-real-as-possible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harry Styles’ sex scenes with another man in the upcoming Amazon Studios film “The Policeman” will “look as real as possible,” an insider said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Pounces...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/newsom-raise-money-tying-caitlyn-jenner-to-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom’s campaign team wasted no time coming after Caitlyn Jenner as she entered the recall race to take his seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Climate' Kerry Scoots After White House Meet...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/ClimateEnvoy/status/1385704140211429376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Faces Barrage of Criticism by Ex-Aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-faces-barrage-of-criticism-by-ex-aide-cummings/ar-BB1fYPTm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson, facing an onslaught of criticism from the man he until recently relied on as his most powerful adviser, denied he’d blocked an inquiry into leaks of sensitive information from within his government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz probe includes scrutiny of potential public corruption tied to medical marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/23/politics/gaetz-probe-public-corruption-medical-marijuana/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities are looking into whether a 2018 trip to the Bahamas involving Republican Congressman Matt Gaetz and several young women was part of an orchestrated effort to illegally influence Gaetz in the area of medical marijuana, people briefed on the matter told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US diplomatic missions to fly LGBTQ Pride flag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/23/blinken-authorizes-us-diplomatic-missions-to-fly-pride-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Tony Blinken has authorized US diplomatic missions to fly the LGBTQ pride flag on the same pole as the American flag at embassies and consulates, a department official confirmed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer complains about jail treatment: 'Epstein effect'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-not-guilty-new-sex-trafficking-charges-203305963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 59-year-old British socialite has been held without bail in Brooklyn’s Metropolitan Detention Center since her arrest last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Face-Masks The New Condoms?</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/are-face-masks-the-new-condoms-f8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some thoughts on plagues, rationality and recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frail Ghislaine Maxwell pleads not guilty to new charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9503995/Ghislaine-Maxwell-pleads-NOT-GUILTY-two-counts-sex-trafficking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell, 59, pleaded not guilty Friday to new sex trafficking charges added to an indictment three weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family indicted, accused of selling bleach as cure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-religion-coronavirus-5f9c2732411f3a14cd6cffd04d787b16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A family accused of selling a toxic industrial bleach as a coronavirus cure through their Florida-based church has been indicted on federal charges. A federal grand jury in Miami returned an indictment Thursday charging Mark Grenon, 62, and his sons, Jonathan, 34, Jordan, 26, and Joseph, 32, with one count each of conspiracy to commit fraud and two counts each of criminal contempt, according to court records. They face possible life sentences if convicted. Mark Grenon is the archbishop of the Genesis II Church of Health and Healing, based in Bradenton, Florida. The church sells chlorine dioxide as a “Miracle Mineral Solution,” officials said. The Grenons claim the solution can cure a vast variety of illnesses ranging from cancer to autism to malaria to COVID-19. A Miami federal judge last April ordered the church to stop selling the substance, but the order was ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL draftees could hug, dap up vaccinated Roger Goodell
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/draft/2021/04/23/nfl-draft-roger-goodell-vaccinated-against-covid-19-bro-hugs/7350561002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With NFL commissioner Roger Goodell vaccinated against COVID-19, bro hugs, daps and handshakes could make their return at the 2021 draft next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dogs that stayed in Chernobyl...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210422-the-guards-caring-for-chernobyls-abandoned-dogs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The descendants of pets abandoned by those fleeing the Chernobyl disaster are now striking up a curious relationship with humans charged with guarding the contaminated area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More risks to pregnant, newborns than known before...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-pregnant-women-stu-idUSKBN2CA1E9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pregnant women infected with COVID-19 and their newborn children face higher risks of complications than was previously known, a study by British scientists showed on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Tells Erdogan He'll Call Armenian Massacre Genocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-tells-erdogan-he-ll-call-armenian-massacre-a-genocide/ar-BB1fZ04f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden told Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Friday that he intends to recognize the early-20th century massacre of Armenians by Ottoman Empire forces as a genocide, according to people familiar with a call between the leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Rush Return To CA? Company Working To Reopen Mine Untouched Since '56...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/04/22/gold-rush-return-to-grass-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been decades since gold country in California has been actively mined, but a Canadian company wants to change that in Grass Valley.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
