<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Psychedelic trips soon part of therapy. What sessions look like...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/24/how-psychedelic-assisted-therapy-with-mdma-and-psilocybin-works.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In as soon as two years, tripping on mind-altering drugs like MDMA and psilocybin could become a regular part of therapy to treat conditions from depression to post-traumatic stress disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Luria's pro-Navy, centrist identity may get Jan. 6 test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-government-and-politics-capitol-siege-navy-cead205203b284a27184b83a99620dbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORFOLK, Va. (AP) — When members of Congress head home to connect with their constituents, some hit tractor pulls. Others might stop by mom-and-pop stores. For Democratic Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Apocalypse Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/07/24/opinion/sunday/climate-change-floods-wildfires.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mother Nature called. She's had it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team USA gets no medals to open Olympics first time in decades...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/564653-team-usa-gets-no-medals-to-open-olympics-for-first-time-in-decades</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Team USA athletes suffered multiple upset losses in the first official day of competition at the Tokyo Olympics on Saturday, the first time in decades the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Officials Warn Healthcare System Crisis 'Highly Possible'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/japan-covid-cases-surge-olympics-1234799395/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the world’s athletes gather in Japan for the Summer Olympics the country is experiencing a fourth wave of Covid-19 infections. Country-wide, case numbers have risen 20% in the past week, w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALASKA: State That Lives Up to Hype...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alaska-the-state-that-actually-does-live-up-to-the-hype</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s the thing about Alaska: There are no wrong decisions, only decisions to be made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: More Money You Make, Longer You'll Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/money-longer-life-net-worth-longevity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money may not buy happiness, but it could buy you a longer life. New research concludes that being wealthy can add years to your lifespan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian anti-lockdown protestors violently clash with police...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9820691/Australian-anti-lockdown-protestors-clash-police-amid-new-restrictions-just-176-new-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protests are a response to harsh Covid lockdowns in New South Wales, Victoria and South Australia, with more than half the country's 25million people ordered to stay at home over the outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Promised Online Fame. She Says They Leaked Her Nudes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/promised-her-online-fame-influencer-144842600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos GettyWith the likes of influencer Tana Mongeau, YouTuber Daisy Keech, Too Hot to Handle cast member turned TikTok provocateur Harry Jowsey, the Clermont Twins, and dozens of other social media stars and models on its roster, the Unruly Agency seems to be the place that could take an influencer’s brand to new heights.But clients and contractors who worked with Unruly and Behave Agency—Unruly’s spinoff for smaller influencers—are warning others agains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Most Influential Spreader of Virus Misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/24/the-most-influential-spreader-of-coronavirus-misinformation-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — The article that appeared online on Feb. 9 began with a seemingly innocuous question about the legal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican reveals it owns more 5,000 properties...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/24/vatican-reveals-it-owns-more-than-5000-properties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real estate holdings published for first time show it owns 4,051 properties in Italy, 1,120 abroad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana farmers blamed for water theft as drought grips west...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/jul/23/water-theft-marijuana-farmers-california-american-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California official says ‘Water stealing has never been more severe’ as water taken from hydrants, homes, rivers and wells</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts express concerns for animal safety as heat waves rip through Pacific Northwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/experts-express-concerns-for-animal-safety-as-heat-waves-continue-to-rip-through-the-pacific-northwest/ar-AAMvT59</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athletes chant 'Dr. Biden' as first lady cheers swimmers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/564659-us-athletes-chant-dr-biden-as-first-lady-cheers-swimmers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Athletes on the U.S. swimming team chanted first lady Jill Biden's name as she sat in attendance for their competition at the Tokyo Olympics on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands join Budapest Pride march against anti-LGBTQ law...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210724130301-kijdh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNGARY-LGBT/MARCH (UPDATE 1, PIX/TV):UPDATE 1-Thousands join Budapest Pride march against anti-LGBTQ law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto-based 'shadow financial market' spooks regulators...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/24/shadow-financial-market-spooks-regulators-500696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watchdogs are warning that some DeFi activities are probably illegal under federal law and pose serious danger to consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China digital yuan could pose challenges to dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/24/the-us-is-deciding-how-to-respond-to-chinas-digital-yuan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are digging into Central Bank Digital Currencies and what a CBDC could look like in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge of delta variant poses new political threat to Biden and his agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/surge-of-covid-delta-variant-poses-new-political-threat-to-biden-and-his-agenda/ar-AAMvWbq?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has sought to place blame elsewhere, calling the resurgence “a pandemic of the unvaccinated” and scolding social-media platforms for misinformation that leads people to refuse vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Green Bank, West Virginia -- quietest place in America...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/24/inside-green-bank-west-virginia-quietest-place-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside Green Bank, West Virginia, the most silent place in America, where 8,000 residents aren’t allowed to use cellphones or Wi-Fi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athens' Old Airport Rivaling New York in Property Prices...</title>
      <link>https://businesshala.com/athens-old-airport-is-rivaling-new-york-in-property-prices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;businesshala.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Businesshala) -- The redevelopment of Athens' old airport offered a unique opportunity to secure ancient seaside homes close to a major city, and even</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With workers in high demand, teens filling void...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-504f6e207d8914070f315225adb58c17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — As businesses have taken “closed indefinitely” signs out of their windows and reopened their doors, the landscape of a post-pandemic workforce is changing and depending on an unexpected demographic — teens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfing debut making clear wave riders masters of science...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-surfing-sports-lifestyle-environment-and-nature-f76fb9c41535bff7c65727830d3ddc79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICHINOMIYA, Japan (AP) — Olympic surfing’s debut is making clear that these wave riders are unsung masters of science -- in climatology, meteorology and oceanography to be exact. Serious wave chasers are by default atmospheric science junkies because there are few, if any, sports that are both dependent on an uncontrollable variable — the weather — and defined by a literal uneven playing field — the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New LAMBO cleans house, cooks dinner, entertains kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3341535/lamborghini-huracan-evo-spyder-alexa-tested-interior-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you were going to spend £180k on a Lamborghini, you’d want the ruddy thing to clean your house. And the new Huracan Evo does just that…plus it’ll sort your dinner out and keep the kids entertain…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China criticises NBC broadcast for 'incomplete map'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/sports/china-criticises-nbc-olympics-broadcast-incomplete-map-2021-07-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China criticised NBC Universal for showing an "incomplete map" of the country in its broadcast of the opening ceremony of the Tokyo Olympics, after a map displayed during the arrival of Chinese athletes included neither Taiwan nor the South China Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA exceeds 3,000 daily cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/la-county-exceeds-3000-daily-coronavirus-cases-as-surge-worsens/ar-AAMuZLh </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives riled up over registering women for draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/07/23/conservatives-riled-up-over-registering-women-for-draft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservatives oppose a Senate bill that would require women to register for the military draft next year and plan to make it an election issue in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Frustration mounts over vax holdouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98patience-has-worn-thin-e2-80-99-frustration-mounts-over-vaccine-holdouts/ar-AAMuLoH </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest lockdown in Sydney...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-sydney-arrests-coronavirus-pandemic-ff50971322d56dc9ce9ec92ea7e940c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY (AP) — Thousands of people took to the streets of Sydney and other Australian cities on Saturday to protest lockdown restrictions amid another surge in cases, and police made several arrests after crowds broke through barriers and threw plastic bottles and plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England facing weeks of 'pingdemic' disruption to services and food supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/23/england-facing-weeks-of-pingdemic-disruption-to-services-and-food-supply</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No 10 scrambles to extend self-isolation exemption scheme for critical workers as companies and councils warn of chaos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Support for recalling Newsom growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-poll-finds-support-climbing-for-gov-newsom-recall/ar-AAMuXoN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative radio host Larry Elder, a last-minute addition to the recall ballot, is polling higher than his competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of America's hottest cities is down to one well...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/one-americas-hottest-cities-down-120002675.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taps could go dry for Needles' 5,000 residents, who each drink as much as two gallons of water daily to cope with 120-degree temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida, Missouri and Texas now account for 40% of new corona cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-missouri-and-texas-now-account-for-40-percent-of-new-us-coronavirus-cases-172032337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just three states are now driving the pandemic in the United States, as the divide between vaccinated and unvaccinated regions of the country becomes ever more stark, as the more transmissible Delta variant of the coronavirus spreads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSOURI WORST COVID IN NATION</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/missouri-covid-delta-variant-thrives-political-discord-public-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the center of the nation’s delta variant outbreak, public health efforts are mired in a political turf war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL COACH FIRED FOR REFUSING VAX</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/31869652/rick-dennison-minnesota-vikings-assistant-refusing-covid-19-vaccine-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After refusing to receive a vaccine for COVID-19, Rick Dennison is out as a Vikings assistant coach, sources told ESPN. Patriots assistant Cole Popovich also won't be with his team in 2021 in a decision related to the vaccine, sources confirmed to ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative talk-show host who said 'probably safer not getting' vax now seriously ill with Covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/conservative-radio-talk-show-host-160604107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that Phil Valentine has become ill with the coronavirus, he has "regrets" about not being more "pro-vaccine," his family said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak pops travel bubble between Australia, New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/delta-variant-outbreak-pops-travel-bubble-between-australia-and-new-zealand/ar-AAMsVck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand has suspended a travel corridor with Australia for eight weeks as a delta variant outbreak that began in Sydney imperils the nation's earlier success in containing the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative talk-show host who said 'probably safer not getting' vax now seriously ill with Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/california-court-says-it-s-ok-to-intentionally-misgender-and-deadname-trans-people/ar-AAMujxn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California court ruled that forcing nursing home employees to refer to patients by their preferred pronouns and names violates freedom of speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Workers Are Taking Back Their Power: 'We All Quit'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akgy7a/we-all-quit-how-americas-workers-are-taking-back-their-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motherboard spoke to economists and historians about why fast food and retail workers around the country are suddenly quitting en masse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panpsychism gains steam in science communities...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/07/23/panpsychism-the-idea-that-inanimate-objects-have-consciousness-gains-steam-in-science-communities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An expanding notion of what "consciousness" is could have profound repercussions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM again recalls its electric vehicles over fire threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/23/business/gm-bolt-recall-fire-threat/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GM is once again recalling nearly 70,000 Chevrolet Bolt electric vehicles because of a risk that the battery will catch fire when the car is parked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod now shark capital of the world...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3337174/shark-attack-explosion-mauled-swimmers-warning-signs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE number of shark attacks has exploded across the globe as swimmers continue to ignore bloodbath warning signs – seeing nearly 800 people mauled in just nine years. America has overtaken Au…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China sparks WWIII fears saying US can't stop them invading Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3336978/china-says-us-has-no-chance-stopping-taiwan-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE are fears WW3 could be closer than previously thought after China boasts that the US would have “no chance” of stopping an invasion of Taiwan. Du Wenlong, a military expert at Chi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST. LOUIS REINSTATES MASK MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/lifestyles/health-med-fit/coronavirus/st-louis-st-louis-county-to-reinstate-mask-mandate/article_b7730c4d-3ee9-5970-8e81-cd704bb67dfa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masks will be required, including for those who are vaccinated, in indoor public places and on public transportation beginning on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge Disrupts Office-Return Plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/delays-more-masks-and-mandatory-shots-virus-surge-disrupts-office-return-plans/ar-AAMuhrZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several hospital systems that previously held off making vaccines mandatory for health care workers are now willing to do so. Google employees in California who have voluntarily returned to the office are again wearing masks indoors. Goldman Sachs is considering whether to reinstitute testing for fully vaccinated employees in the company’s New York City offices, according to a person familiar with the situation who spoke on the condition of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men at ad agency win sex discrimination case...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9817847/Two-men-win-sex-discrimination-payout-female-director-vowed-obliterate-JWTs-reputation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chas Bayfield (left) and Dave Jenner, in their fifties and creative directors at JWT, were axed from the leading ad agency because bosses 'urgently' wanted to address its poor gender pay gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typhoon threatens to derail...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/23/olympics-threatened-by-typhoon-that-could-hit-tokyo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm is forming in the Philippine Sea and will head dangerously close to Japan’s capital city on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Box Office Plunges 70% Due to New Entry Rules...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/global/france-vaccination-mandatory-b-o-drop-1235026283/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French box office has taken a big hit and dropped 70% this week due to the new sanitary measures enforced on July 21 which require a proof of vaccination or a recent negative PCR test to enter …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Since restaurants reopened, customers have been 'unbearable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/SF-Bay-Area-restaurants-customers-rude-Yelp-review-16333535.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the June 15 reopening, customers have gotten … a little difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA BECOMES NATION'S HOTSPOT, AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/coronavirus/article252960743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surgeon general called it an “all-in moment” for the nation as the coronavirus pandemic becomes a more regional phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump friend Barrack ordered released on $250 million bond...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/23/trump-ally-tom-barrack-spac-pulled-bail-hearing-in-uae-case-changed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas Barrack, a close friend of Donald Trump, is accused of illegally lobbying for the United Arab Emirates during Trump's campaign and presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL COACH FIRED FOR REFUSING VAX</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/07/23/report-vikings-coach-rick-dennison-gone-coronavirus-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota Vikings have reportedly cut ties with assistant coach Rick Dennison after he refused to take the coronavirus vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrack Reaches Bail Deal With Prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/tom-barrack-reaches-bail-deal-with-prosecutors-in-uae-case-1.1632353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump ally Thomas J. Barrack Jr. and U.S. prosecutors have reached agreement on a bail package that will allow the founder of Colony Capital Inc. to be freed ahead of a trial on charges that he illegally lobbied the government on behalf of the United Arab Emirates, according to people familiar with the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Herschel Walker eyes Senate run, turbulent past emerges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-sports-nfl-college-football-coronavirus-pandemic-5e2875eec11e93f9a3bf1fc859137ff8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — At first glance, Herschel Walker has a coveted political profile for a potential Senate candidate in Georgia. He was a football hero at the University of Georgia before his long NFL career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen urges Congress to raise debt limit now...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/23/yellen-urges-congress-to-raise-debt-limit-by-aug-2-or-treasury-will-take-extraordinary-measures-to-prevent-default.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER just 39% effective as delta spreads; Still prevents severe illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/23/delta-variant-pfizer-covid-vaccine-39percent-effective-in-israel-prevents-severe-illness.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer's and BioNTech's Covid-19 vaccine is just 39% effective against delta in Israel, but still provides strong protection against severe illness and hospitalization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests break out at Haiti president's funeral, guests run for cover...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723161436-btoxn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-PRESIDENT/FUNERAL (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-Protests break out at Haiti president's funeral, guests run for cover</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX begins to arrest and jail crossers on trespassing charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/texas-begins-to-arrest-and-jail-border-crossers-on-trespassing-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is beginning to arrest migrants on trespassing charges along the U.S.-Mexico border as part of Republican Gov. Greg Abbott's actions that he says are needed to slow the number of border crossings, jailing at least 10 people so far with more on the way.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
