<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick To Release Memoir Under Own Publishing Company...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/columnist/bell/2020/02/13/colin-kaepernick-interview-new-memoir-publishing-company-nfl-return/4736086002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick explains in a rare interview why he is writing a memoir and starting a publishing company, and what it means for NFL playing career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Kelly Finally Lets Loose on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/john-kelly-alexander-vindman-north-korea-and-trump/606496/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former chief of staff explained, in the clearest terms yet, his misgivings about Trump’s behavior regarding North Korea, immigration, and Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement Millionaire Crowd Swells in Roaring Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/retirement-millionaire-crowd-swells-to-record-in-roaring-market</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retirement Millionaire Crowd Swells to Record in Roaring Market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded foreigners tell of fear and rations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/foreigners-stranded-wuhan-virus-tell-fear-rations-094314188.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunkered down at the epicentre of China's virus epidemic and cut off from the world, the remaining foreigners in Wuhan are eking out a life in fear. A coronavirus outbreak that has killed more than 1,300 people and locked down the central Chinese city has left thousands of foreigners trapped as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic crisis complicates sex lives of young Venezuelans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/economic-crisis-complicates-sex-lives-young-venezuelans-050801959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Venezuela, mired in a years-long economic crisis, the price of love can be impossibly high for cash-strapped young couples. In the tropical gardens surrounding the Central University of Venezuela, in Caracas, it is not uncommon to see young student couples making out behind a palm tree. Such public</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek islands should not be migrant warehouses, residents say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200213105115-mckxg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-MIGRANTS/GREECE-PROTESTS (PIX, TV):Greek islands should not be migrant warehouses, residents say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Questions About Origin...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/sudden-militarization-wuhans-p4-lab-raises-new-questions-about-origin-deadly-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg campaign suddenly drops memes everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/michael-bloombergs-campaign-suddenly-drops-memes-everywhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (NYTIMES) - Mr Michael Bloomberg has contracted with some of the biggest meme-makers on the internet to post sponsored content on Instagram promoting his presidential campaign.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US military prepping for pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2020/02/13/us-military-prepping-for-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Northern Command is bracing for an outbreak of the new coronavirus on U.S. soil, if it should occur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake-like UFO returns to Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/snake-like-ufo-returns-florida-21481545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mystery object was similar to those seen across the US in recent months and is the second time it has been seen in Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea 'executes patient'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/breaking-north-korea-executes-coronavirus-21488604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong-un quickly placed those returning from China in a quarantine. But according to reports an official was spotted breaching the order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods on Verge of History and Still Tinkering...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/sports/sport-others/tiger-woods-is-on-the-verge-of-history-and-still-tinkering-6265941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fan hysterics have been a staple at his tournament appearances for decades, but they are now coming during a renaissance of sorts, as Woods, 44, looks to build on the momentum he has accrued since winning the Masters last season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Presence on the Farm: Robots...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/13/a-growing-presence-on-the-farm-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FARMER CITY, Illinois — In a research field off Highway 54 last autumn, corn stalks shimmered in rows 40-feet deep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein jury set to hear closing from #MeToo skeptic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a5aa55367dc47556fc8200e78de064e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Closing arguments at the Harvey Weinsten rape trial are set to begin Thursday, with the jury hearing first from a Chicago attorney who’s taken #MeToo movement heat for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit claims professor used disabled patients in Iowa for sex research...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article240209247.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks judge who will sentence...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/895357/twitter-rampage-trump-attacks-federal-judge-set-sentence-roger-stone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday night attacked the judge presiding over his friend and adviser Roger Stone's criminal case. Stone was found guilty last year of lying to Congress, witness tampering, and obstructing a House investigation. The Department of Justice recommended he receive seven to nine years in prison, but after Trump tweeted on Tuesday morning that this was a 'miscarriage of justice!' the DOJ suddenly reversed course, calling the recommendation 'grossly disproportionate.' All four of the federal prosecutors who worked on the case have withdrawn in an apparent protest, with one of them choosing to resign from the department altogether. Trump began tweeting about Stone's case as the results of the New Hampshire Democratic primary began trickling in. 'Is this the Judge that put Paul Manafort in SOLITARY CONFINEMENT, something that not even mobster Al Capone had to endure?' he tweeted. 'How did she treat Crooked Hillary? Just asking!' The judge in question is Judge Amy Berman Jackson, who has presided over several cases involving people close to Trump, including Manafort, his former campaign chairman. Manafort is now serving a 7-and-a-half year prison sentence after being found guilty of tax and bank fraud and pleading guilty to conspiracy charges. Hillary Clinton has not been on trial for any crimes, and thus has not appeared before Jackson. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donors set to leave Biden...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/12/donors-set-to-leave-joe-biden-after-iowa-and-new-hampshire-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s disastrous results in Iowa and New Hampshire have spooked Democratic donors who are preparing to jump ship and throw their money behind someone else — even as his campaign vowed Wednesd…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 'Mayor Pete'? -- Trump struggles for killer nickname...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/just-mayor-pete-trump-struggles-killer-nickname-214111228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump likes to coin disparaging nicknames for his political opponents -- but so far, he hasn't quite hit the mark with rising young Democrat Pete Buttigieg. Is it perhaps that Trump doesn't see "Mayor Pete" as a credible opponent?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even Critics Praise Merkel as Chancellor's Reign Draws to an End...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-critics-praise-merkel-chancellor-050000805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Portugal’s Socialist Prime Minister Antonio Costa is not a natural ally for the conservative Angela Merkel but as Europe starts to prepare for life without the four-term German chancellor he’s clear that her influence remains vital for the continent’s future.Merkel has not always been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes counting methods...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-virus-death-toll-tops-1-100-cases-042819236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s official death toll and infection numbers from a new coronavirus spiked dramatically on Thursday after authorities changed their counting methods, fuelling concern the epidemic is far worse than being reported. Two top-ranking politicians overseeing the epicentre of the outbreak were also sacked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  'ALL NEWSPAPERS ARE GOING TO DIE'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/munger-tells-newspaper-company-papers-195754744.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Charles Munger, who’s a newspaper company executive as well as a Berkshire Hathaway Inc. vice chairman, said U.S. newspapers have no future.“Technological change is destroying the daily newspapers in America,” Munger, 96, said Wednesday in Los Angeles at the annual meeting of Daily Journal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400 Million Social Media Users Set to Lose Their Anonymity in India...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/400-million-social-media-users-210000021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook, YouTube, Twitter and TikTok will have to reveal users’ identities if Indian government agencies ask them to, according to the country’s controversial new rules for social media companies and messaging apps expected to be published later this month.The requirement comes as governments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Dems fear fallout from Bernie atop ticket...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ee0b0675aacf75270f24126e69378902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Sen. Bernie Sanders' robust start in the race for the presidential nomination is triggering alarm among congressional Democrats, with many warning that a ticket headed by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan Communist Party chief removed...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200213042304-qcdq7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/HUBEI-PARTY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China's Hubei, Wuhan Communist Party chiefs removed amid epidemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio braces for risk during Carnival... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200212214841-b1szx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/BRAZIL-CARNIVAL (TV):Rio braces for coronavirus risk during Carnival party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEXES EXECUTIVE AUTHORITY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Trump-seeks-to-bend-the-executive-branch-as-part-15052083.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump is testing the rule of law one week after his acquittal in his Senate impeachment trial, seeking to bend the executive branch into an instrument for his personal and political vendetta against perceived enemies.  And Trump - simmering with rage, fixated on exacting revenge against those he feels betrayed him and insulated by a compliant Republican Party - is increasingly comfortable doing so to the point of feeling untouchable, according to the president's advisers and allies.  In the span of 48 hours this week, the president has sought to protect his friends and punish his foes, even at the risk of compromising the Justice Department's independence and integrity - a stance that his defenders see as entirely justified.  Trump complained publicly about federal prosecutors' recommended prison sentence for one of his longtime friends and political advisers, Roger Stone. After senior Justice Department officials then overruled prosecutors to lighten Stone's recommended sentence, the president congratulated Attorney General William Barr for "taking charge" with an extraordinary intervention.  Next Trump sought to intimidate the federal judge in the Stone case, badgering her on Twitter for previous rulings, and attacked the four prosecutors who resigned from the case in apparent protest of the Justice Department's intervention. Then Trump floated the possibility of a presidential pardon for Stone, who was convicted by a jury in November of tampering with a witness and lying to Congress.  The president has openly encouraged his Justice Department to retaliate against a quartet of former FBI officials who long have been targets of his ire for their involvement in the Russia probe.  "Where's [James] Comey?" Trump bellowed Wednesday in a stream-of-consciousness diatribe from the Oval Office....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Concerned Spread Through Pipes...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/3050068/coronavirus-your-toilet-how-hong-kong-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reclassification may have allowed virus to travel 10 storeys in a Tsing Yi housing estate – resulting in an evacuation in early hours of Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SETS STAGE FOR STONE PARDON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-declines-rule-out-pardon-roger-stone-n1136091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don't want to say yet," Trump said when asked by reporters whether a pardon was on the table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Taxes and Spending Set New Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-and-spending-set-records-through-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set records for both the amount of taxes it collected and the amount of money it spent in the first four months of fiscal 2020 (October through January), according to data released today in the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING ADMITS:  14,840 NEW VIRUS CASES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/13/coronavirus-latest-updates-china-hubei.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wuhan is the Chinese city at the epicenter of the outbreak and the capital of Hubei province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman floats NEW impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/02/12/swalwell-impeaching-trump-over-roger-stone-is-not-off-the-table/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Eric Swalwell (D-CA) Wednesday on CNN revealed that the Justice Department's reversal on Roger Stone's sentence after President Donald Trump's tweet could be an impeachable offense. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC preparing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/prevention-cures/482794-officials-say-the-cdc-is-preparing-for </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doctor at the CDC updates reporters on the steps the U.S. is taking to tackle the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW SULLIVAN</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/author/andrew-sullivan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;View an archive of articles by Andrew Sullivan for Daily Intelligencer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More sick on quarantined ship...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff4f6baa1b49f96dc15c236b5b467369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan’s health ministry said Thursday 44 more people on a cruise ship quarantined near Tokyo have tested positive for the virus that causes the new disease known as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Retribution tour'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e613b755f0750a1df4127f054561d7d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the week since his acquittal on impeachment charges, a fully emboldened President Donald Trump is demonstrating his determination to assert an iron grip on government, pushing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG Barr agrees to testify as Dems question his leadership...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/027cb88523c183e8b05848be838b1354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General William Barr has agreed to testify before the House Judiciary Committee next month, appearing for the first time before the panel as questions swirl about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPERIMENTAL BRAIN TREATMENT ON NAVY SEAL SPIRALS OUT OF CONTROL... </title>
      <link>http://rewired.inewsource.org/ucsd-kevin-murphy-prtms-navy-seals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rewired.inewsource.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A novel and unproven treatment is at the center of a confidential University of California investigation, lawsuits and a Navy SEAL's psychotic break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snoop Dogg Apologizes to Gayle King, Says He 'Overreacted' to Kobe Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/snoop-dogg-apologizes-to-gayle-king-for-over-kobe-bryant-interview-comments-overreacted-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I publicly tore you down by coming at you in a derogatory manner based off of emotions, me being angry at questions that you asked," rapper says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLE IN PARADISE: Bernie, AOC private feud...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/02/aoc-bernie-sanders-campaign-iowa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOC’s people were said to be unhappy at being called on the carpet and expressed concern over Sanders’s Joe Rogan embrace—but now AOC is back on the stump in New Hampshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ghost' DNA In West Africans Complicates Story Of Human Origins...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/02/12/805237120/ghost-dna-in-west-africans-complicates-story-of-human-origins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modern genomes from Nigeria and Sierra Leone show signals that scientists call "ghost" DNA — from an unknown human ancestor. That means that prehistoric humans likely procreated with an unknown group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  'Hypocrites'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/12/it-didnt-take-long-for-harry-and-meghan-to-prove-they-are-hypocrites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, that was fast. Just weeks after slamming the door on Buckingham Palace, declaring their suffering as wealthy, pampered, world-famous senior royals so unbearable that they must take their leav…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horny Hacker: Latest Ransomware Scheme Demands Nude Photos To Unlock Files...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90463732/hackers-are-demanding-nude-photos-to-unlock-files-in-a-new-ransomware-scheme-targeting-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security firm Emsisoft has released a decryption to circumvent a new ransomware variant that’s demanding explicit photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry, Meghan eyeing big banks' billions...</title>
      <link>https://knewz.com/meghan-markle-and-prince-harry-may-be-eyeing-big-banks-billions-as-his-cousins-divorce-rocks-the-royal-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knewz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barely a week after reportedly raking in $1 million for a Miami appearance, Prince Harry and Meghan Markle are said to be looking to work with Goldman Sachs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire School District Closes For Week After Flu Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/02/11/rio-vista-isd-johnson-county-texas-closing-rest-of-week-flu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio Vista ISD in Johnson County closed its doors early Tuesday and for the rest of the week due to the flu and other illnesses, the district announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS VOTE TO LIMIT TRUMP WAR POWERS...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/02/12/senate-passes-war-powers-measure-tim-kaine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate on Wednesday voted to advance a War Powers resolution which would limit President Trump's ability to use military action without approval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury finds Mar-a-Lago intruder not guilty of trespassing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d786d4f22201a679e964f149a92813ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — A Florida jury acquitted a Chinese woman Wednesday of trespassing at President Donald Trump's Mar-a-Lago resort after she testified she didn't understand a security...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Mark Zuckerberg's Lost Notebook...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/facebook-mark-zuckerberg-lost-notebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the early days of Facebook, Zuck kept his plans for world domination in handwritten journals. He destroyed them. But a few revealing pages survived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Database of Animal Viruses Help Predict Next Pandemic?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/can-a-database-of-animal-viruses-help-predict-the-next-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scientist spent years building a tool to identify coronaviruses that can jump species. Then this winter's virus emerged—and put his system to the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon army fires at Israeli drones, forcing retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.i24news.tv/en/news/israel/diplomacy-defense/1581534339-report-lebanon-army-fires-at-israeli-uavs-forcing-them-to-retreat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.i24news.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalai Lama cancels all events...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/asia/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-02-12-20-intl-hnk/h_44c26bc4035ba6d1e0286237b5a19558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The novel coronavirus has infected more than 43,100 people worldwide as it continues to spread. Follow here for the latest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Israel's new laser weapon shoot drones out of sky...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/12/watch-israels-wild-new-laser-weapon-shoot-drones-out-of-sky/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli drone defense system fit for “Star Wars” has successfully shot down multiple maneuvering targets with a high-powered laser beam, according to reports. “The system achieved 100 percent su…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First case confirmed in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/uknews/10950656/first-coronavirus-case-confirmed-in-london-as-officials-worst-fears-come-true/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE first coronavirus case has been confirmed in London today as the deadly bug spread to the capital. The woman had travelled from China and was diagnosed at a hospital this afternoon, a governmen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost women freeze to death after illegal border crossing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article240230966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photojournalist taken into NYPD custody while filming Manhattan arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-photojournalist-arrested-manhattan-20200212-7xm4kebwe5ed7gukrlsfjdpq4e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amr Alfiky, whose photos have appeared in the New York Times and with Reuters, was taking video of a shirtless, emotionally disturbed man on Ludlow and Division Sts. at about 7 p.m. when police took him into custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hope And Hype Of Diabetic Alert Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/02/12/798481601/the-hope-and-hype-of-diabetic-alert-dogs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies that sell dogs trained to sniff out life-threatening changes in blood sugar for people with diabetes have faced lawsuits or complaints from some of their customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake hits Tennessee a day after cluster...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article240230691.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police raid controversial French writer's publisher...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/police-raid-controversial-french-writer-matzneffs-publisher-142418573.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police on Wednesday raided the headquarters of the company that published the works of Gabriel Matzneff, accused of raping a minor, as a date was set for his trial on a charge of justifying paedophilia. The search at publishing company Gallimard's Paris offices was conducted by a police unit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEGOOGLEMICROSOFT ARE 'MAGA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/02/11/donald-trump-celebrates-maga-trillion-dollar-tech-microsoft-apple-google-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Tuesday celebrated that the top tech companies now had market caps over a trillion dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth, Fentanyl crossing border at record rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2020/02/10/u-s-border-seizures-of-meth-fentanyl-set-to-break-records-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBP data provide insight into cartels' most recent shift in narcotics smuggling and their impacts on American citizens in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Hiding Tortured Political Prisoner in Quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/02/12/report-china-hides-tortured-political-prisoner-in-coronavirus-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese Communist Party officials reportedly transferred a deaf political prisoner into coronavirus quarantine, the Epoch Times revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed chief issues stark warning to Congress on deficits...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/482617-fed-chief-issues-stark-warning-to-congress-on-deficits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell called on Congress to reduce the U.S. federal budget deficit to ensure the central bank could adequately respond to a financial crisis or recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Bigger threat than terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/12/coronavirus-is-a-bigger-threat-than-terrorism-world-health-organization/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus should be treated as “public enemy number one” — posing a bigger threat than terrorism, the World Health Organization (WHO) has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Marshal Shot In Baltimore... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/02/12/officer-with-the-u-s-marshall-shot-in-northeast-baltimore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident happened at the intersection of Cedonia and Radecke Avenues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swallows up more than 500 companies in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/ftc-scrutiny-big-tech-acquisitions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As regulators flex authority, industry advocates say the move risks chilling innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg beating Trump on FB spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/social-media/bloomberg-spends-big-challenge-trump-his-home-court-facebook-n1135791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg spent more than $1 million a day on average during the past two weeks on Facebook, according to data compiled by NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Tops List of Healthiest Cities...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/02/11/wallethub-survey-san-francisco-the-healthiest-city-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the conditions of its street has drawn criticism, a new survey has found that San Francisco is actually the healthiest city in the United States when it comes to access to quality health care, parks to relax in, nutritional food to eat and the desire to stay fit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears Lead To Slumping Chinese Food Sales...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/02/12/coronavirus-boston-chinatown-chinese-food/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts Restaurant Association is hearing from Chinese restaurant owners across the state that sales are down amid coronavirus fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6-year-old with Down syndrome pointed finger gun at teacher. School called cops...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/education/valley-forge-elementary-student-teacher-shooting-threat-chester-county-pa-20200211.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Gaines thinks school staff should have exercised discretion in deciding whether to call the police in response to her daughter, who has Down syndrome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators want Ivanka's women's program to become law...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senators-want-ivanka-trumps-womens-154405248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two senators — one Republican and one Democrat — are leading a legislative effort to have a global women's initiative spearheaded by President Donald Trump's daughter Ivanka written into law. Lindsey Graham, R.-S.C., and Jeanne Shaheen, D-N.H., are behind the effort, the senior White House adviser</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chaos at CONDE NAST...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/12/the-chaos-at-conde-nast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a high-class but increasingly common problem: being a former magazine editor in a digitized world that cares little about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall in new cases raises hope in China outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/22857c9d3f31d3cea98bd793611e71aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The number of new cases in China dropped for a second straight day in the virus outbreak that has infected about 45,000 people and killed more than 1,100, health officials said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pranksters spark panic by pretending to spill virus on NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10947817/shocking-moment-instagram-pranksters-pretend-to-spill-coronavirus-on-ny-subway-train-in-outrageously-bad-taste-stunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INSTAGRAM comedians sparked panic when they pretended to spill coronavirus on a New York subway train. The jokers got on an L train in Brooklyn dressed in hazmat suits and carrying a plastic contai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district scraps 'A-F' grading system for kinder, gentler model...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/school-district-scraps-traditional-a-f-grading-system-for-kinder-gentler-model/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New grading scales obscure a child’s true performance…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Anderson 'FRENCH DISPATCH' debuts trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2020/02/the-french-dispatch-trailer-wes-anderson-chalamet-1202210769/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anderson returns to live-action filmmaking for the first time since "The Grand Budapest Hotel."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 3 American workers run out of money before payday...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/11/32-percent-of-workers-run-out-of-cash-before-payday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost a third of Americans across all income levels are regularly running out of money before their next paycheck hits, according to a new survey from Salary Finance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Homes In on Bloomberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2020/02/12/trump_camp_dismisses_sanders_homes_in_on_bloomberg_142374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early on the morning of Bernie Sanders expected victory in the New Hampshire primary, President Trump was already focused on a newer Democratic threat looming large on the electoral...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitmen disguised as doctor and cop gun down prisoner being treated in hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/hitmen-disguised-doctor-cop-gun-21482508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunmen shot dead the prisoner, who was being treated in hospital after surviving an attack in prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLANKFEIN RIPS BERNIE: Will ruin economy, doesn't care about military...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/12/former-goldman-ceo-blankfein-if-im-russian-i-go-with-sanders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Goldman Sachs CEO and Chairman Lloyd Blankfein has said Russia should back Bernie Sanders for president in order to "best screw up the U.S."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAN JONES: Dem voters 'sad'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/482715-van-jones-people-are-depressed-by-primary-process-just-want-somebody-to-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN analyst Van Jones on Tuesday said he thinks that Democratic voters "are depressed" and "sad" over the Democratic primary process, saying that it is a "messy, confusing choice" and Democrats "just want somebody to vote for against Tru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10,000 steps a day may not actually prevent weight gain...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/10-000-steps-day-may-not-actually-prevent-112814450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the common belief that we should all be walking 10,000 steps a day, new U.S. research has found that although walking more may decrease your sedentary time, it doesn't actually prevent weight gain. Carried out by researchers at Brigham Young University, the new study looked at 120 freshmen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest man: Never get angry and keep smiling!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6e1d588cea92fc8cc2883f777f8ccc54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A Japanese man with a sweet tooth who believes in smiles has become the world's oldest male at 112 years and 344 days old, according to Guinness World Records. Chitetsu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Mike's big play for black voters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/487a4a98bbf7cb5c1b3ab2255e320b2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — A meeting with nearly 80 black pastors in Detroit. A speech before a black Democratic organization in Montgomery. A rally at a historically black university. A tour of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar surged. Can she make it count?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/126ad1dc798c43eca57fb333a174121f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, N.H. (AP) — It took a year of campaigning, countless stump speeches and an especially strong night on the debate stage for little-known Democratic presidential hopeful Amy Klobuchar to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Slavery not crime for half countries in world...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200212132545-vdpzu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although laws allowing slavery have been scrapped worldwide, many of the 193 U.N. member states have not gone on to explicitly criminalise slavery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of locusts swarm motorist in apocalyptic footage as plague grips Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/millions-locusts-swarm-motorist-apocalyptic-21482299</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kenya is facing its worst locust outbreak in decades with swarms also reaching Somalia, Ethiopia, Uganda and Tanzania</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Bat for sale at wildlife market despite warning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bat-sale-indonesias-wildlife-market-despite-virus-warning-104703554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bats, rats and snakes are still being sold at an Indonesian market known for its wildlife offerings, despite a government request to take them off the menu over fears of a link to the deadly coronavirus. Vendors at the Tomohon Extreme Meat market on Sulawesi island say business is booming and curious</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
