<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Where is John Kelly? Missing in Action...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/where-is-john-kelly-chief-of-staff-absent-as-trump-conducts-interviews-for-cabinet-positions-at-mar-a-lago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA teachers who have sex with students seldom go to prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local-education/georgia-teachers-who-have-sex-with-students-seldom-prison/19km7Vn2iyxOZT59tKlr0L/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Factors including the age of consent, 16, and who has "supervisory authority" often make prosecutions difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car owner shot by booter...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/car-owner-shot-booting-company-worker-atlanta-police-say/mr4j6CyH6EFpDZcgmEYOFK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A car owner was shot early Thursday in northwest Atlanta by an employee of a company that had placed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg at center of new FACEBOOK firestorm...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/417933-facebook-faces-calls-for-new-leadership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s leadership is facing a crisis following the company’s latest controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi's political machine ramps up to secure gavel...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/with-honey-instead-of-vinegar-pelosi-steadily-inches-toward-the-speakers-gavel/2018/11/21/5559097e-edd8-11e8-baac-2a674e91502b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic leader has personally courted disgruntled members and deployed her sprawling network to bolster her, all but overwhelming her critics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeach president? House Dem say not so fast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2b71acd882c4e219382c9e9abe9b990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Whatever happened to trying to impeach President Donald Trump? As House Democrats begin laying out the vision for their new majority, that item is noticeably missing from the to-do list and firmly on the margins. The agenda for now includes spending on public works projects, lowering health care costs and increasing oversight of the administration. It's the balance that Democratic Leader Nancy Pelosi is trying to strike in the new Congress between those on her party's left flank who are eager to confront the president, and her instinct to prioritize the kitchen-table promises that Democrats made to voters who elected them to office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandberg changes story about company hired to attack critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/business/i-knew-about-soros-smear-firm-says-facebook-chief-jw98s28pp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheryl Sandberg has changed her account of how much she knew about a PR firm that Facebook recruited to conduct smear campaigns against opponents. The chief operating officer of the social media...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: I'm thankful for the difference I've made...</title>
      <link>https://myfox8.com/2018/11/23/trump-im-thankful-for-the-difference-ive-made/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;myfox8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump said is thankful for his family -- as well as the "tremendous difference" he has made as President. When asked what he wanted to give thanks for during a press gaggle Thursday, Trump responded, "for having a great family and for having made a tremendous difference in this country. I've made a tremendous difference in the country. This country is so much stronger now than it was when I took office that you wouldn't believe it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE THANKSGIVING NIGHT RAMPAGE AT WHATABURGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article222082440.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houston police say a white man in his mid-40s walked into a Whataburger there wearing only a T-shirt and began terrorizing employees and customers. He died at a hospital after being detained by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  WILDEST SHOPPING FIGHT VIDEOS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/BlckFridayFight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rita Ora hits back after 'toe-curling lip-sync fail' at MACY'S Parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6419069/Rita-Ora-mocked-Twitter-toe-curling-lip-sync-fail-Thanksgiving-Parade.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rita Ora came under fire after she was seen lip-syncing out of time during Macy's Thanksgiving Parade held in New York - although the Let Me Love You hit-maker has hit back at her critics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER editor writing book about 'Trump and his women'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/22/national-enquirer-editor-writing-book-about-trump-and-his-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barry Levine, who left the tabloid in 2016, is writing a book about the president for Hachette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin man, 95, charged over 36,000 deaths in Nazi camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181123-berlin-man-95-charged-over-36000-deaths-nazi-camp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced to divert goods...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/744266/black-friday-amazon-workers-conditions-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AYERS READY FOR CHIEF?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/politics/nick-ayers-pence-chief-of-staff-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey slams Trump for turning 'blind eye' to Khashoggi murder...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/23/europe/turkey-khashoggi-saudi-us-trump-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey's foreign minister has accused President Donald Trump of turning a blind eye in the high-profile murder of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi, a day after the US leader doubled down in his defense of Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEASON'S BEATINGS: BLACK FRIDAY BRAWLS</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/seasons-beatings-men-brawl-in-walmart-aisle-during-black-friday-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Black Friday, and you know what that means: People trading in their dignity for discounted toys and paper towels. Two men brawled in the aisle of a Walmart on Thanksgiving evening. It’s not clear what the tussle was over, but women jumped in and cursed them out. Watch (NSFW): ﻿ Others wrestled TVs as …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY SQUIRMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/theresa-squirms-over-brexit-radio-13632685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She refused to say her deal beats cancelling Brexit, hinted she could resign - and that's before you get to the personal questions. Here are the best moments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand islands moving closer together after massive quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6421269/New-Zealands-north-south-islands-moving-closer-7-8-magnitude-earthquake.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kaikōura earthquake initially brought the islands five metres closer to each other when it struck the tip of South Island, New Zealand in November 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil prices hit new low for year...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/418009-oil-prices-hit-new-low-for-the-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices on Friday fell to their lowest point in a year and are on track for the largest one-month drop since 2014.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demands wall funding in 'major security package'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/418010-trump-demands-wall-funding-in-major-border-security-package</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump in an early-morning tweet the day after Thanksgiving demanded funding for a wall at the Southern border as part of a "major border security package."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of Leonardo's 'lost' Salvator Mundi: Vanished after sold for $450 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/the-fate-of-leonardos-lost-salvator-mundi-bvv28pxfc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wanted: Leonardo da Vinci’s spectacular Salvator Mundi, the long-lost, then found painting of Christ — the “saviour of the world” — holding an orb. His enigmatic expression has led some to consider...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPAIN TO BLOW UP BREXIT?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1049338/Brexit-news-UK-EU-Spain-European-Union-Theresa-May-deal-latest-update</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPANISH prime minister Pedro Sanchez threatened the UK that he would veto Theresa May’s draft Brexit agreement with the European Union over fears over Gibraltar and a political correspondent has insisted the Spanish Government feel betrayed by the UK and EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bible Revisited: Alleged Sodom Site Thought to Have Been Hit by Cosmic Blast...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201811231070070217-sodom-gomora-meteor-blast/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the Bible, the ancient cities, thought to have been located on the Dead Sea, were wiped away by God for the sinful behaviour of their people. The preliminary findings of US scientists suggest that this region witnessed a major calamity almost 4 thousand years ago, which left it uninhabited for centuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'End Of The Arctic Ice Scam'...</title>
      <link>https://realclimatescience.com/2018/11/end-of-the-arctic-ice-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclimatescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggle to recover body...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/police-struggle-to-recover-body-of-us-missionary-killed-by-remote-island-tribe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian authorities were struggling Thursday to figure out how to recover the body of an American who was killed after wading ashore on an island cut off from the modern world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tijuana declares humanitarian crisis, asks for international help...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/border-issues/2018/11/22/tijuana-declares-humanitarian-crisis-migrant-caravan/2089905002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The municipal government in Tijuana declared a humanitarian crisis to deal with the arrival of nearly 5,000 mostly Central American migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find previously unknown part of human brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/scientists-just-found-a-previously-unknown-part-of-the-human-brain/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brain cartographer suggests the cluster of cells appears unique to humans and may be responsible for fine motor control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are not robots': AMAZON workers protest against inhumane conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/black-friday-amazon-workers-protest-poor-working-conditions-2018-11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the UK, the GMB trade union and off-shift Amazon workers are demonstrating, while staff in Italy, Spain, Germany, and France went on strike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 person dead, 2 others hurt after Alabama mall shooting...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/multiple-injured-alabama-mall-shooting-suspect-dead-59370214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was shot and killed by a police after a fight at an Alabama mall resulted in gunfire that injured a teen and a 12-year-old girl. A police statement said the shooting occurred shortly before 10 p.m. Thursday at the Riverchase Galleria in Hoover, outside Birmingham. The statement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked tape shows Buddhist monk taking part in drug-fuelled gay orgy at temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7809154/leaked-sex-tape-buddhist-monk-drug-gay-orgy-temple-taiwan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LEAKED sex tape shows a prominent Buddhist monk taking part in a drug-fuelled gay orgy at a temple in Taiwan. Kai Hung, who has been filmed in three explicit clips taking drugs and having sex wit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burger chain closes after video shows rat being cooked on grill...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/nation-and-world/hawaii-burger-eatery-closes-after-video-seems-to-show-rat-cooking-1533601/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Hawaii-based burger chain has closed a Honolulu restaurant for cleaning after a video posted to social media appeared to show a rat being cooked on the grill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear and faith: Inside last days of American missionary killed by remote tribe...</title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/nation-world/2018/11/fear-and-faith-inside-the-last-days-of-an-american-missionary-killed-by-remote-indian-ocean-tribe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Chau's diary reveals a portrait of a young man obsessed with the idea of bringing Christianity to the Sentinelese, who number in the dozens and have lived largely without contact from the outside world for centuries, protected from visitors by Indian law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine particles from wildfire smoke can hurt body in ways never dreamed of...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/fine-particles-from-wildfire-smoke-can-hurt-your-body-in/article_800b6f01-70e0-540d-8706-96d0eed9a7c6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Last year, as the Tubbs fire scorched its way across Napa and Sonoma counties, environmental researchers at the University of California, Davis fielded questions about the health</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Electric shocks, broken bones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/444678-amazon-black-friday-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon warehouse workers are set to protest ‘inhuman’ working conditions in planned demonstrations across Europe on Black Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy hunting firm slammed for $30K killing trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/trophy-hunting-firm-slammed-25k-13630447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunters might have to pay to £25,000 for a 'world-record class' animal with smaller fees between £3,500 and £18,500</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Marxist for China? Radical students rattle Communist leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181123-marxist-china-radical-students-rattle-communist-leaders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak now infecting newborn babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7218446381a247118466fa7d03f15fe1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The World Health Organization says a worrying number of the newest Ebola cases amid Congo's ongoing outbreak are in patients not usually known to catch the disease: babies. In an update published this week, the U.N. health agency reported 36 new confirmed cases of Ebola, including seven in newborn babies and infants younger than 2 years old. Six cases were reported in children aged between 2 and 17 and one case was in a pregnant woman. While Ebola typically infects adults, as they are most likely to be exposed to the lethal virus, children have been known in some instances to catch the disease when they act as caregivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON workers protest against inhumane conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0cc95e84d877439d8e7f2780d6cb752d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Some of Amazon's workers in Europe are protesting against what they call unfair work conditions, in a move meant to disrupt operations on Black Friday. Amazon Spain said around 90 percent of workers at a logistics depot in near Madrid joined a walkout Friday. Only two people were at the loading bay, spokesman Douglas Harper said. However, he said Amazon had diverted cargo deliveries to its other 22 depots in the country. On a picket line, 38-year-old employee Eduardo Hernandez said the walkout intended to hurt the company financially.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER TENSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hundreds-migrants-push-us-mexico-border-bridge-221000657.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Central American migrants staged a boisterous demonstration on the US Mexico border Thursday, screaming for President Donald Trump to let them in as US soldiers and riot police put on a menacing show of force. The increased tension over the presence of a thousands-strong migrant caravan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson appointed adviser to UKIP leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-ukip-robinson/far-right-activist-robinson-appointed-adviser-to-ukip-leader-idUSKCN1NS0P9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of the eurosceptic United Kingdom Independence Party (UKIP) has appoi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MURPHY BROWN' Threatens ICE Agents: 'I Will Spatchcock You,' Tries Intimidation to Stop Raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/karen-townsend/2018/11/22/murphy-brown-threatens-ice-agents-i-will-spatchcock-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nothing says "Thanksgiving" like some virtue-shaming dialogue about illegal immigration recited by a liberal Hollywood feminist, am I right? The Thanksgiving episode of CBS’s Murphy Brown even included a threat of physical violence to ICE agents and when that didn’t work, verbal intimidation was used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLCE &amp; GABBANA Says Sorry as Chopstick Debacle Threatens Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/china-chopstick-debacle-puts-dolce-gabbana-s-future-at-stake#gs.yUN4t40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Chopstick Debacle Puts Dolce &amp; Gabbana's Future at Stake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOPPERS STORM STORES</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/photo-essays/2018-11-23/u-s-shoppers-storm-the-stores-in-black-friday-frenzy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How WHATSAPP Leads Mobs to Murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/how-whatsapp-leads-mobs-to-murder-in-india/17711650/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHIMOOR-KALIYAM, India — In India, false rumors about child kidnappers have gone viral on WhatsApp, prompting fearful mobs to kill two dozen innocent people since April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Zora, the Robot Caregiver...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2018/11/23/technology/robot-nurse-zora.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may not look like much — more cute toy than futuristic marvel — but this robot is at the center of an experiment in France to change care for elderly patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court's future rides on Ginsburg's health...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/417809-supreme-courts-future-rides-on-ginsburg-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some offered to donate their ribs, others recommended cloaking her in bubble wrap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group within 500 feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/sd-me-border-show-of-force-tijuana-20181122-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asking for more humane conditions in the overflowing Benito Juarez shelter and trying to present themselves to United States immigration authorities for asylum, the group carried white flags as they marched from the migrant camp to the foot of the U.S. pedestrian bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scuffles...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6420779/Scuffles-break-armed-guards-called-amid-Black-Friday-chaos-South-Africa.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scuffles broke out amid chaotic scenes at one store in Sao Paulo, Brazil, where crowds of bargain hunters scrambled to get their hands on cheap televisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday chaos around world as frantic shoppers scramble for bargains...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/black-friday-chaos-frantic-shoppers-13630972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black Friday, one of the busiest shopping days of the year, has arrived with shocking scenes already starting to erupt across the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KFC in Ukraine revolutionary ground zero stirs protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181122-kfc-ukraines-revolutionary-ground-zero-stirs-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Push for EVERYONE to Share DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-22/scared-your-dna-is-exposed-then-share-it-scientists-suggest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas nixes plan to liquefy remains of unclaimed bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/dallas-county/2018/11/21/liquid-cremation-ruled-dallas-county-seeks-new-home-unclaimed-bodies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their final resting place used to be here, under a canopy of trees between a busy road and a lush bird sanctuary tucked away inside the UT...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS roasted for mocking NFL QB's broken leg...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/cbs-getting-drilled-for-tasteless-alex-smith-injury-pun/ar-BBPZAwI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Cases Confirmed At University Of Maryland After Freshman Dies From Adenovirus...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/21/what-is-adenovirus-5-more-cases-being-monitored-after-umd-freshman-dies-from-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Maryland College Park is taking new precautions after the death of a student there from an adenovirus-related Illness that can initially feel like a common cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese reporter wins rare police apology...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/chinese-reporter-wins-rare-police-apology-harassment-59359298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The young woman is panting, panicked, her thin arm pointing at four men in police uniforms who had let themselves into her hotel room near midnight. "You cannot treat me like this," she shouts, her voice high and reeling. "You cannot barge in like this late at night, OK? I didn't do...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the men offering sperm to strangers online -- but only 'natural insemination'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/22/meet-the-men-offering-their-sperm-to-strangers-online-but-only-if-they-can-do-natural-insemination-8166317/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men are listing their semen services online with the caveat that sex has to happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELTICS Star Under Fire After Telling Reporter 'F*** Thanksgiving'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/22/kyrie-irving-thanksgiving-apology-boston-celtics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Celtics star Kyrie Irving says he meant "no disrespect" for saying "F--- Thanksgiving," after the Celtics latest frustrating loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS:  Surprising elephant-sized mammal cousin lived alongside dinosaurs...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20181122185635-nsjdt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-CREATURE/ (PIX):Surprising elephant-sized mammal cousin lived alongside dinosaurs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ape On Birth Control Has Surprise Baby...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/11/22/eloise-gibbon-birth-control-gives-birth-san-diego-zoo/2084655002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eloise â€” a 37-year-old siamang who had been on birth control for years â€” gave birth to a new baby on Nov. 12, at the San Diego Zoo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money laundering: Cops find $400,000 in washing machine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/51d77a0431804316959efd2afc46f3c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMSTERDAM (AP) — Dutch police who found 350,000 euros ($400,000) hidden inside a washing machine have detained a man on suspicion of — what else? — money laundering. Police said in a statement Thursday that officers were checking a house in western Amsterdam on Monday for unregistered residents when they found the valuable laundry load. A photo displayed on the police website showed bundles of bank notes, mainly 20- and 50-euro bills, crammed into the drum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN EXORCISM: Priests getting more requests than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2018/12/catholic-exorcisms-on-the-rise/573943/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Priests are fielding more requests than ever for help with demonic possession, and a centuries-old practice is finding new footing in the modern world.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
