<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump Praise for Vlad Showcases Republican Divide at CPAC...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-e2-80-99s-praise-for-e2-80-98savvy-e2-80-99-putin-showcases-party-divide-at-cpac/ar-AAUkUtn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow 'increasingly frustrated' by lack of momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ukraine-invasion-russia-increasingly-frustrated-lack-of-momentum-us-defense-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Ukraine enters its third day of Russian bombardment following President Vladimir Putin’s invasion this week, a senior defense official said Saturday that Moscow has become "increasingly frustrated" by the lack of momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Children of the Cold War Face Off in New Confrontation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/26/two-children-of-the-cold-war-face-off-in-new-confrontation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As President Biden tells the story, he was blunt with Vladimir V. Putin during a meeting in Moscow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelenskyy unlikely journey from comedy to Ukrainian hero...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-volodymyr-zelenskyy-kyiv-poland-europe-c270027c825e009ed66988bb98a3476e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — When Volodymyr Zelenskyy was growing up in southeastern Ukraine, his Jewish family spoke Russian and his father once forbade the younger Zelenskyy from going abroad to study in Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says SPACEX will rescue ISS if Russia tries to drop it from orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4777695/elon-musk-spacex-iss-russia-putins-space-chief/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has said SpaceX will rescue the International Space Station if Russia tries to drop it from orbit after threats by Vladimir Putin’s space chief. Dimitry Rogozin warned that Russian …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBER ATTACK HITS KREMLIN</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-698718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the government of Ukraine has asked for volunteers from the country's hacker underground, 6 Russian government websites including the Kremlins official website are down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops Were Told They Were Going to Drill?</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2022/02/russia-cracks-down-harder-media-facebook-protests-sweep-russia/362478/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citizens “have a certain amount of capacity to express themselves, but it’s narrowing,” one observer says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pattinson suits up for macabre new 'BATMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pattinson-suits-macabre-batman-015609093.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Pattinson had never been interested in playing a superhero -- until Ben Affleck quit his role as Batman, leaving the famous cape unexpectedly up for grabs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War via TIKTOK: New tool for propaganda machine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-technology-europe-media-nationalism-2186dbc533560cb666f59655ecf1ee8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian TikTok video has it all: a cat, puppies and a pulsing background beat. It's cute, watchable and hardly seems the stuff of state propaganda. In 2014, Russia flooded the internet with fake accounts pushing disinformation about its takeover of Crimea .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of the Union speech comes amid crises, setbacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-ketanji-brown-jackson-state-of-the-union-address-stephen-breyer-joe-biden-1986a0e4f180bd419ac9b0167e633cd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The last time President Joe Biden addressed a joint session of Congress, he said the country was “ready for takeoff” after a period of plague and strife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No notes, same logo: Dr. Oz campaign is like his TV show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-arts-and-entertainment-pennsylvania-celebrity-3155d56a4f5d4e633ab2bac379ffa5d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWTOWN, Pa. (AP) — The banners and big red video screen all said Dr. Oz, the host gave a rousing introduction and in strode the candidate, Mehmet Oz, to take up the microphone and become the center of attention for more than an hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone in hand, Zelenskiy takes center stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-zelenskiy-smartphone/smartphone-in-hand-ukraines-president-takes-centre-stage-in-a-capital-under-attack-idUSKBN2KV0LH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The morning after Russian missiles rained down on Kyiv, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy addressed the nation in his favourite style: the selfie video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphones serving as adult pacifiers?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/are-smartphones-serving-as-adult-pacifiers/ar-AAUlin8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT was answer to CNN. Now pro-Putin spin sparking new outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/rt-was-russia-e2-80-99s-answer-to-cnn-now-its-pro-putin-spin-on-ukraine-is-sparking-new-outrage/ar-AAUl8XK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In TX, millennial's political ambitions could upend one of most conservative Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-texas-a-millennial-e2-80-99s-political-ambitions-could-upend-the-career-of-one-of-the-house-e2-80-99s-most-conservative-democrats/ar-AAUkJOG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy's Crusade Against Shots Anguishes Family and Friends...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/26/a-kennedys-crusade-against-covid-vaccines-anguishes-family-and-friends/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kerry Kennedy remembers how much she admired her older brother Robert as they grew up in Hickory Hill, the family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror moment missile hits apartment block...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4776791/moment-russian-missile-smashes-kyiv-apartment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TERRIFYING video shows the moment a missile smashes into an apartment block in Kyiv. With fighting raging in the city, Ukraine has said so far 198 people, including three children, have been now be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe has 'financial nuke weapon'. But uncertain wants to use it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/europe-says-it-has-a-financial-nuclear-weapon-against-russia-but-it-s-uncertain-if-it-wants-to-use-it/ar-AAUjDEJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin humiliated as 3,500 troops killed, 200 captured...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1572251/vladimir-putin-russia-ukraine-invasion-war-humiliated-captured-kyiv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR PUTIN has been left humiliated after Ukrainian sources claimed 3,500 Russians have been killed and 200 captured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DESTROY THE OCCUPIERS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10554483/Zelensky-fires-warning-shot-Putin-noose-tightens-Kyiv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine's president Volodmyr Zelensky has claimed the country's army has successfully repelled Russian forces advancing on Kyiv and is in control of the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I NEED AMMO, NOT RIDE'</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/russian-troops-invade-ukraine-encircle-kyiv-9b4acc6a-1bb1-4862-8280-11b09471608e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The fight is here."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120,000 flee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-poland-migration-united-nations-c3af8a01b6abdfafb022930d9749efa0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Nearly 120,000 people have so far fled Ukraine into Poland and other neighboring countries in the wake of Russian invasion, the U.N. refugee agency said on Saturday. The number was going up fast as Ukrainians grabbed their belongings and rushed to escape from a deadly Russian onslaught on their nation, including an attempt to take the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden questioned veracity of reports about 'invasion' of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>http://www.china.org.cn/world/2022-02/16/content_78051824.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.china.org.cn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADOLF PUTIN graffiti sprayed across buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4775344/russia-ukraine-news-protests-vladimir-putin-hitler/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURIOUS Russians protesting Vladimir Putin’s violent invasion of Ukraine have scrawled graffiti comparing their hardman President to Nazi monster Adolf Hitler. Demonstrations against Russia&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA TO INSTALL OWN GOVT</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2638540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A senior defense official told reporters that the Pentagon view is that Russia intends to “decapitate” the government of Ukraine and install its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First pandemic, then recession, now, WAR. Anything else, world?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-pandemic-then-recession-now-235415083.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A war in Ukraine and a looming humanitarian crisis triggered fresh anxiety and depression for Americans who have endured two years of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe says it has 'financial nuclear weapon'. But  uncertain if it wants to use it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/europe-says-it-has-a-financial-nuclear-weapon-against-russia-but-it-s-uncertain-if-it-wants-to-use-it/ar-AAUjDEJ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA KEEPS MASK ORDER FOR ALL FLIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/catching-a-flight-you-ll-still-need-a-mask-despite-the-cdc-s-new-guidance/ar-AAUjGzQ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some records taken by The Don are so sensitive they may not be described in public...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/some-records-taken-by-trump-are-so-sensitive-they-may-not-be-described-in-public/ar-AAUi7On?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden nominates Ketanji Brown Jackson to be first Black woman to sit on Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/supreme-court-ketanji-brown-jackson/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden nominated Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Friday, setting in motion a historic confirmation process for the first Black woman to sit on the highest court in the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands arrested at anti-war demonstrations in Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/photos-people-protest-russia-war-against-ukraine-c7fecd0e-6dfe-436f-8959-7016797ceeca.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people around the world gathered for protests against Russia's invasion of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump NY criminal probe has new prosecutor after lawyers quit...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-york-criminal-probe-prosecutor-163522880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new prosecutor has been chosen to lead a criminal probe into former U.S. President Donald Trump, the Manhattan district attorney's office said on Friday, after the departures of two top lawyers threw the investigation's future into question. Susan Hoffinger will now lead the probe into Trump and the practices of his family business, the Trump Organization, according to Danielle Filson, a spokeswoman for Alvin Bragg, the Manhattan district attorney. This week Special Counsel Carey Dunne and Mark Pomerantz - who had been leading the probe begun by former District Attorney Cyrus Vance - resigned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Snowden questioned veracity of reports about 'invasion' of Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://news.cgtn.com/news/2022-02-16/Snowden-questions-veracity-of-reports-about-invasion-of-Ukraine-17GQHqbF3NK/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.cgtn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Gauge Highest Since '82, and War Could Make WORSE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-prices-inflation-e44ad9b2088aa352015868a4f6b17785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An inflation gauge that is closely monitored by the Federal Reserve jumped 6.1% in January compared with a year ago, the latest evidence that Americans are enduring sharp price increases that will likely worsen after Russia's invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After decades of lobbying, supporters say they have votes in House to pass reparations bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2022/02/25/reparations-bill-congress-support/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;H.R. 40 would create a commission on reparations for Black Americans modeled on the process Japanese Americans went through to receive reparations for being imprisoned in internment camps during World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death By Robots? Automation Ruining Lives, Raising Mortality Rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/death-by-robots-automation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found automation in manufacturing companies is linked to a rise of suicides and drug overdoses among working-class adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS in AZ unionizes, dealing blow to coffee chain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/25/starbucks-restaurant-in-mesa-arizona-votes-to-unionize.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's now the third company-owned Starbucks location to vote in support of unionizing and the first outside of the Buffalo, New York, area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$6 a gallon? At least 1 gas station in LA hits mark...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/gas-prices-over-6-dollars/11599980/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average price of gas in Los Angeles County has risen to $4.848 a gallon, but one station near the Beverly Center has topped out at over $6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Unveil 'Unified Genealogy of Modern and Ancient Humans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epxqzp/scientists-unveil-unified-genealogy-of-modern-and-ancient-humans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 3,600 individual genome sequences that date back more than 100,000 years, it is largest human family tree ever created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of international law...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/article-698654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The narrative that democracy and international law were on the rise has now been squashed by Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Vax Pass Quietly Rolled Out -- And Red States Getting On Board...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/suzannerowankelleher/2022/02/24/national-vaccine-quietly-rolled-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of all US states now make the SMART Health Card accessible to their residents or have plans to do so soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Adults Over 60 Feel 'Unseen' In Society Due To Their Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/adults-over-60-feel-unseen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A OnePoll study of 2,000 British adults found those in their seventh decade feel most ignored when clothes shopping, going out to dinner, or having a drink at a bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Cuomo TV ads to air as gov seeks redemption...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pro-andrew-cuomo-tv-ads-to-air-on-monday-as-governor-seeks-redemption/ar-AAUjl1C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True scale of homeless crisis on subway revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10552293/NYC-transit-officials-say-350-homeless-people-living-89-subway-stations-tunnels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of homeless people were found camping out in New York City's subway tunnels and stations earlier this month, MTA officials said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Jets, Superyachts Roam Free as Ukraine Attack Rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/russian-billionaire-jets-and-superyachts-roam-free-as-ukraine-attack-rages/ar-AAUjrwo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of new Europe 'iron curtain'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220225-russia-attack-conjures-up-fears-of-new-europe-iron-curtain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's attack on Ukraine could herald a Cold War revival in Europe with two blocs armed to the teeth pointing nuclear weapons at each other across an iron curtain, politicians and experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang claims ransomware attack on MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10553013/Russia-linked-hacker-gang-claims-ransomware-attack-McDonalds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hacker gang Snatch on Friday claimed to have stolen 500 gigabytes of data from the fast-food giant headquartered in Chicago, posting their demand for a ransom on the dark web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At-Home Abortion Demand Skyrocketed Since Texas Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgd7g3/abortion-pill-texas-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group that helps people perform their own abortions initially saw a 1180 percent increase in requests for help from Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Readies 'father of all bombs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10552743/Furious-Putin-prepares-use-father-bombs-brave-Ukrainians-hold-advance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They fear Vladimir Putin could resort to high-power thermobaric weapons - dubbed the 'father of all bombs' - as brave Ukrainians resist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA imposes sanctions on Vlad...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/25/us-to-impose-sanctions-on-vladimir-putin-and-top-aide-white-house-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States will impose a slate of sanctions on Russian President Vladimir Putin and Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC relaxes indoor mask guidelines...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/25/cdc-relaxes-indoor-mask-guidelines-as-covid-cases-in-us-drop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC relaxed their mask guidelines Friday after the agency acknowledged the risk of severe COVID-19 cases has gone down as the Biden administration moves to shift its focus on how it’ll manage t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITISH AIR suffers major outage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-british-airways-suffers-major-26333636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers are having problems at Heathrow Airport tonight as British Airways suffers a big outage, causing the website to fail and flights to be grounded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Z' tank flies Soviet flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17774640/russian-tank-flies-soviet-union-flag-ukraine-ussr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN ‘Z’ tank has been spotted displaying the old flag of the Soviet Union as claims continue to say Vladimir Putin wants to “rebuild the USSR”. Exactly where the footage was filmed it not kno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why sexual identities shifted during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20220224-why-sexual-identities-shifted-during-the-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With time to contemplate and reassess, some people have begun exploring new sexual identities and other desires “beyond the binary”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 more foreign ships hit in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://splash247.com/two-more-ships-hit-in-the-black-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;splash247.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another two ships have been hit by missiles in the Black Sea: the Moldova-flagged chemical tanker Millennial Spirit and the Panama-flagged bulk carrier Namura Queen. The 1974-built Millennial Spirit, formerly Freyja, was fired upon by a Russian Navy ship 12 nautical miles south of Ukraine’s Yuzhniy port, the General Staff of the Armed Forces of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gang threatens countries that punish Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/25/russian-ransomware-gang-threatens-countries-ukraine-00011896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security experts have warned that any cyberattacks on Russia could prompt digital retaliation by either Moscow or sympathetic criminal hackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health ministry docs: Preparing for major medical event...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2022-02-25/russian-health-ministry-documents-show-how-russia-is-preparing-for-casualties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The document indicates Russia is anticipating a massive medical emergency and has ordered health organisations to identify medical staff ready to relocate. | ITV National News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knee pain sidelines Pope...</title>
      <link>https://www.wric.com/news/u-s-world/pope-nixes-florence-visit-ash-wednesday-due-to-knee-pain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wric.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis has canceled a scheduled Sunday visit to Florence and will not preside over Ash Wednesday commemorations next week because of what the Vatican described Friday as a flareup…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Navy Launches Amphibious Assault...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2022/02/25/russian-navy-launches-amphibious-assault-on-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia launched an amphibious assault on Ukraine, bringing in thousands of naval personnel ashore, a senior defense official said Friday. The amphibious assault is underway into Ukraine, through the Sea of Azov, coming into west of Mariupol, the senior defense official told reporters. Until now, the Russian navy largely played a supporting role in the …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
