<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Internet Is Rotting...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2021/06/the-internet-is-a-collective-hallucination/619320/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too much has been lost already. The glue that holds humanity’s knowledge together is coming undone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA wildfire grows to 13,000 acres, threatens pot farms...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/560873-california-wildfire-grows-to-13000-acres-threatens-marijuana-farms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Northern California’s wildfires that erupted from mountain thunderstorms last week has grown to cover more than 13,000 acres as of Tuesday, potentially threatening a massive network of marijuana farms in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widower Seeking New Start in Florida Missing in Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2021-06-30/widower-seeking-new-start-in-florida-is-missing-in-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York City man bought a beachfront condo in Florida to start a new chapter of his life after his wife and parents died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark leaps out of water to bite parasailer!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3187570/sharks-leaps-water-bites-parasailers-foot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a shark leaps out of the water and bites a parasailer’s foot, at a resort in the Red Sea. Footage of the horrifying incident shows the tandem paraglider, a 37-year-old J…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first elderly sex robot with 'wrinkles and silver hair'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3182902/old-male-sex-robot-realdoll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ‘ELDERLY male’ sex doll has been created by sex robot company RealDoll. The grey haired robot has been made at the request of a customer and was posted on the firm’s Instagram …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIANA BONES: Harrison Ford Shoulder Injury to Delay Filming 3 Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3184238/harrison-ford-signed-off-filming-indiana-jones-serious-injury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HE’S taken on the Nazis, overcome the evil Thuggee cult and found the Holy Grail. But when it comes to nasty shoulder injuries, Harrison Ford has had to finally admit defeat. I can exclusively reve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy's shock tests caused collapse?</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2021-06-29/shock-tests-condo-collapse-1995288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People continue to pine for answers after last week’s horrific condo collapse in Surfside, Fla. It may be weeks or months before the actual cause is known — but that doesn’t stop non-experts coming up with their own hypotheses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lava Fire erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/lava-fire-erupts-in-northern-california-amid-stifling-heat-wave/ar-AALAQpe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze has consumed more than 13,000 acres and may be a harbinger of a serious fire season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active-Duty Marine Plotted to Bomb DNC, Feds Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/right-wing-death-squad-active-duty-marine-plotted-to-bomb-dnc-murder-black-people-feds-say/ar-AALANYM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An active-duty U.S. Marine came under federal investigation for allegedly plotting with at least two others to assassinate minorities, drug users, and employees of the Democratic National Committee with explosives, rocket launchers, and automatic rifles. That’s according to a newly unsealed FBI search warrant affidavit obtained by The Daily Beast, which indicates USMC Private First Class Travis Owens and his partners in the unrealized murder...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Sue Me Like That: Anatomy of Copyright Troll...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/don-t-sue-me-like-that-anatomy-of-a-copyright-troll/ar-AALyIRK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How rock photographer Larry Philpot perfected a perfectly legal way to extract settlements from his images of Tom Petty, Willie Nelson, Ted Nugent, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENTLEY Tests Futuristic Biofuel By Climbing Pike's Peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/bentley-s-renewable-fuel-continental-gt3-earns-2nd-place-pikes-peak-time-attack-finish/ar-AALypht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Driver Rhys Millen set out to break the Time Attack record, but a problem with the car -- and the course -- kept that from happening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Throwable military robots sent to assist...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Throwable-military-robots-sent-to-assist-with-16283702.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First responders on the ground at the Miami Beach-area condo that partially collapsed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines hopes all-female Coast Guard unit will keep Chinese ships away...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-Philippines-hopes-this-all-female-Coast-Guard-16283600.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With tensions rising in the South China Sea, the Philippines is turning to an unusual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal team expects charges in coming days...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-organization-charges-expected-manhattan-district-attorney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Organization's legal team anticipates the company will be accused of tax crimes, attorney Ronald Fischetti said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARINGS 20S: Inflation Eats at Surging Wages...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/inflation-eats-at-surging-u-s-wages-with-biden-agenda-at-stake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation Eats at Surging U.S. Wages With Biden Agenda at Stake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying car completes test flight between airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-57651843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vehicle runs on regular fuel and can travel up to 1,000km while airborne, its creator says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>112-year-old Puerto Rican Becomes World's Oldest Living Man...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/112-year-old-puerto-rican-becomes-world-s-oldest-living-man-01625048107</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emilio Flores Marquez from Puerto Rico has become the world's oldest living man at an age of 112 years and 326 days old, Guinness World Records announced on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whose rocket is bigger? How Musk, Branson, Bezos space stuff stacks up...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/29/musk-branson-and-bezos-in-race-to-conquer-space-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Jeff Bezos announced that he would fly into suborbit with his brother, the winner of an auctioned seat and another crew member on July 20, Richard Branson countered with a flight plan of his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NYTIMES editor says he suffered from burnout, wished for death...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/29/ex-new-york-times-styles-editor-says-he-suffered-from-burnout-wished-for-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Choire Sicha quit his high-profile job as editor of the New York Times Styles section in April because he was so burned out that he sometimes cried at work. In a recent blog post to promote a pal&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion grips NYC mayor race after vote 'discrepancy'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/29/eric-adams-narrowly-edges-garcia-in-preliminary-ranked-choice-results-boe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn Borough President Eric Adams’ lead in the Democratic primary shrank to just two percentage points Tuesday as Kathryn Garcia vaulted past Maya Wiley into second place under …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANADA TURNS INTO DEATH VALLEY:  121-DEGREES!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scores-dead-heat-wave-grips-222446237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scores of deaths in Canada's Vancouver area are likely linked to a grueling heat wave, authorities said Tuesday, as the country recorded its highest ever temperature amid scorching conditions that extended to the US Pacific Northwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate ads by conservatives, for conservatives, shift views...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210630113113-dvenb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research shows online ads by leading political conservatives talking about their concerns about climate change boosted worry about the issue among other conservative voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: SUPPORT FOR JOE ERODES AMONG DEMS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210630084859-v7v7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/POLL (POLL, PIX, GRAPHICS):POLL-Support for Biden erodes among Democrats as U.S. looks past pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart inflammation after shots higher-than-expected in military study...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210629173730-oxieu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-VACCINES (PIX):Heart inflammation after COVID-19 shots higher-than-expected in study of U.S. military</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite's impending fiery demise shows how important it is to keep space clean...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/satellites-impending-fiery-demise-shows-120052408.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small satellite is speeding to its demise in a test that could help clean up space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA SPYING ON TUCKER?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/tucker-carlson-nsa-spy-claim-jen-psaki-fox-news-1234783858/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency has given Tucker Carlson a lesson in spycraft and fake news. One which looks certain to crank up the volume in the now war of words, real and imagined. In a rare social…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Teen Drowned His Father In Pool To Baptize Him, 'Exorcise Demons'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/06/29/jack-callahan-duxbury-massachusetts-father-murder-exorcism-baptism-island-creek-pond-massachusetts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Callahan was ordered held without bail after pleading not guilty to a murder charge Tuesday in Plymouth District Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice to World Premiere 'HALLOWEEN KILLS'...</title>
      <link>https://bloody-disgusting.com/movie/3672032/venice-world-premiere-halloween-kills-honor-jamie-lee-curtis-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bloody-disgusting.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first official reviews for Halloween Kills will arrive this September when the David Gordon Green-directed sequel World Premieres at the 78th Venice Film Festival, which runs September 1-11 on the Lido. The festival will this year award a Golden Lion for Lifetime Achievement to American actress Jamie Lee Curtis, add Deadline who says the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William, Harry to unveil Diana statue as royal rift simmers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-entertainment-royalty-50f64f8f06ef4a481fbafe1a93fb9558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — They were once so close. Princes William and Harry grew up together, supported each other after their mother’s untimely death and worked side by side as they began their royal duties — two brothers seemingly bonded for life by blood, tradition and tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error mars count...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/eric-adams-lead-shrinks-nyc-democratic-mayor-primary-0c92450b5dbb57018e2f8e15d8471a97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Democratic primary for mayor of New York City was thrown into a state of confusion Tuesday when election officials retracted their latest report on the vote count after realizing it had been corrupted by test data never cleared from a computer system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy dies after being repeatedly slammed in judo class...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-coaching-taiwan-judo-sports-47392a250cfb597c395f3a227889bc23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — A 7-year-old Taiwanese boy has died after being repeatedly slammed by his coach and others at a judo class. The boy, identified only by his surname, Huang, was taken off life support on Tuesday night after being in a coma since the April 21 incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINKEDIN breach reportedly exposes data of 92% of users, including salaries...</title>
      <link>https://9to5mac.com/2021/06/29/linkedin-breach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;9to5mac.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A second massive LinkedIn breach reportedly exposes the data of 700M users, which is more than 92% of the total 756M users. The database ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYAL CARIBBEAN asks unvaccinated to show proof of insurance...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/29/royal-caribbean-asks-unvaccinated-florida-guests-to-show-proof-of-insurance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Caribbean International said on Tuesday it would require unvaccinated guests traveling from Florida to show proof of insurance that covers COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minister's affair on camera prompts questions about surveillance among UK political elite...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/06/29/uk/matt-hancock-leak-british-security-intl-cmd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westminster, the beating heart of British politics, is very worried about how safe the UK government's most important secrets are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too hot? The robots aren't complaining...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/the-long-game/2021/06/29/too-hot-the-robots-arent-complaining-493413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions skipped church during pandemic. Will they return?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-pandemics-lifestyle-health-religion-cd5fbac2318cb58e1d5ec4a5d1c00ecc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALDOBORO, Maine (AP) — With millions of people having stayed home from places of worship during the coronavirus pandemic, struggling congregations have one key question: How many of them will return?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rolling blackouts for parts of Northwest amid heat wave...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-change-government-and-politics-business-environment-and-nature-6a66be20ed86ad18ed131156c9f7a517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOKANE, Wash. (AP) — The unprecedented Northwest U.S. heat wave that slammed Seattle and Portland, Oregon, moved inland Tuesday — prompting a electrical utility in Spokane, Washington, to warn that people will face more rolling blackouts amid heavy power demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Agrees to $1 Million Fine for Violating Human Rights Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-news-agrees-to-dollar1-million-fine-for-violating-human-rights-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News effectively admitted to a pattern of misconduct and has agreed to pay a civil penalty in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland limits indoor dining to fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210629-ireland-limits-indoor-dining-to-fully-vaccinated-over-delta-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ireland said on Tuesday it will restrict indoor drinking and eating in bars and restaurants to those who are fully vaccinated against COVID-19 or who have previously been infected by it due to concer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPad the size of CAR-WHEEL 'secretly being created'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3181101/apple-secretly-ipad-car-wheel-biggest-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE is considering building its biggest iPad yet to further blur the lines between laptops and tablets, according to a report. The Cupertino iPhone-maker could release a tablet with a much larger…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New gatekeepers: GOOGLE will warn you about 'fake news' websites before you click...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3174436/google-warn-fake-news-websites-click/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOGLE has begun warning users that its search results may be unreliable. The feature is aimed at breaking news stories, when information is often rapidly changing and sometimes inaccurate. Read al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivor describes escape: 'I kept going, screaming... I want to live'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/survivor-describes-escape-from-florida-condo-collapse-i-kept-going-screaming-i-want-to-live/ar-AALAzj3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maria Iliana Monteagudo was asleep early Thursday morning when the building started moving. She grabbed her purse, credit cards, and blew out a candle as she escaped her unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Wuhan lab's rumbling sewers and filthy cages...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3174242/wuhan-labs-leak-covid-chaotic-crowded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH crumbling sewers and filthy animal cages, these are the shoddy conditions of labs in Wuhan which could have unleashed Covid. A bombshell study found grotty sewage systems were potentially cont…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friendly dolphin could die if people keep riding it...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article252442433.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is clear that the dolphin is already in danger from the human interactions.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online activism spilling into streets of Southern California, sparking post-Trump movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Online-activism-is-spilling-into-the-streets-of-16281500.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA ANA, Calif. -- A week before California reopened its economy, a group of 100 or so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta variant  prompts new restrictions worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/spread-of-delta-variant-prompts-new-restrictions-worldwide/ar-AALwoub?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new curbs on travel and daily life stretched from Australia and Bangladesh to South Africa and Germany. The World Health Organization urged faster deployment of coronavirus vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailer: First look at 'SOPRANOS' prequel...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-videos/sopranos-prequel-trailer-many-saints-of-newark-1234973262/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first new Sopranos content in 14 years has been released. Below is the trailer for the long-awaited prequel movie The Many Saints of Newark. The film stars an ensemble cast that includes Michae…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant 'elephant pig' born with trunk and one eye baffles farmer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mutant-elephant-pig-born-trunk-24418776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deformed piglet looked barely able to move in a short video taken at the farm in the Philippines. Despite vets being called, it sadly died shortly after being born</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/slideshows/healthiest-communities-in-the-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;See the counties that scored the highest in U.S. News' annual Healthiest Communities ranking and analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Alamos County, NM, Named Healthiest Community...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-06-29/los-alamos-americas-healthiest-county-has-a-formula-for-battling-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Alamos County repeats as No. 1 in U.S. News’ Healthiest Communities rankings, boasting a reliance on science and a community that proved effective in dealing with the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS:  NSA SPYING ON NETWORK!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tucker-carlson-claims-the-nsa-is-monitoring-his-communications-in-an-attempt-to-take-this-show-off-the-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson claimed on Monday night that his communications are being monitored by the NSA "in an attempt to take this show off the air."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Did Netanyahu sabotage ties with USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/netanyahu-denies-sabotaging-ties-with-us-672274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former prime minister Benjamin Netanyahu denied charges that he was deliberately trying to harm Israel's relationship with the Biden administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming culture war over returning to the office...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/the-coming-culture-war-over-returning-to-the-office-090034061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has been a culture war from the very start: over lockdowns, masks, schools, vaccines. It's likely that it will be ushered out with an entirely new culture war, centered on cubicles and desks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN: LA urges everyone to wear mask indoors as variant spreads...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/l-a-county-urges-everyone-to-wear-masks-in-public-indoor-places-as-delta-variant-spreads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials in Los Angeles County now strongly recommend that people wear masks indoors in public places — regardless of their vaccination status — to prevent the spread of the highly transmis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani being investigated over Turkish lobbying...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/giuliani-investigated-turkish-lobbying-source/story?id=78557555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump's attorney Rudy Giuliani is facing a federal inquiry over possible improper lobbying for Turkey, a source familiar with the matter told ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JILL BIDEN GETS VOGUE COVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3180183/jill-biden-vogue-cover-melania-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JILL Biden has secured the Vogue cover Melania Trump always wanted – and used the interview to take a swipe at Donald, calling Joe “calmer.” The First Lady, wearing a floral Oscar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Great Resignation' gains steam as return-to-work plans take effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/29/more-people-plan-to-quit-as-return-to-work-plans-go-into-effect-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the pandemic, a growing number of workers are rethinking what they want in a job and a lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boring news cycle deals blow to partisan media...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/partisan-media-biden-trump-26f54a8b-d4e2-4319-a185-bd5f55ac661f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outlets most dependent on controversy have struggled to find a foothold in the Biden era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicidal crises, mental fatigue: Kids grapple with reentry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-cf6997107e7991393c70dd62ddbd196e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two suicidal crises during pandemic isolation, 16-year-old Zach Sampson feels stronger but worries his social skills have gone stale. Amara Bhatia has overcome her pandemic depression but the teen feels worn down, in a state of "neutralness.'' Virginia Shipp is adjusting but says returning to normal “is kind of unnormal for me.’’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill To Decriminalize Psychedelics, Ecstasy In CA Gains Momentum...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/28/sb519-proposal-decriminalize-psychedelics-mushrooms-mdma-lsd-gains-momentum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bay Area lawmaker's bill that would decriminalize the personal possession of several psychedelic drugs begins winding its way through the California State Assembly this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Prices Jump Most in Three Decades...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-housing-prices-jump-most-132347212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. home prices jumped the most in more than 30 years in April.Nationally, the S&amp;P CoreLogic Case-Shiller index of property values climbed 14.6% from a year earlier, the biggest gain in data going back to 1988. That came after 13.2% increase in March, and was the 11th straight month that price gains accelerated.Home prices in 20 U.S. cities, meanwhile, jumped 14.9%, beating the median estimate in a survey of Bloomberg economists and was the biggest gain since 2005.“April’s perfor</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
