<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ABRAMS DOWN IN GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/georgia/governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Georgia Governor election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM COMES UP SHORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/florida/governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Florida Governor election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVIDED STATES OF AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/midterm-election-results-2018-n931571?DFsa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Ted Cruz held off a strong challenge from Beto O'Rourke for Senate in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM STARS WIPEOUT:  BETO LOSES...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/ted-cruz-democrat-beto-orourke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Senator Ted Cruz has hung on to defeat Rep. Beto O'Rourke, CBS News projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kobach Goes Down in Kansas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/democrat-laura-kelly-projected-to-beat-republican-kris-kobach-for-kansas-governor-nbc-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race was in a dead heat days before the election, with Kobach either up by 1 point or in a tie with Kelly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shalala in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/democrat-donna-shalala-will-beat-maria-salazar-in-florida-27th-district.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shalala, Bill Clinton's HHS secretary, is the second Democrat to flip a Republican-held House district in the midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MD Republican Governor Reelected...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/gov-larry-hogan-wins-maryland-governors-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Larry Hogan has won Maryland's governor's race. He is the first GOP governor to win a second term in Maryland since 1954.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez to be youngest woman ever elected to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/06/politics/ocasio-cortez-youngest-woman-ever/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Democratic congressional nominee Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez will win her general election race easily and become the youngest woman ever in Congress, CNN has projected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAYLOR SWIFT FAILS TO ELECT DEMOCRAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/11/06/taylor-swift-fails-to-take-out-marsha-blackburn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop superstar Taylor Swift's endorsement of Democratic Senate candidate Phil Bredesen and Congressional candidate Jim Cooper failed to persuade the great people of Tennessee Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida votes to restore ex-felon voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/6/18052374/florida-amendment-4-felon-voting-rights-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victory means more than 1 million people will regain the right to vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp political divide, rising hostility propel heavy voter turnout...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/nov/6/sharp-political-divide-rising-hostility-propel-hea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans stormed the polls Tuesday to send an angry message, driven by a sharp political divide that fuels hostility toward the other side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC PROJECTS DEMS TAKE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/2018-house-election-results-n931416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats could take as many as 31 seats currently held by Republicans, according to the estimate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll chaos - busted machines, 3hr lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7677741/us-midterms-broken-machine-flip-votes  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE claim broken polling machines ‘flipped their vote in front of their eyes’ as chaos hit US midterms. Voters in South Carolina said their candidate picks, including in the governor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Discussion Turns to What Went Wrong...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/election/fox-news-throwing-in-the-towel-discussion-turns-to-what-went-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News Throwing in the Towel? Discussion Turns to What Went Wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Warns: 2018 Thanksgiving Travel Will Be Unprecedented, Busiest Season On Record Expected...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/transportation-security-administration-thanksgiving-holiday-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travel experts are already predicting the busiest Thanksgiving season at the airport on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2018-election/midterms/fl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find real-time results and maps for the 2018 Florida midterm election. Follow NBC News' coverage &amp; results of FL Senate, House and Governors elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First HOUSE seat flip: Wexton Beats Comstock...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/card/wexton-beats-comstock-va-10-nbc-news-projects-n932671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Jennifer Wexton has defeated Barbara Comstock in the race for Virginia's Tenth Congressional District, NBC News projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS:  HOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 House election results &amp; live maps by state. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Rebukes Its Hosts for Participating in Trump Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/06/us/politics/trump-fox-news-hannity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The line between the Trump White House and Fox has always been a little blurry, but in one moment at least, the fusion of president and network seemed complete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2018-election/midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get election results in real-time as NBC News covers state results, exit polls, maps and candidates. View the House estimate, Senate balance and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVS... </title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/midterms-2018/gubernatorial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gubernatorial elections will be held in 36 states and three territories in 2018. Fox News is monitoring the governor races in the 2018 midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://graphics.axios.com/2018-11-06-midterm-election/index.html?view=S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;graphics.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://graphics.axios.com/2018-11-06-midterm-election/index.html?view=G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;graphics.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fullpage/midterm-election-map-2018-live-results-58723598</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow hourly state-by-state senate, governor and house results and see who is in the lead Democrats or Republicans. House forecast in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record high turnout for nonwhites in Georgia races...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-2018-exit-poll-analysis-56-percent-country/story?id=59006586&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_3_hero_headlines_bsq_hed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the polls are set to close in many states, preliminary exit poll results show a deep divide along party lines: Georgia In preliminary exit poll results, turnout among nonwhites is a record 40 percent, including 30 percent black voters. The previous high among nonwhites was 36 percent in 2014 –...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden issues surveillance warning to Israelis...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/snowden-issues-surveillance-warning-israelis-225042347.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US whistleblower Edward Snowden urged Israelis to be on guard against heavy-handed government and private surveillance in a speech by video link Tuesday and defended his 2013 massive leak of classified documents. Snowden highlighted Israel's high-tech capabilities, but warned that accepting too</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Meat tax' to save lives, say health experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apos-meat-tax-apos-almost-180000966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ‘meat tax’ which would almost double the price of a packet of sausages should be brought in to prevent thousands of Britons dying each year, health experts have said. Researchers at Oxford University set out to determine the level of tax needed to offset the healthcare costs of eating red and processed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to become world's No. 1 travel destination...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/destinations/2018/11/06/china-become-worlds-no-1-travel-destination-beating-france/1905119002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.4 billion trips will be made to China in 2018, up 5 percent from last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient dies 'after robot surgery error'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/05/heart-surgeon-turned-training-pioneering-robot-used-operation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A heart surgeon turned down the chance to train on a pioneering robot he used in an operation in which the patient later died, an inquest has heard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two more associates of Roger Stone testify before Mueller grand jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Two-more-associates-of-Roger-Stone-testify-before-13368109.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two more associates of Roger Stone, the longtime adviser to President Donald Trump, testified recently before a grand jury hearing evidence in the investigation into Russia's interference in the 2016 presidential election - the latest in a series of witnesses connected to Stone whose testimony has been sought by the special counsel. David Lugo, a filmmaker who interviewed Stone for a movie, told The Washington Post Tuesday that he has turned over hundreds of text messages, emails and Facebook messages to the grand jury. Lugo, who was a co-producer on the 2015 Oliver Stone film, "A Good American," also said he testified on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin Talk Show Bumped to Saturdays Amid Historically Low Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/alec-baldwin-show-bumped-saturdays-december-abc-1158835</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news follows the actor's arrest and dismal ratings for the talk show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ORANGE planet: Stunning NASA image from Space Station shows Earth enveloped in rare 'airglow'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6360453/The-ORANGE-planet-Stunning-NASA-image-ISS-reveals-Earth-rare-airglow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The orange hue enveloping Earth is known as airglow, a diffuse bands of light that stretch 50 to 400 miles into our atmosphere,' NASA explained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI detects Alzheimer's disease SIX years early...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6359979/AI-detects-Alzheimers-disease-SIX-years-early-100-accuracy-small-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new AI system is 100% accurate in its predictions of Alzheimer's made based on subtle metabolic brain changes - and it catches the the disease six years early, a University of San Francisco study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More bones unearthed at Vatican embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bfc2871b2cc540c8a6ca3f490fbf3e5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — More bones were found on the grounds of the Vatican embassy in Italy, adding grisly new evidence to the growing mystery over who was buried on Holy See territory and why. As police returned to the compound Tuesday, coroner Giovanni Arcudi said preliminary examinations of bones found last week indicated they belonged to a woman likely in her 30s, "not an adolescent." The finding is significant since speculation has focused on whether the bones were Emanuela Orlandi's. She was the daughter of a Vatican employee who disappeared in 1983 at age 15.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tanzania: 10 men arrested for being 'gay'...</title>
      <link>https://www.amnesty.org/en/latest/news/2018/11/tanzania-10-men-arrested-in-zanzibar-for-being-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.amnesty.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They were found at a party sitting in pairs, the police said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS at Crossroads as CEO Search Begins to Ramp Up...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/cbs-board-redstone-moonves-viacom-1203021104/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two months after Leslie Moonves’ ouster from CBS Corp., the search for his successor has been sluggish and only now starting in earnest. But it won’t be a speedy process. The word that the C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>*Clinton campaign manager cautions against exit polls: 'They may break your heart'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/415312-clinton-2016-campaign-manager-cautions-against-exit-polls-they-may-break</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robby Mook, the former campaign manager for Hillary Clinton's 2016 Democratic presidential bid, cautioned ahead of Tuesday's midterms to treat exit polls "like online dating profiles."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEALTH CARE TOP ISSUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/card/watch-health-care-replaces-economy-most-important-issue-voters-early-n932536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 sailors busted for LSD on US nuclear carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2018/11/06/officials-ronald-reagan-lsd-probe-bigger-than-you-think-14-nuke-sailors-snagged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fourteen sailors from the Ronald Reagan's nuclear reactor department face discipline in connection to hallucinogenic drug abuse, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl Scouts sue Boy Scouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/girl-scouts-sue-boy-scouts-for-trademark-infringement-2018-11-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Girl Scouts say a Boy Scout rebranding effort is cutting into their turf, causing confusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55% disapprove of Trump performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/exit-polls-show-trump-a-major-factor-in-2018-midterm-election-voting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two-thirds of voters said President Trump was a factor in their vote, and a majority do not approve of his job performance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly two-thirds said president was a reason for their vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/222fd1571d744aec903604542eb11b70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Health care and immigration were high on voters' minds as they cast ballots in the midterm elections, according to a wide-ranging survey of the American electorate conducted by The Associated Press. AP VoteCast also shows a majority of voters considered President Donald Trump a factor in their votes. Control of the Senate and the House of Representatives is at stake in the first nationwide election of Trump's presidency. Democrats are hoping to take over one or both chambers to put a check on the president. At the same time, Trump is encouraging voters to view the election as a referendum on his leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats flip Republicans in first result of night...</title>
      <link>https://www.guampdn.com/story/news/2018/11/06/guam-general-election-results/1900152002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.guampdn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55% disapprove of Trump performance...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-day-2018-americans-set-vote-historic-contest/story?id=58907692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are voting Tuesday in historic midterms, with control of the House, the Senate and 36 governorships at stake in a vote seen as a referendum on President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXITS:   56% say country on 'wrong track'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/election-2018-exit-poll-analysis-56-percent-country/story?id=59006586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump and control of Congress are front and center in this election, and preliminary results from the national exit poll touch on both of them: In results so far, 44 percent of voters approve of Trump’s job performance, while 55 percent disapprove. And while the House races will be fought...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia plans moon base inhabited by 'avatar robots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/russia/443196-russia-space-avatar-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After unveiling an ambitious plan to install a permanent base on the moon, Russia’s space boss Dmitry Rogozin has now added a truly sci-fi-esque detail: humans will control it from Earth through sophisticated ‘avatar robotics.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wearing CROCS survives crocodile thrashing after breaking into farm, jumping into pond...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/florida/st-johns-county/st-augustine/man-bitten-after-jumping-into-st-augustine-alligator-farm-exhibit-authorities-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who broke into the St. Augustine Alligator Farm after hours and jumped into a crocodile exhibit was bitten and had to be taken to a hospital, according to St. Johns County authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Holiday sales predicted to surpass $1 Trillion for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/us-christmas-retail-sales-to-surpass-1-trillion-this-year-emarketer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Total retail sales in the U.S will hit $1.002 trillion during the Christmas holiday period, marking the "strongest growth since 2011," according to eMarketer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Donde votar' spikes to top of searches...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/donde-votar-spikes-to-top-of-Google-Searches-13366861.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Google Trends, 'Donde votar' - or 'where to vote - shot up to the top search term Tuesday morning, with search frequency jumping 3,350%, according to Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian Physicists Write 'Perfect Pizza' Equation...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64016-physics-of-perfect-pizza.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Physicists and food historians teamed up to create the ultimate pizza equation. The verdict: find a brick oven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T to cut off customers' service in piracy crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-att-to-terminate-service-over-piracy-for-first-time-1541465187-749442e3-7b71-4cc7-a694-865779b6fb96.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The copyright infringers are often illegally pirating hundreds of hours of stolen content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Soda Takes Cues From Tobacco To Combat Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/11/05/664435761/big-soda-and-the-ballot-soda-industry-takes-cues-from-tobacco-to-combat-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in Oregon and Washington will decide Tuesday whether to strip cities of their ability to tax sugary drinks, thanks to ballot initiatives backed by Big Soda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unveils 'Heavenly Palace' space station...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-china-unveils-heavenly-palace-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China unveiled on Tuesday a replica of its first permanently crewed space station, which would replace the international community's orbiting laboratory and symbolises the country's major ambitions beyond Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-old leads cops on high speed chase after mother takes PLAYSTATION away...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/metro/2018/11/mom-took-playstation-away-so-11-year-old-cleveland-boy-led-police-on-second-high-speed-chase-in-13-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 11-year-old boy was arrested in connection with his second high-speed chase with police in 13 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  Trump to 'challenge legitimacy of vote' if Republicans lose...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6360225/Biden-says-Trump-guaranteed-challenge-legitimacy-vote-Republicans-lose.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden signaled after casting his vote in Wilmington that he's ready to take on Donald Trump if he opts in to what's likely to be a crowded 2020 field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee polling sites without power...</title>
      <link>https://www.wvlt.tv/content/news/Severe-weather-causes-disruptions-at-East-Tennessee-polling-locations-499793841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wvlt.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After severe storms rolled through East Tennessee Tuesday morning, several polling locations were forced to use paper ballots and battery back-up systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: FOXCONN may import workers for U.S. plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181106-foxconn-may-import-workers-us-plant-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Acosta Signs Autographs at Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2018/11/05/watch-cnns-jim-acosta-writes-cnn-is-real-news-on-sign-at-trump-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN reporter Jim Acosta signed an autograph for a Trump fan at a rally Monday by writing "CNN is real news."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agenda at stake...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/control-congress-verdict-trump-stake-u-elections-111651400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first national elections since Trump captured the White House in a stunning 2016 upset is a referendum on the polarizing president and a test of whether Democrats can turn the energy of the liberal anti-Trump resistance into victories at the ballot box. The Democrats have a good chance of winning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK referred to EU watchdog over targeting, fake ads...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/british-watchdog-refers-facebook-irish-data-body-101326494--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Information Commissioner has been investigating the use of data analytics to influence politics after consultancy Cambridge Analytica obtained the personal data of 87 million Facebook users from a researcher. The British watchdog said on Tuesday as part of that inquiry it had also found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGMENT DAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9bf157473af413c8cd3668e1f98ff62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's Election Day in America, and voters will deliver their first verdict of President Donald Trump's tumultuous tenure in a midterm that's expected to draw historic numbers to the polls. Immigration, the economy, women's issues, partisanship — all weighed heavily on voters' minds as they cast ballots to decide control of Congress and put Trumpism to the test. Though not on the ballot, the president looms large over decision day, among both supporters and detractors. Across the country, people are talking about this election as one of the most momentous in their lifetimes — a fight for the very soul of America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election presents big test for Trumpism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/705ae08bd6f44012b564b0f37b5ca089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were first-time voters and straight-ticket voters and some who, this go-around, switched sides. They went to the polls considering the caravan of migrants trudging across Mexico, their health insurance and their paychecks, an impotent Congress and the nation's poisonous political culture that has divided even families and friends along party lines. More than anything on this Election Day in America, in a midterm contest like no other before it, voters cast their ballots with one man in mind: President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Democrats Ready to Dominate Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/midterm-election/2018/11/06/california-democrats-set-to-dominate-congress-if-u-s-house-flips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Democrats with lots of seniority are expected to dominate the leadership of the U.S. House of Representatives if their party wins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron pushes for 'true European army'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46108633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As France marks the World War One Armistice, he says Europe must defend itself better alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: Elections 'about health care'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/408de7504f57429497df82a5bd52a35d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on Election Day (all times local): 11:45 a.m. Long lines and malfunctioning machines marred the first hours of voting in some precincts across the U.S. Some of the biggest problems Tuesday were in Georgia, a state with a hotly contested gubernatorial election. Voters reported waiting up to three hours to vote. At a polling place in Snellville, Georgia, more than 100 people took turns sitting in children's chairs and on the floor as they waited in line for hours. Voter Ontaria Woods said about two dozen people who had come to vote left because of the lines. At a poll site in Atlanta, voters waited in the rain in long lines that stretched around the building. Hannah Ackermann said officials at the polling site offered various explanations for the delay, including blaming workers who didn't show up and overloaded machines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Man Threatens To Shoot Up Polling Place After Told Not Registered To Vote...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/washington-county-election-day-polling-place-shooting-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has been arrested on charges that he threatened to shoot workers at a Washington County polling place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential juror tossed for wanting El Chapo autograph...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/potential-juror-tossed-wanting-el-chapo-autograph-195218678.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A potential juror in the mammoth New York trial of Mexican drug baron Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman was dismissed by the judge on Tuesday after requesting the defendant's autograph. The man, whose identity is withheld along with all potential jurors under the rigorous security arrangements</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine malfunctions all over the nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/midterms-2018-voters-face-malfunctioning-machines-long-lines-polls-across-n932156</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security says that there has been no immediate uptick in hacking attempts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twins Unexpectedly Give Birth Hour Apart...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/central-california-twin-give-birth-hours-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twin sisters in California passed on their tradition of sharing a birthday, giving birth to baby daughters within an hour of each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mosh Pit' Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6fb6de6fdb034b889d301efd12602e21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Long lines and malfunctioning machines marred the early hours of voting in some precincts across the country Tuesday. Some of the biggest problems were in Georgia, a state with a hotly contested gubernatorial election, where some voters reported waiting up to three hours to vote. At a polling place in Snellville, Georgia, more than 100 people took turns sitting in children's chairs and on the floor as they waited in line for hours. Voting machines at the Gwinnett County precinct did not work, so poll workers offered provisional paper ballots while trying to get a replacement machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38.4 MILLION ALREADY VOTED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/georgia-gop-gov-candidate-kemp-defends-vote-hacking-investigation-i-n931336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The figure has shattered the total cast ahead of Election Day in 2014, suggesting a high level of enthusiasm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Fattest States In USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksat.com/news/see-where-texas-weighs-in-on-list-of-fattest-states-in-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WalletHub on Tuesday released its ranking of the fattest states in America (Right before the holidays! Seriously?) and Texas made the top 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-rare albino raccoon spotted in backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/animalkind/2018/11/06/memphis-albino-raccoon-found-collierville-released-meeman-shelby-forest/1902095002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weâ€™ve never seen a raccoon like this before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia reports computer bug on International Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russia-reports-computer-bug-international-space-station-182156419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia's space agency says that one of the International Space Station's computers has malfunctioned, but the glitch doesn't pose any risks to the crew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol cancels Election Day 'exercise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-florida-polling-place-lockdown-over-gun-scare-175728381--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The Latest on voting problems in the midterm election (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Machines in Detroit...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2018/11/06/voters-turned-away-due-to-missing-voting-machines-in-detroit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first issues at precincts across Michigan are popping up. Here's some of the snafus we've seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver let teen car surf for $40, resulting in death...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/nation-world/national/article221164315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Uber driver faces manslaughter charges in Suffolk County, NY, after cops said he let a Long Island teen car surf for $40, resulting in a fall and head injury that killed the teen hours later as he slept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ABSOLUTE ZOO': Voting Chaos at Polling Booths...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/overcrowding-polls-elections-midterm-pictures-vote-scanners-broken-new-york-new-jersey-connecticut-499825501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight at Miss Bumbum contest over fake butt accusation...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/06/catfight-breaks-out-at-miss-bumbum-contest-over-fake-butt-accusation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s Miss BumBum competition ended in a shambles after contestants resorted to violence on stage following cheating allegations. The fight was sparked by one contestant accusing the other of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA spacecraft makes 1st close approach to sun...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/32f624584698447d9d7aa450cab9c4d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A NASA spacecraft has made its first close approach to the sun, just 2 1/2 months after liftoff. The Parker Solar Probe flew within 15 million miles (24 million kilometers) of the sun's surface Monday night. Its speed topped 213,000 mph (342,000 kph) relative to the sun, as it penetrated the outer solar atmosphere, or corona. No spacecraft has ever gotten so close to our star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Attorney Testifies To Grand Jury...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/06/roger-stone-mueller-grand-jury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyler Nixon supported Stone's claims about Wikileaks contact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans asking GOOGLE who to vote for...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/805931/lot-americans-are-hoping-google-tell-how-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election Day has Americans turning to our digital civics teacher, Google, with all sorts of questions on when, where, and how to vote. The top trending search Tuesday morning was "dÃ³nde votar," the search engine reported, which is "where to vote" in Spanish. "Where to vote" in English also trended, though with a smaller spike. "DÃ³nde votar" ("where to vote") is the top trending search on Google in the US today - spiking 3,350%.#Midterms #vote https://t.co/7P9QmWr3G9 pic.twitter.com/AQe5gkMw8V â€” GoogleTrends (@GoogleTrends) November 6, 2018 Some of the trending questions don't focus on logistics. As of this writing, "who to vote for today," "what are we voting for today," and "what do midterm elections do?" are among the less, uh, encouraging Google trends. Google also tracks which issues have interested voters most in the run-up to the midterms. Immigration and health care consistently hold the top two spots, with abortion, social security, and minimum wage jockeying for third. Bonnie Kristian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE says it won't be stationed at polling places looking for illegals...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article221192945.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICE said it would not be stationed at polling places during the midterm election, in an attempt to crack down on rumors before the voting started. Hoaxes claimed the immigration agency would be at polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGMENT DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6357771/Will-Trump-crush-Democrat-blue-wave-Americas-mid-term-elections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All 435 seats in the House of Representatives are on the ballot along with 35 of 100 seats in the Senate, with Democrats trying to take control of both from the Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting machine problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2018/11/06/midterm-elections-2018-monitoring-problems-polls/1832659002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters are casting ballots in the first nationwide election since 2016 amid expectations of long lines and polling irregularities. Here's the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBD-infused products being sold everywhere in California -- but are they legal?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldcourier.com/news/national/cbd-infused-products-are-being-sold-everywhere-in-california-but/article_b2cb1033-a5cd-5d78-986a-6c00fdff970d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Greg and Gary Avetisyan make no secret of it: They proudly sell all manner of products infused with CBD, from essential oils to bath bombs to fruity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200 mass graves of thousands of ISIS victims found...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/06/middleeast/mass-graves-isis-un-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mass gravesthat may contain up to 12,000 bodies have been found in areas formerly controlled by ISIS, a United Nations report revealed on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHIFF: If Dems Flip House, Renewing Russia Probe Top Priority...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2018/11/05/rep-schiff-if-democrats-flip-house-renewing-probe-on-russias-election-meddling-will-be-top-priority/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With fewer than 24 hours before polls open, Rep. Adam B. Schiff (D-Burbank) spent Monday afternoon stumping with Democrat Gil Cisneros, who’s locked in a tight battle with Republican Young Kim to replace her former boss Rep. Ed Royce (R-Fullerton). Schiff, ranking member of the House Intelligence Committee, said he was feeling optimistic about Democrats’ chances of netting the 23 seats they need to take back control of the House. If they succeed, Schiff is widely expected to take over as chair of the committee tasked with investigating Russia’s meddling in the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's okay to be white' flyers posted at another university...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/549fe3bdd059488e9032f72fd255d2da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW, Idaho (AP) — Flyers with the slogan "it's okay to be white" were posted on the University of Idaho campus and around Moscow last week as part of a provocation campaign by white nationalist groups. The Moscow-Pullman Daily News reports the flyers were an apparent repeat of a year-old campaign stemming from online message boards, intending to create strong reactions. Washington State University Communications Director Phil Weiler says the Pullman campus was the site of the same campaign last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise outcome could roil stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/11/06/midterm-election-impact-markets-and-401-k/1892337002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street analysts are downplaying the midterm election risks for the stock market, but admit unexpected outcomes could cause volatility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sits in feces on DELTA flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/2018/11/06/bay-city-man-sits-feces-delta-flight-michigan/1900563002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew Meehan said that the crew gave him two paper towels to clean up and a small bottle of gin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election systems face major test...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/415090-election-systems-on-tuesday-face-first-major-test-since-2016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials face a major test on Tuesday, when voters cast ballots in the first national election since Russia’s interference in the 2016 race for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman, 82, Dies Days After Casting First-Ever Ballot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcdfw.com/news/politics/Woman-82-Dies-Days-After-Casting-First-Ever-Ballot-499665521.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcdfw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gracie Lou Phillips, an 82-year-old North Texas woman who voted for the first time in her life last week, died surrounded by family members early Monday morning, her family confirms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Joy Reid at Center of Free-Speech Legal Fight Over Retweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/msnbc-s-joy-reid-at-center-free-speech-legal-fight-retweets-1158266 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter users think of the platform as the Wild West, but a defamation lawsuit against Reid could lead high-profile figures to think twice about what they amplify — especially since damages could be higher for those with big followings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos reveal how cross-dressing Nazis loved to wear women's clothes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6357677/Photographs-line-German-Nazi-soldiers-dressing-womens-clothing.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artist Martin Dammann had intended to research soldiers' lives in the Third Reich, and ended up stumbling across a surprising number of amateur photographs of Nazis dressed as women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisoners ask for execution by firing squad...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2018/11/05/tennessee-death-penalty-firing-squad/1893264002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for four Tennessee death row inmates are asking a federal judge to allow them to choose a firing squad as their means of execution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Day to test resistance...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c0be062914e048d79f70bcf120e1ccbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A turbulent election season that tested President Donald Trump's slash-and-burn political style against the strength of the Democratic resistance comes to a close as Americans cast ballots in the first national election of the Trump era. With voters going to the polls Tuesday, nothing is certain. Anxious Republicans privately expressed confidence in their narrow Senate majority but feared the House was slipping away. Trump, the GOP's chief messenger, warned that significant Democratic victories would trigger devastating consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-SS concentration camp guard goes on trial in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20181106/ex-ss-guard-now-94-goes-on-trial-in-germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former SS guard, aged 94, goes on trial Tuesday in Germany charged with complicity in mass murders at a Nazi concentration camp during World War II, in a case bearing symbolic and moral weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Airs Results Of Florida Gov Election In Test 'Misfire'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/msnbc-graphic-mistake-florida-governor-race-1202496555/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the kind of goof that the folks who scream about “fake news” likely will scream about. MSNBC this evening briefly put a graphic onscreen that showed “vote counts”…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA prepares to fight China...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/military/senkaku-islands-dispute-us-and-japan-draw-up-plans-to-defend-disputed-islands-from-china/news-story/2a21a93585f78175220fe1999927611a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Senkaku Islands are tiny rocky spurs, part of a scattering of islands between the northern tip of Taiwan and the Japanese home islands. They are rapidly turning into a flashpoint for war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booming business of background music...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/nov/06/inside-the-booming-business-of-background-music</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long read: Once derided, the successors to muzak have grown more sophisticated – and influential – than any of us realise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK blocks 115 accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/06/facebook-blocks-115-accounts-ahead-of-us-midterm-elections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook announced Monday evening that it had blocked 115 accounts on its services that may have been engaged in "coordinated inauthentic behavior" ahead of the U.S. midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient dies 'after robot surgery error'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/patient-died-after-robot-surgery-error-with-da-vinci-device-xkq8lpshx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patient died after a heart operation in which the surgeon was using a robot for the first time even though he had not been trained and did not have proper supervision, an inquest has been told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divine intervention? Bullet grazes teen kneeling down to pray...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/teen-grazed-by-bullet-while-praying-in-sw-harris-county/4629026/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deputies told Eyewitness News this situation could have been a lot worse if the girl had not been kneeling during the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fisherman pulls baby from sea alive in 'freakish miracle'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/05/new-zealand-fisherman-pulls-18-month-old-baby-sea-alive-freakish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fisherman in New Zealand pulled an 18-month-old baby from the sea alive after the boy went missing from his campsite where he was staying with his parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unveils new 'Heavenly Palace' space station as ISS days numbered...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181106-china-unveils-new-heavenly-palace-space-station-iss-days-numbered-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Japan's 'Ninja Boy', the prodigy who aims to stun Mayweather...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/sport/meet-japan-s--ninja-boy---the-prodigy-who-aims-to-stun-mayweather-10902024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese kickboxer Tenshin Nasukawa, who aims to make history by defeating boxing superstar Floyd Mayweather Jr, claims his left-hook is like a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poop in hand, Bill Gates backs toilet revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/poop-hand-bill-gates-backs-chinas-toilet-revolution-doc-1al7lu3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP braces for potential wipeout in gov races...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/415080-gop-braces-for-potential-wipeout-in-governors-races</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ranks of Republican governors are poised to thin after this year’s midterm elections, and some party strategists are bracing for major Democratic gains even in some of the most conservative states in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiding face? 'Gait recognition' IDs by walk...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/chinese-gait-recognition-tech-ids-people-walk-58988215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have begun deploying a new surveillance tool: "gait recognition" software that uses people's body shapes and how they walk to identify them, even when their faces are hidden from cameras. Already used by police on the streets of Beijing and Shanghai, "gait recognition"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  LIMBAUGH RALLIES FOR TRUMP IN CAPE GIRARDEAU...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-Erz55hr_7w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday, November 5, 2018: RSBN's Liz Willis and James Willis will be on hand as President Donald J. Trump holds a campaign style rally at the Show Me Center ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Fonda: 'Most Important Election of My Lifetime'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/jane-fonda-midterms-are-important-election-my-lifetime-1154055</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's hard for me to breathe right now," she said, before she heads to Michigan with Taraji P. Henson to help with get out the vote efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah fires back at racist robocall: 'Jesus don't like ugly'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/415100-oprah-fires-back-at-racist-robocall-jesus-dont-like-ugly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oprah Winfrey on Monday responded to a white supremacist group targeting her and Georgia gubernatorial candidate Stacey Abrams in a robocall to voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS hosts campaign for president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/415101-fox-news-hosts-join-trump-on-stage-at-missouri-campaign-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE GIRARDEAU, MO. — Fox News hosts Sean Hannity and Jeanine Pirro joined President Trump on stage at his final campaign rally of the midterms, singing the president's praises and urging attendees to vote Republican.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
