<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Rise and Fall of the Star White House Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/04/29/the-fall-of-the-white-house-correspondent-00028272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years covering the White House was a kind of golden ticket in the media. Then came the Biden administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's favorite inflation measure hit fresh 40-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/29/economy/pce-inflation-march/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insomnia, addiction, depression: Dark side of trading crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/savingandinvesting/insomnia-addiction-depression-the-dark-side-of-life-trading-crypto/ar-AAWJAhm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside plans for human DNA seed bank on Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/5225280/plans-human-dna-seed-bank-on-moon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACEX just launched a lot of human DNA to the International Space Station. The Crew-4 mission blasted off on April 27 and part of the cargo was a biobank containing DNA from 500 different species.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican who refuses to bend the knee surges in Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/29/trump-says-matt-dolan-is-not-fit-for-ohios-senate-seat-hes-gaining-ground-anyway-00028824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt Dolan, who wants the former president to stop pushing "lies about the outcome" of the 2020 election, is showing a late burst of momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loud boom and streaking fireball spook people in three states...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/world/loud-boom-and-streaking-fireball-spook-people-in-three-us-states/ar-AAWJ3tm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fireball, at its peak, shone more than 10 times brighter than a full moon, Nasa said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political stakes high as Beijing responds to virus outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-business-shanghai-beijing-172b7ef4b401adc7781486816e89248a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Classes suspended. Buildings and communities sealed off. Mass testing of residents. A rush to stock up on food, just in case. Beijing, China's sprawling capital, is starting to resemble other Chinese cities grappling with the latest wave of the omicron variant of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Calls Russia Relationship 'New Model' for World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-calls-russia-relationship-a-new-model-for-the-world/ar-AAWJ1GJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron Sublineages Evade Vax, Natural Immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/science/health/new-omicron-ba-4-ba-5-sublineages-may-evade-vaccines-natural-immunity-what-experts-say-11651220350640.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BA.4 and BA.5 sublineages appear to be more infectious than the earlier BA.2 lineage.The sublineages have been detected in seven of South Africa’s nine provinces and 20 countries worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS LOSES BILLIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/bezos-loses-13-billion-in-hours-as-amazon-shares-slump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos Loses $13 Billion in Hours as Amazon Shares Slump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio lawmaker calls pregnancies from rape 'opportunity'...</title>
      <link>https://wfin.com/local-news/ohio-lawmaker-calls-pregnancy-from-rape-an-opportunity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wfin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(ONN) - An Ohio lawmaker who has proposed a bill that would outlaw all abortions in the state is coming under fire for her comments about sexual assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Americans do not support politicians punishing firms for views...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/americans-not-support-politicians-punishing-101147765.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bipartisan majority of U.S. voters oppose politicians punishing companies over their stances on social issues, a cold reception for campaigns like Florida Governor Ron DeSantis' against Walt Disney Co, a Reuters/Ipsos poll found. The two-day poll completed on Thursday showed that 62% of Americans - including 68% of Democrats and 55% of Republicans - said they were less likely to back a candidate who supports going after companies for their views. DeSantis signed a bill last week that strips Disney of self-governing authority at its Orlando-area parks in retaliation for its opposition to a new Florida law that limits the teaching of LGBTQ issues in schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astroworld movie set for release despite lawyers' concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travis-scott-entertainment-business-movies-lawsuits-b7148bf011a3f6fe9b9bf4b6b4e2c80b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — The experiences of panicked concertgoers who couldn’t breathe and had no clear path to escape a massive crowd surge at last year’s deadly Astroworld music festival in Houston are featured in a documentary set for release Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin could declare WWIII in two days...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-probably-declare-new-world-26828838</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK defence secretary Ben Wallace has warned that Putin may try to "mobilise" the Russian people with a global offensive against "Nazis" as his invasion of Ukraine has "failed"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels raid schools and let kids joyride narco tanks in recruitment drive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/drug-cartels-raid-schools-indoctrinate-26830152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearsome drug cartels are trying to recruitment children into their ranks by taking over schools, offering students money and letting them joyride in their customised armoured vehicles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Crypto just one big Ponzi scheme?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/is-crypto-just-one-big-ponzi-scheme/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week we witnessed the latest — and perhaps more striking — sign that crypto might not be the future of finance. On Tuesday, Sam Bankman-Fried, founder of FTX, a huge crypto exchange, opened a can of worms by describing “yield farming” — crypto’s makeshift alternative to traditional bank lending — as a Ponzi scheme. [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Ties to China Could Create Headaches...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/29/musks-ties-to-china-could-create-headaches-for-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — When Elon Musk opened a Tesla factory in Shanghai in 2019, the Chinese government welcomed him with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia City Reckons With New District, Led by Marjorie Taylor Greene...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/29/a-georgia-city-reckons-with-a-new-district-led-by-marjorie-taylor-greene/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWDER SPRINGS, Ga. — Less than a 30-minute drive from Atlanta, Powder Springs embodies the changes reshaping Georgia politics. Shops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Trump, May Could Be Cruelest Month...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/28/for-trump-may-could-be-the-cruelest-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you doubt the power of Donald Trump’s endorsement, look no further than the Ohio Senate race. Since April 15,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First American casualty...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/28/politics/american-killed-ukraine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American citizen, Willy Joseph Cancel, was killed fighting alongside Ukrainian forces in Ukraine, members of Cancel's family confirmed to CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON PLUNGES ON WEAK FORECAST</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/28/amazon-amzn-q1-2022-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon gave a revenue forecast that trailed analysts'Â estimates and recorded a big loss on its Rivian investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID cases rise across bulk of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-cases-rise-across-bulk-of-the-us-1c5e8d29-d1c5-45eb-9678-85dc7ab863eb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID cases are on the rise in all but six states and Washington, D.C. as the Omicron subvariant continues to spread across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investor Who Called Housing Top and Bottom Says It's Time to Sell...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pimco-kiesel-called-housing-top-160339396.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bond manager Mark Kiesel sold his California home in 2006, when he presciently predicted the housing bubble would pop. He bought again in 2012, after U.S. prices fell more than 30% and found a floor. Most Read from BloombergFour European Gas Buyers Made Ruble Payments to RussiaPutin Is Losing So Here’s How He’ll Make the War WorseU.S. Economy Posts Surprise Contraction, Belying Solid Consumer PictureA Powerful Dynasty Bankrupted Sri Lanka in Just 30 MonthsStocks Surge Before Amazo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hang Mike Pence' rioters acted on orders 'from above,' Jan. 6 investigator says...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/hang-mike-pence-rioters-acted-on-orders-from-above-jan-6-investigator-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Capitol rioters who chanted "hang Mike Pence" appeared to be acting on orders "from above," according to a member of the Jan. 6 committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAYOFFS BEGIN AT NETFLIX</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/netflix-tudum-layoffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of the affected writers had only been hired a few months ago; Netflix says it has no plans to shutter the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USS George Washington sailors detail difficult working conditions after string of suicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/uss-george-washington-sailors-detail-difficult-working-conditions-stri-rcna25882</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USS George Washington had at least five shipmates die by suicide in the last year. Sailors detailed their struggles and the working conditions onboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP SHRINKS 1.4%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/28/us-q1-gdp-growth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gross domestic product unexpectedly declined 1.4% in the first quarter, an abrupt reversal for an economy coming off its best performance since 1984.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:   CAN ANYONE SAVE US FROM TWITTER?</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/can-elon-musk-save-twitter-and-can/comments?s=w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve always loved free speech as much as the next guy, and probably more than the next guy when I’m the one speaking freely. His free speech? I …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog's personality may have little to do with breed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-oddities-health-lifestyle-genetics-f6395d4d4aa78d6afc2b9e0bcaf3c7a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Research confirms what dog lovers know — every pup is truly an individual. Many of the popular stereotypes about the behavior of golden retrievers, poodles or schnauzers, for example, aren't supported by science, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosions in Kyiv during UN chief's visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/russia-ukraine-war-news-04-28-22/h_eb11f7ada69f4f85897cfca1b2b9d725</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin has warned that any country interfering in Ukraine would be met with a "lightning-fast" response from Moscow. Meanwhile, heavy fighting continues in the eastern regions of Ukraine. Follow here for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE posts big beat, 9% revenue pop...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/28/apple-aapl-earnings-q2-2022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple reported earnings after the bell. Here are the results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Middle of Invisible Wave?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/are-we-in-the-middle-of-an-invisible-covid-wave/ar-AAWI206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge fire rips through Moscow after car explosions...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1602793/Russia-news-Moscow-Kustanayskaya-Street-car-explosion-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has seen a massive fire rip through Moscow after multiple cars exploded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma passes 6-week abortion ban...</title>
      <link>https://localnews8.com/politics/cnn-us-politics/2022/04/28/oklahoma-lawmakers-pass-6-week-abortion-ban-modeled-after-texas-law-that-allows-civil-enforcement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;localnews8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Veronica Stracqualursi, CNN Oklahoma lawmakers on Thursday gave final approval to a bill modeled after the controversial Texas abortion law, which allows private citizens to take civil action against abortion providers to enforce the law. It’s the latest bill passed this month by Oklahoma’s legislature to restrict abortion rights comes amid a movement of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing halts weddings, funerals and closes schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/apr/28/china-crack-down-price-gouging-food-shortages-covid-shanghai-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stockpiling rife as city acts in attempt to avoid Shanghai-style lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon chipped in for Amber Heard's ACLU donation: Depp trial testimony...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/28/elon-musk-chipped-in-for-amber-heard-s-aclu-donation-depp-trial-testimony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire appears to have chipped in at least $500,000 to ex-girlfriend Amber Heard’s donation to the ACLU, its general counsel testified in Johnny Depp’s defamation trial Thursda…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci Walks Back Comments, Says Pandemic Not Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2022-04-28/fauci-walks-back-coronavirus-comments-says-pandemic-not-over-in-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fauci had said that ‘we are certainly, right now, in this country, out of the pandemic phase.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping on left side might improve waking life...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2022/04/sleeping-on-left-side-might-improve-your-waking-life-aiding-circulation-reducing-heartburn.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small study found that right-side sleeping “increased heartburn and acid reflux.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC probing initial stock buy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/the-ftc-is-looking-at-whether-elon-musks-initial-9-25-stake-in-twitter-violated-antitrust-rules-report-says/ar-AAWHZHo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life in idyllic town split into two Americas...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/Ferndale-is-idyllic-NorCal-town-17127349.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Butterfat Palace may be divided, but the union has not dissolved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops allege military mandate is 'religious purge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2022/04/28/troops-allege-militarys-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-is-a-religious-purge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two airmen and a soldier appeared on a podcast hosted by Rep. Matt Gaetz, R-Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholicism Withering in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/catholic-decline-latin-america-evangelicals-dd2bab11-6a22-48cc-b65a-554578c7a62e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelical faiths, meanwhile, have grown in some countries in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Boasts of Charming Colleagues With 'Cleavage'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/kyrsten-sinema-boasts-of-charming-gop-colleagues-with-cleavage-book-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona's Democratic senator Kyrsten Sinema likes to brag that her "cleavage" has an "extraordinary persuasive effect" on some of her Republican colleagues, according to a new book from New York Times reporters Jonathan Martin and Alexander Burns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Mars Helicopter Captures Eerie Wreckage of Landing Gear...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3ab9ev/nasas-mars-helicopter-captures-eerie-wreckage-of-landing-gear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spent remains of the mission’s backshell and parachute were surveyed during Ingenuity’s 26th flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA moves to ban menthol cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/fda-moves-to-ban-menthol-cigarettes-flavored-cigars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men on motorcycle rob 6 women in 90 minutes in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/robbers-motorcycle-women-purses-bronx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six women were victims of violent robberies in less than 90 minutes in the Bronx.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NATO commander warns West: Prepare for war...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-ukraine-war-latest-former-nato-commander-warns-west-must-gear-up-for-war-125133397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Russia’s invasion of Ukraine hits its 64th day, a former NATO commander urged the West to prepare for a “worst-case” scenario: war with Russia. Meanwhile, U.N. Secretary-General António Guterres on Thursday visited areas around Kyiv that were formally held by Russian forces. “The war is evil,” he said while standing beside destroyed apartment blocks in Borodyanka.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE: Dem Strategy Is 'Absolute Political Failure'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2022/04/bernie-sanders-wants-democrats-to-make-unions-their-biggest-message</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The moment is finally meeting the man, as national unionization efforts grow. “To turn your back on the working class, in general, is political suicide,” the senator tells Vanity Fair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW RUSSIA FRAMES WAR: CRITICAL RACE THEORY, ORGAN THIEVES, NAZIS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/critical-race-theory-poison-gas-and-organ-harvesting-how-the-kremlin-is-trying-to-frame-the-war-in-ukraine-as-a-clash-of-cultures-and-civilizations-153424329.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Americans are accustomed to walking on scorched earth,” Nikolai Patrushev, one of Russian President Vladimir Putin’s most loyal and most powerful aides inside the Kremlin, said in a jarringly expansive interview with Rossiyskaya Gazeta on Tuesday that touched on a variety of cultural and geopolitical grievances. Using the kind of Soviet-era rhetoric that is more reminiscent of 1982 than 2022, Patrushev aimed his remarks not only at ordinary Russians but also, perhaps, to war dissenters in the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Staffers Voice Fears of Cut Backs...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/netflix-staff-morale-1235136372/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the streaming giant is humbled with subscriber losses and falling stock prices, employees say they are anxious about future layoffs, smaller budgets and their stock options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy Coke 'to put the cocaine back in'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/04/28/elon-musk-jokes-about-buying-coca-cola-to-put-the-cocaine-back-in-16549792/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even for Musk, Coca-Cola's price tag of $284 billion might be a challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit killed fighting in first UK casualty...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5221967/brit-killed-fighting-russian-troops-ukraine-another-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRIT has been killed “fighting Russian troops” in Ukraine and another one is missing. It is believed the two soldiers were volunteers to Ukraine’s army although it has not been …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen says more shocks likely to challenge economy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-economy-janet-yellen-356153601cd404a0967c26e7a50875ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said Thursday the global pandemic and Russia’s invasion of Ukraine highlight the possibility of big economic shocks in the future, adding that downturns are “likely to continue to challenge the economy.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women fed up with flagrant sexism could swing Australia's election...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/ap/international/women-fed-up-with-flagrant-sexism-could-swing-australia-s-election/article_ace294c9-df69-57a9-add9-f06a1eafa576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women in Australia have endured more than a year of shocking allegations of misconduct from inside their nation’s parliament revealing a culture that has normalized sexual violence and humiliation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mean tweets from inside House? Incivility up among politicians...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mean-tweets-coming-inside-house-130040342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found that tweets by members of Congress have grown more uncivil over the last decade. Researchers attribute the change in part to how Twitter incentivizes mean tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: TESLA stock slide puts Musk's TWITTER deal in jeopardy...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2022/04/28/tesla-stock-slide-puts-musks-twitter-deal-in-jeopardy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla stock fell 20% in a week, wiping some $125bn from the company’s value as its CEO Elon Musk instead worked on shitposting and his quixotic plan to buy Twitter. As the deal he struck depe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Wall St's stars, Big Tech falls back to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-economy-ea18403e71a0b45a5fdbd22e3c32491f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
