<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Killer whale 'committed suicide' by repeatedly ramming head against tank...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3667235/killer-whale-hugo-committed-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUGO the killer whale was said to have been so unhappy in his captivity at an aquarium that he slammed his head into the wall of his tank until he died. The orca suffered a brain aneurysm after rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swift growth of Latinos reshaping big states, small towns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/specials/new-latino-landscape/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The swift growth of U.S. Latinos is reshaping big states and small towns. Meet the faces of a new era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JENNER:  'You get the government you deserve'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/politics/1004868/caitlyn-jenner-tells-californians-who-voted-to-keep-newsom-you-kind-of-get-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://money.com/collection/best-places-to-live-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We found the Best Places to Live in 2021-2022 after analyzing data points regarding economic stability, cost-of-living, cultural diversity, safety, and education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chanhassen, MN Named 'Best Place To Live In America'...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/09/15/chanhassen-named-best-place-to-live-in-the-country-according-to-money-magazine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Money Magazine has named Chanhassen the best place to live in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 out of 3 adults in TX!</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article254256643.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC revealed an updated map showing which states have an adult obesity prevalence at or above 35%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest Living WWII Vet Turns 112, Says Key To Long Life Is Being Nice To Others...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/09/13/lawrence-brooks-americas-oldest-living-wwii-vet-112-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence Brooks, who was part of a Black army battalion, had a drive-by celebration at his New Orleans home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA LAUNCHES</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-north-korea-fires-unidentified-24986872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launch came after North Korea said it successfully tested a new long-range cruise missile last weekend, calling it "a strategic weapon of great significance"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Praises FOXNEWS for 90% Staff Vaccination, Daily Testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/14/media/white-house-fox-covid-policy-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSOM WINS IN BLOWOUT...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/photos-californians-stream-polls-recall-235042804.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California voters overwhelmingly rejected the attempt to remove Gov. Gavin Newsom before the end of his term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Developing 'Superhuman Immunity' Against Covid...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/09/14/researchers-superhuman-immunity-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s a descriptive term for an individual to generate very high amounts of neutralizing antibodies,” Dr. Mohanakrishnan Sathyamoorthy, Chair of Internal Medicine, TCU and UNTHSC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of states with high obesity rate doubles since '18...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/572357-number-of-states-with-high-obesity-prevalence-nearly-doubles-since-2018-cdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of states with an obesity rate of at least 35 percent has nearly doubled in two years, with continuing racial and ethnic disparities, according to research released by the Centers for Disease Control</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Unseat Trudeau, Canada's Top Conservative Leans Left...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/15/to-unseat-trudeau-canadas-top-conservative-leans-left/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA — The leader of Canada’s Conservative Party, Erin O’Toole, lacks the name recognition, celebrity pedigree and charismatic hair of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Shasta nearly snowless; Rare event helping melt glaciers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/mount-shasta-is-nearly-snowless-a-rare-event-that-is-helping-melt-the-mountain-s-glaciers/ar-AAOteLF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shasta’s glaciers have lost more than 50 percent of their volume and area in this 21st century, with 2021 as the largest year of volume loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GMA' Staffer Claims ABC Retaliated Against Her After Sex Assault Complaint...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/abc-news-michael-corn-lawsuit-good-morning-america-1234833941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer on Good Morning America has filed a new claim against ABC, contending that the network retaliated against her after she filed a formal complaint alleging that the show’s top produce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average American Sleeps Poorly 3 Nights A Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/average-american-sleeps-poorly-3-nights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four in five workers believe the quality of sleep they get at night directly sets the tone for the following day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Worst Pitch in MLB History?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/watch-pitcher-throws-the-ultimate-blooper-and-nearly-hits-himself-with-worst-pitch-in-mlb-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Royals trailing Oakland 7-4, reliever Jake Brentz opened the frame with a strike, before throwing what might be the worst pitch in MLB history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WEST SIDE STORY' Drops Grandiose Trailer for Spielberg Remake...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/west-side-story-trailer-steven-spielberg-remake-1235014279/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20th Century film is due in theaters Dec. 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shari Redstone Radical PARAMOUNT Overhaul Sets Up Clash With Filmmakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/paramount-overhaul-sets-up-clash-with-filmmakers-1235013964/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the ViacomCBS mogul ousts film chief Jim Gianopulos, insiders expect the legacy studio to start churning out low-cost, often mediocre features for streamer Paramount+.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital doggies: Pet influencers on rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/digital-doggies-pet-influencers-rise-024806664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two fluffy white terriers wearing neckerchiefs pant quietly as their owner waves a treat and snaps a photo for the dogs' tens of thousands of Instagram followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'70s are back in '21...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/opinions-the-70s-are-back-in-2021-but-not-in-the-way-you-think/ar-AAOsViH </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor will sign religious exemption for vax if donate to his church...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/this-pastor-will-sign-a-religious-exemption-for-vaccines-if-you-donate-to-his-church/ar-AAOsOMt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pastor is a 29-year-old small-business owner running in the Republican primary challenge to Sen. James Lankford (Okla.) in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake news to fan culture: Beijing lays out what's allowed on 'Marxist civilized' Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/news/world/from-fake-news-to-fan-culture-china-lays-out-what-e2-80-99s-allowed-on-a-e2-80-98marxist-civilized-internet/ar-AAOsgmX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's over-arching idea is to ensure online content abides by “the guiding status of Marxism in the ideological cyberspace sphere,”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priciest Food Since '70s Big Challenge for Govts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/priciest-food-since-1970s-is-a-big-challenge-for-governments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Europe to Turkey and India, politicians are now handing out more aid, ordering sellers to cut prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival Koreas test missiles hours apart...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seoul-south-korea-north-korea-pyongyang-1bf74218556e36697983cf6669ec9166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North and South Korea tested ballistic missiles hours apart Wednesday in a display of military might that is sure to exacerbate tensions between the rivals at a time when talks aimed at stripping the North of its nuclear program are stalled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Westerns Enter New Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/15/movies/the-harder-they-fall-black-westerns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The genre dates back decades, when the films were made for segregated audiences. “The Harder They Fall” nods to the past but takes a new attitude altogether.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions wiped from Macau casino stocks as city eyes gambling review...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/macau-casino-stocks-tumble-as-city-proposes-gambling-industry-crackdown/ar-AAOs6Tp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macau casino operators saw billions wiped off their value Wednesday as their shares collapsed after officials in the world's biggest gambling city unveiled plans for a crackdown that would tighten their grip on the already beleaguered industry. The move comes as the government in mainland China embarks on a crackdown on a wide range of industries -- including tech and private education firms -- as it looks to tighten its grip on the world's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan jets land on highway for invasion wargame...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taiwan-jets-land-highway-chinese-055654323.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fighter jets practised landing on a highway in southern Taiwan on Wednesday as part of an annual live-fire military exercise that simulates defending the island against an invasion by China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Strategy Offers Republicans Warning...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/15/newsoms-anti-trump-recall-strategy-offers-republicans-a-warning-for-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN LEANDRO, Calif. — California basks in its clairvoyance. “The future happens here first,” says Gov. Gavin Newsom, calling his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to make history with first all-civilian crew launched into orbit...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/spacex-set-history-first-civilian-100656278.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest in a recent line of space-obsessed billionaires was set for liftoff on Wednesday with three less wealthy private citizens along for the ride aboard a SpaceX rocket ship, seeking to become the first all-civilian crew launched into Earth orbit. The quartet of amateur space travelers, led by the American founder and chief executive of e-commerce firm Shift4 Payments Inc, Jared Isaacman, were due for blastoff as early as 8 p.m. EDT (0000 GMT) from the Kennedy Space Center in Cape Canaveral, Florida. SpaceX's senior director of human spaceflight, Benji Reed, told reporters at the Cape on Tuesday that "everything looked great" following a final "static" test-firing of the rocket engines on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>88% FOR GAVIN IN SAN FRAN; 76% IN LA; 61% IN SAN DIEGO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/election/2021/results/california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fifth conservative radio talkshow host dies of covid --  in just six weeks!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/conservative-radio-host-who-spurned-vaccines-mocked-aids-patients-dies-of-covid-19/ar-AAOrt8l?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Enyart is at least the fifth conservative radio talk-show host to have died of covid-19 in recent weeks after speaking out against vaccination and masking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DONALD:  WOODWARD A 'SLEAZE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-accuses-milley-of-treason-denies-he-thought-about-attacking-china-calls-woodward-a-sleaze/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump accused General Mark Milley of committing "treason" if new reporting about his post-election actions is true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House eyes mandate for international fliers...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/U-S-has-weighed-vaccine-rule-for-international-16459668.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As White House officials rushed to shape last week's sweeping new vaccine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sept. 18 rally organizer asks attendees not to wear pro-Trump clothing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/572268-sept-18-rally-organizer-asks-attendees-not-to-wear-pro-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organizer for Saturday's “Justice for J6” rally is asking that attendees do not wear pro-Trump clothing at the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN APPROVAL SINKS TO 42%...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/poll-release?releaseid=3819</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The misery of fashion...</title>
      <link>https://www.spectator.co.uk/article/what-s-the-point-of-aoc-s-tax-the-rich-dress-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spectator.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’ve probably already seen that Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez rocked up at the Met Gala – where individual tickets are $35,000 (£20,000) and tables start at $200,000 (£150,000) – wearing a white dress saying in big red letters TAX THE RICH. It’s what the Clash called ‘turning rebellion into money’. Not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs Have Infiltrated L.A. Sheriff's Dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/los-angeles-sheriffs-department-gangs-rand-report-1225982/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new official report finds efforts to clean up the decades-old gang culture within the department are failing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exit polls  show SUPPORT for Covid restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/california-recall-election-results-newsom-n1279205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could take several days for the final results to be known if the race is close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA BELIEVED ATTACK IMMINENT</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-general-was-so-fearful-trump-might-spark-war-that-he-made-secret-calls-to-his-chinese-counterpart-new-book-says/ar-AAOr86X?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Peril," by Bob Woodward and Robert Costa, reveals how Gen. Mark A. Milley, the Joint Chiefs chairman, called his Chinese counterpart before the election and after Jan. 6 in a bid to avert armed conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug sting sends two Miami-Dade cop pals to prison. They were big fans of 'BAD BOYS' movies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/drug-sting-sends-two-miami-dade-cop-pals-to-prison-they-were-big-fans-of-e2-80-98bad-boys-e2-80-99-movies/ar-AAOqYAR?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their everyday lives, they served as young Miami-Dade cops who patrolled the county’s streets in their police cruisers. It would only take a single sting operation produced by undercover drug agents to bring down the buddy cops, who had a thing for the hit police action-movie franchise, “Bad Boys.” Next week, Roderick Flowers and Keith Edwards will be headed to federal prison for one year ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA players WILL NOT be required to get vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/32208394/sources-nba-players-required-get-covid-19-vaccination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 vaccine won't be required for NBA players this season, sources tell ESPN's Baxter Holmes and Adrian Wojnarowski.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK BOMBSHELL:  GENERAL FEARED TRUMP WOULD USE NUKES IN LAST DAYS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/14/politics/woodward-book-trump-nuclear/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two days after the January 6 attack on the US Capitol, President Donald Trump's top military adviser, Joint Chiefs Chairman Gen. Mark Milley, single-handedly took secret action to limit Trump from potentially ordering a dangerous military strike or launching nuclear weapons, according to "Peril," a new book by legendary journalist Bob Woodward and veteran Washington Post reporter Robert Costa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAVY TURNOUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Californians-turn-out-to-decide-Newsom-s-fate-16459774.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES - Californians lined up at polling places Tuesday in what appeared to be a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians decide gov's fate...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914191712-l2yw8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-RECALL/ (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-California voters deciding governor's fate in Republican-led recall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2021-recall-elections/california-governor-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fountain Of Youth' Substance May Reverse Aging In Bones...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fountain-of-youth-aging-bones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study finds adding acetate to specific bone marrow stem cells can reverse the aging process that weakens bones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reopening of 3 monster Broadway shows signals 'wait over'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-entertainment-lifestyle-bruce-springsteen-arts-and-entertainment-4459e4ef46f4c7617a2b2046c274763c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A digital marquee in Times Square says it all: “The Wait Is Over.” Eighteen months after the global pandemic shuttered live theater in March 2020, Broadway takes a big step forward Tuesday when three powerhouse shows — “The Lion King,” “Hamilton” and “Wicked” — rev their engines again with new safety protocols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Concerned Citizen' At Holmes' Trial Turns Out To Be Family...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/14/1036835868/elizabeth-holmes-trial-hotelier-bill-evans-goes-incognito</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious attendee at Elizabeth Holmes' fraud trial derided the case against her to reporters. Turns out, he was not whom he claimed to be, but was the father of Holmes' partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 ex-U.S. intel, military operatives admit to providing hacking technology to UAE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-united-states-hacking-5700a1fa8b1b4612477658b883e58f31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Three former U.S. intelligence and military operatives have admitted providing sophisticated hacking technology to the United Arab Emirates and agreed to pay nearly $1.7 million to resolve criminal charges in an agreement that the Justice Department described Tuesday as the first of its kind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slaughter of dolphins sparks debate on traditions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-denmark-dolphins-0a6d669d0742e56e575ed6849f1dd45b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — The slaughter of 1,428 white-sided dolphins over the weekend, part of a four-century-old traditional drive of sea mammals into shallow water where they are killed for their meat and blubber, has reignited a debate on the small Faeroe Islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BART passenger tethered to dog dies after being dragged onto tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvu.com/news/bart-train-drags-woman-to-death-as-shes-tethered-to-dog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BART passenger was dragged and killed by a train departing the Powell Street station as she was on the platform but her leashed dog remained inside the car, authorities said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Household Income Fell...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/income-americans-2020-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first two stimulus payments lifted 11.7 million people out of poverty, the analysis found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion house in backlash over 'racist' $1,190 sweatpants...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-58563242</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics say the $1,190 pants, which come with a built-in pair of boxer shorts, rip off US hip hop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College sports under siege -- and want K Street to save them...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/14/ncaa-college-sports-athletes-511700</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NCAA is tasking seasoned D.C. hands to help it figure out a world in which college athletes can earn cash off their name and likeness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alanis Morissette Rips 'Salacious Agenda' Of HBO 'JAGGED' Doc...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/alanis-morissette-slams-jagged-film-hbo-alison-klayman-1234833230/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alanis Morissette has torn into the documentary about her landmark Jagged Little Pill album that’s set to world premiere Tuesday night at the Toronto Film Festival. On a short break in her tour wit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi mocked 'fat butt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9990487/Nancy-Pelosi-mocked-Donald-Trumps-fat-butt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi slammed then-President Donald Trump in the days following the January 6th riot on Capitol Hill, mocking him for having a 'fat butt' and saying he's 'crazy,' new book reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She's Congress's Leading Progressive -- Just Not In Her Own Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/addybaird/pramila-jayapal-staff-treatment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former staffers who worked for Rep. Pramila Jayapal, a House Democrat who built her reputation on being a champion of workers, say her treatment of her staff was often inconsistent with her public image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House encouraging state, local mandates...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210914191542-rov9q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-BIDEN (URGENT):White House says it is encouraging state, local COVID vaccine mandates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>56% of Young People Think Humanity Doomed...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88npnp/fifty-six-percent-of-young-people-think-humanity-is-doomed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major study of 10,000 young people across 10 different countries lays bare the scale of climate crisis-related anxiety felt around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNKIN' Opens First 'Digital-Only' Restaurant In Boston...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/13/dunkin-digital-only-restaurant-boston-common/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new kind of Dunkin' has just opened in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' star, stand-up comedian with cult following...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/awards/norm-macdonald-former-saturday-night-live-player-stand-comic-dies-n1279164</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stand-up comedian had been privately battling cancer for nearly a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long private battle with cancer...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/norm-macdonald-dead-obituary-comedian-saturday-night-live-weekend-update-anchor-was-61-1234833212/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norm Macdonald, whose laconic delivery of sharp and incisive observations made him one of Saturday Night Live’s most influential and beloved cast members, died today after a nine-year private…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking arm amputation surgery makes 'phantom' hand seem real...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/09/14/i-can-still-feel-it-new-arm-amputation-surgery-makes-a-phantom-hand-seem-real/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The procedure aims to restore proprioception, the ability to sense where our limbs are in space and how fast and forcefully they’re moving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE unveils iPhone 13...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/apple-event-iphone-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple announced the new iPhone 13 and iPhone 13 Pro phones, new iPads and the Apple Watch Series 7 during its fall event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving boosters to healthy people 'not right,' WHO says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/14/giving-covid-booster-shots-to-healthy-people-is-not-right-who-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are countries with less than 2% vaccination coverage, most of them in Africa, who are not even getting their first and second dose" Tedros said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing purging celebrities, tech billionaires. Problem bigger than 'sissy men'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-purging-celebrities-tech-billionaires-100047948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the economy slows, China's crackdown on the rich and famous may be an attempt to distract from ordinary families' anxiety over their children's future.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
