<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrators take control of govt buildings in Beirut amid violent protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/beirut-braces-for-protests-as-grief-over-blast-turns-to-fury-resign-or-hang/2020/08/08/5c050e3e-d8e2-11ea-a788-2ce86ce81129_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators storm the Foreign Ministry amid deep anger in a country already reeling from economic collapse and chronic corruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK fate was shaped by 'knockdown, drag-out' Oval Office brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/TikTok-s-fate-was-shaped-by-knockdown-drag-out-15469209.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Last week, as leaders in Silicon Valley, China and Washington raced to seal the fate of one of the world's fastest-growing social media companies, a shouting match broke out in the Oval Office between two of President Donald Trump's top advisers.  In front of Trump, trade adviser Peter Navarro and other aides, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin began arguing that the Chinese-owned video-sharing service TikTok should be sold to a U.S. company. Mnuchin had talked several times to Microsoft's senior leaders and was confident that he had rallied support within the administration for a sale to the tech giant on national security grounds.  Navarro pushed back, demanding an outright ban of TikTok, while accusing Mnuchin of being soft on China, the people said, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discuss private discussions freely. The treasury secretary appeared taken aback, they said.  The ensuing argument - which was described by one of the people as a "knockdown, drag-out" brawl - was preceded by months of backroom dealings among investors, lobbyists and executives. Many of these stakeholders long understood the critical nature of establishing close connections with key figures in the Trump administration.  But over the past few weeks, they also were reminded of the unpredictable and precarious nature of business dealings under a Trump-led government - and how the winner of a heated debate in front of the president could help decide the fate of a multibillion-dollar deal that may reshape the technology business landscape for years to come.  Over the past two weeks, TikTok's future has been publicly tossed about, first as it appeared that the president would agree to a sale, then that he would ban it outright, then that he would allow a sale again - but only if a fee were paid to the U.S. Treasury.  Behind...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Data Shows 207,000 'Excess Deaths' During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/cdc-data-shows-207000-excess-deaths-during-coronavirus-pandemic-far-eclipsing-160000-confirmed-death-count/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a New York Times analysis of data from the Centers for Disease Control, there have been 207,000 excess deaths in the United States during the coronavirus pandemic, much higher than the current total of 161,000 confirmed deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump path to winning runs through small Rust Belt towns - like one near Biden hometown...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/politics/pennsylvania/carbondale-pennsylvania-trump-biden-2020-election-20200808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Trump rebounds from a slide in the polls to win Pennsylvania again, it will be partly thanks to smaller cities like Carbondale scattered all across the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia pastor has potential to take Senate seat away from warring Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Georgia-pastor-has-potential-to-take-Senate-seat-15469097.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats have longed for the day when once ruby-red Georgia would be ready to transform into a diverse urban-suburban stronghold in their column.  Joe Biden's presidential campaign has made it a top target. Republicans and their allies have already reserved $30 million in ad spending to defend Sen. David Perdue, a Republican, from a surprisingly strong challenge.  But the GOP fear of a perfect storm has always involved the second Georgia Senate race, an odd special election with five potentially strong contenders thrown together on the initial November ballot, including appointed Sen. Kelly Loeffler, a Republican, and the Rev. Raphael Warnock, a Democrat.  A confluence of events has created a moment for Warnock's campaign that, if he can seize it, could turn into a political disaster for Republicans and a boon for Democrats.  Warnock, as senior pastor of Ebenezer Baptist Church, just oversaw the nationally televised funeral of John Lewis, the congressman and civil rights icon whose stature brought three presidents to Warnock's pulpit for eulogies.  His bid to become Georgia's first Black U.S. senator had already begun to find its footing after the death of George Floyd in Minneapolis and the ensuing police brutality protests. And on Tuesday, as the WNBA launched its pandemic-delayed season, many players adorned "VOTE WARNOCK" warm-up shirts before games, including those on the Atlanta Dream.  That's the team Loeffler owns, a protest to the senator's public opposition to basketball players embracing the Black Lives Matter movement.  Now Warnock gets to test something that he highlighted when he launched his long-shot campaign on Jan. 30, touting his rise from one of 12 children growing up in the Savannah projects to running the church the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. used as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Execute them'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200808-execute-them-lebanon-protesters-demand-revenge-after-blast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Execute them': Lebanon protesters demand revenge after blast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly 'Romeo and Juliet' risk COVID-19 for one final embrace...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/08/elderly-florida-couple-braved-covid-19-for-one-final-embrace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was love in the time of COVID-19 for a 90-year-old Florida man who died Saturday after he insisted on visiting his beloved wife who had caught the virus. Sam Reck died of coronavirus-related com…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over deadly explosion...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/08/clashes-erupt-in-beirut-at-blast-protest-as-lebanons-anger-boils-over/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT, Lebanon — Clashes between demonstrators and security forces broke out near Lebanon’s Parliament on Saturday at a protest fueled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Dodd, an Insider From Biden's Past, Is Helping Him Pick His Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/08/us/politics/biden-vp-chris-dodd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Biden works to win over progressive voters, he has empowered a Washington uber-veteran long trailed by allegations of personal and financial indiscretion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VP PICK DOWN TO WIRE</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/08/how-the-final-stretch-of-bidens-vp-search-is-playing-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been an abnormal, increasingly contentious process, but the wait is finally almost over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: No Wrist Corsages, Please...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/08/08/opinion/sunday/biden-vice-president-geraldine-ferraro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Has America grown since 1984, or will the knives still be out for Biden’s running mate?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From levitation to super-strength: Exorcist on why 1973 classic is 'real'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/levitation-super-strength-christian-exorcist-22462051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Exorcist Reverend Bill Bean tells Daily Star Online about the chilling ways demonic possession presents itself and claims he has seen cases of levitation and superhuman strength</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dire outlook for movie theaters as covid resurges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/08/dire-outlook-for-cinemas-as-coronavirus-resurges-in-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American studios have had to make tough decisions about film releases due to resurgences of coronavirus cases in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebs' gratuitous apologies make Black Lives Matter all about them...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/08/celebrities-gratuitous-apologies-make-blm-all-about-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arson, looting and rioting have died down, but we’re still a long way from cultural normalcy in the US of A. (That A is for antagonism). One strange new feature of the culture is the abject, I-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Pesticides, Pathogens Ruled Out as Cause for Mass Elephant Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/botswana-rules-out-pesticides-and-pathogens-as-cause-for-elephant-deaths/ar-BB17Hg7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complaints Allege People Tricked Into Signing Kanye Nomination Paperwork...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/politics/2020/08/07/group-accuses-lawyer-working-trump-and-west-campaigns-simultaneously/3318242001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney for Trump's re-election campaign submitted West's papers, and some wonder if the two are working together to siphon Biden votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Broker Turns to New Zealand as New York Luxury Market Wilts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/star-broker-turns-to-new-zealand-as-new-york-luxury-market-wilts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Broker Turns to New Zealand as New York Luxury Market Wilts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bourbon Street to Food Banks, Signs of Slow Recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/from-bourbon-street-to-food-banks-signs-of-a-slow-u-s-recovery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Bourbon Street to Food Banks, Signs of a Slow U.S. Recovery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: QUASH QANON...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/qanon-is-running-amok-and-the-time-has-come-for-interventions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QAnon Is Running Amok, and the Time Has Come for Interventions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela jails two U.S. ex-soldiers for 20 years after failed incursion...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200808122442-5a38w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/:Venezuela court jails two U.S. ex-soldiers for 20 years after failed incursion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics say watching Shia LaBeouf new film like having face dragged across asphalt...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/the-tax-collector-film-reviews-shia-labeouf-a9660906.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short on Money, Cities Around World Try Making Own...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-07/a-depression-era-idea-gets-a-new-look-local-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible 'external interference' in blast; Israel swift to deny...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807150756-2a2hg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON-SECURITY/BLAST (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Lebanon sees possible 'external interference' in port blast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saint-Tropez resort makes masks mandatory outdoors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d94752dd1bc0be5fddf17baf3aeac860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAINT-TROPEZ, France (AP) — The glamorous French Riviera resort of Saint-Tropez is requiring face masks outdoors starting Saturday, threatening to sober the mood in a place renowned for high-end,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is France helping Lebanon, or trying to reconquer it?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8eab366aa599b101eb2aad10f9e6528d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — It was almost as if Emmanuel Macron forgot that Lebanon is no longer a French protectorate. Visiting explosion-ravaged Beirut this week, France’s leader comforted distraught...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 Test Positive For Virus After Attending Funeral...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/08/06/almost-30-test-positive-for-covid-19-after-attending-funeral-in-becker-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's human nature to want to gather and grieve together when someone you lose someone close to you, but the COVID-19 pandemic is making that more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Number of Americans Giving Up Citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/americans-continue-giving-up-citizenship-at-record-levels-reports-bambridge-accountants-new-york-301107675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prnewswire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/PRNewswire/ -- Americans are continuing to renounce their citizenship at the highest levels on record, according to research by the Enrolled Agents and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Drilling Shrinks to 15-Year Low... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/oil-drilling-drops-to-15-year-low-with-shale-in-full-retreat/ar-BB17Hunz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55% of virus patients still have neurological problems three months later...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/55-of-coronavirus-patients-still-have-neurological-problems-three-months-later-study-2020-08-07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mounting evidence suggests COVID-19 could cause brain damage in adults and kids</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president defends record as toll soars...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexican-president-defends-record-virus-201152670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador on Friday defended his government&amp;#39;s record fighting the coronavirus and ruled out a change in strategy after the official death toll surged past 50,000. The Latin American nation recently overtook Britain to become the third hardest-hit country in terms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America now region with most covid deaths... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-deaths-latin-america-hit-212054477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin America and the Caribbean surpassed Europe on Friday to become the region hardest-hit by coronavirus deaths, as India passed the sombre step of recording over two million infections. The world&amp;#39;s worst-hit region had reported 213,120 fatalities, 460 more than Europe, according to an AFP tally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Susan Rice sells NETFLIX options...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/susan-rice-sells-netflix-options-175217810.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Former national security adviser Susan Rice, a Netflix director, sold some of her shares of the video streaming company worth $305,323 this week as speculation swirls that she is among the candidates to be Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden’s running mate.A spokeswoman for Rice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arpaio loses sheriff's race in 2nd failed comeback bid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ee55d22b1ad5910bb42b64a78f714bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Joe Arpaio on Friday was narrowly defeated in his bid to win back the sheriff’s post in metro Phoenix that he held for 24 years before being voted out in 2016 amid voter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitmer traveled to Delaware last weekend...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/65025dc16aa18353cf868658d9b2314a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Gov. Gretchen Whitmer traveled to Delaware last weekend to meet with Joe Biden, the presumptive Democratic presidential nominee's first known in-person session with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Falwell Jr. put on 'indefinite leave' from LIBERTY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/53437a0f21d0b3df86f96a11e76e5687</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Jerry Falwell Jr. took an indefinite leave of absence Friday as the leader of Liberty University, one of the nation's top evangelical Christian colleges, days after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy on verge of 'lost year'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wvgazettemail.com/washington_post/finance/the-u-s-economy-is-on-the-verge-of-a-lost-year/article_b0efcb40-0ebd-590d-932a-a0558a2976df.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wvgazettemail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Hartman has spent a lot of time this summer pacing his restaurant, Bixler’s Lodge in Reading, Pennsylvania, with a tape measure. Whatever way he places it, he comes to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>52 DAYS UNTIL FIRST DEBATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Trump-tries-to-muscle-through-changes-in-debates-15468276.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's efforts to influence the timing and makeup of this fall's presidential debates, some of the last planned events with the power to shift the trajectory of the campaign, have been rejected, with both the independent debate commission and the Biden campaign showing no interest in altering course.  But that has not stopped Trump from trying to gain advantage by making the debates a top-tier issue, as he and his advisers circulate unfounded claims that Joe Biden may try to dodge the events and suggest that the Democrat may try to cheat by using notes if the sessions are held virtually.  "I would be highly surprised if Joe Biden actually went through with all three debates," Trump campaign senior adviser Jason Miller said Friday. "I think their strategy will be to show up to one, show that he is able to function and then pull the plug on any additional debates."  Biden pledged in June to attend all three of the scheduled debates, a commitment that the president only matched in a letter Thursday, after the debate commission rejected a request to use a list of Trump-approved moderators and move up the timing of the debates. The Biden team has taken to mocking the Trump campaign's effort to shape the rules and timing of the events, with one Biden aide suggesting that the president and his staff can Google the phrase "be there" if they have any questions.  "The Trump campaign's attempt to create a debate about debates is as phony as the president's claim that coronavirus will vanish on its own," Biden campaign spokesman Andrew Bates said. "It's unsurprising they have adopted this embarrassing tactic."  The debates, set to begin Sept. 29, are expected to carry outsize importance in a remarkably bizarre election cycle - without public rallies or much in-person campaigning - offering homebound...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service overhauls leadership as Dems press for investigation of mail delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Postal-Service-overhauls-leadership-as-Democrats-15468160.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Postmaster General Louis DeJoy unveiled a sweeping overhaul of the nation's mail service, displacing the two top executives overseeing day-to-day operations, according to a reorganization memo released Friday. The shake-up came as congressional Democrats called for an investigation of DeJoy and the cost-cutting measures that have slowed mail delivery and ensnared ballots in recent primary elections  Twenty-three postal executives were reassigned or displaced, the new organizational chart shows. Analysts say the structure centralizes power around DeJoy, a former logistics executive and major ally of President Donald Trump, and de-emphasizes decades' worth of institutional postal knowledge. All told, 33 staffers included in the old postal hierarchy either kept their jobs or were reassigned in the restructuring, with five more staffers joining the leadership from other roles.  The reshuffling threatens to heighten tensions between postal officials and lawmakers, who are troubled by delivery delays - the Postal Service banned employees from working overtime and making extra trips to deliver mail - and wary of the Trump administration's influence on the Postal Service as the coronavirus pandemic rages and November's election draws near.  It also adds another layer to DeJoy's disputes with Democratic leaders, who have pushed him to rescind the cost-cutting directives that have caused days-long backlogs and steady the Postal Service in the run-up to the election. DeJoy clashed with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., and Senate Minority Leader Charles Schumer, D-N.Y., in a meeting on the issue earlier this week.  Rep. Gerald Connolly, D-Va., chair of the House subcommittee responsible for postal oversight, called the reorganization "a deliberate sabotage" to the nation's mail service and a "Trojan Horse."  David...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX, ULA wins billions in Pentagon rocket contracts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/spacex-and-ula-win-2022-pentagon-rocket-launch-contracts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force on Friday awarded rocket builders United Launch Alliance and SpaceX with contracts worth billions to launch national security missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare syndrome found in 600 American children...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807203644-7i3cv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHILDREN:Rare syndrome linked to COVID-19 found in nearly 600 U.S. children -CDC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison Escapee Caught After 50 Years on Run...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2020-08-07/colorado-prison-escapee-caught-after-nearly-50-years-on-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNERMEDIA layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/warnermedia-ceo-reorganizes-company-with-layoffs-focus-on-hbo-max.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the changes, streaming executive Andy Forssell will lead a new HBO Max operating business unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  Vaccine has 'not great' chance of being highly effective...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/coronavirus-vaccine-dr-fauci-says-chances-of-it-being-highly-effective-is-not-great.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are hoping for a coronavirus vaccine that is at least 75% effective, but 50% or 60% effective would be acceptable, too, Dr. Anthony Fauci said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Sanders Staffer Jailed in Belarus, Charged with Disrupting Peace...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/christopherm51/us-campaign-aide-jailed-belarus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vitali Shkliarov faces up to three years behind bars for allegedly organizing an illegal campaign rally for the candidate challenging President Alexander Lukashenko, known as “Europe’s Last Dictator.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released from jail at height of pandemic, rape suspect kills accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.11alive.com/article/news/local/virginia/rape-suspect-washington-post-alexandria-crime/65-13310ff6-43bf-444d-acc3-e229d7699b6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.11alive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ibrahm E. Bouiachi was indicted on rape charges last year. After being released due to the pandemic, police say he shot and killed his accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus hastens newspapers' slide into shaky digital future...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/virus-hastens-newspapers-slide-shaky-080216711.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus crisis has weighed heavily on print newspapers already battling for survival around the world, with the number of copies sold tumbling while less profitable digital readerships surge. Simply delivering printed papers to the shops -- or having customers come in to buy them -- has become</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell 'boasted' about oral sex with George Clooney...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12340128/ghislaine-maxwell-schoolgirl-oral-sex-george-clooney-virginia-giuffre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell boasted about performing an alleged sex act on George Clooney and “giggled like a schoolgirl”, Virginia Giuffre has claimed. The sensational claims were made in the ma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOOKS: RUSSIA WANTS TRUMP; CHINA WANTS BIDEN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/07/politics/2020-election-russia-china-iran/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US intelligence community's top election security official said in a statement Friday that China "prefers" an outcome where President Donald Trump is not reelected in November and Russia is working to denigrate former Vice President Joe Biden's White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released from jail at height of pandemic, rape suspect kills accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/crime-law/2020/08/06/released-jail-height-pandemic-alexandria-rape-suspect-allegedly-killed-his-accuser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ibrahim Bouaichi had been in jail since October on rape and abduction charges. But he was released in April, and is now charged with killing his accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-ANGELS employee charged in pitcher's fatal opioid overdose...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/former-l-angels-employee-charged-pitcher-tyler-skaggs-fatal-opioid-n1236179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyler Skaggs was just 27 when he was found dead in his hotel room, as his team prepared to play the Texas Rangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado 'recon' teams quietly monitor mask wearing...</title>
      <link>https://coloradosun.com/2020/08/06/mask-wearing-compliance-surveys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coloradosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tri-County Health Department has been dispatching volunteers to conduct mask surveys since April. Now Boulder and Gunnison counties are starting their own coronavirus recon missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman is 1st in US to get 2nd face transplant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4cb2c94741618736fc91f2a51899b458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — For the second time in a decade, a New Hampshire woman has a new face. Carmen Blandin Tarleton, whose face was disfigured in an attack by her ex-husband, became the first...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Media Led Great Racial Awakening...</title>
      <link>https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/media-great-racial-awakening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tabletmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Years before Trump’s election the media dramatically increased coverage of racism and embraced new theories of racial consciousness that set the stage for the latest unrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will curtain fall on Broadway for good?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/covid-19-knocked-actors-broadway-stage-are-lights-dim-forever-n1235957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have to pave a new way forward, because this industry is not ever going to be the same," one actor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL owner Dan Snyder files $10M lawsuit over false sex trafficking stories...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/511056-nfl-owner-dan-snyder-files-10m-lawsuit-over-false-sex-trafficking-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indian-based website has since taken down the stories.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
