<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA MISSILE BLITZ</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-invades-ukraine-in-europe-s-darkest-hours-since-wwii/ar-AAUeeBE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House calls Donald 'nauseating, fearful pig'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10547729/White-House-deputy-press-secretary-calls-Trump-nauseating-fearful-pig.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House deputy press secretary Andrew Bates hammered former President Donald Trump for heaping praise for days on Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans divided over response to Russian aggression...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-ukraine-invasion-republican-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans agree on criticism of President Biden's handling of the crisis, but they split on how much the U.S. should be involved in the conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls on citizens to fight, promises weapons...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ukraines-zelenskiy-calls-citizens-fight-094540518.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy on Thursday called on all citizens who were ready to defend the country from Russian forces to come forward, saying Kyiv would issue weapons to everyone who wants them. Russia launched an all-out invasion of Ukraine by land, air and sea on Thursday, the biggest attack by one state against another in Europe since World War Two and confirmation of the worst fears of the West. Zelenskiy urged Russians to come out and protest against the war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many flee to Poland...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/leaving-behind-possessions-pets-ukrainians-104235740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainians fleeing a Russian invasion have started trickling into Poland, with dozens arriving at the normally quiet Medyka crossing on Thursday, some carrying luggage and accompanied by children. Officials in European Union countries bordering Ukraine, including Romania and Slovakia, said there was no big influx of refugees for now, but local media and witnesses said foot traffic was increasing. Alexander Bazhanov fled his home in eastern Ukraine with his wife and young child, taking only what they could carry and walking the final part of their journey into Poland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops storm Chernobyl...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4762650/chernobyl-russian-invaders-battle-nuclear-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BATTLE was raging in the Chernobyl nuclear exclusion zone today after Russian troops stormed in from Belarus. Ukrainian guards fought back as officials warned a direct hit on a waste storage faci…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANET FITNESS CEO says Gen Z signing up for gym memberships at high rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/24/planet-fitness-ceo-gen-z-is-fueling-overall-membership-growth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Planet Fitness is seeing more pre-teens and teens sign up for their first gym memberships during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON Growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93bg5a/qanon-conspiracy-theory-prri-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people hoped that Trump’s 2020 loss and the disappearance of “Q” would dissolve QAnon. A new survey shows the opposite has happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle For Airbase On Kyiv Outskirts...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/russia-ukraine-forces-battle-for-airbase-on-kyiv-outskirts-2787601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian and Ukrainian forces are battling for control of an airbase on the northern outskirts of Kyiv, a senior Ukrainian officer said Thursday, as dozens of attack helicopters swooped on the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Taiwan Next?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2022/02/vladimir-putin-ukraine-taiwan/622907/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia’s invasion of Ukraine makes the frightening possibility of China seizing control of the island more real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns West of consequences greater than any in history if interferes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10545641/Putins-gives-chilling-warning-West-early-morning-TV-broadcast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin declared war on Ukraine and gave a chilling warning to its allies in the west in an early Thursday morning address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan reports nine Chinese aircraft in its air defence zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-taiwan-china-defence/taiwan-reports-nine-chinese-aircraft-in-its-air-defence-zone-idUSKBN2KT20M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan's air force scrambled again on Thursday to warn away nine Chinese aircraft that entered its air defence zone, Taiwan's defence ministry said, on the same day that Russia invaded Ukraine, a crisis being watched closely in Taipei.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trendy IV vitamin infusions don't work -- and might be unsafe...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Trendy-IV-vitamin-infusions-don-t-work-and-16943636.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past few years, intravenous vitamin treatments have exploded in popularity....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos, Video Emerge: 'That's F*cking Missile!'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/thats-a-fcking-missile-photos-video-emerge-from-ukraine-as-russia-continues-military-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive surge of photos and videos have been posted online from Ukraine as the country faces an ongoing assault from Russian military forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 In 3 Teens HAPPIER During Lockdowns?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/young-people-happier-lockdowns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say teens and adolescents felt less lonely, avoided bullying, got more sleep and exercise, and their mental health improved while staying at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Sharp Brain In Old Age -- Owning Pet?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/owning-pet-slow-mental-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study reveals having a furry friend in your life for more than five years can slow cognitive decline in older adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, surprised by sudden incursion, denies backing...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/China-surprised-by-sudden-Ukraine-incursion-16943357.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Thursday denied backing Russia's military assault in Ukraine as it treaded a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single and looking: Rise of solo American homebuyer...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/money-realestate-singles/single-and-looking-the-rise-of-the-solo-american-homebuyer-idUSKBN2KT0GA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Crane is part of a booming proportion of the housing market: solo buyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen wrongly charged in shooting says police offered him fast food to get confession...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-teen-wrongly-charged-in-a-shooting-says-police-offered-him-fast-food-to-get-a-confession/ar-AAUe6a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slain cinematographer's husband angry Baldwin deflects blame...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/alec-baldwin-entertainment-business-arts-and-entertainment-shootings-f29d492deb5fec1752e014dadcc2c4a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The husband of a cinematographer shot and killed on the set of the film “Rust” says it's “absurd” that Alec Baldwin believes he's not to blame for the shooting and he was “so angry” when Baldwin didn't accept responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls on citizens to fight, promises weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-zelenskiy-citizens/ukraines-zelenskiy-calls-on-citizens-to-fight-promises-weapons-idUSKBN2KT151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy on Thursday called on all citizens who were ready to defend the country from Russian forces to come forward, saying Kyiv would issue weapons to everyone who wants them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing far-right agenda, French news networks shape election debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20220224-pushing-far-right-agenda-french-news-networks-shape-election-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a presidential campaign dominated by talk of far-right pundit Eric Zemmour, some of France's leading news networks stand accused of fostering his Elysée Palace run and plugging his hardline agenda…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltics wondering: Are we next?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-russia-estonia-race-and-ethnicity-soviet-union-187f098422b7a3170143de238865b526</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VILNIUS, Lithuania (AP) — Viewed from Paris, London and Washington, the events unfolding in Ukraine may seem like a new Cold War taking shape in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving behind possessions and pets, many flee to Poland...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-poland-border/leaving-behind-possessions-and-pets-ukrainians-flee-to-poland-idUSKBN2KT1CO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainians fleeing a Russian invasion have started trickling into Poland, with dozens arriving at the normally quiet Medyka crossing on Thursday, some carrying luggage and accompanied by children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Fed considers minting first digital dollar, it is tapping experts from crypto company with stake in outcome...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/as-the-fed-considers-minting-the-first-digital-dollar-it-is-tapping-experts-from-a-crypto-company-with-a-stake-in-the-outcome/ar-AAUdERb </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO to deploy more troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/24/ukraine-russia-news-vladimir-putin-orders-attack-as-explosions-are-reported.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explosions were reported in multiple cities in Ukraine after Russia's Vladimir Putin ordered an attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sad Coda for Lovelorn Octogenarians Who Absconded Through Outback...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/24/sad-coda-for-lovelorn-octogenarians-who-absconded-through-outback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia — It was a journey that seemed doomed from the start: An octogenarian couple, one spiriting the other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blasts Before Dawn. Rooster's Crow. Then Panic...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/24/in-eastern-ukraine-blasts-before-dawn-a-roosters-crow-then-panic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SLOVYANSK, Ukraine — The explosions began before dawn. Loud booms of artillery in the distance, shaking a region that knows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courting Mainstream and Extreme, McCarthy Plots Rise to Speaker...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/24/courting-g-o-p-s-mainstream-and-extreme-mccarthy-plots-rise-to-speaker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Over a breakfast of bacon and eggs in his California district last week, Representative Kevin McCarthy, the House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst European Crisis of Postwar Era...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/putin-decides-conduct-military-operation-030111468.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia began a full-scale invasion of Ukraine after President Vladimir Putin vowed to “demilitarize” the country and replace its leaders, triggering the worst security crisis in Europe since World War II and prompting the West to threaten further punishing sanctions in response.Most Read from BloombergRussia Invades Ukraine in Worst European Crisis of Postwar EraRussia Hits Airfields; Kyiv Imposes Martial Law: Ukraine UpdateThe $200 Billion Club Loses Last Member as Elon Musk’s We</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror images of blood-drenched civilians...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4760015/horror-pics-wounded-civilians-russia-blitzes-apartment-block/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HORRIFYING images show civilians walking covered in blood after Russia blitzed an apartment block in Ukraine. The airstrike in Kharkiv killed a boy in the area after a building was shelled, emergen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Repeating Fast Radio Burst Traced to Very Unexpected Location...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/mysterious-repeating-fast-radio-burst-traced-to-very-unexpected-location</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recently discovered repeating fast radio burst (FRB) named FRB 20200120E is deepening the mystery of these already deeply mysterious space signals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelenskiy Says Suffered 'Serious Losses' As Air Strikes Hit 25 Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.rferl.org/a/putin-ukraine-military-operation/31719680.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rferl.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Volodymyr Zelenskiy told his nation that Ukraine had suffered “serious losses” in the initial stages of Russia’s long-feared attack early on February 24, with an adviser saying at least 40 people had been killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA MISSILE BLITZ</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10545389/BREAKING-NEWS-Explosions-heard-Ukraine-port-city-Mariupol.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has today launched all-out war on Ukraine, with attacks coming from the north, south and east simultaneously as bombs, cruise missiles and rockets rained down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $200 Billion Club Loses Last Member as Musk Wealth Tumbles...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/200-billion-club-loses-last-233641617.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- No person on the planet has a fortune of more than $200 billion -- at least for now. Most Read from BloombergRussia Launches Attack on Ukraine in ‘Dark Day’ for EuropeRussia Hits Airfields; Kyiv Imposes Martial Law: Ukraine UpdateBiden’s First Salvo of Russia Sanctions Hits With Thud, Not RoarThe $200 Billion Club Loses Last Member as Elon Musk’s Wealth TumblesGoldman Sachs Wants Its Bonuses Back as Punishment for Jumping ShipElon Musk, the only billionaire who still exceeded that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL-OUT ATTACK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-attack-a05e7c4563ac94b963134bba83187d46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russia launched a wide-ranging attack on Ukraine on Thursday, hitting cities and bases with airstrikes or shelling, as civilians piled into trains and cars to flee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World expresses outrage, plans stronger sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-asia-europe-united-nations-8744320842fca825ae4e4ccae5acbe34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — World leaders expressed a raw outrage shrouded by an impotence to immediately come to the aid of Ukraine to avoid a major war in Europe, condemning Russia’s attack on its neighbor as the European Union and others promised unprecedented sanctions to hit the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  LET'S GO, PUTIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-praises-putin-again-even-as-the-russian-invasion-of-ukraine-looms-saying-the-russian-president-is-playing-biden-like-a-drum/ar-AAUeiEY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like a Trump rally': Inside the former president's social app...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-rally-inside-former-presidents-033338657.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Joe Biden in Taliban fighter garb or stumbling over his words or bungling efforts to avert war in Ukraine –- posts on Donald Trump's new social media network "Truth Social" have a go-to target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly woman robbed while praying in church...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/police-78-year-old-woman-robbed-while-praying-in-church</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Clarksville, Tennessee. are looking for a group of women who robbed a 78-year-old woman while she was praying inside a sanctuary at Hilldale Baptist Church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to test subway barriers to keep people from being pushed onto tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/mta-to-test-platform-barriers-at-three-nyc-subway-stations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MTA is launching a pilot program to install platform doors at three subway stations in order to prevent any more riders from being shoved onto the tracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL BREAKS $100</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/commodities/oil-price</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil Price: Get all information on the Price of Oil including News, Charts and Realtime Quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen is ALIVE despite reports...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-queen-holds-weekly-call-26312661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her Majesty, 95, is continuing to experience mild cold-like symptoms after testing positive for coronavirus on Sunday and has been self-isolating at Windsor Castle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRSPACE CLOSED</title>
      <link>https://www.marketbeat.com/articles/the-latest-ukrainian-airspace-closed-to-civilian-flights-2022-02-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketbeat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airspace over all of Ukraine has been shut down to civilian air traffic, according to a notice posted to air crews early Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Murphy resurrects Andy Warhol for NETFLIX using AI...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/tv/the-andy-warhol-diaries-trailer-ai-narration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The Andy Warhol Diaries' director Andrew Rossi discusses resurrecting the artist's voice and honoring all the chapters of his life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin announces military operation in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-russia-moscow-kyiv-626a8c5ec22217bacb24ece60fac4fe1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin on Thursday announced a military operation in Ukraine, claiming it’s intended to protect civilians. In a televised address, Putin said the action comes in response to threats coming from Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRSPACE CLOSED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-new-zealand-australia-europe-08ae29f98152817b1b503b4b957c63f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest on the Russia-Ukraine crisis : WASHINGTON — Airspace over all of Ukraine has been shut down to civilian air traffic, according to a notice posted to air crews early Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry Sues 'DAILY MAIL' For Libel...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/carlieporterfield/2022/02/23/prince-harry-sues-daily-mail-publisher-for-libel/?sh=84c0cc72576f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Harry’s second lawsuit against the British media company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermobaric rocket launchers 'explode' enemy's lungs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17749817/russia-ukraine-news-thermobaric-rocket-launcher-vladimir-putin-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin is deploying some of the world’s most devastating weapons in his planned full-scale assault on Ukraine, experts have claimed. Russia’s terrifying arsenal of thermobaric w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin to Request New Trial in NYT Defamation Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sarah-palin-to-request-new-trial-in-n-y-times-defamation-case/ar-AAUdC4n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CABLE NETS COURT PSAKI TO HOST...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jen-psaki-talking-to-msnbc-and-cnn-about-her-own-cable-news-show-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki Already Talking to MSNBC and CNN About Her Own Cable News Show, Reports Puck's Dylan Breyers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN:  Condescending face of White House...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/23/jen-psaki-is-the-condescending-face-of-the-biden-administration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Jen Psaki’s statements seem aimed at one cohort alone: High-earning, highly educated liberals and progressives just like her, ones who think anyone on the other si…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY GOES HOLLYWOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/tom-brady-jane-fonda-road-trip-comedy-1235098335/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood icons Lily Tomlin, Jane Fonda, Rita Moreno and Sally Field will star in '80 for Brady,' which Kyle Marvin will direct and Brady will produce via his 199 Productions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psaki the Next Maddow?</title>
      <link>https://puck.news/is-jen-psaki-the-next-rachel-maddow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;puck.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s spokesperson, who plans to leave the White House this year, is being feverishly courted by CNN and MSNBC, among others. And Psaki has ambitions to become a marquee star. Is she the next Maddow or Anderson?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka in talks for voluntary interview with Jan 6 committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/23/politics/ivanka-trump-january-6-committee/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump's daughter Ivanka, who also served as senior White House adviser, is in discussions with the House select committee investigating the January 6 insurrection to voluntarily appear for an interview, her spokesperson and two sources familiar with the probe confirmed to CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  White Supremacists Plotted Power Grid Attacks to Start Race War...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/white-supremacists-plotted-power-grid-attacks-to-start-a-race-war-feds-say/ar-AAUdDE0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chemical plant in evacuated, may be pretext for aggression...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/ukraine-says-plant-in-crimea-evacuated-may-be-pretext-for-aggression</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Leading Fraud Investigation in NY Resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/prosecutors-leading-trump-fraud-investigation-in-ny-resign/ar-AAUdAzK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids These Days Truly Weaker?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20220218-are-younger-generations-truly-weaker-than-older-ones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Younger cohorts are often stereotyped as being lazy, entitled or self-obsessed – and have been for centuries. Is there something to this perception?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State TV paints Moscow as savior...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-entertainment-media-europe-moscow-a760a2b6dcf5ef820cee7138336a5b3b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — As the West sounded the alarm about the Kremlin ordering troops into eastern Ukraine and decried it as an invasion, Russian state media painted a completely different picture — of Moscow coming to the rescue of war-torn areas tormented by Ukraine’s aggression and bringing them peace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Prosecutors Leading NY Inquiry Resign, Clouding Case's Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/02/23/nyregion/donald-trump-fraud-investigation-new-york.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prosecutors had abruptly stopped presenting evidence to a grand jury in the high-stakes criminal investigation into the former president’s business practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of cities blanketed with antisemitic flyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/02/23/1082568636/antisemitic-flyers-colleyville-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating the distribution of antisemitic flyers just a month after a gunman took worshippers hostage in a synagogue. Similar materials have been dropped in driveways across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Classifies Medical Treatment of Trans Minors as Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/02/23/texas-classifies-medical-treatment-of-trans-minors-as-abuse-threatens-parents-orders-caregivers-to-snitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These orders aren’t about safety. They’re a complete rejection of the legitimacy of these procedures, and a denial of individual liberty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skiers stunned as Black Hawks crash near Utah resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2022/02/22/black-hawk-helicopter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wreck was a "training accident," according to the Utah National Guard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security costs spike for campaigns as threats rise...</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2022/02/22/security-costs-spike-for-campaigns-as-rules-ease-and-threats-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rise in threats and new rules from the FEC led to candidates spending $3 million on security last year, campaign disclosures show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON:  'NINTENDO Generation' Has Weak Skeletons...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gk4p/pentagon-says-nintendo-generation-has-weak-skeletons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A military press release announced that Gen Z may be at risk for more injuries in boot camp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas candidate poses nearly nude atop oil pump...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/23/texas-candidate-kicks-up-controversy-by-posing-nearly-nude-atop-an-oil-pump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Stogner is running for railroad commissioner in Texas and has raised eyebrows over her racy campaign video — in which she straddles an oil pump wearing little more than a cowboy hat and boots…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSIVE CYBERATTACK</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/amid-massive-cyberattack-on-ukraine-us-warns-of-russian-invasion-within-48-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense and foreign ministry websites taken down in attack, as predicted by US officials ahead of full-blown invasion, to include airstrikes, missiles and push to Kyiv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing Mass Text Operation Terrorizes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/disturbing-mass-text-operation-terrorizes-ukraine-as-russian-troops-move-in/ar-AAUdejJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY getting into real estate business...</title>
      <link>https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/disney-storyliving-community</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architecturaldigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first Storyliving by Disney development will arrive in California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Let's Go Brandon' Crypto Tries to Relaunch, Amid 'Penis' Website Defacing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lets-go-brandon-crypto-team-tries-to-relaunch-after-james-koutoulas-threatened-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man behind the “Let’s Go Brandon” crypto coin threatened to sue key investors last week, blaming them for the nearly worthless token’s demise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venus Flytrap Could Revolutionize Brain Implants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/this-venus-flytrap-could-revolutionize-brain-implants/ar-AAUdnms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly lethal bird flu detected in Delaware poultry...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-698385</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Department of Agriculture reported a highly lethal form of bird flu in a commercial poultry flock in Delaware on Wednesday, expanding an outbreak that has limited exports of poultry products. The agency has recently reported infections of highly pathogenic avian flu in commercial turkey and chicken operations in Indiana and Kentucky, triggering trade restrictions from buyers like China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TANKS, FORCES MOVING IN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-news-02-23-22/h_6d205f365f501bc935268528b826a824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between Moscow and Kyiv are at their highest in years, US President Biden announced a new round of sanctions following Russian President Putin recognizing two separatist pro-Moscow regions in Ukraine as independent. Follow here for the latest updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESERVISTS DRAFTED...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/595435-ukraine-president-orders-reservists-to-be-drafted-urges-ukrainians-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine on Wednesday began drafting reservists aged 18 to 60 into its armed forces as the country prepares for a possible invasion by Russia.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
