<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside supersonic presidential jet that can fly TWICE speed of sound...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2631486/inside-supersonic-presidential-jet-speed-sound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is what a supersonic presidential plane that could hit speeds of 1,380mph as it jets at nearly twice the speed of sound could look like. New renderings show the incredible supersonic president…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NATION OF ISLAM FOLLOWER'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9431911/How-college-football-star-lost-job-devout-Nation-Islam-follower.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Noah Green's descent into paranoia and deeply-troubling mental illness began in 2019, it appears, and rapidly worsened this year when he went to Botswana and attempted suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orgies, blackmail, extortion, Iran hostages...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/02/matt-gaetzs-alleged-scandals-include-orgies-blackmail-extortion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alleged orgy with prostitutes. Accusations of sex with an underage girl. A trophy photo of a woman wearing only a hula hoop. And a convoluted extortion plot involving a likely dead American host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills store let criminals stash guns, drugs, cash...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beverly-hills-store-let-criminals-013647942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI and DEA raid of an Olympic Boulevard strip mall found safe deposit boxes crammed with contraband, indictment says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unique 4/3/21 date draws lines for Vegas wedding licenses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/occasions-weddings-couples-marriage-las-vegas-39d3418e06b212a63ade2e61eda295dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Soon-to-be newlyweds lined up out the door of the marriage license office in Las Vegas on Friday, ahead of a unique date to tie the knot: 4/3/21. Nearly 700 couples obtained...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAR RAMMING,  EMERGED WITH KNIFE</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2628651/capitol-lockdown-suspect-knife-car-barrier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE suspect who was shot dead by cops in the fatal car-and-knife rampage at the US Capitol on Friday was a devoted follower of ‘Nation of Islam’ leader Louis Farrakhan, according to his…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'END TIMES'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/suspect-custody-after-car-rams-two-officers-u-s-capitol-n1262917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The slain officer, William Evans, was an 18-year-veteran of the force and a member of the Capitol Division’s First Responder’s Unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NATION OF ISLAM FOLLOWER'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9431125/Capitol-cops-injured-car-smashes-barrier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Capitol police officer killed by a knife-wielding driver in Washington DC on Friday has been identified as veteran cop Billy Evans. Evans had worked for the Capitol Police for 18 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece of SPACEX rocket debris lands at Washington state farm...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-04-piece-spacex-rocket-debris-washington.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A piece of burning rocket debris seen streaking across the Pacific Northwest sky last week crashed on a farm in eastern Washington state, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROTHER NOAH X KILLS CAPITOL COP</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/02/suspect-who-smashed-into-barrier-at-us-capitol-identified-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver who killed a US Capitol cop before he was gunned down by police is a Nation of Islam devotee from Indiana, according to reports and his social media. Noah Green, 25, who may have been li…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach partygoers in Barcelona defy restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210403104641-ah1sh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN-TOURISM (PIX):Beach partygoers in Spain's Barcelona defy COVID-19 restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen kidnap pastor during FACEBOOK live ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210403014317-21gqq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-VIOLENCE/:Gunmen kidnap Haiti pastor during Facebook live church ceremony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Swarms of Ships, Beijing Tightens Grip on South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/03/with-swarms-of-ships-beijing-tightens-its-grip-on-south-china-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese ships settled in like unwanted guests who wouldn’t leave. As the days passed, more appeared. They were simply</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot artist sells art for $688,888, now eyeing music career...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/music-hong-kong-robotics-asia-pacific-3e9cf6949ad3cd8c5884e63b6630b774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Sophia is a robot of many talents — she speaks, jokes, sings and even makes art. In March, she caused a stir in the art world when a digital work she created as part of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aiming big, Joe looking to restore faith in government...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lyndon-johnson-e1980730f351435701e80dfa4c001800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As President Joe Biden preaches patience but acts with urgency, his vision of the powers of the Oval Office is quickly taking shape, modeled after Democratic predecessors who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some dying while awaiting jab...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immunizations-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-veterans-d43aade61cf70abe1f9de070a8d1280b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of hoping to receive a COVID-19 immunization and then weeks of fighting the illness after one never came, Air Force veteran Diane Drewes was down to her last few breaths at a hospice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California OKs indoor sports, concerts as cases plunge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-nba-theater-los-angeles-lakers-ed9645feef26e713d4a84aaa189791dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Sports, theater and music fans will be able to take their seats again in California as the state's coronavirus cases plummet and vaccinations jump. After a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish suffer pain and stress, claims report that criticizes welfare failings...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/apr/02/farmed-fish-suffer-pain-and-stress-says-report-that-criticises-welfare-failings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of Atlantic salmon and trout, the aquaculture sector should focus on cultivating species with less complex needs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St. fixation on quick profits 'wreaking havoc in real economy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Wall-Street-s-fixation-on-quick-profits-wreaking-16073231.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast sums of money sloshing around the financial sector are enriching shareholders but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America passes 25 million corona infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/latin-america-passes-25-million-coronavirus-infections/ar-BB1ffqJI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin America and the Caribbean passed the 25 million mark Friday for recorded coronavirus cases as a surge in infections saw countries place restrictions on travel and movement while vaccine campaigns catch up. An AFP tally showed the region reaching the grim milestone of 25,001,533 infections, putting it in third place after Europe with 44.2 million cases and the United States and Canada with over 31.5 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risked player walkout if not moved...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/mlb-risked-player-walkout-star-230256192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseball risked having several top players boycott the All-Star Game had it not been moved from Atlanta, according to some who celebrated Friday's announcement by commissioner Rob Manfred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA PASSES 100 MILLION VACCINATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-million-vaccines-europe-hiccups.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States reaped the fruits Friday of its vaccination campaign against Covid-19 as it became the first nation to reach 100 million people, but Europe's rollout faced fresh impediments and South America tightened restrictions in the face of Brazil's soaring infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops open criminal investigation into Texans QB Watson after flood of sex harassment claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2630281/houston-police-department-investigating-deshaun-watson-texans-qb-allegations/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deshaun Watson is being investigated by the Houston Police Department after another person filed a complaint against the Texans quarterback. “Today, a complainant filed a report with the Hous…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA HERO IN MEGA MESS!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Gaetz-is-said-to-have-boasted-of-his-access-to-16073588.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Matt Gaetz repeatedly boasted to people involved in Florida politics...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With new immigration role, Kamala gets perilous assignment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/with-new-immigration-role-harris-gets-a-politically-perilous-assignment/ar-BB1ffEWc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democrats worry that the vice president’s new task will collide with her long-term ambitions and that, for better or for worse, she could own much of what happens on the border in coming months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS:  NFI...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/matt-gaetz-appeared-on-fox-news-18-times-in-march-his-scandal-has-gotten-zero-mentions-on-the-network-in-april/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz is such a regular presence on Fox News that when it was reported he was eyeing an early retirement from Congress for a gig at Newsmax, the biggest surprise was the choice of network. Gaetz appeared on Fox News 18 times in March. According to a Washington Post analysis, in the last […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossings in March jumped to highest in 15 years!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Border-crossings-in-March-jumped-to-highest-level-16073570.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Preliminary enforcement data for March confirms what border officials have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Federal Taxes for Dozens of Big, Profitable Companies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/02/no-federal-taxes-for-dozens-of-big-profitable-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as the Biden administration is pushing to raise taxes on corporations, a new study finds that at least 55 of America’s largest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few  rush to defend...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prosecutors-possible-payments-for-sex-gaetz-investigation-b43b8340f9e81f6c6eebf95e956be962</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The political peril for conservative Republican Rep. Matt Gaetz deepened Friday as the often outlandish, Trump-styled provocateur appeared politically isolated amid a federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOU'RE OUT:  MLB All-Star Game moved from GA after voting law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mlb-baseball-rob-manfred-georgia-voting-rights-e1cf72c8b2d61afad049cae498ccbbe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Atlanta lost Major League Baseball’s summer All-Star Game on Friday over the league’s objections to sweeping changes to Georgia voting laws that critics — including the CEOs of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin Airport arrests after 2 refuse mandatory quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-56617914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irish broadcaster RTÉ says it's understood the two women had travelled for a cosmetic procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMA fighter has finger severed in match...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mixed-martial-arts-philadelphia-martial-arts-2867c4cd67ba048c1dd1efe287b40f5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — A mixed martial arts fighter had his finger severed during a match in Philadelphia, but doctors were eventually able to reattach it. Khetag Pliev was injured Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos mulling CHARGERS purchase?</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/is-jeff-bezos-checking-out-opportunity-to-purchase-chargers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ownership of the Los Angeles Chargers may be in jeopardy, and former Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos just might swoop in to save the day. That is, if you really</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Northern Edge' brings firepower to Alaska, with eye on Arctic jockeying...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/04/01/northern-edge-brings-firepower-to-alaska-with-an-eye-on-arctic-jockeying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pacific Air Forces will lead the Army, Navy, and Marine Corps in the biennial, 12-day Northern Edge exercise beginning May 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVES Blast Move: Victimizes Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/02/braves-respond-after-mlb-moves-2021-all-star-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlanta Braves are digging in their cleats. Shortly after Major League Baseball announced it would be moving the 2021 All-Star Game from Atlanta amid backlash over new Georgia voting laws, the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida prohibits passports, citing 'freedom'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210402-florida-prohibits-vaccine-passports-citing-freedom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida prohibits vaccine passports, citing 'freedom'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVES Blast Move: Victimizes Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/Braves/status/1378072546088738818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO: GOOD COVID NEWS THREATENS AGENDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the U.S. and Iran agree to indirect talks next week in a possible breakthrough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth to 'super twins' conceived 3 weeks apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/super-twins-superfetation-three-weeks-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Roberts said when she found out she was pregnant with a second baby, she was shocked. "It was a good job I was laying on the couch or I would have fainted on the floor," she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Friend has been singing to the feds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9430921/Matt-Gaetzs-arrest-imminent-sources-say-Joel-Greenberg-singing-feds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep Matt Gaetz is expected to be indicted within the next few weeks as sources say former Florida official and friend Joel Greenberg has been 'singing to the feds' in the investigation against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB All-Star Game moved from Atlanta after voting law...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/sports/atlanta-braves/mlb-will-move-all-star-game-out-of-atlanta/TCUEJPUPZZD2RCO3DY5OZH62OU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game, a marquee event that had been scheduled for Truist Park in July, will be moved out of Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerable Dems fret after getting shock: AOC campaign cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/02/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-campaign-contributions-478943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez's largesse — and an oversight at the campaign headquarters — has raised awkward questions among her colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider-trading indictment shows ties to BLOOMBERG scoops...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/business_of_news/an-insider-trading-indictment-shows-ties-to-bloomberg-news-scoops.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more than six months, federal prosecutors say, a New York man used inside information to make illegal profits in the stock market—and a core element of his alleged scheme was his interaction with Bloomberg News, which published several stories shortly after the trader arranged to make significant purchases of the companies’ shares. Last month, […]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite Public School Changes Admissions To Help Whites, Hurt Asians...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/04/02/thomas-jefferson-asian-admissions-plf-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the name of helping racial minorities, officials are adopting a plan that would boost whites at the expense of Asian Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After year of 'hibernation,' cities wake up...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/after-year-of-coronavirus-hibernation-israels-cities-wake-up-663884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATIONAL AFFAIRS: “When the shuk is full, the heart is full,” a vendor in Mahaneh Yehuda told a television reporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% of adults dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/about-40-percent-of-adults-in-the-united-states-have-received-one-dose-of-a-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America is hitting a milestone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians mark Good Friday amid lingering virus woes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/christians-good-friday-coronavirus-93d314d71d1b64ee936c5727c4c2c76b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Christians in the Holy Land are marking Good Friday this year amid signs the coronavirus crisis is winding down, with religious sites open to limited numbers of faithful but none...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer crashes through school bus, lands on sleeping student!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/wild-video-shows-deer-crashing-through-school-bus-landing-sleeping-n1262896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He’s laying there asleep and the deer comes in, lays on top of him and rolls off onto the floor,” a Virginia school official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonic origins aside, checks please evangelical critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/demonic-origins-aside-checks-please-biden-s-evangelical-critics/article_527e4235-367d-51cd-b160-9a940b0087e9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelical Christians and small-government activists, among the fiercest critics of President Joe Biden and the Democratic Congress, are finding solace in $1,400 stimulus checks that some are sharing with churches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a prescription to die remains tricky even as aid-in-dying bills gain momentum...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/montana-medical-aid-in-dying-legal-gray-zone-reviving-legislation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access to physician-assisted death is expanding across the U.S., but the procedure remains in Montana’s legal gray zone more than a decade after the state Supreme Court ruled physicians could use a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER STRAIN FEARS ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2627827/covid-super-mutation-beat-vaccines-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID could mutate into a new super variant which could beat vaccines, make people sicker and reinfect victims in a devastating new outbreak, leading experts have warned. Scientists told The S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torches 'Looneyville' FOXNEWS and 'nut' hosts...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/john-boehner-spills-on-shocking-meeting-with-roger-ailes-to-try-to-put-a-leash-on-fox-news-hosts-like-nut-sean-hannity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former House Speaker John Boehner did not hold former Fox News founder Roger Ailes, or current prime time host Sean Hannity, in the highest esteem. Politico has just published an excerpt adapted from his book On the House, to be published by St. Martin’s Press on April 13, 2021, in which Boehner calls out the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of new witnesses to testify at Netanyahu trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/hundreds-of-new-witnesses-to-testify-at-netanyahus-trial-663890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu’s trial hears witnesses, and the public will hear what the cases are about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Grew by 136,000 Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/national/terence-p-jeffrey/government-grew-136000-workers-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal, state and local governments in the United States increased their employment by a combined 136,000 in March, according to the numbers released today by the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACKER...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-variant-tracker-where-different-strains-are-spreading-ffd71934-1596-43e6-923d-32c4698e2f8b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our live tracker keeps you updated with the need-to-know info on the new coronavirus variants now spreading through the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUPER MUTATION' FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14509332/covid-super-mutation-beat-vaccines-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID could mutate into a new super variant which could beat vaccines, make people sicker and reinfect victims in a devastating new outbreak, leading experts have warned. Scientists told The S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby boy 'first in world born with three penises', doctors say...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/baby-boy-first-world-born-23841946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unidentified child, from Duhok city, Iraq, has a rare condition called triphallia and it was only diagnosed after three months when his parents discovered swelling in his scrotum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang hospitalized with likely kidney stone...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210402132703-55zwe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/YANG-NEW YORK (PIX):Andrew Yang, New York City mayoral candidate, hospitalized with likely kidney stone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Gov Was Tested by Pandemic. Now Recall Looms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/02/californias-governor-was-tested-by-the-pandemic-now-a-recall-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — Things have been looking up in California. Vaccines will soon be available to everyone over 16. Los Angeles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just living his life'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210331224231-zj3vm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/GEORGEFLOYD (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-'Just living his life': Jurors see videos taken before and after Floyd's deadly arrest</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
