<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 7 In 10 Americans Hide Unhealthy Eating Habits...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-7-in-10-americans-hide-unhealthy-eating-habits-from-their-partners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over half of 2,000 Americans with romantic partners make efforts to hide their unhealthy eating habits from their better halves, according to a new survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia alarmed by U.S. Air Force visit to Norwegian island...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-alarmed-by-us-air-force-visit-to-norwegian-island/ar-BBZXRmZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Warns Of 'Credible Threat' Targeting Officers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/02/13/nypd-warns-of-credible-threat-targeting-officers-in-the-bronx/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is investigating what it's calling a "credible threat" to again target officers in the Bronx, just four days after a violent weekend when police were targeted by multiple shootings including an attack inside the 41st Precinct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biologically Male Runner To Compete In USA Women's Olympic Trials...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/02/13/megan-youngren-transgender-runner-olympic-trials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megan Youngren, a biologically male marathon runner who identifies as a transgender woman, is set to compete in the USA Olympic trials on Feb. 29.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate moves to limit President on military force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6286252716f16d09c23451cf95443c6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate approved a bipartisan measure Thursday aimed at limiting President Donald Trump's authority to launch military operations against Iran, with eight Republicans joining...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC admits test kits flawed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7997201/US-health-authority-shipped-faulty-coronavirus-test-kits-country.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest patient, who was aboard a flight from the city of Wuhan that arrived at Marine Corps Air Station Miramar in Southern California last week, is now in isolation at a hospital in San Diego.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force to allow turbans, beards, hijabs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/13/us/air-force-dress-code-sikhs-muslims-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the new guidelines, Sikhs and Muslims can seek a religious accommodation to serve with their articles of faith and expect to be approved, except under extremely limited circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign office vandalized in Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://www.toledoblade.com/local/politics/2020/02/13/mike-bloomberg-toledo-campaign-office-defaced-overnight/stories/20200213092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Mike Bloomberg’s campaign field office in Toledo was defaced just before the space is set to mark its grand opening on ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks MICROSOFT Pentagon cloud contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/13/amazon-gets-restraining-order-to-block-microsoft-work-on-pentagon-jedi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Amazon filed a motion asking the court to pause Microsoft's work on the $10 billion cloud contract.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Fund to Take Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-13/mcclatchy-company-newspaper-publisher-files-for-bankruptcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New rape charges against Islamic scholar...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rape-charges-against-islamic-scholar-ramadan-182234031.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Islamic scholar Tariq Ramadan has been charged with raping two women besides two others he was already facing accusations over, his lawyer told AFP Thursday. The 57-year-old Ramadan, a Swiss national, was already charged in France with raping a disabled woman in 2009 and a feminist activist in 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk on track to become world's richest person!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8000057/Elon-Musk-worlds-richest-man-April-Teslas-value-stays-100billion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla founder Elon Musk is on track to becoming the richest person once the EV maker has achieved a $100 billion market value over a period of six months, as well as hitting certain financial targets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Brown died in 2006. Now a prosecutor is looking into...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/13/us/atlanta-prosecutor-looking-into-james-brown-death/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The county's chief prosecutor will examine singer James Brown's death after meeting Wednesday with a woman who said she has evidence that Brown was murdered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic hiring spree triggers other campaigns...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/02/13/bloomberg-spending-local-state-campaigns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is hands down the toughest time I’ve ever had finding field staff,” said one operative, reflecting on the sweeping impact of Bloomberg’s spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Underground could be hotbed...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/coronavirus-doctors-fear-tube-could-spread-covid-19-as-london-gets-first-case-11932794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A total of nine people in the UK are now being treated for COVID-19, the disease caused by the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Remove Black Man Wearing KKK Robe Outside TARGET; 'Social Experiment'...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/02/12/virginia-deputies-confront-black-man-wearing-kkk-robe-outside-target/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A black man wearing a Ku Klux Klan robe at a Virginia Target told deputies he was performing a social experiment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never Mind the Internet. Here's What's Killing Malls...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/never-mind-the-internet-heres-whats-killing-malls/ar-BBZXavj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THE VILLAIN'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/weinstein-lawyer-mocks-d-case-163718232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A lawyer for Harvey Weinstein slammed prosecutors at his rape trial, saying they failed to prove he sexually assaulted any of his accusers and urging the jury to have the “courage” to clear her client.“We’re asking you to do the right thing,” defense attorney Donna Rotunno told the jurors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC SHOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/12/trump-roger-stone-justice-department-114684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alarmed veterans of the Justice Department said the legal system was entering uncharted territory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Critics' Groups Squabble Over Who Is a Hollywood Critic...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/hollywood-critics-groups-squabble-who-is-a-hollywood-critic-1278712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Critics' Choice Association — the folks who run that selfie festival known as the Critics' Choice Awards — are trying to clamp down on another critics' group in L.A that changed its name to the Hollywood Critics Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat owners urged to keep pets indoors...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1241832/Coronavirus-UK-pets-catch-virus-keep-cats-indoors-vet-advice-symptoms-coronavirus-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORONAVIRUS is being treated as a global emergency and pet owners have been told to keep their pets indoors as coronavirus infections hit more than 60,000 globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elites Shun Commercial Airlines, Look to Private Jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/02/13/global-elites-shun-commercial-airlines-look-to-private-jets-as-coronavirus-death-toll-surges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy travelers and corporate clients are looking to private jets as a way to isolate themselves from the deadly coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE pulls clip of Rand Paul reading 'whistleblower' name...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rand-paul-whistleblower-name-youtube-video-removed-fcbeb035-c486-4aa1-a563-44deb10dd0be.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kentucky senator said the move was "dangerous and politically biased."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RAY DONOVAN' will get proper ending after sudden cancellation...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/02/13/ray-donovan-will-get-a-proper-ending-after-sudden-cancellation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Liev Schreiber drama will either come back for a few final episodes or a movie to lay the characters to rest, Page Six can reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radical New 'WEST SIDE STORY' Paints an Angry Young America...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/radical-west-side-story-paints-154640449.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In spring 2016, Belgian theater director Ivo van Hove was in New York, preparing his Broadway production of Arthur Miller’s The Crucible. Between rehearsals, he found himself captivated by the crowded and chaotic Republican presidential primaries. Like the rest of the country, he watched</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Poised to Get Its Lowest Rate Ever at 30-Year Bond Sale...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-poised-lowest-rate-ever-155052521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. government’s sale of 30-year bonds Thursday is likely to draw a record low yield near 2% after the Treasury rally spurred by the spread of the Wuhan coronavirus in China and around the world helped drive rates across the curve to multi-month lows.Trading of Treasury securities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Hits Back: 'Carnival Barking Clown'; 'Behind Back They Laugh at You'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-obsesses-over-loser-mike-bloomberg-54-mass-of-dead-energy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Need evidence that Mike Bloomberg is now viewed as a political threat to the second term of President Donald Trump? Look no further than Thursday's insults hurled at the former New York City mayo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHINGTON EXAMINER Editor Dumped Over Secret Recordings...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/washington-examiner-editor-out-after-colleague-secretly-recorded-sexist-and-hateful-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-level bloodletting at the Washington Examiner continued this week with the dramatic ouster of its managing editor on Monday, days after the conservative magazine fired its breaking news edito</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders saying 'millionaires' less often...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/13/bernie-sanders-says-millionaires-less-in-2020-democratic-primary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After famously railing against "millionaires and billionaires," Bernie Sanders is focusing more on billionaires in the 2020 Democratic primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 8,000 Pounds Of Trash Removed In 'Worst Nightmare' Hoarding Case...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/02/12/8000-lbs-trash-fairfield-home-police-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crews carried out 8,000 pounds of trash from one home in Fairfield on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Attorney Says Prosecutors 'Strip Adult Women' Of All Responsibility...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/harvey-weinstein-trial-closing-arguments-strip-adult-women-1202858773/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insisting that Harvey Weinstein “sits here an innocent man,” defense attorney Donna Rotunno began her closing arguments in Weinstein’s rape trial today by imploring the jury of se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman 'escapes after held captive as sex slave for 31 years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/woman-captivity-sex-slave-man-arrest-venezuela-maracay-a9331096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn movie shot at holy site outrages Myanmar...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/porn-movie-shot-holy-outrages-myanmar-133924225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outrage is growing in Myanmar after the emergence of a 12-minute porn video shot in Bagan, the country's best-known tourist hotspot and UNESCO heritage site of thousands of hallowed Buddhist pagodas. "Our Bagan pagodas are The Holy Land," wrote Mg Khin Gyi on Facebook with multiple angry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causing first drop in oil use in decade...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-causing-first-drop-oil-decade-iea-095845008--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global oil demand will suffer its first quarterly drop in a decade as the COVID-19 virus lashes the economy in China and its impact ripples throughout the world, the IEA said Thursday. "Global oil demand has been hit hard by the novel coronavirus (COVID-19) and the widespread shutdown of China’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 UGLY: Trump Rips BLoomberg: '5' 4" Mass of Dead Energy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/trump-obsesses-over-loser-mike-bloomberg-54-mass-of-dead-energy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Need evidence that Mike Bloomberg is now viewed as a political threat to the second term of President Donald Trump? Look no further than Thursday's insults hurled at the former New York City mayo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCUST PLAGUE: THE DAY THE SKY TURNED DARK...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1241433/Locust-Apocalyptic-footage-biblical-scale-Africa-Kenya-crop-wipe-out-plague-latest-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APOCALYPTIC footage has shown the terrifying moment drivers in Kenya were descended upon by billions of locusts sparking further panic among east African countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'undercover robot spies' blend into human population...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-deploy-undercover-robot-spies-21489076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Dr Ian Pearson predicts undercover robot spies that look human will be deployed by countries around the world for surveillance, blending into human environments without us even knowing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick To Release Memoir Under Own Publishing Company...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/columnist/bell/2020/02/13/colin-kaepernick-interview-new-memoir-publishing-company-nfl-return/4736086002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick explains in a rare interview why he is writing a memoir and starting a publishing company, and what it means for NFL playing career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Kelly Finally Lets Loose on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/john-kelly-alexander-vindman-north-korea-and-trump/606496/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former chief of staff explained, in the clearest terms yet, his misgivings about Trump’s behavior regarding North Korea, immigration, and Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement Millionaire Crowd Swells in Roaring Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/retirement-millionaire-crowd-swells-to-record-in-roaring-market</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retirement Millionaire Crowd Swells to Record in Roaring Market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded foreigners tell of fear and rations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/foreigners-stranded-wuhan-virus-tell-fear-rations-094314188.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunkered down at the epicentre of China's virus epidemic and cut off from the world, the remaining foreigners in Wuhan are eking out a life in fear. A coronavirus outbreak that has killed more than 1,300 people and locked down the central Chinese city has left thousands of foreigners trapped as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic crisis complicates sex lives of young Venezuelans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/economic-crisis-complicates-sex-lives-young-venezuelans-050801959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Venezuela, mired in a years-long economic crisis, the price of love can be impossibly high for cash-strapped young couples. In the tropical gardens surrounding the Central University of Venezuela, in Caracas, it is not uncommon to see young student couples making out behind a palm tree. Such public</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek islands should not be migrant warehouses, residents say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200213105115-mckxg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-MIGRANTS/GREECE-PROTESTS (PIX, TV):Greek islands should not be migrant warehouses, residents say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Questions About Origin...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/sudden-militarization-wuhans-p4-lab-raises-new-questions-about-origin-deadly-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg campaign suddenly drops memes everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/michael-bloombergs-campaign-suddenly-drops-memes-everywhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (NYTIMES) - Mr Michael Bloomberg has contracted with some of the biggest meme-makers on the internet to post sponsored content on Instagram promoting his presidential campaign.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US military prepping for pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2020/02/13/us-military-prepping-for-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Northern Command is bracing for an outbreak of the new coronavirus on U.S. soil, if it should occur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake-like UFO returns to Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/snake-like-ufo-returns-florida-21481545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mystery object was similar to those seen across the US in recent months and is the second time it has been seen in Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea 'executes patient'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/breaking-north-korea-executes-coronavirus-21488604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong-un quickly placed those returning from China in a quarantine. But according to reports an official was spotted breaching the order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods on Verge of History and Still Tinkering...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/sports/sport-others/tiger-woods-is-on-the-verge-of-history-and-still-tinkering-6265941/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fan hysterics have been a staple at his tournament appearances for decades, but they are now coming during a renaissance of sorts, as Woods, 44, looks to build on the momentum he has accrued since winning the Masters last season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Presence on the Farm: Robots...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/13/a-growing-presence-on-the-farm-robots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FARMER CITY, Illinois — In a research field off Highway 54 last autumn, corn stalks shimmered in rows 40-feet deep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein jury set to hear closing from #MeToo skeptic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a5aa55367dc47556fc8200e78de064e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Closing arguments at the Harvey Weinsten rape trial are set to begin Thursday, with the jury hearing first from a Chicago attorney who’s taken #MeToo movement heat for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit claims professor used disabled patients in Iowa for sex research...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article240209247.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks judge who will sentence...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/895357/twitter-rampage-trump-attacks-federal-judge-set-sentence-roger-stone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Tuesday night attacked the judge presiding over his friend and adviser Roger Stone's criminal case. Stone was found guilty last year of lying to Congress, witness tampering, and obstructing a House investigation. The Department of Justice recommended he receive seven to nine years in prison, but after Trump tweeted on Tuesday morning that this was a 'miscarriage of justice!' the DOJ suddenly reversed course, calling the recommendation 'grossly disproportionate.' All four of the federal prosecutors who worked on the case have withdrawn in an apparent protest, with one of them choosing to resign from the department altogether. Trump began tweeting about Stone's case as the results of the New Hampshire Democratic primary began trickling in. 'Is this the Judge that put Paul Manafort in SOLITARY CONFINEMENT, something that not even mobster Al Capone had to endure?' he tweeted. 'How did she treat Crooked Hillary? Just asking!' The judge in question is Judge Amy Berman Jackson, who has presided over several cases involving people close to Trump, including Manafort, his former campaign chairman. Manafort is now serving a 7-and-a-half year prison sentence after being found guilty of tax and bank fraud and pleading guilty to conspiracy charges. Hillary Clinton has not been on trial for any crimes, and thus has not appeared before Jackson. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donors set to leave Biden...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/12/donors-set-to-leave-joe-biden-after-iowa-and-new-hampshire-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s disastrous results in Iowa and New Hampshire have spooked Democratic donors who are preparing to jump ship and throw their money behind someone else — even as his campaign vowed Wednesd…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 'Mayor Pete'? -- Trump struggles for killer nickname...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/just-mayor-pete-trump-struggles-killer-nickname-214111228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump likes to coin disparaging nicknames for his political opponents -- but so far, he hasn't quite hit the mark with rising young Democrat Pete Buttigieg. Is it perhaps that Trump doesn't see "Mayor Pete" as a credible opponent?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even Critics Praise Merkel as Chancellor's Reign Draws to an End...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-critics-praise-merkel-chancellor-050000805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Portugal’s Socialist Prime Minister Antonio Costa is not a natural ally for the conservative Angela Merkel but as Europe starts to prepare for life without the four-term German chancellor he’s clear that her influence remains vital for the continent’s future.Merkel has not always been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes counting methods...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-virus-death-toll-tops-1-100-cases-042819236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s official death toll and infection numbers from a new coronavirus spiked dramatically on Thursday after authorities changed their counting methods, fuelling concern the epidemic is far worse than being reported. Two top-ranking politicians overseeing the epicentre of the outbreak were also sacked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  'ALL NEWSPAPERS ARE GOING TO DIE'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/munger-tells-newspaper-company-papers-195754744.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Charles Munger, who’s a newspaper company executive as well as a Berkshire Hathaway Inc. vice chairman, said U.S. newspapers have no future.“Technological change is destroying the daily newspapers in America,” Munger, 96, said Wednesday in Los Angeles at the annual meeting of Daily Journal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400 Million Social Media Users Set to Lose Their Anonymity in India...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/400-million-social-media-users-210000021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook, YouTube, Twitter and TikTok will have to reveal users’ identities if Indian government agencies ask them to, according to the country’s controversial new rules for social media companies and messaging apps expected to be published later this month.The requirement comes as governments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Dems fear fallout from Bernie atop ticket...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ee0b0675aacf75270f24126e69378902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Sen. Bernie Sanders' robust start in the race for the presidential nomination is triggering alarm among congressional Democrats, with many warning that a ticket headed by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan Communist Party chief removed...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200213042304-qcdq7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/HUBEI-PARTY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China's Hubei, Wuhan Communist Party chiefs removed amid epidemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio braces for risk during Carnival... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200212214841-b1szx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/BRAZIL-CARNIVAL (TV):Rio braces for coronavirus risk during Carnival party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEXES EXECUTIVE AUTHORITY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Trump-seeks-to-bend-the-executive-branch-as-part-15052083.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump is testing the rule of law one week after his acquittal in his Senate impeachment trial, seeking to bend the executive branch into an instrument for his personal and political vendetta against perceived enemies.  And Trump - simmering with rage, fixated on exacting revenge against those he feels betrayed him and insulated by a compliant Republican Party - is increasingly comfortable doing so to the point of feeling untouchable, according to the president's advisers and allies.  In the span of 48 hours this week, the president has sought to protect his friends and punish his foes, even at the risk of compromising the Justice Department's independence and integrity - a stance that his defenders see as entirely justified.  Trump complained publicly about federal prosecutors' recommended prison sentence for one of his longtime friends and political advisers, Roger Stone. After senior Justice Department officials then overruled prosecutors to lighten Stone's recommended sentence, the president congratulated Attorney General William Barr for "taking charge" with an extraordinary intervention.  Next Trump sought to intimidate the federal judge in the Stone case, badgering her on Twitter for previous rulings, and attacked the four prosecutors who resigned from the case in apparent protest of the Justice Department's intervention. Then Trump floated the possibility of a presidential pardon for Stone, who was convicted by a jury in November of tampering with a witness and lying to Congress.  The president has openly encouraged his Justice Department to retaliate against a quartet of former FBI officials who long have been targets of his ire for their involvement in the Russia probe.  "Where's [James] Comey?" Trump bellowed Wednesday in a stream-of-consciousness diatribe from the Oval Office....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Concerned Spread Through Pipes...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/3050068/coronavirus-your-toilet-how-hong-kong-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reclassification may have allowed virus to travel 10 storeys in a Tsing Yi housing estate – resulting in an evacuation in early hours of Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SETS STAGE FOR STONE PARDON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-declines-rule-out-pardon-roger-stone-n1136091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don't want to say yet," Trump said when asked by reporters whether a pardon was on the table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Taxes and Spending Set New Records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-and-spending-set-records-through-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government set records for both the amount of taxes it collected and the amount of money it spent in the first four months of fiscal 2020 (October through January), according to data released today in the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING ADMITS:  14,840 NEW VIRUS CASES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/13/coronavirus-latest-updates-china-hubei.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wuhan is the Chinese city at the epicenter of the outbreak and the capital of Hubei province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman floats NEW impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/02/12/swalwell-impeaching-trump-over-roger-stone-is-not-off-the-table/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Eric Swalwell (D-CA) Wednesday on CNN revealed that the Justice Department's reversal on Roger Stone's sentence after President Donald Trump's tweet could be an impeachable offense. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC preparing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/prevention-cures/482794-officials-say-the-cdc-is-preparing-for </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doctor at the CDC updates reporters on the steps the U.S. is taking to tackle the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW SULLIVAN</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/author/andrew-sullivan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;View an archive of articles by Andrew Sullivan for Daily Intelligencer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More sick on quarantined ship...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff4f6baa1b49f96dc15c236b5b467369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan’s health ministry said Thursday 44 more people on a cruise ship quarantined near Tokyo have tested positive for the virus that causes the new disease known as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Retribution tour'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e613b755f0750a1df4127f054561d7d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the week since his acquittal on impeachment charges, a fully emboldened President Donald Trump is demonstrating his determination to assert an iron grip on government, pushing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG Barr agrees to testify as Dems question his leadership...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/027cb88523c183e8b05848be838b1354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General William Barr has agreed to testify before the House Judiciary Committee next month, appearing for the first time before the panel as questions swirl about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPERIMENTAL BRAIN TREATMENT ON NAVY SEAL SPIRALS OUT OF CONTROL... </title>
      <link>http://rewired.inewsource.org/ucsd-kevin-murphy-prtms-navy-seals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rewired.inewsource.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A novel and unproven treatment is at the center of a confidential University of California investigation, lawsuits and a Navy SEAL's psychotic break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snoop Dogg Apologizes to Gayle King, Says He 'Overreacted' to Kobe Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/snoop-dogg-apologizes-to-gayle-king-for-over-kobe-bryant-interview-comments-overreacted-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I publicly tore you down by coming at you in a derogatory manner based off of emotions, me being angry at questions that you asked," rapper says</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
