<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Florida Reopening Party Season Already Fiasco...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/florida-coronavirus-outlook-veers-toward-disaster-as-young-people-lean-into-reopening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strip clubs. Bars. Pools and golf clubs. Pro sports. As one doctor put it, “There’s active community spread. If you’re young, you’re old, it doesn’t matter.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race to face McConnell hurtles toward unpredictable finish...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/22/booker-mcgrath-kentucky-senate-334617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. Charles Booker is still considered the underdog in Tuesday’s primary against Amy McGrath, the party favorite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS: TEXAS CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL ADMITTING ADULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/health/coronavirus/texas-childrens-hospital-admitting-adult-patients-as-covid-19-cases-continue-to-rise/285-5aa0a132-a318-4a41-81b3-6659086c2ef7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One pediatrician tweeted that she is up for the challenge, but she also asked the public to wear a mask and stay home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CASES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/23/us/us-coronavirus-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With half of US states reporting a rise in new cases, one expert warns of 'danger signs' in some parts of the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clash near White House prompts Secret Service to tell press to leave grounds in unusual move...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/22/politics/white-house-secret-service-press/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A confrontation between protesters and police in the park across the street from the White House on Monday evening led the US Secret Service to take the unusual step of ordering members of the White House press corps to immediately leave the grounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton on Trump second term: Be afraid...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bolton-trump-second-term-b16f9ec9-1d0a-4749-8753-567ae06af00a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two subjects the former national security wouldn't discuss: his legal situation and note-taking practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore restaurant denies service to Black woman, son...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/baltimore/2020/06/restaurant-apologizes-after-black-woman-son-denied-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Baltimore restaurant issued an apology after video showed a Black woman and her son being denied service because of the boy’s clothes while a white child dressed a similar way had been served.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's #1 tennis player Djokovic positive after hosting tournament!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/504032-worlds-1-tennis-player-novak-djokovic-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's top-ranked tennis player, Novak Djokovic, said on Tuesday that he tested positive for the novel coronavirus after participating in an exhibition series he organized in Serbia and Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: AMAZON Delivery Driver Dumps Packages Into Sewer...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/amazon-delivery-drive-packages-thrown-in-sewer-maryland-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating after an Amazon delivery driver was caught on camera allegedly throwing packages down a sewer in Parkville, Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS CASES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jun/23/first-thing-covid-19-cases-surging-us-states-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infections have risen in 29 states, with several breaking their daily records. Plus, how a botched assassination plot exposed the rot in Russia’s spy services</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega-Church Set to Host Rally Falsely Claim Air Filter Zaps COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/arizona-mega-church-set-to-host-trump-rally-falsely-claim-its-air-filter-zaps-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dream City Church’s claim that it has technology to kill the coronavirus and protect rallygoers “is absurd,” says one epidemiologist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENNIS STAR DJOKOVIC POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennis.com/pro-game/2020/06/world-no-1-novak-djokovic-tests-positive-coronavirus/89329/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Serb has come under tremendous criticism since Grigor Dimitrov&amp;#39;s positive test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC SCAPEGOAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/23/trump-cdc-overhaul-coronavirus-335039</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Trump under fire for his handling of the outbreak, his advisers are eyeing the federal bureaucracy for other culprits ahead of the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky meat plant cited, penalized after cow shot in the head 4 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/state/kentucky/article243711552.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS PLUNGING...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-s-polls-are-plunging-but-it-s-too-early-to-count-him-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every recent poll shows President Donald Trump headed to defeat in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI TESTIFIES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a36ac8c2b3edf7f9c41f850e945c32e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With coronavirus cases rising in about half the states and political polarization competing for attention with public health recommendations, Dr. Anthony Fauci returns to Capitol...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priceless 17th century painting of Virgin Mary ruined in horror restoration...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1023879/painting-virgin-mary-ruined-repair-spain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BAROQUE painting of the Virgin Mary is the latest in a long line of pictures to be disfigured while undergoing restoration. A private art collector is said to have been charged €1,200 (£1,084) by…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decline of dollar could happen at 'warp speed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-decline-of-the-us-dollar-could-happen-at-warp-speed-in-the-era-of-coronavirus-warns-prominent-economist-stephen-roach-2020-06-22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Roach, a Yale University senior fellow and former Morgan Stanley Asia chairman tells MarketWatch that his forecast for a sharp deterioration of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hot springs in January, no traffic, universal healthcare. The best retirement escape?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hot-springs-in-january-no-traffic-and-universal-healthcare-the-best-retirement-escape-youve-never-heard-of-2020-06-22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh, and it’s not too hard to immigrate, says Matt Patsky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch on cusp of biggest win yet in war against GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishtimes.com/business/media-and-marketing/rupert-murdoch-is-on-the-cusp-of-his-biggest-win-yet-in-his-war-against-google-1.4286229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US antitrust lawsuit against the internet giant would mark progress for News Corp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY braces for stunners...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/504017-ny-democrats-brace-for-primary-night-stunners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats in New York are bracing for a turbulent election day, with incumbents feeling the heat from upstart primary challengers while open seats attract huge fields of candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's that sound? Fireworks exploding across USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/whats-sound-not-just-york-025006561.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fireworks are a summer tradition. But in New York and cities around the country, complaints over displays have exploded this summer. The exact reasons for the uptick remain a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China launches final satellite to complete rival to GPS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-launches-final-satellite-complete-rival-gps-025337926.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Tuesday launched the final satellite in its homegrown geolocation system designed to rival the US GPS network, marking a major step in its race for market share in the lucrative sector. The launch of the Beidou-3GEO3 satellite from the Xichang Satellite Launch Center was originally scheduled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark's high tax consensus wobbles as Danes told to spend...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200623105244-0u92d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/DENMARK-ECONOMY (PIX):Denmark's high tax consensus wobbles as Danes told to spend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai vets perform mass sterilization as hungry monkeys terrorize tourist city...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200623102311-dsz8t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THAILAND-MONKEYS/STERILISATION (PIX):Thai vets perform mass sterilisation as hungry monkeys terrorise tourist city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduced voting sites 'recipe for disaster'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200623091534-6rgsj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/VOTE (PIX, TV):Amid coronavirus, reduced voting sites in Kentucky, elsewhere a 'recipe for disaster'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars About to Have 'Wright Brothers Moment'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/23/nasa-mars-helicopter-will-be-red-planets-wright-brothers-moment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is about to take to the air on another planet. As part of its next mission to Mars, leaving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spate of shootings raises fears of violent summer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5f676600b6173c58cf6b5da48f6f4840</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A spate of shootings over the past several days has law enforcement on edge, with some warning that a turbulent brew of a pandemic, racial unrest, historic surges in gun sales and a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimmel Under Fire For Using N-Word, Donning Blackface...</title>
      <link>https://www.hotnewhiphop.com/jimmy-kimmel-criticized-for-saying-n-word-donning-blackface-news.113065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotnewhiphop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resurfaced audio of Jimmy Kimmel dropping the n-word in a rap parody has resurfaced. Cancel Culture is coming for Jimmy Kimmel. The late-night talk show host has been under fire recently after an old interview involving him and Megan Fox resurfaced. While speaking with the actress in the video clip,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's probably not coming on Nov. 3? A result in race for White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Barring-a-landslide-what-s-probably-not-coming-15358093.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After voters in Pennsylvania, Georgia and Nevada went to the polls this month, some races hung in the balance for days as election officials waded through thousands of absentee ballots.  On Tuesday, a similar scenario is expected to play out in Kentucky and New York, where officials have already announced that some results will not be available for as long as a week.  In all five states, officials have contended with an avalanche of mail ballots as voters seek to avoid exposure to the novel coronavirus. It was a fresh illustration of how the pandemic is transforming the way elections are conducted in the United States.  It is also a stark preview of what's coming on Nov. 3 - or, more accurately, what may not be coming: an election night result in the race for the White House.  If voters remain reluctant to cast ballots in person, November is likely to bring an even more massive wave of voting by mail than what has swept across the country during primary season. That, in turn, means a close race between President Donald Trump and former vice president Joe Biden in a pivotal state could take days, even weeks, to resolve, election officials across the country are warning.  Barring a landslide for either candidate, that scenario could invite an unprecedented test of the country's faith in its elections: an extended period without a declared winner. Amid that uncertainty, few expect Trump, who has said repeatedly that he thinks mail voting could cost him the election, to soothe voter anxieties.  On Monday, the president fired off tweets making unfounded assertions that voting by mail will cause massive fraud and allow foreign countries to manipulate the vote, echoing claims by his attorney general, William P. Barr.  "Because of MAIL-IN BALLOTS, 2020 will be the most RIGGED...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump increasingly preoccupied with defending his physical, mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-increasingly-preoccupied-with-defending-his-15358423.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The early June meeting in the Cabinet Room was intended as a general update on President Donald Trump's reelection campaign, but the president had other topics on his mind.  Trump had taken a cognitive screening test as part of his 2018 physical, and now, more than two years later, he brought up the 10-minute exam. He waxed on about how he'd dazzled the proctors with his stellar performance, according to two people familiar with his comments. He walked the room of roughly two dozen White House officials and reelection staffers through some of the questions he said he'd aced, such as being able to repeat five words in order.  At the time, the Montreal Cognitive Assessment - which includes animal pictures and other simple queries aimed at detecting mild cognitive impairment such as dementia - was intended to quell questions about Trump's mental fitness. But in recalling it, Trump said he thought presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden would never be able to pass it and suggested challenging him to take the test, said the people familiar with Trump's comments, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to share private details.  The seeming non sequitur was part of Trump's growing preoccupation in recent weeks over perceptions of his mental and physical health at a time when critics have mocked him for episodes in which they say he has appeared frail or confused. The attacks Trump has previously levied against Biden - dismissing the former vice president as "Sleepy Joe," secreted away in his basement and enfeebled - have boomeranged back on him, as opponents have seized on Trump's own missteps to raise concerns.  Another sign of Trump's unease came Saturday night in Tulsa, Okla., when the president devoted more than 14 minutes to regaling a campaign rally crowd with the tale of "the ramp and the water." Eager to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower Claims Chinese Communists Pay Vatican $2 Billion in Bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2020/06/23/whistleblower-claims-chinese-communists-pay-vatican-2-billion-in-bribes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exiled Chinese dissident Guo Wengui alleged the Chinese Communist Party “allocates $2 billion a year” to pay off the Vatican for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Germany orders first local lockdown since easing...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/germany-orders-first-local-lockdown-since-easing-state-premier-01592903407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German authorities on Tuesday ordered a new lockdown for an entire district -- the first since easing coronavirus restrictions and a major setback to  hopes of a swift return to normality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm brewing after chaotic Berman firing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/503994-the-memo-storm-brewing-after-chaotic-berman-firing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shock over the Trump administration’s firing of a top government prosecutor is reverberating across the political world, but not even the president’s foes are confident he will face consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Steve Bing, philanthropist and film producer, dies after fall from building...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/steve-bing-philanthropist-film-producer-034422947.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Bing, the heir to a $600-million fortune, was a noted film producer and philanthropist. He became a household name after paternity suits involving Elizabeth Hurley and Kirk Kerkorian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Catching Up to Trump Money 'Juggernaut'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/23/how-joe-biden-is-catching-up-to-the-trump-money-juggernaut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. will hold his first event of the 2020 campaign with former President Barack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR rallies around Wallace as FBI investigates noose...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af5f2437b470984c26d8acb6b66ac807</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bubba Wallace steered the No. 43 to the front of pit road, NASCAR champion Kyle Busch pushing the famous car on one side and close friend Ryan Blaney pushing on the other.  The entire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online registrar threatens to drop anti-immigration website...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/online-registrar-threatens-drop-anti-immigration-website-71391728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An internet registrar is threatening to delist a website that is a leading promoter of white nationalist and anti-immigration views</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossils show 1st humans left Africa 200,000 years ago for icy Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/fossils-show-1st-intrepid-humans-left-africa-200000-years-ago-for-an-icy-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discovery of fossils of cold-climate rodents alongside remains of region's 1st modern humans shows they arrived from hot cradle of Africa during Ice Age, but were able to adapt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Build 'WikiLeaks For Cops' With Leaked Police Dept Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90519693/report-highly-sensitive-police-department-data-hacked-for-a-wikileaks-style-website</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data reportedly includes financial information, as well as personal data about people who had dealings with the police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man ends up in court for calling ex's Irish boyfriend 'leprechaun'...</title>
      <link>https://www.eveningexpress.co.uk/fp/news/local/court/man-ends-up-court-for-calling-exs-irish-boyfriend-a-leprechaun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eveningexpress.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Aberdeen man has been fined after branding his ex partner's new boyfriend a "leprechaun" in a threatening email.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire garage rallies behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8448563/NASCAR-race-begins-support-Bubba-Wallace.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an extraordinary act of solidarity with NASCAR's only black driver, dozens of drivers pushed the car belonging to Bubba Wallace to the front of the field before Monday's race in Talladega, Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Gov Urges Residents To Wear Masks...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/gov-greg-abbott-texans-masks-keep-texas-open/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disturbed by the recent uptick of coronavirus cases and hospitalizations in Texas, Governor Greg Abbott urged Texans to follow CDC guidelines and wear a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 killed, 11 hurt in Charlotte Juneteenth party shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcnc.com/article/news/crime/deadly-shooting-north-charlotte-beatties-ford-road/275-781db2ad-0768-402f-8ebc-09f2526172a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcnc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CMPD Deputy Chief Gerald Smith said officers believe over 100 shots were fired during the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists develop 3D prosthetic eye -- better than real thing?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/superhuman-sight-scientists-develop-3d-prosthetic-eye-better-than-real-thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of scientists has created a 3D artificial eye that looks human-like -- and actually functions better than a human eye or any other bionic creation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid threats, public health officials leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/amid-threats-and-political-pushback-public-health-officials-are-leaving-their-posts/ar-BB15Q3Ip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Senator demands masks, social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8447385/Florida-Sen-Rick-Scott-demands-masks-social-distancing-Republican-Convention-Jacksonville.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rick Scott asserted Monday morning that if Republicans move their convention to Florida, he expects the massive crowds to wear masks and practice social distancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WANTED: SPIES. CIA turns online for new recruits...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-cia-jobs-idUSKBN23T2TT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. defense and spy agencies played a major role in creating the internet, and now the CIA is turning for the first time to online streaming services to recruit spies between the ages of 18 and 35.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign staffers who attended Tulsa rally test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/22/coronavirus-2-more-trump-campaign-rally-staffers-test-positive-for-covid-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight advance team members, two of whom are Secret Service agents tested positive either before or after President Donald Trump's Tulsa rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic ripped for wild tennis party after positive coronavirus tests...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/22/novak-djokovic-in-hot-water-over-reckless-partying-tournament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple tennis stars — including world No. 1 Novak Djokovic — are facing backlash for a video that has surfaced depicting reckless partying at a Serbian nightclub days before No. 14-ra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Women Less Likely To Date Men With Cats...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/keep-cat-out-dating-profile-colorado-state-university-researchers-warn-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Men holding cats were viewed as less masculine; more neurotic... and less dateable," researchers from CSU wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis police urged EMS workers to subdue dozens with powerful sedative...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/at-urging-of-police-hennepin-emts-subdued-dozens-with-powerful-sedative/485607381/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings of a draft report prompted the Minneapolis Police Department to tell officers that it's not their role to encourage sedation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bizarre': High water, erosion create floating island...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/06/19/bizarre-floating-island-meandering-in-muskegon-lake/3223308001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patch of ground and vegetation probably broke away locally - but maybe not. "I'm bewildered," a local scientist said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE watch to remind you to wash your hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/22/apple-introduces-apple-watch-handwashing-reminders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple wants to help people follow the public health guidelines during the Covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can scientists really make it rain?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-really-rain-174330254.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wing-mounted generator emits particles of silver iodide as circular fields of crops are seen in the distance as Scott Bryant flies a cloud seeding mission for the Western Kansas Weather Modification program Aug. 28, 2007, near Lakin, Kan. The program aimed to reduce crop damage from hail by saturating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee's largest county could return to Phase 1 reopening...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/tennessees-largest-county-return-phase-reopening-due-spike/story?id=71379050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennessee's largest county could go back to the first phase of its reopening plan due to a recent spike in novel coronavirus infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona wildfires grow as flames flicker throughout Desert Southwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Arizona-wildfires-grow-as-flames-flicker-15357348.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wildfires continue to rage in Arizona, leading into another week set to feature hot, dry conditions from the Desert Southwest to California. At the same time as the fires are burning, prompting evacuations, spikes in coronavirus cases are being recorded in several states in the region, including Arizona.  The fifth-largest wildfire in Arizona state history continued to rage Monday morning, swelling to 186,086 acres in size. The so-called Bush Fire northeast of Phoenix had torched an area of land seven times larger than Disney World and thirteen times larger than the island of Manhattan. It was 42% contained, with more than 700 personnel working to fight the flames.  State Route 87 was closed from Payson to Bush Highway, spanning 52 miles of the roadway. Routes 188 and 88 also experienced closures as well. And it was just one of a spattering of blazes dotting the region.  Elsewhere, officials were combating a number of other wildfires amid unfavorable weather conditions, with temperatures heating up into the upper 90s or triple digits for some, with little chance for rain. There's likely no immediate end in sight to the dry and hot weather, with Arizona's wildfire season likely to push on through at least mid-July.  California's fire season is barely getting started.  The communities of Sunflower and Apache Lake remained under evacuation notices, where danger was "imminent and life threatening." Other communities initially threatened by the Bush Fire were returned to a "set" level on a "ready, set, go" scale, and several thousand residents were permitted to return to their homes. However, they've been urged to be ready to evacuate with little or no notice.  The evacuations are more complicated this year due to concerns over the coronavirus, as cases of covid-19 continue to grow in the state. Cases are also on the increase...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Soldier Allegedly Gave Classified Info to Satanic Neo-Nazi Group...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/u-s-army-soldier-allegedly-gave-classified-info-to-satanic-neo-nazi-group-sources-say/2478537/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Army soldier is facing charges they allegedly gave classified military information to a white supremacist group with Satanic leanings. The charges, expected to be announced later Monday, allege the soldier gave information about U.S. troops stationed overseas to the Order of the Nine Angles (O9A), law enforcement and military officials told NBC News. The Southern Poverty Law Center…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joel Schumacher Dead at 80...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/joel-schumacher-dead-dies-batman-director-1234644961/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Schumacher, costume designer-turned-director of films including “St. Elmo’s Fire,” “The Lost Boys” and “Falling Down,” as well as two “Batman&amp;#8…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome sees scooter invasion as city emerges from lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rome-sees-scooter-invasion-city-emerges-lockdown-151434282.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Rome emerging from lockdown into warm summer days, electric scooters have invaded its streets as the Italian capital joins the debate over urban public transport during the pandemic. For some Romans the self-service battery-run scooters, already common in other European cities, ease congestion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 59% in Jacksonville against convention...</title>
      <link>https://floridapolitics.com/archives/342752-poll-shows-duval-voters-oppose-rnc-coming-to-jacksonville-worry-about-coronavirus-impact</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;floridapolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Fight Pandemic Loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/covid-19-robot-companions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's hard to replace human contact. But during a pandemic, robots can help patients fight off feelings of isolation and despair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High levels of cortisol associated with greater risk of death... </title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/high-levels-stress-hormone-cortisol-greater-risk-death-from-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research suggests that high levels of the stress hormone, cortisol, are associated with a greater risk of death in COVID-19 patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX testing fever-detecting cameras... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/LAX-is-testing-fever-detecting-cameras-as-15357205.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting Tuesday, some travelers at Los Angeles International Airport will be asked to undergo a new screening process long before they get to security checkpoints: walking past cameras that can flag travelers with a fever.  Officials on Monday planned to announce a pilot program to test the use of thermal imaging cameras at the departures entrance and the corridor for international arrivals in the airport's Tom Bradley International Terminal.  "We're trying to do everything we can to make sure that our airport terminals are a safe environment, and we're making sure that we're doing everything we can to make it healthy for people to come in," said Justin Erbacci, chief executive of Los Angeles World Airports.  Signs will direct travelers to walk through an area where cameras are stationed, which detect whether someone has a temperature of 100.4 or higher. Those who show an elevated temperature will be pulled aside for a secondary screening to confirm. Participation will be voluntary, and the airport will not stop anyone from continuing with their journey during the pilot - though workers will give advice handed down from county and federal health officials about traveling with an elevated temperature.  Airlines that are doing their own temperature screening can still prohibit travelers from flying if they have fevers.  "Through this pilot, we are not going to stop anybody from traveling," Erbacci said. "We want to test the accuracy of the technology and to understand if it is really able to capture accurate body temperatures of passengers en masse as they walk through this portal."  Similar technology has been used in airports in Asia since the SARS epidemic; during the coronavirus pandemic, workplaces, foreign airlines, resorts and others have invested in thermal imaging...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Office of Hate': Bot Army Target of Brazil's Top Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/In-hunt-for-office-of-hate-Brazil-s-Supreme-15356841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's known as the "office of hate." And like all good conspiracies, there's no hard proof it actually exists.  The alleged clandestine network of bots, businessmen and bloggers is said by some lawmakers and Brazil's biggest newspaper to rain vitriol on all who oppose President Jair Bolsonaro -- whether it be a super-star judge who jumps ship, a health minister who won't toe the line on the administration's covid strategy or a journalist who pens a critical article.  Now, the Supreme Court is trying to unmask pro-Bolsonaro social-media attack dogs after saying it found "serious evidence" pointing to the group's existence. The president blasts the effort as an affront to free speech and a political witch-hunt by a deep state cabal. The top court, which took the unusual step of launching its own investigation, alleges the "office of hate" may have weaponized fake news in a coordinated bid to topple opponents, institutions and perhaps even democracy itself.  There are "two or three campaigns every day in real time on every issue," said Marco Aurelio Ruediger, director of the Department of Public Policy Analysis at Getulio Vargas University, known as FGV, in Rio de Janeiro. "It's spontaneous, but also professional."  The Supreme Court investigation set in motion an interstate raid last month of properties linked to a far-right blogger, three high-profile businessmen and a dozen others. The case builds on two more probes already under way: One ordered by the nation's electoral watchdog and another by Congress.  Combined, the probes target the very way Bolsonaro communicates and energizes his base. Rulings against him could not only muzzle the social media machine that helped shoot him to power, but could also be grounds for impeachment.  "All these people were decisive in the construction of Bolsonaro, decisive in the creation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER SOLSTICE:  President's Shock at Rows of Empty Seats at Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-president-e2-80-99s-shock-at-the-rows-of-empty-seats-in-tulsa/ar-BB15O5Ht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSPITALIZATIONS GROW</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/22/coronavirus-hospitalizations-grow-in-arizona-and-texas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Sunday, the nation's seven-day average of new Covid-19 cases increased more than 24% compared with a week ago, according to a CNBC analysis of Johns Hopkins University data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Threatens 'Sensational Event' to End America...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/06/22/north-korea-threatens-sensational-event-to-end-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statement from North Korea's embassy in Moscow this weekend threatened a "sensational event" leading to the destruction of America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan supercomputer named fastest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/speed-japan-supercomputer-worlds-fastest-150435285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's Fugaku supercomputer, built with government backing and used in the fight against coronavirus, is now ranked as the world's fastest, its developers announced Monday. It snatched the top spot on the Top500, a site that has tracked the evolution of computer processing power for more than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Sales Fall to 9-1/2-year Low...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200622144752-zkcve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/ (WRAPUP 1):WRAPUP 1-U.S. home sales tumble to 9-1/2-year low; price growth slows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tearful Mexican cartel chief threatens government after mother's detention...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200621184831-yvaz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/ (PIX):Tearful Mexican cartel chief threatens government after mother's detention</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND:  104 shot, 14 fatally, over Father's Day weekend...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/crime/2020/6/20/21297470/chicago-fathers-day-weekend-shootings-homicide-gun-violence-june-19-22-104-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five children were among the 14 people killed, including a 3-year-old boy and 13-year-old girl killed in separate shootings in Austin on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVER 6 MILLION WATCH BOLTON INTERVIEW....</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/621639303687176192/martha-raddatzs-exclusive-interview-with-john</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News Chief Global Affairs Correspondent Martha Raddatz’s first exclusive interview with John Bolton stood as Sunday’s No. 1 program in Adults 18-49 (0.7/5) and Adults 25-54 (1.1/5).  In addition,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120,000 DEAD IN 4 MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/u-s-coronavirus-death-toll-surpasses-120-000-china-south-n1231663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus has infected nearly 8.8 million people as of Sunday and killed more than 464,000, according to Johns Hopkins University data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He has no philosophical grounding'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/21/trump-poses-danger-for-the-republic-if-re-elected-john-bolton-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump poses a “danger for the republic” and would be an even greater threat if he wins a second</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER SOLSTICE:  President's Shock at Rows of Empty Seats at Rally...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/21/the-presidents-shock-at-the-rows-of-empty-seats-in-tulsa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and several staff members stood backstage and gazed at the empty Bank of Oklahoma Center in horror. Mr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  38%  APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Bolton fears for the Republic if President re-elected...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bolton-hopes-trump-term-president-warns-country-imperiled/story?id=71320449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the many headlines from ABC News' interview with President Trump's former national security adviser John Bolton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-red House seat in Va. could turn blue...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Long-red-House-seat-in-Va-could-turn-blue-15356874.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats in central and Southside Virginia are choosing a nominee for an open congressional seat that the party thinks it could win for the first time in more than a decade.  Republicans last week ousted freshman Rep. Denver Riggleman in favor of Bob Good, who calls himself a "biblical conservative," to the delight of Democrats surveying their field of well-funded hopefuls competing in Tuesday's primary.  "I think everybody sort of breathed a sigh of relief and said, 'Bring it.' Bob Good really does not reflect the view of voters in this district," said Suzanne Long, chairwoman of the 5th District Democratic committee.  Four Democrats are on the ballot in the primary, which is being conducted mostly by mail because of the coronavirus pandemic but also has in-person voting from 6 a.m. to 7 p.m. Tuesday.  They are R.D. Huffstetler, a Marine veteran and former congressional chief of staff with Silicon Valley experience; John Lesinski, a retired Marine Corps colonel and former elected official in Rappahannock County who works in commercial real estate; Claire Russo, a former Marine intelligence officer and advocate for victims of military sexual assault; and Cameron Webb, a physician, former White House fellow and health policy researcher.  Applications for absentee ballots were due June 16, and in-person absentee voting was allowed through Saturday.  Huffstetler had the most cash on hand by the start of June, with $286,811, followed by Russo with $201,530, Webb with $139,661 and Lesinski with $36,078, reports show.  Good's campaign consultant, Chris Shores, declined to distinguish among the Democrats.  "No matter who they nominate, there is no doubt that they will adopt the radical agenda of the left - supporting restrictions on our gun rights, defunding police departments,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC Inks NASA Deal for Commercial Space Flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/virgin-galactic-inks-deal-with-nasa-for-private-trips-to-iss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It will act as a travel agency for trips to the space station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: What if Trump just gives up?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/921381/what-trump-just-gives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the president grapples with his growing unpopularity, will he lash out or lose interest?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: NJ Least Patriotic State...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/06/22/new-jersey-ranked-worst-patriotic-state-in-america-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study ranked New Jersey the worst patriotic state in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socially distanced orgies at NYC sex club...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/22/a-soho-sex-club-reopens-amid-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As NYC enters into Phase Two of reopening, Soho sex club NSFW is navigating how to get down and dirty while still staying squeaky clean and coronavirus-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe is no Hillary -- and that's problem for President...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-joe-biden-no-130040808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's best hope for reelection is dragging Biden down. That's harder when many voters like the guy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newest U.S. Attorney Faces Slate of Cases of Interest to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/newest-u-attorney-faces-slate-080000814.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Audrey Strauss takes over one of the most high-profile prosecutor jobs in America with a lot on her plate.The 72-year-old former deputy to Geoffrey Berman is taking the reins as acting U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York after an unusual shuffle -- her boss refused to leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO: At least 70 shot, including 4 children, in violent weekend...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/at-least-70-shot-10-fatally-including-4-children-in-violent-weekend/6259526/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten people were killed, including four children, and at least 60 others wounded in shootings across Chicago over the weekend, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police say deaths of black people by hanging are suicides. Many aren't so sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/Police-say-deaths-of-black-people-by-hanging-are-15356603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historical seasons have changed, and once again, America's trees are bearing a strange and bitter fruit - dead black bodies.  In less than one month, six black people have been found hanging from trees, in California, Georgia, New York, Oregon and Texas. Authorities say that all of these deaths appear to be suicides, with no signs of foul play. But family members of the deceased, protesters and activists, and some scholars of anti-black violence are intuitively suspicious about those conclusions. Rumors are also swirling on social media that these deaths are lynchings, with Twitter users saying things like: "With sound body and mind, I'm here to tell you right now, if my body is found hanging from a tree, I did NOT commit suicide, I was murdered."  These incidents are happening at a time of nationwide racial upheaval - when people are already on edge and suspicious about police accounts of their encounters with black people. Tree hangings evoke traumatic memories of America's grisly history of unpunished lynchings of thousands of black adults and children between 1880 and 1968.  Black people do commit suicide, of course, though the rate is 60% lower than for whites, according to data from the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. In black American culture, suicide is widely regarded as a shameful act; when it happens, it's generally private, and hanging is not a preferred method.  "It is very uncommon for young black men to commit suicide, let alone by hanging," says Raymond Winbush, a psychologist since 1976 who has treated hundreds of black men and boys and is the director of Morgan State University's Institute for Urban Research. The American Association of Suicidology reports that firearms are the predominant method of suicide among African Americans (as they are for the nation overall), regardless of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation dog may finally bark, investors bet...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-inflation-analysis/inflation-dog-may-finally-bark-investors-bet-idUSKBN23S09E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold, forests, property stocks, inflation-linked bonds - these are just some of the assets investors are pouring money into on the view that the recent explosion of government spending and central bank stimulus may finally rouse inflation from its decade-long slumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India, China commanders meet after border clash amid calls for boycott of Chinese goods...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200622124443-918dj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA-CHINA/ (WRAPUP 3, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 3-India, China commanders meet after border clash amid calls for boycott of Chinese goods</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From California to Texas, Triple-Digit Heat Set to Bake West...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-texas-100-degree-heat-113402336.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Temperatures forecast to hit 100 degrees Fahrenheit or more will bake the U.S. West, pushing up power demand and making going outside a misery from California to Texas over the next few days.Heat advisories and warnings have been issued from Oregon through California’s Central Valley east</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
