<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New blood test detects 20 types of cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/09/28/new-blood-test-could-detect-20-types-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new blood test could detect more than 20 types of cancer, allowing cases to be identified and treated far earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk to Unveil Mars Spaceship...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/elon-musk-starship-design-update-2019-preview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's time for the annual architecture update!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still time...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/with-biden-damaged-and-warren-surging-could-hillary-clinton-still-enter-the-presidential-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just a few weeks ago, it seemed exceedingly unlikely that Hillary Clinton would enter the race for the White House in 2020.  But now the Biden campaign is deeply struggling, and the constant focus that the impeachment inquiry is putting on his son's dealings in Ukraine has already significantly dama</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Gearing Up For Late-Stage Do-Over?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/hillary-gearing-late-stage-do-over-against-corrupt-human-tornado-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PREVIEWS GOSPEL MOVIE...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/entertainment/music/brian-mccollum/2019/09/27/kanye-west-plays-jesus-king-detroit-fans-previews-new-imax-movie/3794975002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper's Detroit adventure with Kim Kardashian continued Friday as fans at the Fox got the first listen to his upcoming album "Jesus Is King."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Premiere Disinvites Interview Press From Red Carpet...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/joker-premiere-red-carpet-journalists-1203352046/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros. Entertainment has restricted access for print and broadcast journalists from the red carpet at the upcoming U.S. premiere of “Joker.” The event, which will take place on Sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METALLICA postpone tour after frontman enters rehab...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/metallica-postpone-australia-nz-tour-frontman-enters-rehab-111535502.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington (AFP) - Metallica are postponing their upcoming tour of Australia and New Zealand after lead vocalist James Hetfield re-entered rehab, the American band announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PUMP: Fed Girding for Repo Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/economy/the-fed-is-girding-for-repo-trouble-monday-even-as-market-calms-1988022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Why 2019 feels like 1929...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/463441-why-2019-feels-like-1929-and-what-we-can-do-to-change-course</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The notion that we could be even remotely near another global paroxysm will strike many as ridiculous and unthinkable. But that’s how everyone at Downton Abbey felt too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC bans speech that might offend illegal aliens, up to $250,000 per offense...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/26/city-bans-calling-someone-an-illegal-alien-out-of-hate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s now against the law in New York City to threaten someone with a call to immigration authorities or refer to them as an “illegal alien” when motivated by hate. The restriction…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked couple fall to deaths during balcony sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10023126/balcony-sex-fall-deaths-ecuador/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NAKED couple fell to their deaths while having sex on a third-floor balcony after a house party, it was reported yesterday. The woman, a 28-year-old mother, and her 35-year-old lover slipped over…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politics taking physical, emotional toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/a-nation-divided-u-s-politics-taking-physical-emotional-toll-on-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to researchers, the current U.S. political climate is literally making Americans physically sick, damaging friendships, and driving man "crazy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 1/2 HOUR EPIC</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/09/27/1st-look-martin-scorseses-stunning-the-irishman-with-de-niro-pacino-finally-unveiled-three-and-half-hour-epic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Scorsese’s three and a half hour epic was unveiled to press this morning at Lincoln Center’s Alice Tully Hall. The monumental achievement, a capping note to Scorsese’s amaz…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST SHOCK:  DRUDGE COVERING IMPEACHMENT!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Matt-Drudge-played-a-major-role-in-the-Clinton-14473330.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Impeach Yourselves!" read the banner headline on Breitbart.com Wednesday morning, summing up what much of the right-wing news world thinks of the congressional impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump that had been launched the previous day.  "The psychotic anti-Trump hysteria has now completely overtaken the entire Democratic Party," Fox News anchor and Trump booster Sean Hannity told nearly 4 million viewers Tuesday.  "They think anytime a Republican is elected president, there must have been something 'illegitimate' going on," Kevin D. Williamson wrote in the National Review Thursday.  So far, so typical. This is, after all, the umpteenth Trump scandal to set the country's mainstream news outlets on fire while conservatives roll their eyes.  But there's one conspicuous exception: The Drudge Report has for the last three days been spewing ALL CAPS, bolded, underlined, and sometimes bright-red headlines that sound terribly grim for the president.  "HILL ROCKED"  "REPUBLICAN CRACKS EMERGE"  "AMERICA BRACES FOR IMPEACHMENT"  These were presumably written by the elusive Matt Drudge, who has been courted by Republican presidents and would-be presidents since he helped bring about President Bill Clinton's impeachment in 1998 using exactly the same website and screaming all-capital type. In some ways Drudge's fervent coverage of "IMPEACHMENT 2019" is a return to form. But it's also an extraordinary break between the right-wing internet's godfather and its favorite president.  Drudge, who could not be reached for comment, exploded out of obscurity during the Clinton era, when he turned his political gossip blog into a fount of juicy scoops about the president.  "EXCLUSIVE ... MORE THAN 75 PIXS THAT SHOW LEWINSKY/CLINTON TOGETHER!" read a typical headline. "LEWINSKY...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERALDO:  Entire Presidency Defined By Snitches And Rats And Backstabbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/09/27/geraldo_rivera_this_poor_president_whole_term_in_office_defined_by_snitches_and_rats_and_backstabbers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday morning on "FOX &amp; Friends," FOX News correspondent Geraldo Rivera said the whistleblower who reported President Trump's phone call with Ukraine is "a rotten snitch."  "I would love to wap him, but that is another story," he said about the whistleblower. "Imagine this poor president, his whole tenure in office has been marked by snitches and rats and backstabbers -- it’s amazing how he functions at all." GERALDO RIVERA (FOX NEWS CORRESPONDENT): After listening to the Democrats, they believe that they have it now.  That everything else, Russia collusion, Stormy Daniels, taxes, making money on hotels, and all that. They are going to put everything away and they are going to laser focus on this. This is gonna be what the impeachment is all about, maybe one or two little other things fall in.  So it’s going to be the president of the United States in a conversation that was intercepted by a rotten snitch -- I’d love to wap him, but that’s another story.  Imagine this poor president, his whole tenure in office has been marked by snitches, and rats, and backstabbers, it’s amazing how he functions at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG GOES MOB...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/cover-story/cover-story-2019-10-07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inspiration behind the artist’s cover for the October 7, 2019, issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLDFELLAS!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/irishman-review-nyff-2019-1243731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Scorsese assembles a powerhouse cast headed by Robert De Niro, Al Pacino and Joe Pesci in Netflix's saga of mob hitman Frank Sheeran and his complicated association with union boss Jimmy Hoffa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any stonewalling will 'boost case'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/27/politics/white-house-stonewalling-democratic-strategy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are developing a new plan to deal with any White House stonewalling to their upcoming demands for records and testimony: They will use it as evidence for an article of impeachment against President Donald Trump, according to sources involved in the discussions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAK:  White House restricted access to Trump calls with Putin and Saudi crown prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/27/politics/white-house-restricted-trump-calls-putin-saudi/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House efforts to limit access to President Donald Trump's conversations with foreign leaders extended to phone calls with Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman and Russian leader Vladimir Putin, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI releases files on Roy Cohn...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/27/fbi-releases-file-on-trumps-late-lawyer-roy-cohn.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Where's my Roy Cohn?" President Donald Trump has been quoted lamenting when faced with political and legal pressures. Cohn was at least the first of two personal lawyers for Trump to be disbarred. The second was Trump's more recent attorney and fixer, Michael Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Andy Cohen became ringmaster of our insane celebrity circus... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/How-Andy-Cohen-became-the-ringmaster-of-our-14473906.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Andy Cohen bounced in his seat and pumped his fist. Diane von Furstenberg, one of his guests on his Bravo late-night show "Watch What Happens Live with Andy Cohen," had just gone there - dished about her long-ago "brief love affair" with Richard Gere, not just on live TV but in the most deliciously, bluntly vulgar terms.  "Iconic! Iconic!" Cohen cheered, leaning over to give the fashion designer a high-five as his studio audience screamed.  Cohen, a reality-TV innovator behind the camera long before he became a talk-show host, has an uncanny radar for juicy details of famous and semifamous people's lives. That may be why his show has become a nightly raucous confessional for bona fide celebrities - even if they don't always plan on it.  The Gere story wasn't new news - von Furstenberg revealed it in her 2014 memoir - but it was new enough, or at least fun enough, to light up Cohen's audience that March night, as well as Page Six, People and dozens of other gossip-accumulating sites the next day. Yet it wasn't even the biggest scoop from that one 30-minute show. Cohen went to the phones to take questions from viewers. One asked his other guest, actress Julianne Moore, why she abandoned the leading role in "Can You Ever Forgive Me?" which turned into an Oscar nomination for Melissa McCarthy.  Moore, who had just set down a glass of white wine, winced. "I didn't leave that movie," she said, her voice light. "I was fired."  A gasp rose from the small audience. "Were you?!" Cohen exclaimed, then shifted into reporter mode: "Was there a reason? ... So you started shooting it? ... Did you see the movie?" She replied quietly: Creative differences. It happened during rehearsals. No, she hadn't yet seen the film. "It's still kind of painful."  Cohen, 51, who sharpened his interview skills at CBS News before deploying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 'TRIUMPH'</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/reviews/the-irishman-review-martin-scorsese-robert-de-niro-al-pacino-joe-pesci-1203351142/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the film that, I think, a lot us wanted to see from Scorsese: a stately, ominous, suck-in-your-breath summing up, not just a drama but a reckoning, a vision of the criminal underworld that&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:   'JUDY' has Zellweger pouting, posing and pursing her lips like she swallowed turpentine...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/09/judy-movie-review-renee-zellweger-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a fool would attempt to play the one and only Judy Garland, onscreen or anywhere else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 House Dems don't support!</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2019/09/27/politics/house-democrats-impeachment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past week -- amid allegations that President Donald Trump abused the power of his office for personal political gain -- there has been an absolute rush among House Democrats to call for impeachment proceedings against the President. What was once regarded as a risky position, politically, has now become a default position of the vast majority of the Democratic caucus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani to make paid appearance at Kremlin-backed conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Giuliani-scheduled-to-make-paid-appearance-at-14474063.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rudy Giuliani, whose actions as President Donald Trump's personal lawyer have helped set in motion an impeachment inquiry, is set to appear as a paid speaker at a Kremlin-backed conference in Armenia on Tuesday - an event expected toinclude the participation of Russian President Vladimir Putin and other top Russian officials.  Giuliani confirmed to The Washington Post on Friday that he plans to take part in a panel at the conference sponsored by Russia and the Moscow-based Eurasian Economic Union, a trade alliance launched by Putin in 2014 as a counterweight to the European Union.  According to an agenda for the event posted online, Giuliani is set to participate in a panel led by Sergey Glazyev, a longtime Putin adviser who has been under U.S. sanctions since Russia's invasion of Ukraine five years ago.  Giuliani's decision to take part in the conference astounded national security experts. His scheduled appearance comes days after the release of a whistleblower complaint accusing Trump and Giuliani of pressuring Ukrainian officials for damaging information about Democrats.  Trump this summer withheld military aid from Ukraine, which counts on U.S. support to help fend off pro-Moscow separatists in the country's eastern provinces. As part of his efforts in Ukraine, Giuliani has said the focus on Russia's interference in the 2016 election has overlooked what he claims was meddling by Kiev.  The agenda for the Eurasian conference shows Giuliani is the only American scheduled to speak at the gathering.  In an interview Friday, Giuliani angrily rejected questions about whether it was appropriate for him to attend the event at which he also appeared last year.  "I will try to not knowingly talk to a Russian until this is all over," he retorted.  The former New York...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearings as soon as next week...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/27/rep-adam-schiff-trump-impeachment-hearings-could-start-as-early-as-next-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the House Intelligence Committee claimed Friday that the panel could begin impeachment hearings targeting President Trump as early as next week. California Democratic Rep. Adam Schi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long list of possible witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-have-a-long-list-of-possible-targets-for-trump-impeachment-inquiry-212224633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The list of people Democrats may seek information from regarding President Trump's attempt to obtain dirt on Joe Biden seems to grow by the minute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani to make paid appearance at Kremlin-backed conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/giuliani-set-to-make-paid-appearance-next-week-at-kremlin-backed-conference/2019/09/27/a15ab242-e133-11e9-8dc8-498eabc129a0_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s personal attorney is the only American scheduled to speak at the event, which Russian President Vladimir Putin is also set to attend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Meets NRA For Financial Support For Defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/09/27/us/politics/trump-lapierre-nra-impeachment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In return for the support, Mr. LaPierre asked that the White House “stop the games” over gun control legislation, people familiar with the meeting said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 Trans Killings Raise Fears of 'Epidemic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/18-transgender-killings-this-year-raise-fears-of-an-epidemic/ar-AAHVMAB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cautionary tale of Japan's 'sex recession'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/japan-virgins-the-cautionary-tale-of-a-sex-recession/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more adult virgins in Japan than any other rich nation, leading to a worrying decline in fertility, and experts say it's spreading</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS IN A RUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democrats-eye-quick-impeachment-probe-of-Trump-as-14471555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democratic leaders are eyeing a fast-paced investigation into the possible impeachment of President Donald Trump, instructing the committees handling the probe to wrap up their findings within weeks in hopes of concluding before the holiday season.  Multiple Democratic lawmakers and congressional aides said there is no formal timeline for the inquiry, but the "need for speed," as one aide put it, comes as Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., is under pressure from vulnerable freshmen to keep the investigation narrowly focused and disciplined.  The emerging strategy of a rapid investigation focused mainly on the explosive accusation that Trump urged Ukraine's president to dig up dirt about a political rival comes as lawmakers prepare to leave Washington on Friday for a two-week recess. In addition to Trump's call, a whistleblower complaint claimed that unidentified White House officials tried to keep the conversation a secret within the government.  "The consensus in our caucus is that our focus now is on this allegation," Pelosi told reporters earlier in the day, adding: "This is a coverup."  Pelosi and other leaders huddled in a basement conference room Thursday evening with more than a dozen "front-liner" members representing the toughest districts for incumbent Democrats to discuss the fledgling probe and, in the words of multiple attendees, "get on the same page."  Inside the room, the group urged the leadership to keep the messaging around impeachment on national security and the Ukraine probe being led by the House Intelligence Committee and Chairman Adam Schiff, D-Calif. - not on the litany of potential Trump offenses being investigated by other panels, including the House Judiciary Committee, which traditionally takes the lead in impeachment proceedings.  "I'm very supportive of Adam Schiff and what...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootleg marijuana vapes tainted with hydrogen cyanide...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/vaping/tests-show-bootleg-marijuana-vapes-tainted-hydrogen-cyanide-n1059356</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News commissioned laboratory tests of knock-off marijuana vapes that found a pesticide linked to hydrogen cyanide in 10 out 10 products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS Surprise: Clint Eastwood's 'RICHARD JEWELL' Set for December Release...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/clint-eastwood-directed-richard-jewel-gets-an-awards-release-1243923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie will open opposite Sony's 'Jumanji: The Next Level.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter who exposed racist tweets fired for own tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-49857358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Des Moines Register has been forced to hire extra security for its newsroom due to threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL FLASHBACK: If House acts, Senate must have trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2bc10ed20dbf4041935b37bec9542c53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and the House impeachment inquiry (all times local): 2:30 p.m. Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said months ago that if the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges Silicon Valley to avoid slide toward new 'barbarism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vatican-technology-ethics-idUSKBN1WC11N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis urged Silicon Valley giants on Friday to make sure technological ad...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters: VP, AG Involved In 'Conspiracy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/sarahmimms/maxine-waters-pence-barr-ukraine-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They’re all involved,” Waters told BuzzFeed News’ AM to DM on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan with human rights to begin new life in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-49856859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Sandra the orangutan won a landmark appeal in 2014 which deemed her a "nonhuman person".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE tech 'Orwellian nightmare' to spy in your home...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/google-rolls-out-orwellian-nightmare-technology-spy-you-your-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average age of car on American roads: 12 years old...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/09/27/new-cars-last-longer-and-interiors-need-more-durable-materials/2211617001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cars are lasting longer than ever. Sounds good, right? It's actually a problem, and automakers are scrambling to respond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Probes Communist Police Impersonators...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/california-probes-chinese-communist-police-impersonators/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in California are investigating at least two cases of people posing as Chinese police driving cars with markings of the Communist Party of China's People's Armed Police (PAP).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Busted for 'Shoplifting' Just Had Penis Bulge...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/09/27/shoplifting-bulge-pants-england/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Scottish man got into a very awkward situation this week when he was accused of stealing items from a shop and putting them into his pants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FACEBOOK begins to phase out 'Likes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/09/26/facebook-hides-like-counts-test-australia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is going to start hiding "Like" counts as part of a new test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOIGHT:  WAR AGAINST TRUTHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2019/09/26/jon-voight-impeachment-effort-against-trump-is-war-against-truths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran actor Jon Voight has called upon the country to "stand with our President Trump in a time of such evil words," as Democrats push for impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain security firm probed 'for spying on Assange for CIA'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spain-security-firm-probed-spying-assange-cia-152919133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Spanish private security firm, which is under investigation in Madrid, spied on Wikileaks founder Julian Assange on behalf of the CIA while he was inside the Ecudoran embassy in London, El Pais daily reported Friday. Citing unspecified documents and statements, the paper said Undercover Global Ltd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary rock-star treatment at progressive group...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020-vision-hillary-rock-star-treatment-at-progressive-group-profile-rises-as-trump-faces-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Hillary Clinton received a wild standing ovation at the 50-year anniversary celebration for NARAL, a nonprofit that advocates for abortions. NARAL President Ilyse Hogue introduced the “rightful 45th president of the United States” to the 50th Anniversary Celebration Dinner on Thursday at the Capitol Hilton in D.C., where the twice-failed presidential candidate …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF California voters consider leaving state...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-09-27/who-wants-to-leave-california-berkeley-igs-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many conservatives feel marginalized and want to leave California, and young people are stressed by housing costs, a Berkeley IGS poll for The Times shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers could draft articles of impeachment by end of October...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/27/complaint-in-hand-democrats-aim-for-a-fast-and-focused-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — A crucial cache of evidence in hand, House Democrats moved quickly on Thursday with an impeachment inquiry they said would be focused tightly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcript...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Almost-a-spy-Transcript-of-Trump-s-remarks-at-14471796.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump delivered wide-ranging remarks at the U.S. Mission to the United Nations on Thursday morning where he dismissed the complaint against him from an intelligence community whistleblower and suggested that the person's actions are akin to being a spy or committing treason.  The closed-door event was intended for staff and families of the U.S. mission to honor the work they'd done for the president's visit to the United Nations. The president focused on condemning the whistleblower, lambasting the media and bragging about the size of his political rallies.  Below is a transcript from a 9-minute video of Trump's remarks obtained by The Washington Post. The video begins as U.S. Ambassador to the United Nations Kelly Craft leaves the stage and Trump takes the podium:  - - -  "They tell you you're going to be a star, the only way you're going to be a star, no matter how you look or feel or talk is when you make good deals. I found that out over the years, you've got to make good deals otherwise it's over. And [Craft] is going to make great deals.  I was with her now for three days and she's developed incredible relationships in a very short period of time and we appreciate it. (Looks at her) You'll be out there. You'll be in the firing line today for us. For instance, today I just heard while I'm coming up here, you know they have a whistleblower (laughter) he turned out to be a fake, he's a fake, a highly partisan whistleblower. The lawyer contributed to Biden, they contributed to - the whole thing is - but more importantly, you know what the whistleblower [complaint] is? The same letter that we announced yesterday, which was perfect, I couldn't have written it better if I wrote it myself. I could not have said or had a better conversation.  And we had a really nice gentleman in the president of Ukraine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN:  BIDEN FRIST CASUALTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/patrick-j-buchanan/joe-biden-impeachments-first-casualty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi speaks to reporters on September 26 2019. (Photo by ANDREW CABALLERO-REYNOLDS/AFP/Getty Images)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/tictoc/status/1177396573283573760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“"That's close to a spy." WATCH: Trump demands to know who gave information to the whistle-blower in the #UkraineTranscript that has spurred the #Impeach45 drive. More @business: https://t.co/lmgTALLGsi https://t.co/WTFeEX7K96”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Plane Passenger Goes Berserk Over Long Bathroom Line, Threatens To Kill Pilot...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/09/27/jfk-flight-emergency-landing-unruly-passenger-upset-over-bathroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flight that left John F. Kennedy International Airport had to make an emergency landing Thursday after an angry passenger allegedly started making threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG GOES MOB...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/new-yorker-cover-shows-trump-and-giuliani-as-mobsters-murdering-uncle-sam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cover for the upcoming edition of the New Yorker depicts President Trump and his personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani as mobsters who are murdering Uncle Sam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia quietly building network of spy satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10017217/russia-spy-satellite-missile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has launched another of its secretive spy satellites designed to silently track nukes fired from the US. Hurled into orbit from a launchpad in northeast Russia, the probe can detect long-ran…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult led by female buddha raided...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/cops-raid-killer-exorcism-cult-20314410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING GRAPHIC IMAGES: It's alleged people were beaten for trying to run away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAN DIET BLAMED FOR NFL QUARTERBACK'S BAD SEASON...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/sports/nfl/carolina-panthers/article235295427.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein butler dishes on Paris pad guests including Bill Gates, Steve Bannon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/27/epsteins-butler-dishes-on-paris-pad-guests-including-bill-gates-steve-bannon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The butler who managed Jeffrey Epstein’s posh Paris pad claims he waited on a rotation of famous faces including Prince Andrew, Bill and Melinda Gates, as well as Steve Bannon, according to a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAYDON CARTER:  IT'S WON'T BE PRETTY...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2019-9-28/the-view-from-here-2019-9-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air Mail is a weekly newsletter that will unfold like the better weekend editions of your favorite newspapers. Air Mail is delivered to subscribers' in-boxes every Saturday at 6:00 AM E.S.T.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans Completely Unprepared For Recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/personal-finance/shocking-new-survey-finds-most-americans-are-completely-unprepared-next-recession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman with 'WiFi' allergy sleeps in copper bag; Fears 5G may kill her...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10014593/woman-wifi-allergy-copper-sleeping-bag/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN who claims she is allergic to WiFi sleeps in a £400 copper sleeping bag and is terrified that the rollout of 5G will kill her. Rosi Gladwell, 70, a self-diagnosed radiation sufferer has spe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Feels Like 1776 Kind of Fight'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/09/27/trump-impeachment-national-security-house-democrats-moderate-mikie-sherrill-228430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freshman congresswoman reckons with the historical weight of standing up to the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXORCIST: Cases getting darker...</title>
      <link>https://www.koin.com/news/oregon/oregon-priest-performs-exorcisms-cases-are-getting-darker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.koin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KOIN 6 News spent an afternoon with a self-professed exorcist as he cleansed a man of what he believed to be evil spirits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: China Unveils 'Super Surveillance Camera' That Links To Social Credit System...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/china-unveils-super-surveillance-camera-that-can-link-to-its-social-credit-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Device can identify individual faces out of crowds of tens of thousands; Will take mass surveillance to a new level</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers warn about threat of political deepfakes by creating one...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Lawmakers-warn-about-threat-of-political-14472593.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Michael Waltz wants Navy to beat Army in this year's football game, according to a newly released political deepfake - a video doctored with artificial intelligence. But it the content wasn't true, as Waltz is a former Army Green Beret.  But Waltz teamed up with Rep. Don Beyer, D-Va., to craft the mock deepfake for the House Science subcommittee to illustrate just how realistic this kind of disinformation can be. The SUNY-Albany and University of Chicago researchers took a recorded video statement from Beyer and transposed it onto Waltz's image - designed to be a jarring sight for subcommittee chair and former Navy pilot Mikie Sherill, D-N.J.  The resulting video is a warning for lawmakers - and the public - that bad actors could abuse this technology for much more nefarious purposes than having a friendly joke about a sports rivalry. Watch it here:  "You see how dangerous and misleading it could be; I'm sure we fooled a couple of people," Beyer said. "For instance, what if instead of 'Go Navy, Beat Army,' I said, 'It's time to impeach the president'? That would be viral everywhere."  "My friends might appreciate that, but I think he would not," he added of his Republican colleague.  As the 2020 election looms, Washington lawmakers are increasingly concerned that bad actors will use deepfake technology to sow chaos and stoke divisions among the American public - much like Russian actors did with traditional social media posts during the 2016 election.  Waltz and Beyer are warning that United States needs to be investing in technology to quickly detect such fakes to keep up in an arms race, as the tools to create misleading videos become even cheaper and more widely available.  "These videos and this technology have the potential to truly be a weapon for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Snake-like UFO returns to California...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/snake-like-ufo-returns-california-20097741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The man claims to have never seen anything like the object before, but similar UFOs have been spotted across the US in recent months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Skydiver collides with semi-truck in fatal jump...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/09/26/skydiver-killed-by-truck-after-landing-on-california-highway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A skydiver died after hitting a big rig on a Northern California highway Thursday, according to KTLA sister station KTXL in Sacramento. Around 2 p.m., witnesses told the California Highway Patrol they saw a parachute fall from the sky toward Highway 99 in Acampo, between Sacramento and Stockton.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
