<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tumultuous mayor's race closes as voters struggle to choose...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jun/19/new-york-city-mayor-race-early-voting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 1% of the city’s registered voters have turned out so far in a primary filled with allegations and accusations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Riot, Looting Cases From Last Year Dropped by Prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/most-riot-looting-cases-from-last-year-dropped-by-nyc-das/3114714/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One year ago, parts of New York City felt out of control as crowds of looters were seen smashing storefront after storefront. The mayhem continued night after night from late May into June. At one point, there was even a so-called “looting dance party” on the streets of SoHo. The mobs seemingly pillaged at will. Many were caught on tape, some…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Trump Considered Sending Covid-Infected Americans To Gitmo...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jemimamcevoy/2021/06/21/trump-reportedly-considered-sending-covid-infected-american-tourists-to-guantanamo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new book from Washington Post journalists, the former president mulled the idea as a way of keeping the U.S.’s Covid-19 numbers down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's longest-known COVID-19 patient dies after 15 months...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britain-longest-known-covid-19-014500908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British man has died 15 months after first contracting COVID-19, his wife said. Jason Kelk, 49, was hospitalized in Leeds in March 2020, according to The Guardian. However, he died Friday after he was transferred to a hospice center. Kelk is believed to have been Britain’s longest-known COVID-19 patient. “It was definitely important for him to do it on his terms. But he is leaving an awful ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds gather at Stonehenge for Solstice despite advice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-arts-and-entertainment-042b5a42ddddc98828e8119c23d9b27f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Dozens of people have ignored advice not to travel to Stonehenge for the annual summer solstice celebrations, which were cancelled Monday due to coronavirus concerns. English Heritage, which looks after the Neolithic monument, had planned a live feed of the sunrise at Stonehenge for the second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli food truck banned from Philly food festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9707329/Israeli-food-truck-BANNED-Philadelphia-food-festival-causing-fierce-backlash-cancellation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decision by organizers to remove an Israeli food truck from its food festival lineup in Philadelphia this Sunday sparked a backlash, ultimately leading to the festival's cancellation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery-Store Boom Poised to Live On Even as Pandemic Fades...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/grocery-store-boom-is-poised-to-live-on-even-as-pandemic-fades</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grocery-Store Boom Is Poised to Live On Even as Pandemic Fades</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danger and demons: Mysterious 'Well of Hell'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210621-danger-and-demons-yemen-s-mysterious-well-of-hell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danger and demons: Yemen's mysterious 'Well of Hell'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House eyes ending migrant family expulsion...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-white-house-eyes-ending-migrant-family-expulsion-b6d0a178-001e-41e8-9f5b-17cc7547cccc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Title 42 hinges on COVID-19, making it harder to defend while the Biden administration touts climbing vaccination rates and slowing death and infection numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After death threats, Liz Cheney now surrounded by security...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/559357-after-death-threats-liz-cheney-now-surrounded-by-security-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gangs get paid off as officials struggle for fix...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-government-and-politics-technology-business-3b81e8116c42439566040a052617ad55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — If your business falls victim to ransomware and you want simple advice on whether to pay the criminals, don't expect much help from the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Workers Telling Boss to Shove It...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/06/quitting-your-job-economic-optimism/619242/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Americans are leaving their job. Is the workplace undergoing a revolution—or just a post-pandemic spasm?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents in 20 cities receiving $500 a month basic income...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9705819/It-lessens-bills-500-payments-tested-upstate-NY.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are testing pilot Universal Basic Income programs that hand out $500 payments per month in multiple cities after the popularity of Andrew Yang's proposal during his presidential run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves stealing truckloads of nuts. Latest heist was 42,000 pounds of pistachios...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/thieves-have-been-stealing-truckloads-of-nuts-police-say-the-latest-heist-was-42000-pounds-of-pistachios/ar-AALgeZ0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tulare County Sheriff's Office said it found the stolen pistachios in Alberto Montemayor's tractor trailer, siphoned into smaller bags and packaged for resale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN: World in worst cascade of human rights setbacks in our lifetimes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-worst-cascade-human-rights-102033369.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UN rights chief called Monday for "concerted action" to help recover from the worst global deterioration of rights seen in decades, highlighting situations in China, Russia and Ethiopia among others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear shakes Mexico border city after violence leaves 18 dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-mexico-shootings-34e04ff423d3f8427a233ca1ded882ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD VICTORIA, Mexico (AP) — Fear has invaded the Mexican border city of Reynosa after gunmen in vehicles killed 14 people, including taxis drivers, workers and a nursing student, and security forces responded with operations that left four suspects dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson Calls Journalists 'Animals.' He's Also Their Best Source...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/06/20/business/media/tucker-carlson.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His platform on Fox News made him a big player in Donald Trump’s circle. Off camera, he shapes the coverage of Trump’s world and Fox’s own internal politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears Set To Address Conservatorship First Time in Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/britney-spears-address-conservatorship-first-time-court-1600895</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Baby One More Time" hitmaker has been under the conservatorship, with her father Jamie Spears as conservator, for the last 12 years. Spears has now asked to permanently remove him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy's Deadliest New Subs Hobbled by Spare-Parts Woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/us-navy-e2-80-99s-deadliest-new-subs-are-hobbled-by-spare-parts-woes/ar-AALgAHD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy has swapped more than 1,600 parts among its new Virginia-class submarines since 2013 to ease maintenance bottlenecks as components that are supposed to last 33 years wear out decades sooner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morning People at Lower Risk of Depression Than Night Owls...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/21/morning-people-may-be-at-lower-risk-of-depression-than-night-owls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Lumber Prices Fall, Threat of Inflation Loses Bite?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/21/as-lumber-prices-fall-the-threat-of-inflation-loses-its-bite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild gun battle in Bronx streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/video-police-seeking-suspects-after-wild-gun-battle-in-the-bronx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video shows the suspects ducking behind cars and firing multiple shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside secure village, where athletes forced to eat alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3121750/inside-tokyo-covid-olympic-village/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO is a city full of famous buildings and iconic architecture. And its Olympic and Paralympic Village comes across as a homely, if slightly sterile, home for athletes that will descend upon it n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fans sues town for $25M after being told to remove MAGA flags from car...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3119621/trump-supporter-sues-town-for-25m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DIE-HARD Trump fan is suing a Long Island town for $25million after being ordered to take MAGA flags off his car. Michael Wasserman claims Long Beach authorities are trying to “silence̶…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST TRANS OLYMPIAN!</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/sport/tokyo-olympics-kiwi-weightlifter-laurel-hubbard-to-become-first-transgender-athlete-to-compete-at-the-games/DM7ZUGW3HQ2IDL6O7OSAXT3YJU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurel Hubbard will make history at the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK GAMES:  Olympian tests positive for virus upon arrival in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ugandan-olympian-tests-positive-for-virus-upon-arrival-in-japan-the-first-detection-as-athletes-head-to-tokyo/ar-AALfAsS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uganda’s team was reportedly all vaccinated with AstraZeneca and tested negative for the virus before departure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disappearance of circus from American life leaves us lonelier...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-the-disappearance-of-the-circus-from-american-life-leaves-us-lonelier/ar-AALeIis?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Circuses made entertainment a community event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen suffers disappointment in French elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210620-far-right-leader-le-pen-suffers-first-round-disappointment-in-france-s-regional-elections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party of France's far-right leader Marine Le Pen performed weaker than expected in the first round of regional elections Sunday, in a vote marked by record levels of abstention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  One killed in 'tragic accident' as truck hit Florida Pride parade...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/one-killed-truck-hits-crowd-022637693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man was killed and another injured in what US authorities said Sunday was a "tragic accident" at a Pride parade in Florida where a pickup truck driver unintentionally accelerated, striking pedestrians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Counting Enters New Era as Threat Shifts Away from Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/lifestyle/coronavirus/covid-counting-enters-new-era-as-threat-shifts-away-from-cases/ar-AALeYID</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST CRUISE IN YEAR SETS SAIL OUT OF MIAMI</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/first-us-cruise-in-15-months-set-to-sail-as-restrictions-ease/ar-AALforp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guests lined up to board Royal Caribbean Cruises Ltd.’s Freedom of the Seas on Sunday, marking the first cruise from a U.S. port since the pandemic suspended operations 15 months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROJECT LIBERTY:  Real Estate Mogul Has $100 Million Plan to 'Save the Internet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/a-real-estate-mogul-has-a-24100-million-plan-to-save-the-internet/ar-AALfdW1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank McCourt wants to build a blockchain-based alternative to Facebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,000 women being monitored after reporting period problems following vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3120109/vaccine-watchdog-monitoring-women-period-problems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE vaccine watchdog is “closely monitoring” 4,000 women who have reported period problems after getting their Covid jab. A change in menstrual cycle is not included on the list of pote…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Israel on verge of new covid outbreak?..</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/is-israel-on-the-verge-of-a-new-covid-19-outbreak-671558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel Health Ministry official says to 'remain calm' amongst worries of a possible future coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand names trans athlete to women's Olympics weightlifting team...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210620211050-scgha</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLYMPICS-2020/WEIGHTLIFITING (URGENT):New Zealand names transgender athlete Hubbard to women's Tokyo Olympics weightlifting team</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic-delayed surgeries share blame for blood shortage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-business-coronavirus-pandemic-health-20353f0a14431ef99f913c2220091015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Some New England hospitals are delaying or rescheduling surgeries because of a shortage of blood donations during the pandemic. “We haven’t seen anything like this in about 30 or 40 years at least,” Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  Iran's nuclear power plant undergoes emergency shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-europe-entertainment-business-6729095cdbc15443c6135142e2d755e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran’s sole nuclear power plant has undergone an unexplained temporary emergency shutdown, state TV reported on Sunday. An official from state electric company Tavanir, Gholamali Rakhshanimehr, said on a talk show that the Bushehr plant shutdown began on Saturday and would last "for three to four days.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials: Deadly Pride parade crash appears unintentional...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-music-eae400f8ef28e9a1f97019e2ed01caf5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — A member of a men’s chorus group unintentionally slammed into fellow chorists at the start of a Pride parade in South Florida, killing one member of the group and seriously injuring another, the group's director said Sunday, correcting initial speculation that it was a hate crime directed at the gay community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver rams cyclists in AZ race, critically injuring 6...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arizona-sports-bcaa4de628461416c92f181764ca8618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Bicyclist Tony Quinones had only just shaken hands with a fellow cyclist and wished him good luck in this weekend's community race in an Arizona mountain town when a truck sped into a crowd of bike riders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 children killed after crash in drenched Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/alabama-crash-interstate-65-claudette-girls-tropical-weather-6c1105ca3a0d1a80c1e516a0e1e4213a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Eight children in a van from a youth home for abused or neglected children were killed in a fiery multi-vehicle crash on a wet interstate that also killed a man and his baby in another vehicle, the most devastating blow from a tropical depression that claimed 12 lives in Alabama as it caused flash floods and spurred tornadoes that destroyed dozens of homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 children killed after crash in drenched Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3121026/alabama-crash-kills-nine-children-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HORROR crash led to the deaths of nine children and one adult in Butler County, Alabama over the weekend. The crash — which took place on Saturday in a storm-plagued Alabama — likely occurred whe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUCK ACCIDENT OR TERROR?</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/police-1-dead-1-hospitalized-after-truck-hits-pedestrians-at-stonewall-pride-parade-driver-in-custody/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILTON MANORS, FLA. (WSVN) - A night of celebration turned into a night of tragedy when, police said, a truck driver ran over two pedestrians...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicles hydroplaned... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/floods-environment-and-nature-6c1105ca3a0d1a80c1e516a0e1e4213a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Tropical Depression Claudette claimed 12 lives in Alabama as the storm swept across the southeastern U.S., causing flash flooding and spurring tornadoes that destroyed dozens of homes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
