<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Musk slammed over NEURALINK project that could see brains hacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4669936/elon-musk-deadly-neuralink-project-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEURALINK CEO Elon Musk is facing scrutiny for experiments that allegedly left monkeys dead, ahead of human clinical trials. The internet is shunning Elon Musk after the Physicians Committee for Re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Violence Rises in West Bank, Settler Attacks Raise Alarm...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/12/as-violence-rises-in-the-west-bank-settler-attacks-raise-alarm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURIN, West Bank — The Israeli settlers streamed down the hill toward Palestinian farmland, some waving sticks, some throwing stones,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear hunter kills self after accidentally shooting brother...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/man-takes-life-after-accidentally-26198875</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police deputies were dispatched to a property in an unincorporated community in Oregon, US, to reports a man had accidentally shot his brother while loading a gun after being startled by a black bear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden weighs appeal of 3 top candidates for high court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/stephen-breyer-joe-biden-us-supreme-court-congress-judiciary-235cba1d2bfb1466e10b17ffd637843f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden had zeroed in on a pair of finalists for his first Supreme Court pick when there were rumors last year that Justice Stephen Breyer would retire. But since the upcoming retirement was announced late last month, it has come with the rise of a third candidate, one with ready-made bipartisan support that has complicated the decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AI Program Can Spot Rare Diseases By Analyzing Face...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/ai-facial-analysis-rare-diseases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say a new facial analysis program can actually detect the warning signs of rare diseases by examining the features of a person's face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will record warmth favor RAMS?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/sports/will-record-warmth-favor-the-rams-in-super-bowl-56/1140672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super Bowl this year is not just the hottest ticket it town -- in could also feature the hottest game-time temp ever for the big game. What do some fans think about how that will affect the two teams facing off?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burrow crossover appeal inspires Namath comparisons...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/12/nice-fit-joe-burrow-belongs-to-everyone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Burrow strode into Arrowhead Stadium two Sundays ago for the A.F.C. championship game clad in a black turtleneck, rimless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing maximum pressure from Russia, Zelensky refuses to blink...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/facing-maximum-pressure-from-russia-zelensky-refuses-to-blink-at-the-negotiating-table/ar-AATKLBA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tear gas fired as convoy enters Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/police-stop-50-vehicles-heading-paris-protest-convoy-2022-02-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police fired tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs Elysees avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a "Freedom Convoy" protesting against COVID-19 restrictions made it into the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'Huge, Silent' Earthquake Caused Mysterious Global Tsunami...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/how-huge-silent-earthquake-caused-mysterious-global-tsunami-1678486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "hidden" earthquake caused a tsunami recorded over 6,200 miles from the epicenter, researchers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS backlog hits 24 million returns, further imperiling tax filing season...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/taxes/irs-backlog-hits-nearly-24-million-returns-further-imperiling-the-2022-tax-filing-season/ar-AATKL3A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE INVASION IMMINENT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10505243/The-Anglo-Saxons-need-war-Russia-blames-WEST-Putin-decides-invade-Ukraine-WEDNESDAY.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Secretary of State Antony Blinken is on a call to Russian diplomat Sergey Lavrov after 'extremely detailed' invasion plans stoked fears of war in Eastern Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN CALLS PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-emmanuel-macron-europe-moscow-1f353699f0be1609da5435c98cfc8022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin and U.S. President Joe Biden are to hold a high-stakes telephone call on Saturday as tensions over a possibly imminent invasion of Ukraine escalated sharply and the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Canada police arrive to remove protesters at border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-united-states-justin-trudeau-blockades-f3368c041216343175d255a2ce23eb84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDSOR, Ontario (AP) — Canadian police moved in Saturday to remove protesters who have disrupted Canada-US trade at a major bridge border crossing. Protesters at the busiest crossing between the United States and Canada remained overnight despite new warnings to end the blockade that has disrupted the flow of goods between the two countries and forced the auto industry on both sides to roll back production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR WARNING: RUSSIA INVASION IMMINENT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-news-02-11-22/h_26bf2c7a6ff13875ea1d5bba3b6aa70a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between Moscow and Kyiv are at their highest in years, with a large Russian troop buildup near the shared borders of the two former Soviet republics. Follow for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL SPIKES: $95</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/11/oil-jumps-amid-escalating-tensions-between-russia-and-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices jumped amid escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia, with the U.K. advising British nationals to leave Ukraine immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOREIGNERS FLEE UKRAINE</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60355295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden and Vladimir Putin to talk as the US says Russia could invade Ukraine "at any time".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin Case Goes to Jury in Dueling Tales NYT Hit Job, Honest Mistake...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sarah-palin-case-goes-to-jury-in-dueling-tales-of-n-y-times-hit-job-honest-mistake/ar-AATKxEa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Building More Muscle -- Healthy Gut...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/build-muscle-gut-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study shows evidence that the gut microbiome may play a role in muscle growth and development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  SLATE Struggles to Find Identity -- and Profit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/11/slate-struggles-to-find-its-identity-and-profit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early January, two days after an abrupt announcement that the top editor of Slate was stepping down, the publication’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 officers hurt in 'ambush,' shootout at Phoenix home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/phoenix-police-shot-0a2f975dd259309de3912f4b17ca7634</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — A man ambushed a police officer who responded to a call at a Phoenix home early Friday, shooting him several times, then rained more gunfire on other officers who tried to rescue a baby that was placed outside the door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Supply Hurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/trucker-protest-starts-hurt-food-supply-independent-grocers-rcna15935</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian independent grocers face delays on fruits, vegetables and cereal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What truckers really want...</title>
      <link>https://bariweiss.substack.com/p/what-the-truckers-want</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bariweiss.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve spoken to 100 of the protestors gathered in the Canadian capital. What's happening is far bigger than the vaccine mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of sober love and sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20220209-dry-dating-the-rise-of-sober-love-and-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alcohol has long been a player in getting people together, but an increasing number of daters are trying romance without ‘liquid courage’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta District's Secession Bill Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/atlanta-district-s-secession-bill-is-dead-georgia-leaders-say/ar-AATKlQw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Boosters' Protection Plunges After 4 Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/11/covid-booster-effectiveness-wanes-after-4-months-but-still-provides-protection-study-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at Covid-19 booster shots during the recent omicron wave showed a decline in effectiveness against severe cases, shots still offered strong protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's fight to keep emotional support pig...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/02/11/1080045003/a-man-in-upstate-new-york-is-fighting-to-keep-his-emotional-support-pig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wyverne Flatt says his 110-pound potbellied pig Ellie is "family." Officials in his village of Canajoharie see it very differently. To them, the pig is a farm animal Flatt is harboring illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL lobbying SEC on blockchain tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/11/nfl-lobbies-the-sec-on-blockchain-technology.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Football League has been lobbying the Securities and Exchange Commission on blockchain technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's horror king seeks 'meaning' in schlock...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220211-italy-s-horror-king-seeks-meaning-in-schlock</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call girls in jeopardy, a serial killer on the loose, fountains of blood -- horror master Dario Argento has returned to filmmaking after a 10-year hiatus, saying Friday it's been his mission to bring…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron urges calm as motorists close in on Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20220211-macron-urges-calm-as-french-freedom-convoy-motorists-close-in-on-paris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France mobilised thousands of police, armoured personnel carriers and water cannon trucks in Paris on Friday to keep out convoys of motorists converging on the capital for a protest against COVID-19…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER pulls FDA request for vax for kids under 5...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/pfizer-covid-vaccine-kids-fda-authorization-postponed-rcna15730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company said it believes three doses "may provide a higher level of protection in this age group."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deltacron' real after all...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10502843/Health-chiefs-officially-keeping-tabs-variant-thats-Omicron-Delta-merger.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In its weekly update the UKHSA revealed the strain had been detected in the UK and was 'currently under monitoring'. It evolved in someone that caught Delta and Omicron at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO olympic medals on Day 7 as struggling nation plunges in overall count...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/beijing-winter-olympics/olympic-medal-count-2022-see-who-has-won-the-most-overall-and-gold-medals/3536634/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which nation has the most medals? Here's a look at the Olympic medal count for the 2022 Winter Games.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
