<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL GOODWIN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/michael-goodwin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doomed submarine crew filmed singing in final video before all 53 died...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2778186/doomed-indonesia-submarine-crew-singing/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HAUNTING video shows a doomed submarine crew singing just weeks before all 53 of them died when the vessel sank. The chilling final footage of the Indonesian sailors shows them smiling around a g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.newsmax.com/insiders/michaelsavage/id-526/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYLE SMITH</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/kyle-smith/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala has been visible.  But is she influential?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2021-04-26/kamala-harris-100-days-vice-president-influential</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris is often at President Biden’s side publicly, and plays a key role in selling his agenda, but her level of pull behind the scenes is uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80-year-old former NFL player accused of dealing cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/1960s-ny-giants-player-arrested-on-drug-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elderly former NFL player is accused of trying to sell a large amount of cocaine out of his Manhattan apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>https://www.creators.com/features/ben-shapiro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.creators.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL O'REILLY</title>
      <link>https://www.billoreilly.com/currentcolumn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billoreilly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN CALLAHAN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/maureen-callahan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-Year-Old Whiz Kid Offering Financial Advice To More Than 5,000 Subscribers Online...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/04/26/rishi-vamdatt-easy-peasy-finance-financial-literacy-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People all over the world looking to learn about stocks, bonds and even how to improve their credit score are turning to a New Jersey sixth grader!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARLES HURT</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/staff/charles-hurt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two dead as suicidal man jumps off building, lands on woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/26/man-jumps-building-lands-woman-san-diego-both-die/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was killed when an apparently suicidal man jumped off a parking structure and landed on her in downtown San Diego, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S.E. CUPP</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/ny-se-cupp-staff.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>https://thebulwark.com/author/billkristol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATT TAIBBI</title>
      <link>https://taibbi.substack.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taibbi.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regular news and features by award-winning author and investigative reporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRANDA DEVINE</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/miranda-devine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://greenwald.substack.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;greenwald.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Independent, unencumbered analysis and investigative reporting, captive to no dogma or faction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BART</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/author/peter-bart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter moved to Deadline in 2016 from his longtime home at Variety, where he had been a fixture since 1989 as that trade's Editor-In Chief. He began his career as a staff reporter for The Wall Street Journal and The New York Times before his entry into the movie business, becoming Vice President for Production at Paramount. At that studio, he played a key role in such films as The Godfather, Rosemary’s Baby and Harold &amp; Maude. He later served as Senior Vice President for Production at MGM and, later, as President of Lorimar films. Peter is also the author of nine books, and is a member of PMC's board of advisors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL FLEMING</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/author/mikefleming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike joined Deadline in 2010 after working at Variety for 20 years as a reporter, writer and columnist. He was not only nationally recognized as Variety's premiere film reporter but also for his “Dish” and “The Buzz” columns. Mike is known for his industry relationships and his ability to break news wherever it happens, including on the ground at festivals like Sundance, Cannes and Toronto. He also is an author: Doubleday published his book about The Three Stooges, "From Amalgamated Morons to American Icons," which ABC turned into a telepic executive produced by Mel Gibson. One of Mike’s early jobs in journalism was editor of the well-known Media Industry Newsletter (MIN). He then joined New York Newsday as a columnist, reviewer and entertainment writer. During his career, he has written for numerous magazines including Playboy, Details, TV Guide and Esquire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARD TIME:  Appeals judges weigh Ghislaine Maxwell's harsh confinement at federal jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-ghislaine-maxwell-bail-appeal-20210426-5rk3l6bvezbttnmdequ66bee74-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judges for the 2nd Circuit Court of Appeals seemed alarmed Monday by Ghislaine Maxwell’s treatment behind bars, asking why it was necessary jail staff shine a light in her cell every 15 minutes overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB Founder's Mansion Burns Down 'in Suspected Arson'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9513573/Montreal-mansion-embattled-Pornhub-founder-burns-arson-fire.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syrian-born Pornhub founder Feras Antoon's, 45, unfinished Montreal home burned down Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Troubles Grow as UK Govt Battles Sleaze Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-s-troubles-grow-as-u-k-government-battles-sleaze-claims/ar-BB1g4Uic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson is facing mounting questions over the way he operates at the top of the government, as the row over allegations of sleaze and incompetence intensifies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos challenges NASA moon contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/jeff-bezos-challenges-nasa-moon-contract-award-to-elon-musk-e2-80-99s-spacex/ar-BB1g4Zz0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin said NASA had inappropriately allowed SpaceX to revise its pricing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will set $1 million threshold for capital gains tax hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/04/26/business/biden-set-1-million-threshold-capital-gains-tax-hike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden intends to raise capital gains taxes for those earning more than $1 million a year his top economic adviser confirmed Monday, arguing that the move would affect only a tiny share of American households.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California now has lowest coronavirus case rate in nation!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-coronavirus-case-rate-now-184916537.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's latest seven-day new case rate — 40.3 per 100,000 people — is dramatically lower than the nationwide rate of 135.3 over that same time period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Congress 'Bailout' Utah For $1.5 Billion --  When State Has A $1.5 Billion Budget Surplus?</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamandrzejewski/2021/04/26/why-did-congress-bailout-utah-for-15-billion--when-utah-has-a-15-billion-budget-surplus/?sh=36cd43a06929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans voted no, but took the dough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE ROLLS OUT DREADED 14.5...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/26/apple-ios-14point5-iphone-update-is-out-now-heres-whats-new.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOS 14.5 adds a lot of new features, such as privacy changes, new Siri voices and the option to unlock your iPhone with an Apple Watch if you're wearing a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY BACK AT FULL LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210426174032-vu2ja</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/TURKEY (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Turkey announces "full lockdown" from April 29 to curb COVID spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ GOES BUST</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arts-and-entertainment-entertainment-academy-awards-television-d17308440bfa7388a2d21ca8c2d7fee8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Academy Awards television audience plunged to 9.85 million viewers on ABC, less than half of the Oscars' previous low and continuing a startling trend of viewer tune out for awards shows. The Nielsen company's preliminary estimate shows that the audience who watched “Nomadland” win best picture on Sunday was 58% below last year's tally of 23.6 million, which had set the previous record for least-watched Oscars telecast. Following a year where movie theaters were mostly closed due to COVID-19, people were unexcited about or unfamiliar with movies they primarily streamed at home. Producers tried to fight through pandemic fatigue with a hostless program and a small, socially-distanced audience that didn't wear masks during the broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Winners and losers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/electoral-college-census-2020-government-and-politics-politics-86e1a31aeeea02004a3c71abd58097ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a year since the 2020 census began in a remote Alaska village, the first numbers to emerge from the nation's once-a-decade head count were released on Monday, showing how many congressional seats and Electoral College votes each state is getting based on its population. Because the number of seats in the House of Representatives is set at 435, it's a zero-sum game with one state's gain resulting in another state's loss — like a pie with uneven slices. As one state gets a larger slice because of population gains, that means a smaller slice for a state that lost population or didn't grow as much. Here's a look at the 13 states that will gain or lose political power — and federal money — through the apportionment process because of changes in population over the past decade:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Drought Drains CA Lake, Stunning Sea Of Purple Wildflowers Blooms In Place...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/04/25/theyre-incredible-people-visit-drained-folsom-lake-after-super-bloom-pops-up-in-its-place/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Folsom Lake doesn't look like much of a lake right now. A dry season drained the lake, but what popped up in its place has people in awe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC sees bloodiest week this year with 46 shootings...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/26/nyc-sees-bloodiest-week-this-year-with-46-shooting-incidents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYPD data shows 50 people were shot in 46 separate shooting incidents over a seven-day period ending Sunday evening — a more than 300 percent surge from the same week in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Court Reveals: FBI Hunted for Domestic Terrorists Without Warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/secret-court-reveals-fbi-hunted-for-domestic-terrorists-without-a-warrant/ar-BB1g4UPz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI, without any court order, sifted through the National Security Agency’s massive troves of foreign communications for information on American “racially motivated violent extremists,” a newly declassified order from the secret surveillance court details. Even though the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance (FISA) Court warned the FBI in 2018 that its warrant-free queries, known as backdoor searches, were constitutionally alarming, the bureau...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES retiring 'op-ed'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/26/the-new-york-times-is-retiring-the-word-op-ed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Old Gray Lady’s opinion pages will simply refer to columns by the paper’s staff writers and editorial board as editorials and pieces by external contributors as “guest essays.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  TESLA posts record income; Revenue surges 74%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/26/tesla-tsla-earnings-q1-2021-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the first quarter, Elon Musk's electric vehicle business reported vehicle deliveries of 184,800 Model 3 and Model Y cars, a new record for Tesla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach can't guarantee QB 'will be alive Sunday'...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/04/26/kyle-shanahan-no-guarantee-jimmy-garoppolo-will-be-on-roster-after-draft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 49ers are set to take a new quarterback with the third overall pick in this week’s draft and that player will be on the roster come the start of the regular season. It’s less clear whether Jimmy Garoppolo will be joining him. Head coach Kyle Shanahan said at a Monday press conference that the [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas gains Congress seats, Calif. loses first time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/census-congressional-districts-7dd29f02c7d68038920c7e1a23f842a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The nation's political center of gravity shifted further to the Republican-led South and West on Monday, with Texas, Florida and other Sun Belt states gaining congressional seats while chillier climes like New York and Ohio lost them. Altogether, the U.S. population rose to 331,449,281, the Census Bureau said, a 7.4 increase that was the second-slowest ever. The new allocation of congressional seats came in the U.S. Census Bureau's first release of data from a 2020 headcount. The numbers chart familiar American migration patterns, and confirm one historic marker: For the first time in 170 years of statehood, California is losing a congressional seat , a result of slowed migration to the nation’s most populous state, which was once a symbol of the country’s expansive frontier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSUS:  USA population rises to 331,449,281...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-census-2020-united-states-government-and-politics-ce81fbc89a17223b6e3f52f1f62eef25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Census Bureau says the population of the United States is 331,449,281. The 7.4% increase over the last decade is the second slowest ever. The Census Bureau is releasing the first data from its 2020 headcount. The release marks the official beginning of the once-a-decade redistricting battles. The numbers released Monday, along with more detailed data expected later this year, will be used by state legislatures or independent commissions to redraw political maps to account for shifts in population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech condoms of the future...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210423-how-grass-and-gel-could-make-condoms-better</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From condoms that self-lubricate to ones with in-built medication that protects against STDs, the contraception of the future is already in development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Ninjas, hired by AZ Senate to recount ballots, asks court to keep secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/elections/2021/04/25/cyber-ninjas-wants-to-keep-its-arizona-election-recount-secret/7379117002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Christopher Coury asked Cyber Ninjas to turn over its plans and procedures amid concerns about the security of Maricopa County's ballot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ERA</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/04/24/opinion/academy-awards-oscars-hollywood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Craving escapism from the Oscar contenders that reflect our sad reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF to respond strongly if Gaza rockets continue...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/israel-restricts-gaza-fishing-zone-in-response-to-palestinian-rockets-666334</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fishing zone in the Gaza Strip has been completely closed until further notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ GOES BUST</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2021/04/26/tv-ratings-oscars-93rd-academy-awards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To the surprise of exactly no one, this year’s Oscars telecast won zero awards for viewership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says John Kerry told him about Israeli covert operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/iran-foreign-minister-john-kerry-javad-zarif-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian foreign minister Mohammad Javad Zarif claimed in leaked audio that then-Secretary of State John Kerry informed him of more than 200 Israeli operations in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratings Plummet to Record Low, Down 58%...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/tv-ratings-oscars-2021-down-record-low-1234960615/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 93rd Academy Awards ceremony, broadcast live from both Union Station and the Dolby Theatre in L.A. on ABC, hit a staggering low. Per Nielsen Live+Same Day preliminary national numbers, an avera…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA will share ASTRAZENECA doses with world...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-health-business-government-and-politics-coronavirus-26fa41b98fab721218d9a51065351d9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. will begin sharing its entire pipeline of vaccines from AstraZeneca once the COVID-19 vaccine clears federal safety reviews, the White House told The Associated Press on Monday, with as many as 60 million doses expected to be available for export in the coming months. The move greatly expands on the Biden administration's action last month to share about 4 million doses of the vaccine with Mexico and Canada. The AstraZeneca vaccine is widely in use around the world but not yet authorized by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration. The White House is increasingly assured about the supply of the three vaccines being administered in the U.S., particularly following the restart of the single-dose Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson shot over the weekend. The U.S. has also been under mounting pressure in recent weeks to share more of its vaccine supply with the world, as nations like India experience devastating surges of the virus and others struggle to access doses needed to protect their most vulnerable populations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENTCOM Commander: Drones Dropping Explosives 'Concerns Me the Most'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hstoday.us/subject-matter-areas/airport-aviation-security/centcom-commander-drones-dropping-explosives-probably-concerns-me-the-most/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hstoday.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandkids part of White House scene...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-6793fd6e88cbab278cb14df89c415aff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden's grandkids say anyone who wants to take a crack at their “Pop” has to go through them first. When Biden calls to check in, he doesn't stop with one grandchild but ends up dialing all of them for updates. Even son Hunter Biden gets a nightly call from Biden. Biden’s big Irish American family has been a prominent part of the White House scene during his first 100 days in office, with his wife, children and grandchildren providing the grounding that people close to the president say has served Biden during nearly a half century of public service. “Anyone who wants to get to @JoeBiden will have to get past us first,” says the caption on a photo granddaughter Naomi Biden tweeted of herself, her sisters and cousins. She added emojis of a flexed bicep, a high voltage sign, a fist and a winking face with a stuck-out tongue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami's wealthiest areas 100% vaccinated. Black communities at 31%...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article250841644.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roselle Monestime Noel, a 68-year-old home healthcare aide from North Miami, tried to get a coronavirus vaccine for two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL ST GETS PSYCHEDELIC:  String of drug developers go public...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-pro-rata</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHENEY:  DONALD NOT PARTY LEADER...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/congress/liz-cheney-trump-not-party-leader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump is not the leader of the Republican Party, House GOP Conference Chairwoman Liz Cheney told reporters Monday at a lawmaker retreat not far from Trump’s Mar-a-Lago estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN TESTS SPACE BUSTER</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14765533/putin-test-missile-blast-us-space-weapons-bits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has staged a “successful” test of a mystery new anti-ballistic missile that could “blast US space weapons to smithereens”. It comes as the Russian president a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEX:  China touts THREE new warships as tensions with Taiwan surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2773325/china-warship-nuclear-missile-cruiser-flexes-muscles-taiwan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has unveiled three new warships as tensions with Taiwan reach boiling point. President Xi Jinping showed off the country’s newest assets – an amphibious helicopter carrier, a nucl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Examines Heart Inflammation After PFIZER Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/israel-examines-heart-inflammation-cases-after-pfizer-covid-shot/ar-BB1g46pq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel is examining dozens of cases where people experienced heart inflammation after receiving Pfizer Inc. and BioNTech SE’s coronavirus vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan rocked by 4th wave less than 100 days before Olympics!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/japan-covid-emergency-olympics-tokyo-a25061c6-6317-4918-91dd-3946935feb81.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bars, department stores and theaters across Japan will be closed for 17 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  Forgets How to Entertain...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2021/04/25/oscars-2021-review-abc-academy-awards-poll/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Regina King confidently strutted her way through Union Station at the top of this year’s Oscars broadcast with candy-colored movie-style credits popping up behind her, I got excited that…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Rotten Teeth to Advanced Cancer, Patients Feel Effects of Treatment Delays...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/from-rotten-teeth-to-advanced-cancer-patients-feel-the-effects-of-treatment-delays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health providers are seeing the consequences of pandemic-delayed preventive and emergency care, from longer hospital stays to more root canals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office of future outdoors?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90628880/the-office-of-the-future-is-outdoors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landlords and designers are adding more outdoor space to office buildings, so employees can actually work outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: SOS messages, panic as virus breaks India's health system...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-india-coronavirus-1bda2318594d65be400074da41fa13c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Dr. Gautam Singh dreads the daily advent of the ventilator beeps, signaling that oxygen levels are critically low, and hearing his critically ill patients start gasping for air in the New Delhi emergency ward where he works. Like other doctors across the country, which on Monday set another record for new coronavirus infections for a fifth day in a row at more than 350,000, the cardiologist has taken to begging and borrowing cylinders of oxygen just to keep his most critical patients alive for one more day. On Sunday evening, when the oxygen supplies of other nearby hospitals were also near empty, the desperate 43-year-old took to social media, posting an impassioned video plea on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Let the bodies pile high'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9510133/Boris-Johnson-said-bodies-pile-high-order-lockdown-sources-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downing Street last night strongly denied the Prime Minister made the comment, insisting it was 'just another lie'. But those who say they heard it stand by their claim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOO BORING TO BEAT?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/979486/biden-boring-republicans-beat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden hits the traditionally symbolic first-100-days mark of his presidency this week, and 'it has dawned on Republicans that the man their standard-bearer once mocked as 'Sleepy Joe' is a formidable adversary,' Jonathan Chait writes in New York on Monday. 'And the quality that has made him so effective up to this point is, well, his sleepiness.' Before Biden's immediate predecessor, the last handful of presidents were 'nice,' but Biden is 'also tedious,' Chait argues: He is relentlessly enacting an ambitious domestic agenda — signing legislation that could cut child poverty by more than half, expanding ObamaCare, and injecting the economy with a stimulus more than twice the size of what [President Barack] Obama's Congress passed in 2009 — while arousing hardly any controversy. There's nothing in Biden's vanilla-ice-cream bromides for his critics to hook on to. Republicans can't stop Biden because he is boring them to death. [Jonathan Chait, New York] All signs point to this being a deliberate strategy, borne of wisdom or expediency, and it's 'a fascinating counterpoint to a career spent trying desperately to be interesting,' Chait adds. 'Biden used to overshare, with frequently disastrous results that led him to accurately self-diagnose as a 'gaffe machine,'' but now 'the tedium is the message.' Biden's new persona has been very effective at promoting progressive ideas in a way that strikes centrist voters as pretty anodyne, Democratic strategist Cornell Belcher tells the Los Angeles Times. 'You cannot underestimate how comfortable Uncle Joe is for a lot of people. They give an old, white guy the benefit of the doubt.' Certainly, 'lowering the temperature of Washington's political debates' has helped Biden's agenda, David Lauter writes at the Times. 'But it could create a problem down the road, depriving Biden of the fervent support that can sustain a president in bad times.' If his sleepiness does end up leaving Democratic allies cold, Biden will still have hot Oval Office chocolate chip cookies for potential allies in Congress. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of cities greatly exaggerated...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/978456/death-cities-greatly-exaggerated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the pandemic predictions about urban flight were wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space junk map shows '200 ticking time bombs' in orbit around Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mind-blowing-space-junk-map-23983994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have created the space junk map, AstriaGraph, which shows where thousands of human-made objects are located. The technology can track and predict its behaviour</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Kanye sneakers snag world record $1.8 million in private sale...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/kanyes-yeezy-sneakers-snag-world-130528028.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kanye West sneakers that sent athletic shoes strutting down fashion runways sold for $1.8 million, a new world record price for a pair of sneakers, Sotheby's announced on Monday. The American rapper's 2008 'Grammy Worn' Nike Air Yeezy samples were prototypes for a line developed by West and Mark Smith for Nike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pink Supermoon' To Brighten Skies...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/04/26/april-pink-supermoon-full-moon-monday-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;April's full moon is the "pink" moon, and it's a supermoon, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I have given up fight': 'Italy's Robinson Crusoe' to leave island...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/26/mauro-morandi-budelli-island-italy-robinson-crusoe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mauro Morandi has lived alone on Budelli since 1989 but will relocate after several eviction threats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Actor Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9511165/Academy-Awards-ends-fizzle-Best-Actor-Anthony-Hopkins-skips-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film fans have blasted the Oscars as the 'wokest ever' after an evening of virtue-signalling speeches by celebs and controversy over Anthony Hopkins winning best actor instead of Chadwick Boseman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE will spend $1 billion to open 3,000-employee campus in NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/26/apple-announces-1-billion-north-carolina-campus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campus is a sign of Apple's continued expansion beyond its home in Cupertino, California, where most of its engineering has been based.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars unlike any other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/strangest-oscars-ever-snubbing-chadwick-055209751.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Wawrychuk/Getty ImagesFor the first time in my lifetime, the Academy Awards weren’t a spectacle, but an awards show. I’ve never been so moved by it.I’ve also never been so frustrated by it. That was inevitable, given the circumstances circling the now-infamous pandemic Oscars, but also owed to a handful of chaotic producing decisions. (Where was the comedy? Could that whiplash-inducing In Memoriam segment have been more disrespectful? And Best Picture before Best Actor and Actress?!? Absolute nonsense.)An intimate gathering at a train station with satellite cameras in locations like London and Sydney, this year’s ceremonies felt nothing like the Oscars we know. That seems correct, as having an awards show at all in these times can feel completely inappropriate. The traditional glitz, bombast, and Hollywood narcissism needed Sunday night’s humbling. At the same time, it is a television show, one that needed more spark.There will be complaints that the night was a bit of a bore, and the show, while finishing closer to three hours than most ceremonies, seemed endless.Not saving Best Picture for the night’s climax may rank among the worst creative misfires in the show’s history. Presumably, producers assumed Chadwick Boseman would win for Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom, not Anthony Hopkins for The Father, and were then building up to an emotional close to the telecast.Hopkins’ surprise win, his not being in attendance, and the show just ending after that was nothing short of disorienting. You should feel guided through an award show, not wondering what the hell just happened. The blunder is a slight to movie fans, to Hopkins, and to Nomadland, one of the refreshing cases of the right film at the right moment winning Best Picture. Because of that production choice, the very Academy that selected the film to win seemed to have dismissed it.What makes the whole thing more egregious is that the producers didn’t need to manipulate the traditional show order to manufacture an emotional night. Until it veered off the rails near the end, it was already an incredibly heartfelt, powerful, meaningful telecast. I’m an easy target, but I found myself crying...constantly?There are few better choices for launching any major event than by having Regina King strut in a long tracking shot to a stage and deliver a sermon about the complexity of our times, the impulse to fete movies, and why the art matters: "Now, I know that a lot of you people at home wanna reach for your remote when you feel like Hollywood is preaching to you, but as a mother of a Black son, I know the fear that so many live with, and no amount of fame or fortune changes that, OK?"Starting with her, the tenor of the telecast was a celebration of inclusivity, dictated by the memorable speeches given by the winners. It was a gratitude for opportunity, and a demand for a platform. After months of screaming “who cares?” about the idea of the Oscars taking place, and anecdotal evidence about how few people watched the nominees—even though they were all available to watch from home—the show seemed to make a point of emphasizing why the show matters and why the movies matter. Reuters Chloé Zhao made history, becoming the second woman to ever win Best Director for her work in Nomadland. The love was spread around this year. While Nomadland took home three of the biggest prizes—Best Picture, Director, and Actress for Frances McDormand, now the second woman to win the category three times—Promising Young Woman, The Father, Sound of Metal, Judas and the Black Messiah, and Minari all won major awards.Early speeches by Emerald Fennell (Best Original Screenplay, Promising Young Woman) and Florian Zeller (Best Adapted Screenplay, The Father) were babbling and overwhelmed and earnest. Thomas Vinterberg (Best International Feature, Another Round) and Mia Neal (Best Makeup and Hairstyling, Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom) made poignant dedications in their thank yous that had the in-person audience in tears, and me at home practically inconsolable.Yuh-jung Youn and Daniel Kaluuya, winning Best Supporting Actress and Actor, respectively for Minari and Judas and the Black Messiah, were magnetic and charismatic as they accepted their trophies. That the set and the ceremony was so intimate made those winning moments feel even more electric.Throwing to the Zoom locations abroad felt seamless—so much so that all the hand wringing from producers ahead of time over whether they could or should allow satellite feeds seems ridiculous. And the presenters, the “ensemble cast” as the producers kept advertising them, were on their game.I remember years in which a new Hollywood It Girl would walk to the microphone and giggle about how they forgot their glasses and couldn’t read the teleprompter. This year, the actors presenting, which included King, Angela Bassett, Reese Witherspoon, Harrison Ford, and Riz Ahmed, were serving as actual emcees. It may have been a little buttoned-up, but it was impressive.Hours later, after the whole ceremony has unfolded and I’m thinking back on it, I keep returning to King’s striking introduction.She had a thankless task, making the argument for why an award show is taking place in such serious times, even admitting that if the jury in the Derek Chauvin trial had ruled differently, “I’d have traded in my heels for marching boots.”She also had to defend the optics of Hollywood’s rich and famous gathering maskless when most of us still safely can’t get together with friends and family. When Regina King shows up, she’s gonna do her job. And damn if she didn’t sell the lunacy of the excuse that this was “an Oscars movie with a cast of over 200 nominees” and the show was a “film production” and they were all at work.I still don’t understand all the “it’s an award show and it’s a movie” nonsense that the show’s producers kept repeating in interviews leading up to the telecast. Nothing about it felt like a “movie,” at least not any more or less than any other year’s awards. Actors came out, presented awards, and people gave speeches. Nothing seemed more cinematic than usual. It actually felt more like an award show than an entertainment event than in any year I can remember.Some of that didn’t work. Viewers who hadn’t seen all the nominees were starved of clips of the nominees that only played for a few categories.Two and a half hours of the ceremony passed without a comedy bit. By that time, it was not entirely welcome—at that point, you just want the whole thing to be done with—though Glenn Close dancing to “Da Butt” may be the greatest Oscars moment of all time. Still, after a long night that seemed disinterested in creating anything resembling a viral moment, it felt out of place, funny as it was.And Frances McDormand, begging for there to be karaoke while on stage accepting Best Actress, articulated what we were all thinking: The show was missing music.For the first time, the stage had an accessible ramp. The ramp was also poorly placed, with winners who walked from stage left having to awkwardly jump over it, a rare case in which the production design made no sense neither aesthetically and logistically; I get that the ceremony was filmed at a train station to make COVID safety easier, but did the stage they built have to look so cheap?The show looked and felt, at times, like a perfunctory luncheon. And while that often was refreshing—it actually seemed like it was produced by people who like movies and the artists who make them, not ratings-hungry egotists—it shined a harsher spotlight than usual on the fact that it is a slog to present 24 award categories. When there are no sketches, montages, or musical performances distracting from the task at hand, the task does seem more like a chore.That said, past efforts to minimize the act of handing out awards never made sense to me. Why not lean into the purpose of the whole thing? Yes, presenting 24 awards is a tedious exercise, but Sunday night’s show was the most emotional exercise of tedium I’ve ever partaken in.There were moments that felt surreal, like every time the show returned from commercial break and panned across the in-person audience and you’d see flashes of Amanda Seyfriend and Carey Mulligan’s gorgeous gowns and oversized skirts. It’s still jarring to see celebrities in red-carpet fashion when everyday life is still in pandemic disarray.And, while there were plenty of powerful speeches that spoke to our volatile cultural moment, that still can seem like an awkward fit in this venue. Case in point, the wild transition from Best Short Film winner Travon Free speaking movingly about police killings of Black people to his collaborator, Martin Desmond Roe, saying, “We’d like to thank Netflix…”But for all the faults, from the small ones (that stage design) to the major ones (not saving Best Picture for last was egregious and nearly show-ruining), it was just plain poignant to watch the Academy Awards and celebrate movies.I think the producers made the right choice when it came to the scale of the ceremony, allowing that celebration to seem invigorating instead of ostentatious. It does feel like the country is starting to heal, even if slowly and only a little bit, and it’s exciting to embrace possibility again.Maybe the most meaningful part of the night to me was when the In the Heights trailer played, and I actually felt the thrill and anticipation of getting to see it in theaters. There’s a way of looking at this year’s Oscars show as a failure, if the most memorable part of the night didn’t involve any of the nominated films or the telecast itself. But I actually think of it as a triumph.The last year has made me so cynical. My expectations for the Oscars were so low you’d have to dig for them. So what a surprise it was, and even a rejuvenation, to come away from the ceremony hopeful about film and the community that surrounds it once again.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Economic Confidence Positive First Time in Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/348959/economic-confidence-positive-first-time-pandemic.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since the coronavirus pandemic led to widespread business closures in the U.S., Gallup's Economic Confidence Index has registered a net positive reading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state passes carbon pricing measure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-government-and-politics-washington-legislature-1da0a978342ad9787552f8e7926cee0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLYMPIA, Wash. (AP) — Washington is on track to become the second state in the nation to have a comprehensive carbon pricing policy under a measure passed by the state Legislature Saturday. The Seattle Times reported that the Senate gave the final 27-22 vote on the measure. It now heads to Gov. Jay Inslee, who had requested the legislation. “We are genuinely, authentically on the march toward Paris accord levels of emissions reductions,” said Democratic Sen. Reuven Carlyle, the bill's sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Examines Heart Inflammation After PFIZER Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/israel-examines-heart-inflammation-cases-after-pfizer-covid-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel Examines Heart Inflammation Cases After Pfizer Covid Shot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're Coming for You': For Public Health Officials, Year of Threats and Menace...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/public-health-officials-year-of-threats-menace-santa-cruz-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local health officials have become the face of government authority as they work to stem the pandemic. That has made them targets for chilling threats from some of the same militia groups that stor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked recording of Iran's top diplomat offers blunt talk...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/iran-iran-nuclear-middle-east-europe-0068e6e181a4cc9aaa8433d8257ce04e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — A recording of Iran's foreign minister offering a blunt appraisal of diplomacy and the limits of power within the Islamic Republic has been leaked, providing a rare look inside the country's theocracy. The release of the comments by Mohammad Javad Zarif set off a firestorm within Iran, where officials carefully mind their words amid a cut-throat political environment that includes the powerful paramilitary Revolutionary Guard, ultimately overseen by the country's supreme leader. Zarif has been suggested as a possible candidate for Iran's June 18 presidential election as well. Outside of Iran, Zarif's comments could also affect talks in Vienna aimed at finding a way for Tehran and the U.S. to both come into compliance with Iran's 2015 nuclear deal with world powers. Already, sabotage targeted Iran's nuclear facility at Natanz  during the talks as Tehran has begun enriching a small amount of uranium up to 60% purity , which edges the country closer to weapons-grade levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1970s-Era Taxes on Rich Collide With GOP, SALT Rebels...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-1970s-era-taxes-on-rich-collide-with-gop-and-salt-rebels/ar-BB1g3kSO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is poised to unveil a plan that would raise taxes on the income, investments and estates of the wealthiest Americans to levels not seen in more than four decades, a move that will trigger intense debate in Congress about whether and how to address income inequality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business class opens to masses as affordable refuge from virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2021/04/26/business/business-class-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flush with cash and a record number of air miles after a year on the ground, leisure travelers are splurging on premium seats for their first trips back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking barrier, women become Marines after surviving the 'crucible'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210426085347-p9nzn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MARINES/WOMEN (PIX):Breaking a barrier, women become U.S. Marines after surviving the 'crucible'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preachers 'n' Sneakers Trend Alive and Well and Spawning Merch...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/26/the-preachers-n-sneakers-trend-is-alive-and-well-and-spawning-merch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Kirby started the Instagram account @preachersnsneakers as a gag in 2019. Mr. Kirby, then a 29-year-old MBA student and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Point: How Zuckerberg, Cook Became Foes...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/26/breaking-point-how-mark-zuckerberg-and-tim-cook-became-foes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — At a confab for tech and media moguls in Sun Valley, Idaho, in July 2019, Timothy D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Time Gun Buyers Push Record Fireman Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/04/26/989699122/1st-time-gun-buyers-help-push-record-u-s-gun-sales-amid-string-of-mass-shootings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from the FBI's firearms background check database shows six days in March of this year made up the top 10 highest days of firearms background checks since 1998.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India patients dying in streets; Hunt for black market oxygen...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/india-covid-crisis-victims-dying-23981902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India is struggling with a devastating second wave of coronavirus with cases and deaths now at record highs and experts fearing they could actually be up to five times worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm Droid Kills 100,000 Weeds per Hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.freethink.com/articles/farming-robot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freethink.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carbon Robotics’ Autonomous Weeder is a smart farming robot that identifies weeds and then kills them using high-power lasers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBD Superbug Slayer?</title>
      <link>https://www.freethink.com/articles/cbd-and-antibiotics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freethink.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the search for new weapons against superbugs, CBD and antibiotics in combination, as well as CBD alone, may prove to be promising candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC cop cars totaled after officers drag race...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox29.com/news/dc-cop-cars-totaled-after-officers-drag-race-in-ne-says-commander</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox29.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two D.C. police cars were totaled after officers decided to drag race each other, according to an internal email obtained exclusively by FOX 5’s Lindsay Watts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bali hunts tourist who made porn video on sacred volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/police-hunt-russian-tourist-model-23983312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage, taken on Mount Batur in Bali, was afterwards uploaded to Pornhub and received millions of views. Police are now trying to work out if the pair are still on the island</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most elite sex club reopens...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/worlds-most-elite-sex-club-23982542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snctm – AKA the world's most elite sex club – has returned with a very saucy event. The exclusive members club has a new penthouse venue where wild orgies are set to take place</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodies fall from overloaded ambulances...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9511529/India-Morgues-run-stretchers-deaths-hit-2-800-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India recorded 2,812 Covid deaths overnight and infections in the last 24 hours rose to 352,991 on Monday - a record peak for a fifth day running - as vital life-saving oxygen is in short supply in hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans worry fiscal conservatism losing rallying cry...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/550074-gop-worries-fiscal-conservatism-losing-its-rallying-cry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans say fiscal conservatism simply isn’t the GOP rallying cry it used to be, and that’s making it much harder to counter President Biden’s push for trillions of dollars in new government spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Using Deepfakes to Imitate Political Rivals...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/russia-accused-using-deepfakes-imitate-political-rivals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities suspect that Kremlin operatives have used the deepfakes in order to gain information against Alexei Navalny's opposition movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Groups Step Into Venezuela as Lawlessness Grows...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/26/armed-groups-step-into-venezuela-as-lawlessness-grows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUARERO, Venezuela — They bring drinking water to residents in the arid scrublands, teach farming workshops and offer medical checkups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinated Americans CAN visit Europe this summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9510375/Vaccinated-American-tourists-allowed-visit-Europe-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American tourists who are fully vaccinated will be allowed to visit Europe this summer while the European Union hailed progress the U.S. has made in its COVID vaccine drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker  'mugged' after ceremony switches venue to homeless hotspot Union Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9510299/Homeless-ordered-LAs-Union-Station-ahead-tonights-Academy-Awards.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The glitzy awards show will be held Sunday at Union Station, close to encampments set up by vagrants in the city's downtown area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playboy businessman arrested for posing with nude models in Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2769768/playboy-businessman-photoshoot-nude-dubai-speaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE American playboy behind the Dubai balcony naked photoshoot has spoken for the first time. Vitaliy Grechin, 41, remains detained in the Gulf city where he has tested positive for Covid but has i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheerleader's SNAP rant leads to 'momentous' Supreme Court case on speech ...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Cheerleader-s-Snapchat-rant-leads-to-momentous-16128064.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The high school cheerleader relegated to the JV squad for another year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg Releases 'WEST SIDE STORY' trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/steven-spielbergs-west-side-story-unveils-first-trailer-during-oscars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-year-old accused of gunning down neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-90-accused-of-shooting-neighbor-in-trenton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say a 90-year-old man has been arrested in the shooting death of his neighbor on a side street across from police headquarters in New Jersey’s capital city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot dog security force roams Air Force base...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/air-force-base-deploys-pack-of-robot-dogs-to-enhance-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyndall AFB is using robodogs as an added layer of security on base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinated Americans CAN visit Europe this summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/coronavirus-eu-set-to-allow-vaccinated-us-tourists-this-summer-report/a-57331605</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen said in a newspaper interview that the vaccines used in the US should enable "free movement and travel" to the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhao makes history as director...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210426001021-xhcj0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AWARDS-OSCARS/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Chloe Zhao nabs historic best director win for 'Nomadland'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red carpet makes comeback...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210425221246-sj4vc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AWARDS-OSCARS/RED CARPET (UPDATE 1, REPEAT, PIX, TV):RPT-UPDATE 1-Red carpet makes a comeback at history-making Oscars</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
