<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FBI lawyer Lisa Page slams Trump attacks in first interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lisa-page-speaks-theres-no-fathomable-way-i-have-committed-any-crime-at-all</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former FBI lawyer and ongoing Trump target breaks two years of silence in this exclusive interview. And she has quite a lot to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Bloomberg Could Win. Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/12/02/michael-bloomberg-win-new-york-mayor-race-074060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s getting in late. He’s out of step with his party. The news media thinks he’s a joke. All of that was true when he first ran for mayor of New York City, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOLFF: Every Magazine Either Dead or Will Die Shortly...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/michael-wolff-every-magazine-is-either-dead-or-will-die-shortly-i-have-nothing-left-to-say-about-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire and Fury author Michael Wolff announced he has "nothing left to say" about President Donald Trump, in an article for The Spectator's U.S. edition Spectator USA, Friday, noting that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA: MAN INTERROGATED FOR CRITICIZING POLICE ON SOCIAL MEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/china-man-interrogated-for-criticizing-police-on-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social credit score coming to the west soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania unveils patriotic-themed White House Christmas decorations...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7745473/Melania-Trump-unveils-patriotic-Spirit-America-themed-White-House-Christmas-decorations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Posting footage from the stunning decor online Sunday, the first lady wrote: '</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady frustration boils over as PATRIOTS take bad loss...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/tom-bradys-frustration-boils-over-as-patriots-take-bad-loss-to-texans-043601647.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots offense didn&amp;#39;t do much and Tom Brady didn&amp;#39;t seem happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew could be in more trouble after Giuffre interview...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/02/prince-andrew-could-be-in-more-trouble-after-virginia-roberts-giuffre-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TV interview with Prince Andrew accuser Virginia Roberts Giuffre set to air Monday could spark further “ramifications” for the disgraced royal, according to a report. Giuffre is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bond 25: 'NO TIME TO DIE' Releases First Trailer Teaser...</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/movies/2019/12/02/bond-no-time-to-die-first-trailer-teaser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before too long, No Time to Die will hit theaters, marking Daniel Craig's last outing as the [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Mount Rainier caps swarm of weekend seismicity with 3.6 mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/mount-rainier-caps-swarm-of-weekend-seismicity-with-3-6-magnitude-quake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a spurt of seismic activity this weekend, Mount Rainier National Park was shaken by a 3.6 magnitude earthquake Sunday afternoon. The quake hit at 12:31 p.m. and was felt as far as Kent, nearly 80 miles away, the U.S. Geological Survey...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to suspend US Navy visits to Hong Kong over new law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e8b33f191ac64e55acef0e1405059f02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — China said Monday it will suspend U.S. military ship and aircraft visits to Hong Kong and sanction several American pro-democracy and human rights groups in retaliation for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Wave of Abuse Suits Could Hit Church Like Never Before...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/621efb9528384f278c71a97308404531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — At the end of another long day trying to sign up new clients accusing the Roman Catholic Church of sexual abuse, lawyer Adam Slater gazes out the window of his high-rise Manhattan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar view? Space hotels race to offer tourists room in sky...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191202002950-4ux9n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Movement has raised questions about the adequacy of current space laws, which mainly deal with exploration and keeping space free of weapons, not hotels and holidaymakers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Average Person Feels 'Too Old' To Work Out Regularly At 41...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-reveals-the-surprisingly-young-age-many-give-up-on-working-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of 2,000 adults found that on average, the age when most in the survey felt too old to work out regularly was just 41 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead' heart brought back to life in pioneering surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/dead-heart-brought-back-life-21009096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors at Duke University’s Division of Cardiovascular and Thoracic Surgery have completed the first adult ‘donation-after-death’ (DCD) transplant in the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Larry Page's Turbulent Flying Car Startup: Returned Deposits, Battery Fires, BOEING Shakeup...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2019/12/01/inside-larry-pages-kitty-hawk-returned-deposits-battery-fires-boeing-cora/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secretive flying car startup promised to bring personal flying to the masses. But those hopes have failed to take wing amid breakdowns and safety issues with its Flyer aircraft, former employees tell Forbes. Meanwhile, a partnership with Boeing on its Cora air taxi goes deeper than announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wild Cards in Senate Trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/impeachment-wild-cards-trump-confronts-090000840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump has openly cheered for the impeachment process to move to the friendlier confines of the GOP-led Senate, but there may be some surprises in store for him on the way to a likely acquittal.Majority Leader Mitch McConnell has said it’s “inconceivable” at this point</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggles Continue For Brady...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/12/02/struggles-continue-for-tom-brady-patriots-offense-were-battling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England offense is still searching for answers at a time of the year when they usually have them all lined up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process getting very real...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/01/politics/impeachment-week-ahead-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 64 days until the Iowa caucuses and a record number of Democratic candidates, the 2020 election will be here before you know it. Every Sunday, I deliver to your inbox the 5 BIG storylines you need to know to understand the upcoming week on the campaign trail. And they're ranked -- so the No. 1 story is the most important of the coming week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON ALERT OVER TERROR COPYCATS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/spy-chiefs-on-alert-for-london-bridge-copycats-gcnzmszfh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An associate of the London Bridge killer was arrested as security agencies scrambled to stamp out the threat of copycat attacks. Nazam Hussain, 34, was held in a police raid on his home in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High stakes move...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/01/trump-impeachment-response-house-judiciary-074712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is too late to cure the profound procedural deficiencies that have tainted this entire inquiry,” his counsel said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT:  Trump's Lawyers Won't Participate in Judiciary Impeachment Hearing...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-lawyers-wont-participate-upcoming-impeachment-hearing-sources/story?id=67420879</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and his lawyers will not participate in Wednesday’s impeachment hearing in the House Judiciary Committee, according to a letter from the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON sparks outrage by selling Christmas decorations picturing Auschwitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10463495/amazon-auschwitz-christmas-decorations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON has caused outrage by selling Christmas decorations and novelty bottle openers that picture Auschwitz. Products on offer include star and bell-shaped Christmas tree baubles featuring photos …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC wants you to shop while watching TV... </title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/entertainment/article/NBC-s-latest-gamble-depends-on-the-idea-that-14873956.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a recent episode of NBC's "Songland" - a primetime show featuring aspiring songwriters who compete to create hit songs - viewers were treated to a new form of high-tech advertising.  Midway through the episode, Ryan Tedder, a Grammy Award-winning singer and producer featured as a judge on the show, tinkered with an eye-catching, illuminated keyboard called Lumi. As Tedder played the instrument, a QR code casually appeared at the bottom of the screen with instructions that read more like commands than suggestions: "Open Camera, Scan Code, Shop Now."  In the minutes after the code appeared, NBCUniversal executives say, thousands of viewers did exactly that, using their smartphones to link directly to a website where Lumi was available for purchase. To get there, they didn't have to download an app, call a shopping network in a limited timeframe or embark on an online hunt. And that, executives say, was precisely the point.  "The Holy Grail has always been you seeing a person on TV talking about a product or wearing a product and being able to buy that product right now," said Josh Feldman, NBCUniversal's executive vice president in charge of marketing and advertising creative partnerships. "In the past there's been friction. You have to leave your screen and go to the Internet and search for that product."  "Nobody has ever done this before in television," Feldman added. "It's real time results and we can do this across the entire NBC portfolio."  The name for this new fusion of entertainment and mobile commerce is readily comprehensible, and purposefully so: "ShoppableTV." It's the latest attempt, among many, to add interactivity to what is essentially a passive medium, and it arrives as traditional television scrambles to adapt to new pressures.  Not only are audiences inundated by various streams of content,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCORSESE Lectures:  Don't Watch 'IRISHMAN' on Your Phone!</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/martin-scorsese-the-irishman-watching-phone-1203420472/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Scorsese’s three-and-a-half-hour long mob epic “The Irishman” became available on Netflix — and therefore its app — Wednesday, but that doesn’t mean the d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorbachev warns of 'hot war' between US, Russia...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/472527-gorbachev-warns-of-hot-war-between-us-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Soviet leader Mikhail Gorbachev warned in a new interview that tensions between the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel to vote on Ukraine report as Trump mulls defense...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5869552714da4f98884aefe53e3d1be8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House impeachment inquiry enters a pivotal stage this week, with investigators planning a vote Tuesday to approve their report making the case for President Donald Trump’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg turns to black pastor to discuss racism, poverty...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/325523971dc146baa082edc0370f3d18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOLDSBORO, N.C. (AP) — As he labors to win over black voters whose support is vital to his Democratic presidential bid, Pete Buttigieg found a receptive host on Sunday in a civil rights activist...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: RAVENS Win Thriller In Possible SUPER BOWL Preview...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/12/01/ravens-keep-winning-streak-beat-49ers-20-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Baltimore Ravens beat the 49ers 20-17, after a close game right down to the last few seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Highly contagious' urine clears movie theater...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/state/washington/article237936289.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys to be sterilized by AI after rampages as aggressive primates targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkeys-sterilised-ai-after-rampages-21004542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attacks by aggressive monkeys in India have been reaching epidemic proportions and humans are having to go to extreme lengths to control them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal clouds gather over Rudy... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/01/rudy-giuliani-trump-ukraine-legal-jeopardy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts say an indictment is likely as prosecutors focus on Giuliani’s work for Trump and himself in Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Santa rally power stocks to best in generation?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/will-a-santa-claus-rally-power-the-sp-500-and-dow-to-their-best-years-in-a-generation-2019-11-30?mod=home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strong showing in December could set the S&amp;P 500 for its best year since 1997.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala imploding...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7743559/Kamala-Harris-aide-writes-stinging-resignation-letter-joins-Mike-Bloombergs-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kelly Mehlenenbacher, the former state operations director on Kamala Harris' presidential campaign who quit to join rival Mike Bloomberg's bid for the White House, left behind a stinging resignation letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trillion-dollar deficits as far as eye can see, and hardly a voice of caution to be heard...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/472480-trillion-dollar-deficits-as-far-as-the-eye-can-see-and-not-a-voice-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the old days, a decade or so ago, Democrats would have assailed Donald Trump's failure on federal deficits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief says humanity's 'war against nature' must stop...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-chief-says-humanitys-war-against-nature-must-134851057.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The devastating impact of global warming that threatens humanity is a pushback from Nature under assault, UN chief Antonio Guterres warned Sunday ahead of a key climate conference. "For many decades the human species has been at war with the planet, and now the planet is fighting back," he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM MESS ON BIGGEST TRAVEL DAY</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191201160957-1t1aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/ (PIX):U.S. snowstorms, rain make Thanksgiving trip home a nightmare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese tech groups writing UN facial recognition standards...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191201154956-tr6nz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDIA-Chinese tech groups writing UN facial recognition standard:MEDIA-Chinese tech groups writing UN facial recognition standards - FT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces two deadlines as Congress ramps up impeachment focus...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191201154626-kvh7r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Trump faces two deadlines as U.S. Congress ramps up impeachment focus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unsavory,' not impeachable: Dem explains why he opposes removing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/12/01/democratic-lawmaker-trump-unsavory-not-impeachable/2567848001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Democrat Jeff Van Drew, who knows Donald Trump, said voters should decide next year whether to remove the president, not lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Divided Left Is Losing Abortion Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/01/us/politics/abortion-planned-parenthood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miscalculations, and an unexpected victory by President Trump, have put abortion access at its most vulnerable point in decades, and the left on the defensive. Now it is trying to recover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV vaccine in 2021? Leading experts 'optimistic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/hiv-vaccine-2021-leading-experts-optimistic-about-ongoing-trials-n1092021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drs. Susan Buchbinder and Anthony Fauci, two of the world’s leading HIV experts, say three ongoing HIV vaccine trials are reason to be hopeful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURSE: NFL Teams With Cat Nicknames 0-12 Since Black Cat Ran Onto Field On MNF...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/nfl-teams-with-cat-nicknames-are-0-12-since-infamous-black-cat-ran-onto-the-field-at-metlife-stadium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perhaps it's a little bit of black cat voodoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian Asks Fans to Sign $1 Million NDA Before Show...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/pete-davidson-nda-sign-snl-saturday-night-live-dave-chappelle-1203420180/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever you do, never tweet at a Pete Davidson comedy show. The “Saturday Night Live” cast member has recently been dolling out non-disclosure agreements before each of his recent come…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
