<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bkyUv5ih_r0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House discusses vax mandate for interstate travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-08-12/biden-eyes-tougher-vaccine-rules-without-provoking-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as President Joe Biden becomes more aggressive in pressuring Americans to get vaccinated, he has refrained from using all his powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER SENTIMENT LOWEST IN DECADE...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/economy/consumer-sentiment-in-us-plunges-to-lowest-since-2011-2589476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer Sentiment in U.S. Plunges to Lowest Since 2011</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO SPEAKS; FIRST INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/andrew-cuomo-resigns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How he lost the governorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H'wood may require wearable proof...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/covid-hollywood-proof-of-wearing-visible-proof-vaccination-tv-film-sets-1234814461/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Some cast and crew members on films and TV shows soon might be required to wear identification that “clearly and visibly” verifies their Covid vaccination status while workin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi seeks doctors, nurses and ventilators...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/mississippi-seeks-doctors-nurses-and-ventilators-as-covid-patients-pack-icu-beds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi seeks doctors and nurses and has asked federal officials for ventilators as the state hit a record of more than 5,000 new Covid cases in one day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 9/11 anniversary could inspire extremist attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-religion-race-and-ethnicity-bfde115ff5407b2e2042c8108f8ca270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The upcoming 20th anniversary of the Sept. 11 attacks as well as approaching religious holidays could inspire extremist attacks, the Department of Homeland Security said in a terrorism alert issued Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' warns of violence from MAGA fans over reinstatement theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3469741/homeland-security-maga-violence-trump-reinstated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WARNING issued by the Department of Homeland Security is alerting Americans of MAGA supporter violence if Trump isn’t returned to the White House. The threat comes from QAnon conspiracy theorists…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Reeks of shady deal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9891933/New-York-State-Assembly-SUSPENDS-Cuomo-impeachment-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State Assembly has suspended impeachment proceedings in the wake of Cuomo's resignation, leaving the door open for him to seek re-election next November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Jake Paul won't face federal charges after FBI raided his mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jake-paul-won-t-face-federal-charges-after-the-fbi-raided-his-mansion-he-was-being-investigated-for-filming-looting-at-an-arizona-mall-in-2020/ar-AANhS9G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The YouTube star will not face any charges after the FBI raided his home in response to looting at an Arizona mall in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>63 on Martha's Vineyard test positive since Obama's party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9891873/63-people-Marthas-Vineyard-tested-positive-Covid-Obamas-60th-birthday-bash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A total of 63 people on Martha's Vineyard have tested positive for Covid-19 since former President Barack Obama's 60th birthday on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Diplomats Shredding, Burning Docs in Case Taliban Wins...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/u-s-embassy-shredding-burning-documents-in-case-taliban-wins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Embassy Shredding, Burning Documents in Case Taliban Wins</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bulk' of additional troops arriving in days...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210813182349-j5brh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/USA-MILITARY (URGENT):'Bulk' of additional U.S. troops will be in Afghanistan in coming days -Pentagon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In West, Connection Between Covid and Wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-the-west-a-connection-between-covid-and-wildfires/ar-AANi9MP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exposure to wildfire smoke during last summer’s wildfire season could be associated with thousands of additional coronavirus infections as well as hundreds of deaths, potentially causing an even greater challenge to public health officials in Washington, Oregon and California, a new study has found. Wildfire smoke contains high levels of the smallest, most dangerous type of soot known as PM 2.5. Researchers at Harvard University estimated that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Jill Gets a Boot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-joe-biden-health-hawaii-51a60bd0eb961d204e7373eeeec8b275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Jill Biden is wearing a medical boot following a recent foot injury on a Hawaiian beach. The boot was on the first lady's left foot Friday as she and President Joe Biden boarded a helicopter in Delaware to fly to the Camp David presidential retreat in Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Talent Agent Sues NYTIMES, Reporter for Defamation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/tiktok-talent-agent-ariadna-jacob-013737418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ariadna Jacob, an agent who represented TikTok stars like Charli D’Amelio and other online Influencers, filed a defamation lawsuit on Thursday against The New York Times and reporter Taylor Lorenz for an August 2020 article about her business. Jacob says the article contained “numerous false and disparaging statements” about her and her business, including the accusation that she leaked nude images of one of her clients and hiked up the rent on her content house tenants. She said the article als</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Jury Weighing Criminal Charges Against Deshaun Watson...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox26houston.com/news/deshaun-watson-latest-grand-jury-investigation-being-used-for-possible-criminal-charges-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox26houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources tell FOX 26 that Johna Stallings, Human Trafficking Section Chief for the Harris County District Attorney’s Office, is sending out the subpoenas for the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign jihadis flocking to launch new terror war...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3468810/chilling-map-jihadis-flocking-afghanistan-terror-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOREIGN fighters are flocking to Afghanistan to launch a new terror war on the West as the Taliban tears through the country. Jihadis from the UK, Syria, Libya and central Asia have been heading to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago speed cameras now ticket drivers going 6 mph over...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/chicago-speed-cameras-now-ticket-drivers-going-6-mph-over-the-new-rules-resulted-in-about-300000-citations-and-dollar11-million-in-fines-in-the-first-2-months/ar-AANhbY8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across the street from a car wash, next to a fenced-off former lumber yard stands one of Chicago’s most prolific park safety speed cameras. And two blocks west on Lawrence Avenue, on the other side of a railway viaduct, sits the small park the camera is ostensibly protecting from speeding cars. Until last March, that camera and more than 100 like it around the city could ticket drivers going ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian army to end virginity test for female soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/08/13/indonesian-army-to-end-archaic-virginity-test-for-female-soldiers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two-finger test has no scientific value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOAA: July Was Hottest Month Ever Recorded...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/climate-change-july-2021-hottest-month-noaa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's "very likely" that 2021 will be among the world's 10 warmest years on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 photojournalists sue DC police, claim use of illegal chemical irritants...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/08/2-photojournalists-sue-dc-police-claim-use-of-illegal-chemical-irritants-at-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two photojournalists who covered a protest at Black Lives Matter Plaza, in D.C., against police brutality last August are suing the District and eight members of the police, claiming officers used chemical irritants and stun grenades that had been banned by D.C. law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS sets new high for catch-and-release at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/13/dhs-sets-new-high-catch-and-release-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security set a new monthly high in July for illegal immigrants caught and released during the southern border surge with nearly 60,000 people turned loose into communities, according to new numbers the department released Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NY Assembly to suspend Cuomo impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/new-york-state-assembly-will-suspend-cuomo-impeachment-investigation-after-resignation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York state Assembly will suspend its impeachment investigation of Gov. Andrew Cuomo after his resignation takes effect on Aug. 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent Attacks, Bloodies Elementary Instructor Over Mask Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/08/12/amador-counnty-sutter-creek-mask-fight-parent-teacher/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A district dad came back to campus after picking up his daughter and confronted the school principal. He was angry his daughter was forced to wear a mask inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to require air travelers to be vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-canada-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-f504cb07e496c8569529bd5b8f5b2cf5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — The Canadian government will soon require all air travelers and passengers on interprovincial trains to be vaccinated against COVID-19. Transport Minister Omar Alghabra said Friday that includes all commercial air travelers, passengers on trains between provinces and cruise ship passengers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War veterans horrified: 'Why did my friend get blown up?'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98why-did-my-friend-get-blown-up-for-what-e2-80-99-afghanistan-war-veterans-horrified-by-taliban-gains/ar-AANhE8k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veterans across the world are voicing frustration over the Taliban’s faster-than-expected comeback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOPES Co-Founder Caught Writing Plagiarized Articles Under Fake Name...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/deansterlingjones/snopes-cofounder-plagiarism-mikkelson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You can always take an existing article and rewrite it just enough to avoid copyright infringement."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC woman arrested for walking dogs without leash...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-arrested-over-unleashed-dogs-in-nyc-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was handcuffed and arrested over her unleashed dogs in a Manhattan park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fast Carbs' Won't Make You Fat?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fast-carbs-dont-make-you-fat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The theory is that high-GI foods raise glucose levels and insulin secretion, which may lead to health issues through overeating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Lawsuit Could Jeopardize NASA 2024 Moon Landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/08/spacesuits-and-lawsuits-put-2024-moon-landing-jeopardy/184476/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two lunar-exploration spacesuits won’t be ready, a new report says, while bid protests have held up work on the lander.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE staffers in revolt over plan to scan users' iPhones for 'abuse' pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3464672/apple-revolt-tech-scan-customers-iphones-child-abuse-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE staffers are openly revolting over the tech-giant’s plans to scan iPhones for child abuse images – amid fears users’ privacy could be compromised. More than 800 messages on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhDs are most hesitant to take shot...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/the-most-vaccine-hesitant-education-group-of-all-phds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been much debate over how to get the unvaccinated to get their jabs — shame them, bribe them persuade them, or treat them as victims of mis- and disinformation campaigns — but who, exactly, are these people? Most of the coverage would have you believe that the surge in cases is primarily down to [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City marks fall of Aztec capital 500 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-mexico-caribbean-coronavirus-pandemic-21d75936dc02a995797612be69133eb6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Walking for hours through the gritty streets in the center of Mexico City, you can hear the daily urban soundtrack: Car engines, the call of the man who buys scrap metal and the handbells that announce the passing of a garbage truck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX deploys 2,500 out-of-state medical workers as younger, healthy patients crowd hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/texas-covid-abbott-deploys-2500-out-of-state-medical-workers-as-younger-patients-crowd-hospitals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said the state was bringing in 2,500 out-of-state medical personnel to relieve exhausted doctors and nurses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>440 Palm Beach Students Forced To Quarantine 2 Days Into School Year!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/440-students-palm-beach-county-quarantine-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Thursday, there are a total 131 confirmed cases of COVID-19 across more than 50 K-12 schools in the district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Florida Teachers Die In 24 Hours...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/13/broward-educators-lose-battle-with-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vicious virus, in less than one day this week, between Tuesday and Wednesday, claimed the lives of three Broward County school teachers and one of its assistant teachers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cornel West on Why the Left Needs Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/08/cornel-west-jesus-progressives/619741/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The famous professor has found himself out of step with cancel culture and the search for political purity among progressives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Dems threaten mutiny over Pelosi budget plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/13/9-dems-threaten-mutiny-over-pelosis-budget-plan-504408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi can afford to lose only three votes in the House and will need near unanimity among Democrats to pass the budget resolution, which is slated for a vote when the House returns the week of Aug. 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treehouses getting booked by wealthy travelers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/13/where-to-rent-treehouses-in-us-japan-australia-and-costa-rica.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modern treehouses are in demand by travelers who want a five-star, outdoor experience with a dose of childhood nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Toddler fatally shoots mother during work video call...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/shootings-c6fca7d62ef3225327e111b760ee897a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, Fla. (AP) — A toddler found an unsecured, loaded handgun inside an apartment and fatally shot a woman while she was on a work-related video call, police in central Florida said. According to news outlets, the woman was the mother of the toddler who shot her in the head Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Sydney outbreak prompts new borders inside Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210813-growing-sydney-outbreak-prompts-new-borders-inside-australia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growing Sydney outbreak prompts new borders inside Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra shot OK'd for those with weak immune systems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-coronavirus-pandemic-283298fb55b0556dbd9e45a62b782095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. regulators say transplant recipients and others with severely weakened immune systems can get an extra dose of the Pfizer or Moderna COVID-19 vaccines to better protect them as the delta variant continues to surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27 people aboard CARNIVAL cruise test positive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-travel-caribbean-4dd34f14b6a6365f48b3375c57ba4fb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELIZE CITY (AP) — Twenty-seven people aboard a Carnival cruise tested positive for COVID-19 just before the ship made a stop in Belize City this week, according to the Belize Tourism Board. The positive cases were among 26 crew members and one passenger on the Carnival Vista, which is carrying over 1,400 crew and nearly 3,000 passengers, the board said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Pioneer SONOS Fighting GOOGLE in 'Golden Age of Audio'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/speaker-pioneer-sonos-fighting-google-in-e2-80-98golden-age-of-audio-e2-80-99/ar-AANgPV8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sonos Inc. became a favorite with audiophiles by selling sleek, wireless speakers for streaming music long before technology titans such as Alphabet Inc.’s Google entered the market with cheaper, internet-connected models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Billionaires Stir Alarm With Absence of Safety Oversight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/space-billionaires-stir-alarm-with-absence-of-safety-oversight/ar-AANgXh0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaires who blasted into space in recent weeks did so with style. Blue Origin’s Jeff Bezos sported a cowboy hat after landing and Richard Branson wore a blue Virgin Galactic jumpsuit he’d called “sexy.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem moderates threaten Pelosi strategy; Demand vote on infrastructure bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/13/politics/house-moderate-democrats-infrastructure-strategy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine Democratic House moderates are threatening to withhold their support for their party's must-pass budget resolution until Speaker Nancy Pelosi changes course and instead allows their chamber to first vote on the $1.2 trillion bipartisan infrastructure plan the Senate approved this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touchless TACO BELL could be future of drive-thrus...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/touchless-taco-bell-could-be-the-future-of-drive-thrus-b9468c0b-a215-4c6c-a022-b1aa40ac54dc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scan a QR code, and your order is lowered down from the kitchen above</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The great American dog shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/the-great-american-dog-shortage-63218738-4472-47be-9428-76b1d9299a77.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the U.S. imports more than 1 million dogs a year, the annual demand is 8 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Humanitarian catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210813101141-av7xb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/UN (UPDATE 1, TV):UPDATE 1-Afghanistan on brink of 'humanitarian catastrophe', UN agencies say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan crisis intensifying...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-taliban-c6c8d4a41c554f36031a8131538d1402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban captured another three provincial capitals in Afghanistan on Friday, completing their sweep of the country's south in a lightning offensive that is gradually encircling Kabul, just weeks before the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators want answers about AMAZON biometric data collection...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/567628-senators-want-answers-about-amazons-biometric-data-collection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bipartisan group of senators sent a letter to Amazon Friday raising questions about its collection of biometric data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Port Shutdown Raises Fears of Closures Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/massive-china-port-shutdown-raises-210441619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Supply Lines is a daily newsletter that tracks trade and supply chains disrupted by the pandemic. Sign up here.A Covid outbreak that has partially shut one of the world’s busiest container ports is heightening concerns that the rapid spread of the delta variant will lead to a repeat of last year’s shipping nightmares.The Port of Los Angeles, which saw its volumes dip because of a June Covid outbreak at the Yantian port in China, is bracing for another potential decline because of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human sperm mutations that cause disease identified...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-08-human-sperm-mutations-disease-children.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout development, life and the processes of aging, all human cells accumulate mutations, resulting in what is called mosaicism, a condition in which different cells in the same person have different DNA sequences or genetic makeup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overheated Real Estate Market Begins to Cool...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/13/overheated-real-estate-market-begins-to-cool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic created a frenzied real estate market in much of the United States that has yet to let up,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUMBLE, a YOUTUBE rival popular with conservatives, will pay creators who 'challenge the status quo'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/rumble-youtube-rival-popular-conservatives-173004776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-growing YouTube rival popular with conservative influencers has a new strategy to expand its online audience: Paying hundreds of thousands of dollars to well-known media personalities it says work to "challenge the status quo." The Toronto-based upstart Rumble said Thursday that it has struck deals with former U.S. congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard, the journalist firebrand Glenn Greenwald and others who had committed to posting their videos first to the site.Subscribe to The Post Most newslett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Preparing to Recognize Taliban if Kabul Falls...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-08-12/china-prepared-to-recognize-taliban-if-kabul-falls-sources-say-undermining-us-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move comes at the expense of the U.S., which has held up the Taliban’s international legitimacy as its remaining source of leverage while the militant group storms across Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children born during pandemic 'have lower IQs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/12/children-born-during-pandemic-have-lower-iqs-us-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers blame lack of stimulation as parents balanced childcare with working from home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow Seriously Considers Leaving MSNBC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rachel-maddow-considers-leaving-msnbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As her contract draws to a close, sources told The Daily Beast, the MSNBC icon has been weighing taking her brand elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears father agrees to step down as conservator 'when time is right'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3463967/britney-spears-dad-jamie-steps-down-conservator-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’ dad Jamie has agreed to STEP DOWN as conservator of her estate, court documents obtained by The Sun state.  The move comes after years of the singer BEGGING for the patriarch to be …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July busiest month for illegal border crossings in 21 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/july-was-busiest-month-for-illegal-border-crossings-in-21-years-cbp-data-show/ar-AANfIrr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is encountering “an unprecedented number of migrants,” DHS Secretary Mayorkas said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Plant-based diet best way to avoid heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/nutrition/a-plant-based-diet-is-the-best-way-to-avoid-heart-disease-according-to-a-new-report/ar-AANf1jj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers advise consuming whole foods and avoiding red and processed meat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,000 Marines Deployed to Evacuate Embassy Staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/12/afghanistan-us-urges-citizens-to-leave-immediately-as-taliban-nears-kabul.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Embassy warned its ability to assist Americans is "extremely limited even within Kabul" due to deteriorating security and reduced staffing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants seize Kandahar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-afghanistan-taliban-26d485963b7a0d9f2107afcbc38f239a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban captured two major Afghan cities, the country's second- and third-largest after Kabul, and a strategic provincial capital on Thursday, further squeezing the embattled government just weeks before the end of the American military mission in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  More Dem voters favor socialism than capitalism in major shift...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/democrats-favor-socialism-capitalism-shift</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats have grown considerably more accepting of socialism since the coronavirus pandemic began, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan crisis intensifying...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/taliban-on-the-verge-of-capturing-two-of-afghanistan-s-largest-cities-after-taking-11th-provincial-capital/ar-AANeMF2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clashes pushed into the center of both Kandahar and Herat as Taliban fighters took control of some of the main government buildings in the two cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court won't block Indiana University vaccine mandate as Justice Barrett rejects student plea...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-won-e2-80-99t-block-indiana-university-vaccine-mandate-as-justice-barrett-rejects-student-plea/ar-AANg9rj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first case about mandatory coronavirus vaccinations to reach the Supreme Court, but Justice Amy Coney Barrett gave no reason for rejecting the request.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
