<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen jokes about women being raped...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/uknews/6786774/sacha-baron-cohen-rape-skit-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORAT star Sacha Baron Cohen is facing fresh controversy over his new TV series after it emerged he jokes about women being raped. In one skit Cohen plays an Israeli terrorism expert called Erran M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS MAYHEM AFTER WORLD CUP WIN...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5956427/French-fans-home-abroad-erupt-celebration-sides-second-World-Cup-triumph.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police fired tear gas as scuffles broke out on the Champs-Élysées as French football fans celebrate their side's spectacular World Cup victory over Croatia in Moscow today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delirious French revel in World Cup victory...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/delirious-french-revel-world-cup-victory-203440468.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France erupted in joy on Sunday as the country clinched the World Cup, with fans streaming into the streets, honking car horns and flying the tricolour flag at the start of an enormous national celebration. Cheers rang out throughout the country for each of four goals in the final as "Les Bleus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May warns rebels...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/british-pm-may-warns-rebels-back-risk-no-074800526--business.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Guy Faulconbridge and William James LONDON (Reuters) - British Prime Minister Theresa May warned her divided party on Sunday that there may be "no Brexit at all" if they wrecked her plan to forge a close relationship with the European Union after leaving the world's biggest trading</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police clash with unruly fans, clear Champs Elysees...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180715225652-3exti</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOCCER-WORLDCUP-FINAL/PARIS-TROUBLE (TV, PIX):French police clash with unruly fans, clear Champs Elysees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago police release video of shooting that sparked violent protests...</title>
      <link>http://abc7chicago.com/chicago-police-release-body-cam-video-of-south-shore-police-shooting/3766539/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities released Sunday the identity of a man who was fatally shot by Chicago police in the South Shore neighborhood on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Brexit referendum 'is only way to end deadlock'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/justine-greening-new-brexit-referendum-is-only-way-to-end-deadlock-55gd5rcpc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May’s hopes of winning support for her Brexit compromise have been dealt a huge blow as Justine Greening has become the first senior Conservative to support calls for a second referendum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Trump in White House, candidates who sound like him hit campaign trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/With-Trump-in-the-White-House-candidates-who-13077071.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA - In last week's debate between Georgia's Republican candidates for governor, policy was quickly abandoned as Lt. Gov. Casey Cagle and Secretary of State Brian Kemp lit into one another with a familiar slate of accusations. Kemp called Cagle a liar at least a dozen times. Cagle accused Kemp of conspiring with another Republican to release a recording of an "out of context" private conversationKemp accused Cagle of spreading "fake news" to Georgians, and Cagle repeatedly refused to apologize for saying what he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrant children held in shelters: 'They told us to behave, or we'd be here forever'... </title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Immigrant-children-held-in-shelters-They-told-13077041.php?src=hp_totn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON - When the 8-year-old stepped off a plane here earlier this month with freshly cut bangs and a shelter-issued sweatsuit, she was met by crowds and television cameras and finally, in a carpeted airport conference room, by the mother who had been taken from her two months earlier at the border. But now, a day after that joyous reunion, the girl from Guatemala was shoving a toddler who had tried to give her a hug and a kiss at a welcoming party in the suburbs. Now she was screaming and crying and telling the boy to stay away. This is what two months in a Texas shelter had taught Sandy Gonzalez. "They always kept the boys and the girls separate," the second-grader explained last week. "And they punished us if we went near each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games show off modern Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/445a4d2de1ba4b898b6dcc8e3c24140d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Despite a national wave of elation from the World Cup that bathed Russia in a rosy light, President Vladimir Putin will face some challenges in extending the post-so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadians still visiting USA despite trade flap...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cc07ddb7c9f469081c414021d2bd19d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLD ORCHARD BEACH, Maine (AP) — The United States and Canada are engaged in a trade dispute, angering Canadians, but it doesn't seem to be having an impact on tourism. Not yet, an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump resists Mueller interview, leaving decision on subpoena before fall elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-resists-mueller-interview-leaving-decision-on-subpoena-before-fall-elections/ar-AAA7owy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVS apologizes after white manager calls police on black customer...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/news/black-woman-says-cvs-manager-called-police-because-she-had-wrong-coupon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the video went viral on Facebook, representatives of the company reached out to Camilla Hudson to apologize "profusely" for the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gowdy rules out Rosenstein impeachment... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/sunday-talk-shows/397127-gowdy-rules-out-rosenstein-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Trey Gowdy (R-S.C.) on Sunday ruled out the possibility of impeaching Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein, saying there is not enough support for his ouster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pedo guy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/thai-cave-rescue-elon-musk-british-diver-vern-unsworth-twitter-pedo-a8448366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Sorry pedo guy, you really did ask for it'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley eyes Africa as new tech frontier...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-07-silicon-valley-eyes-africa-tech.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna at 60: Pop culture still reeks of her influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jul/15/barbara-ellen-on-madonna-sexist-slurs-pop-surivor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the singer’s 60th birthday approaches, the Observer columnist celebrates pop’s greatest survivor• Thurston Moore on Madonna: ‘She was really ahead of the game’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUBRICK FROM BEYOND THE GRAVE? Lost screenplay found 60 years on...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jul/15/stanley-kubrick-lost-screenplay-burning-secret-found</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Script co-written by master director is so close to completion that it could be developed into a full feature film</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists peer into heart of hurricanes to improve intensity forecast...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180715100024-aeg6u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a better way to predict a storm's power, people will be more prepared in knowing whether a hurricane headed their way will cause devastating floods and winds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk attacks hero diver and questions if he was even involved in Thai rescue...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5955753/British-caver-helped-save-Thai-boys-says-Elon-Musk-stick-submarine-hurt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk has hit back at a British caver who helped rescue 12 Thai school boys and their soccer coach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botswana may put elephants in cross-hairs as it moves to lift hunting ban...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/botswana-may-put-elephants-cross-hairs-moves-lift-133639202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Botswana, home to the world's largest elephant population, may lift a ban on hunting for sport in the face of what the government says is growing conflict between humans and wildlife, a move sure to provoke protest from animal welfare groups. Conservationists estimate the land-locked southern African</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES HELSINKI!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6f78cad4eb024bf2a2d47b2df035f664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — A face-to-face sitdown with a long-feared foe. Endless media hype. Huge ratings.        Although President Donald Trump has met with Russia's Vladimir Putin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok arrogance 'product of corrupt FBI'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/14/peter-strzoks-arrogance-is-the-product-of-a-corrupt-fbi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching FBI agent Peter Strzok battle with Congress, my initial reaction was pure anger. His repeated, arrogant insistence that he had done nothing wrong despite tons of evidence to the contrary c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Jaguar escapes New Orleans zoo, goes on animal killing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6782468/jaguar-valerio-escapes-new-orleans-zoo-killing-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A JAGUAR escaped from its zoo enclosure and slaughtered six other animals in a terrifying hour-long killing spree. The big cat, named Valerio, was sedated he after he killed four alpacas, one emu, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHAME IS DEAD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/who-is-america-review-1127051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacha Baron Cohen's new Showtime comedy is occasionally funny, but it's hard to be outrageous in a world where ideologies that used to be concealed are now proudly public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret plot to EVICT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716573/julian-assange-wikileaks-evicted-ecuadorian-embassy-london-usa-deported</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary begins speech: 'I'm so tired, I can barely stand'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/hillary-starts-speech-im-so-tired-i-can-barely-stand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton may have visions of 2020 — if she can just keep her eyes open. The failed presidential candidate started her speech to the American Federation of Teachers union on Friday in a bizarre way: by telling everyone how tired she was. ﻿ “Well, I’ll tell you,” she said, “I’ve been back there listening …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26-year-incumbent snubbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article214913325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Sen. Dianne Feinstein lost the California Democratic Party endorsement to her more liberal challenger, Kevin de León, on Saturday, July 14, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA DEMS REBUKE FEINSTEIN...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-pol-ca-senate-feinstein-de-leon-endorsement-20180714-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;De León’s victory over the longtime senator reflects the increasing strength of the state party’s liberal activist core, which was energized by the election of Republican President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama in ancestral home Kenya to launch sister's project...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c9f3ed226c784f25895354b62c2f5d3c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — Former U.S. President Barack Obama arrived in Kenya Sunday, the country of his father's birth, his first visit to this East African country since leaving off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Urges USA NOT to Tap Oil Reserve...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-15/iran-official-urges-trump-not-to-use-u-s-strategic-oil-reserve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Iranian oil official urged U.S. President Donald Trump not to use the nation’s Strategic Petroleum Reserve to push prices lower, and instead drop sanctions on Iran’s crude exports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man intros teen 'wife' to cop: 'It's OK, she's gonna be 16 soon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2018/07/14/dallas-man-introduces-teenage-wife-cop-ok-gonna-16-soon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dallas man arrested last week after he parking illegally near Trinity Groves introduced the arresting officer to his 15-year-old wife, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech mirror points out all your flaws...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/07/14/high-tech-mirror-points-flaws-should-come-mental-health-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high-tech mirror that tells you how ugly you are should come with a mental health warning, campaigners have claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS-ROYCE plans flying taxi take off...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rolls-royce-plans-off-flying-taxi-market-120417550--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British jet engine maker Rolls-Royce has designed a propulsion system for a flying taxi and is starting a search for partners to help develop a project it hopes could take to the skies as soon as early next decade. Rolls-Royce said on Sunday it had drawn up plans for an electric vertical take-off and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren 2020 Prep -- And Biden, Booker, Harris and Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/15/us/politics/democratic-presidential-candidates-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many top Democrats eye a run for president in 2020, Elizabeth Warren has all but announced her candidacy, while Joe Biden is planning to campaign up to four days a week this fall for midterm candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Hamas cell launching arson kites during Gaza ceasefire...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-strikes-hamas-cell-launching-arson-kites-during-gaza-ceasefire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians say one injured by drone strike in Beit Hanoun area; Netanyahu and Liberman vow zero tolerance to ongoing, cross-border arson attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman survives week after driving off Big Sur cliff...</title>
      <link>'https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article214901920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper publisher resigns after N-word usage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/East-Bay-Express-publisher-resigns-after-13075990.php?t=5c5350a3f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publisher of the East Bay Express weekly newspaper resigned on Saturday, admitting to "indiscretions" and saying his presence had "become a threat to the mission ....of healthy independent journalism."         Stephen Buel stepped down one day after posting a lengthy "apology and pledge" on the newspaper's website in which he admitted that he used derogatory words while discussing a story he had unilaterally removed from the newspaper website that described "white people singing along to live hip-hop songs that contained the N-word."         "I said a couple of those words aloud," Buel wrote in his apology. "I should not have done so and am extremely sorry that my remark caused others pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveals 'brutal' president gave her:  Sue EU...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6782684/theresa-may-finally-reveals-brutal-brexit-advice-donald-trump-gave-her-to-sue-the-eu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May has finally revealed the explosive Brexit advice Donald Trump gave to her – to sue the EU. The Prime Minister said the US President told her not to even enter into a negotiation with Br…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES IN HELSINKI!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-russia-low-expectations-putin-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump gave an exclusive interview to "CBS Evening News" anchor Jeff Glor in Scotland ahead of his meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA recalls common heart drug over cancer concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/fda-recalls-common-heart-drug-over-cancer-concerns/i7TSPdFqzbclCMleFaDynO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: CON JOB...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/who-is-america-review-sacha-baron-cohen-spoof-bernie-sanders-dick-cheney-sarah-palin-showtime-1202426515/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When David Nevins called Sacha Baron Cohen “the premier provocateur of our time” in announcing the new Who Is America? series, the Showtime boss was certainly honest to a fault. Full of mild shock,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: CHARACTERS...</title>
      <link>http://www.vulture.com/2018/07/sacha-baron-cohen-who-is-america-characters-ranked.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vulture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Infowars-esque conspiracy theorist, an NPR liberal, a British ex-con, and an Islamophobic Israeli soldier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen nabs Bernie Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sacha-baron-cohen-targets-gop-congressmen-bernie-sanders-in-who-is-america-premiere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime’s ‘Who Is America?,’ premiering Sunday night, more than lives up to the hype, and stands as Sacha Baron Cohen’s most subversive work since ‘Da Ali G Show.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO recognizes 'compulsive sexual behavior' as mental disorder...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/recognises-compulsive-sexual-behaviour-mental-disorder-200546301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization has recognised "compulsive sexual behaviour" as a mental disorder, but said Saturday it remained unclear if it was an addiction on a par with gambling or drug abuse. The contentious term "sex addiction" has been around for decades but experts disagree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban reforms stress free market, private property and investment...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cuban-reforms-stress-free-market-private-property-investment-192824723.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socialist Cuba is planning a series of potentially far-reaching changes, with a new constitution set to recognize the free market and private property, while dividing political powers between a president and a prime minister. In a reform of the island nation's 1976 constitution expected to be quickly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYALS SNUB...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/royal-family-snub-trump-5kwvt5h5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Charles and Prince William were unwilling to meet Donald Trump on his visit to Britain, leaving the Queen to greet the US president alone. The first two in line to the throne let it be known...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans prep impeachment docs on Rosenstein... </title>
      <link>https://www.bizpacreview.com/2018/07/14/rosenstein-not-smiling-anymore-after-house-republicans-spotted-with-his-impeachment-docs-654125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bizpacreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two House Republicans are seeking to file impeachment documents against Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein as early as Monday, according to Capitol Hill sources who spoke with Politico. Reps. Jim Jordan and Mark Meadows, both members of the House Freedom Caucus, take issue with both the deputy attorney general’s poor handling of the Russia investigation and his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange faces eviction from embassy...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/14/assange-could-soon-be-evicted-from-london-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange may soon be evicted from the London embassy that has sheltered him for the last six years. Ecuador, which has played host to the political provocateur since 2012, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scottish Slam Security Bill For Trump Golf...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5954999/Outrage-5M-taxpayers-cash-spent-security-Donald-Trumps-private-trip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump sparked outrage again today after it was revealed his decision to visit Scotland and play golf at his Ayrshire course may cost the British taxpayer as much as £5million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May warns there could be 'no Brexit at all'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5954683/THERESA-MAYs-steely-warning-Tory-rebels-bully-boys-Brussels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May, writing for the Mail On Sunday, said: 'Brexit isn’t about trading with other countries instead of trading with Europe, it is about doing both.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists in Egypt discover mummification workshop...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/archaeologists-egypt-discover-mummification-worskshop-110445367.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — Archaeologists in Egypt stumbled upon a new discovery dating back to more than 2,500 years ago near Egypt's famed pyramids at an ancient necropolis south of Cairo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Goldmine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/14/a-goldmine-mummies-secrets-uncovered-in-egypt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists find mummification workshop in the Saqqara necropolis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST:  Fired BILLBOARD CEO probed for gay slurs, sex harassment, financial misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ousted-billboard-ceo-john-amato-being-probed-for-sexual-and-financial-misconduct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amato was forced to resign after current and former employees came forward with evidence that he harassed employees and engaged in other misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare double shark attack closes Florida beach; Bites were just minutes apart... </title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/national/rare-double-shark-attack-closes-florida-beach-bites-were-just/article_9ba28c16-62b2-5c55-a9d6-1738fb2ecca9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike southern Florida, shark encounters are relatively rare farther up Florida's Atlantic coastline and are almost unheard of in northernmost Nassau County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Having a Bawl in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/14/opinion/sunday/trump-having-a-bawl-in-europe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Baby kicks Jolly Old England when she’s down but embraces mendacious Mother Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Director Uncovered Whitney Houston's Secret Pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/13/movies/whitney-houston-documentary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of a new documentary said he consulted addiction experts and repeatedly interviewed her brothers to reveal her childhood abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British tabloid hits Trump for sitting in Churchill's chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/donald-trump-sparks-fury-posing-12914158</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You insult our country, attack our NHS, embarrass our Queen, undermine our ‘special relationship’, humiliate our PM...and then smugly pose in Winston Churchill’s armchair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haitian prime minister resigns after fuel riots...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/haiti/article214692715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haiti’s prime minister, Jack Guy Lafontant, and his 18 cabinet members resigned Saturday, one week after his government’s temporary suspension of an unpopular fuel price hike failed to halt a violent civil unrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students, civilians trapped in church amid gunfire by militias...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Students-civilians-trapped-in-Nicaraguan-church-13074966.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANAGUA, Nicaragua - The first student I met outside the Church of the Divine Mercy had a fresh bullet hole in his lower back. "It's ugly in there," he said. "In there" was the vast, jungly campus of the National Autonomous University of Nicaragua (UNAN), which by Friday afternoon had become a battleground. Far from the initial fighting was the Catholic church, a supposedly safe place for triage, and beleaguered and wounded students were arriving from the front lines by pickup truck, by motorbike, and on foot. "We had to evacuate," Jonas Cruz, 18, said. "They are invading the barricades. They are already inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaraguan protests getting deadlier, activists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/nicaraguan-protests-are-getting-deadlier-activists-say/article_92368de9-0b5e-5905-9e25-5238afe1d8e2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zayda Hernandez and Victor Cuadras are among the Nicaraguan university students risking their lives in mass protests against Nicaraguan President Daniel Ortega and his wife, Vice President Rosario Murillo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot addiction: Clinics braced for humans hooked on cyborgs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716215/sex-robot-dolls-addiction-clinics-humans-hooked-treatment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serena Williams denied historic Grand Slam title at Wimbledon...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/14/serena-williams-denied-historic-grand-slam-title-at-wimbledon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Angelique Kerber was so steady, so patient, so accurate throughout the Wimbledon final. She never really gave Serena Williams much of a chance. Kerber won her first championship at the All…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Under Fire For 'Flipping Coin' To Decide Whether They'll Arrest Speeding Driver...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/13/georgia-police-flipping-coin-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To add insult to injury, the "coin" flipped in the woman's favor, but Roswell Police officers Courtney Brown and Kristee Wilson decided to arrest her, anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DOES IT AGAIN:  Gospel song flagged as 'political'...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/07/is-this-a-political-ad-facebook-thinks-so/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add one more arbitrary and capricious act of anti-Christian-censorship bigotry to the list of Facebook blocks. The Gospel music group Zion’s Joy! posted its new song “What Would Heaven Look Like,” a purely spiritual Christian praise song, to Facebook, boosting it with a $100 purchase – only to see the song censored for “political content.” […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller, pushing to wrap up parts of Russia probe, faces question of American involvement...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/philly/news/politics/presidential/robert-mueller-investigation-russia-probe-american-involvement-20180714.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are signs that the special counsel is moving to finish a significant portion of his investigative work by the end of the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man suspected of attacking wife with chain saw was deported 11 times...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-chainsaw-deported-20180713-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man suspected of attacking his wife with a chain saw in Whittier and then fleeing had been deported 11 times since 2005, according to immigration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago's last SEARS to close for good...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-sears-last-chicago-store-0714-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears' last remaining department store in Chicago, the company's longtime hometown, will close on Sunday after nearly 80 years in operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES IN HELSINKI!</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/trump-heads-to-putin-summit-with-no-clear-goal-and/article_1be21be3-115c-5dba-9701-c3997b4912cc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI, Finland — When President Donald Trump flew to Singapore last month to meet with Kim Jong Un, he had a clear agenda: to try personal diplomacy, rather than insults</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE HEATS BATTLE WITH CNN...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/397055-white-house-we-cancelled-boltons-interview-with-cnn-after-jim-acosta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders said Saturday that the White House decided to cancel an interview between CNN and national security adviser John Bolton after a CNN reporter “disrespected” President Trump earlier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem lawmaker dances to Drake song to promote millennial voter turnout...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/397054-dem-lawmaker-dances-to-drake-song-to-promote-midterm-voting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Democratic lawmaker posted a video of herself dancing to Drake's newly released song "In My Feelings" on Twitter Friday, urging the song's mysterious "Keke" to vote in November's midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
