<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Record wildfire burns amid drought in Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-environment-and-nature-droughts-hawaii-wildfires-ca2f8cbf76abf6affbbee9fce3be69a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Firefighters gained more control over a wildfire in Hawaii that forced thousands of people to evacuate over the weekend and destroyed at least two homes on the Big Island, but officials warned that strong winds will return on Tuesday, raising the danger again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titanic museum iceberg wall collapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/us/titanic-museum-iceberg-injured-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wall of ice collapsed Monday at the Titanic Museum Attraction, injuring three visitors to the popular tourist spot in Tennessee's Smoky Mountains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran to give J&amp;J recipients 'supplemental dose'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/jj-covid-vaccine-recipients-can-get-supplemental-pfizer-or-moderna-shots-in-san-francisco.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J&amp;J recipients can make special requests to get a "supplemental dose" of an mRNA vaccine, San Francisco health officials said in a statement to CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan &amp; Harry set to make Hollywood debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3407104/meghan-markle-prince-harry-present-emmy-award/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMY awards bosses want Prince Harry and wife Meghan to make their Hollywood debuts at the ceremony next month. TV execs are keen for the pair to attend the A-list event in downtown LA. They may ev…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Covid Wave Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-faces-its-worst-coronavirus-wave-yet/ar-AAMRrMm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the highly contagious Delta variant of the virus rips through the unvaccinated population in the United States, Florida is heading toward its worst outbreak since the start of the pandemic. The state is still about one month away from its peak, according to an epidemiologist who has been tracking the virus’s reach there. “Short term and long term, the cases are going to explode,” Edwin Michael, a professor of epidemiology at the University of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Mexico's most terrified city...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/featured/ct-aud-nyt-mexico-fresnillo-20210803-b447rgfxsjhhhg7nlqugcloovi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The violence was already terrifying, she said, when grenades exploded outside her church in broad daylight some five years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL hospitalizations break record for 3rd straight day...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/566156-florida-covid-19-hospitalizations-break-record-for-third-straight-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's COVID-19 hospitalization record was broken on Tuesday for the third day in a row as the state struggles with the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  RESIGN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/biden-calls-on-cuomo-to-resign-after-bombshell-sexual-harassment-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden called on Democratic New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo to resign Tuesday, following a report that Cuomo sexually harassed 11 women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth About the Quietest Town in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-truth-about-the-quietest-town-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Radio Quiet Zone limits wireless communications. But a journey to its center in Green Bank, West Virginia reveals a town at odds with itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabinet approves new restrictions, considers lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/covid-israel-registers-almost-4000-cases-as-cabinet-prepares-to-meet-675707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting August 20, the full green pass system will be in place again, and starting Sunday, masks will be mandatory in all outdoor gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Philadelphia Reveals About Homicide Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/philadelphia-homicide-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many explanations for the rise in killings in U.S. cities, including the pandemic and the choices made in response to it. In Philadelphia, the causes, the human costs — and the suffering — are particularly stark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PODHORETZ:  The Mad King, Alone Upon His Throne...</title>
      <link>https://www.commentary.org/john-podhoretz/cuomo-the-mad-king/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.commentary.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How art the mighty fallen. I encourage you, if you did not see it, to watch Andrew Cuomo's statement in response to the release of a report by New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trucking crisis has USA looking for more drivers abroad...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2021/08/02/trucking-crisis-has-u-s-looking-for-more-drivers-abroad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The obstacles foreign workers usually face may be easier to overcome following the creation of a Biden administration task force that addresses the supply chain problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Response Includes Photos of Biden, Harris, Obama Hugging, Kissing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/cuomos-response-to-investigation-includes-photo-trove-of-biden-harris-obama-and-more-hugging-and-kissing-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The office of Governor Andrew Cuomo has a lengthy response to the findings of the New York Attorney General's Office that includes photos of himself and other prominent politicians hugging and kissing people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Commissioner Escorted From Official Meeting After Refusing To Wear Mask...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/county-commissioner-j-j-koch-refuses-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas County Commissioner J.J. Koch (R-Pct. 2) was escorted out of Tuesday's Aug. 3 commissioner's meeting for not wearing a face  mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coroner in Missouri county keeps off of death certificates...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/coronavirus/article253147128.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I do what pleases the family,’ said Macon County Coroner Brian Hayes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONTIER Passenger Duct-Taped to Seat After Allegedly Groping Flight Attendants...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/news/frontier-airlines-passenger-duct-taped-seat-after-allegedly-groping-flight-attendants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was duct-taped to his seat by Frontier Airlines employees this weekend after allegedly [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Woman exposed herself on flight, assaulted officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/florida/2021/08/03/daytona-beach-shores-woman-exposed-herself-on-flight-assaulted-officer-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman is facing multiple charges after police say they took her off a plane at the Rapid City Regional Airport for exposing herself and becoming unruly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP DNC BRASS RESIST UNION EFFORT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/566125-staff-seeks-to-create-union-at-dnc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rank-and-file staff at the Democratic National Committee (DNC) are pressing to form a union after months of negotiations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Cuomo Appears to Have Helped Draft Brother's Response to Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chris-cuomo-appears-to-have-helped-draft-brother-andrews-response-to-harassment-allegations-ag-report-reveals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bombshell report by the office of New York attorney general Letitia James, which concluded that New York Governor Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed multiple women, revealed that his brother, CNN host Chris Cuomo, testified as part of the investigation about his role in advising the governor on how to respond to the allegations. Chris Cuomo, […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:   Cop killed outside Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/politics/pentagon-shooting-lockdown/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With France 'health pass' to expand, bugs and questions remain...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210803-with-france-s-health-pass-measure-set-to-expand-bugs-and-questions-remain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists are once again flooding into France – albeit not at pre-pandemic levels – as use of the so-called Covid-19 “health pass” is set to expand. So far, the implementation of the measure has not b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFUSES TO RESIGN</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/cuomo-responds-to-sexual-harassment-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Letitia James says investigators found the governor sexually harassed multiple women, in violation of state and federal law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran suspected of being behind hijack off UAE coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/britain-warns-of-non-piracy-incident-underway-off-uae-coast-675737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran: The potential hijack of ships off coast of UAE is 'suspicious' • Possible attack follows attack on Israeli-managed tanker off coast of Oman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis Tense Exchange With Reporter When Asked About Children In ICU...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/covid-florida-desantis-downplays-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis doubled down Tuesday in defending his actions and his ban of mask mandates amid the coronavirus pandemic just as the state once again broke its record for COVID-19 hospitalizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives call for new probe, impeachment of Justice Kavanaugh...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/2/progressives-call-new-probe-impeachment-supreme-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive activist groups have renewed calls for a new probe into Supreme Court Justice Brett M. Kavanaugh and his possible impeachment, saying a further FBI investigation is necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  Israel Adds USA to List Requiring VACCINATED in Quarantine!</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-may-place-us-under-severe-travel-warning-675718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beginning next Wednesday, travelers from some 18 additional countries will be required to quarantine even if they are fully vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How artists lost their courage...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/08/how-artists-lost-their-courage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keeping silent is the price of a successful career</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READ IT ALL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/read-the-cuomo-report-from-the-ny-attorney-generals-office/3196417/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators appointed by New York Attorney General Letitia James concluded that Gov. Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed multiple women in violation of state and federal law. Read their report below or click here to open in a new window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Men to vastly outnumber women within decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/men-could-soon-vastly-outnumber-24675636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few decades from now, blokes in some countries could find themselves struggling to find a wife or girlfriend, as millions of girls are not being born due to parents opting to hold out for boys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CILLIZZA:  Biden having worst week...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/politics/joe-biden-eviction-president-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's presidential honeymoon has officially ended, with a series of problems -- led by the ongoing surge of the Delta variant of the coronavirus -- coalescing to make the last few days some of the worst ones he has spent as president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROPING, KISSING, VERBAL ABUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/attorney-general-expected-to-release-findings-of-probe-into-cuomo-harassment-allegations/3196087/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Attorney General Letitia James and the team of attorneys selected to investigate allegations of sexual harassment made against Gov. Andrew Cuomo have completed their investigation and released a public report of their findings. The attorney general’s report, which is being made available to the public for the first time, found that the harassment claimed by a number of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG:  CUOMO HARASSED WOMEN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/ny-gov-andrew-cuomo-sexual-harassment-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed multiple women who worked for the state and elsewhere, according to report by state Attorney General Letitia James.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RETALIATED!</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/governor-cuomo-investigation-sexual-harassment-scandal/10927185/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Letitia James on Tuesday announced the findings of her inquiry into accusations against Andrew Cuomo, concluding that the governor sexually harassed multiple women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Crashes Into World Trade Center Building...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/02/small-drone-hits-7-world-trade-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources told CBS2 a man visiting from Texas was flying the small drone when it crashed into 7 World Trade Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL HOSPITAL RECORD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-f7a383de8065b5824344a6a79aa1eece</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — The number of people hospitalized for COVID-19 in Florida rose to an all-time high of 11,515 patients in one day, according to data the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services released Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida district drops covering mandate after DeSantis threatens funding...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/566056-florida-district-reverses-on-mask-mandate-after-desantis-threatens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida school district has dropped its mask mandate for schools after Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) issued an executive order that would cut off funding to schools that did so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Keto Diet Disease-Promoting Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/keto-disease-promoting-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new report finds restricting carbohydrates actually tilts a person's diet towards more cancer-causing foods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to mandate jab certification for indoor activities...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/city-hall/story/2021/08/03/new-york-city-to-mandate-vaccine-certification-for-a-range-of-indoor-activities-1389396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enforcement will begin in mid-September, according to City Hall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maui residents rail against spike in tourism during water shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2021/08/03/maui-hawaii-water-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As travel returns to pre-pandemic levels in Hawaii, some natives are saying they are tired of catering to visitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio elections: Primaries test Dem loyalty, Trump influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ohio-elections-primaries-test-democratic-loyalty-trump-e2-80-99s-influence/ar-AAMSTtp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nina Turner, a co-chair of Bernie Sanders’s 2020 presidential campaign, is pitted in a high-profile race with Shontel Brown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Willing to Take Pay Cut to Never Go Back to Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/americans-are-willing-to-take-pay-cuts-to-never-go-into-the-office-again/ar-AAMSYrz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey shows 65% of workers who said their jobs could be done entirely remotely were willing to take a 5% reduction to stay at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Judy $47M Salary Isn't Excessive, Appeals Court Agrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/judge-judy-salary-1234991870/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS wins the first appellate round in a legal battle now in its sixth year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's steepest dive' rollercoaster to open with drop from 150ft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/travel/travel-news/worlds-steepest-dive-rollercoaster-open-24676672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'd have to be an adrenaline junky to take on the "world's steepest dive" rollercoaster that's set to open in Six Flags theme park next year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming soon: America's own social credit system...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/565860-coming-soon-americas-own-social-credit-system</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same issue with government censorship exists with corporate censorship: If there is a line, who draws it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People recovering may have 'substantial' drop in intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/08/03/people-recovering-from-covid-may-have-substantial-drop-in-intelligence-15030236/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research has suggested that coronavirus has had a big impact on the IQ of the British people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone volcano rocked by record number of quakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1471580/yellowstone-volcano-earthquakes-usgs-latest-yellowstone-eruption-scn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YELLOWSTONE volcano experienced more than 1,000 earthquakes last month - a four-year record high that the US Geological Survey (USGS) said will "likely increase" in the coming days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD: Border Crossers Highest in 20 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/index.php/article/national/patrick-goodenough/surge-number-migrants-stopped-us-mexico-border-july-highest-20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection agents recorded around 210,000 “encounters” with migrants along the southwest border in July, the highest monthly figure in two decades, a senior Department of Homeland Security (DHS) official said in a court filing on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mao pins test rules...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-winter-olympics-china-olympic-team-united-states-olympic-team-62e3a9a9f4c71629b64b2026d0304c34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The image of Communist China's founding leader, Mao Zedong, made an unscheduled appearance at the Tokyo Olympics, and the International Olympic Committee said Tuesday it is “looking into the matter.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Kim Jong Un Head Bandage to List of Health Mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/add-kim-jong-uns-head-bandage-to-list-of-health-mysteries-2501519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea's Kim Jong Un has appeared in recent days with a bandage about the size of a few postage stamps on the back of his head, in the latest episode to stoke speculation about the reclusive leader's health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Raisi Starts Presidency as New Crisis Grips Persian Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/news/world/irans-ebrahim-raisi-starts-presidency-as-new-crisis-grips-persian-gulf-11627964350191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ebrahim Raisi, 60, will begin his tenure after he’s officially confirmed by Ayatollah Ali Khamenei in a televised ceremony, ending the eight-year rule of Hassan Rouhani</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans hailed as debate rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210803-transgender-olympian-hubbard-hailed-as-debate-rages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transgender Olympian Hubbard hailed as debate rages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Belarus dissident found hanged in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210803-belarus-dissident-found-hanged-in-ukraine-police-open-murder-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Belarusian activist living in exile in Ukraine was found hanged in a park near his home in Kyiv early on Tuesday, and Ukrainian police said they had launched a murder case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER partners with AP, REUTERS to clean up 'misinformation' on site...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/twitter-partners-ap-reuters-battle-200356209.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter Inc will partner with the Associated Press and Reuters to more quickly provide credible information on the social networking site as part of an effort to fight the spread of misinformation, it said on Monday. Like other social media companies, the San Francisco-based firm has been under pressure to remove misleading or false information on its site. Earlier this year Twitter launched a program called Birdwatch, asking its users to help identify and fact-check misleading tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean, repeat: At Tokyo Games, virus Olympians' chief foe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-6c8a1fd6c9c1ef1cea9656c7d30a2494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Holding each other tighter than lovers, the wrestlers smear each other with sweat, spittle and — when they inadvertently cut each other — sometimes blood. Lungs heaving, mouths agape, they huff and puff into each others' flushed faces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epidemic of Military Sex Assault...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/03/a-poison-in-the-system-the-epidemic-of-military-sexual-assault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfc. Florence Shmorgoner woke up one afternoon in 2015 and realized that she was in someone else’s bed in someone</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
