<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Record heat broils Japan, prompting warnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/record-heat-broils-japan-prompting-warnings-061956266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese officials issued new warnings Monday as a deadly heatwave blankets the country, producing record high temperatures in Tokyo just two years before the city hosts the 2020 Summer Olympics. Officials said last week that the heatwave had killed at least 15 people and forced the hospitalisation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying groundskeeper to testify in ROUNDUP cancer trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/dying-groundskeeper-testify-roundup-cancer-trial-doc-17u0b71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gays strike, march in Tel Aviv...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/22/gays-go-strike-israel-over-surrogacy-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Israeli LGBT advocates and their supporters are on strike, protesting the exclusion of gay men from a recently passed surrogacy law. Protesters marched in Tel Aviv and other Israeli cities on Sunday, waving rainbow flags and briefly blocking a major highway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risks for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/22/trump-manafort-trial-mueller-russia-probe-735084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's former campaign chairman is set to be the first to go before a jury in the Mueller investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort faces trial in first court test of special counsel prosecution...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-manafort-mueller-trial-20180723-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort spent decades wheeling and dealing with U.S. politicians and foreign despots. Now President Trump's former campaign chairman faces his toughest audience yet — a federal judge and jury. He's the first person to face trial on charges brought by special counsel Robert S. Mueller</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vaccine scandal sparks fury, roils markets...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180723102815-y5p0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-VACCINES/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Bitter pill: China vaccine scandal sparks fury, roils markets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration and Border Suddenly Tough Issues for Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/23/immigration-and-the-border-are-suddenly-tough-issues-for-trudeau#gs.fJcFMU8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration and the Border Are Suddenly Tough Issues for Trudeau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chemicals in Food May Harm Children, Pediatricians' Group Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/chemicals-in-food-may-harm-children-pediatricians-group-says/17714679/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major pediatricians’ group is urging families to limit the use of plastic food containers, cut down on processed meat during pregnancy and consume more whole fruits and vegetables rather than processed food. Such measures would lower children’s exposures to chemicals in food and food packaging that are tied to health problems such as obesity, the group says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems get set for 2020 starting gun...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/398102-dems-get-set-for-2020-starting-gun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dozens of Democrats considering running for president in 2020 are pondering how, and when, to formally declare their candidacies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-Setting Heatwave In Japan Kills Dozens...</title>
      <link>http://malaysiandigest.com/frontpage/29-4-tile/749028-record-setting-heatwave-in-japan-kills-dozens-as-temps-soar-to-40c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;malaysiandigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran dismisses Trump threat, says he 'won't dare' attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/iran-dismisses-trump-threat-says-he-wont-dare-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gen. Gholam Hossein Gheibparvar downplays US president's tweeted warning as simply 'psychological warfare' against Tehran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient boulder dislodges from Western Wall, crashes onto prayer platform...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/ancient-boulder-dislodges-from-western-wall-crashes-onto-egalitarian-plaza/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic footage shows large stone coming loose from revered site, shattering on platform below; no injuries reported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger pees on floor in cabin as plane refuels...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6842956/shocking-moment-female-passenger-wees-on-the-floor-of-a-wizz-air-flight-from-britain-to-poland-because-the-toilet-was-engaged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a female passenger squats and pees in the galley of a Wizz Air flight from the UK to Poland. The woman is seen relieving herself on the flight from London Luton to Warsa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers claim injuries all over bodies for big payouts -- but continue active lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/workers-claim-injuries-all-over-their-bodies-for-big-payouts/article_2eac03e0-6bf8-5e8e-9d55-2abb1b2e2487.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — After nearly two decades on the force, former LAPD Officer Jonathan Hall ended his career the way many veteran officers do these days, claiming job-related injuries across</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious creatures frozen for MILLENNIA holding lost secrets of past...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/717845/weird-news-ancient-history-mysterious-creatures-frozen-ice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought forces emergency measures for West's wild horses...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/drought-forces-emergency-measures-us-wests-wild-horses-56750967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harsh drought conditions in parts of the American West are pushing wild horses to the brink and spurring extreme measures to protect them. For what they say is the first time, volunteer groups in Arizona and Colorado are hauling thousands of gallons of water and truckloads of food to remote...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia has billions in sunken treasure off coast, but ownership disputed...</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/colombia-has-billions-in-sunken-treasure-off-its-coast-but/article_05925497-9c02-5a11-b336-443937f247c3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTA, Colombia—Sitting at the bottom of the ocean, just off Colombia’s coast, is one of the Western Hemisphere’s richest treasures: a Spanish galleon packed with billions of dollars worth of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert makes case for $400 barrel oil...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy/expert-makes-the-case-for-400-per-barrel-oil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new analysis shows oil prices could rise to $200 per barrel, and even higher, in the next 12 to 18 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tremors shove Washington westward, offer clues into next big quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/science/tremors-shove-washington-westward-offer-clues-into-next-big-earthquake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pacific Northwest last saw a big earthquake about 300 years ago. Scientists widely expect the region to experience a similar event every 500 years on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 9 injured after gunman opens fire in Toronto... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/at-least-9-injured-after-shooting-in-busy-toronto-neighbourhood-1.4023591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China robotic submarines to launch new sea power era...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2156361/china-developing-unmanned-ai-submarines-launch-new-era-sea-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unmanned AI subs, expected in the 2020s, could challenge the advantage Western naval powers have in strategic waters like the South China Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMLO Letter Floats 'New Relationship'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexicos-lopez-obrador-floats-idea-relationship-letter-trump-012622637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's incoming president on Sunday said he had floated the idea of a new relationship between the neighboring countries in a letter to US President Donald Trump. Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said he sent Trump proposals on bilateral relations -- which have reached one of their lowest points in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOWDY: If There Was Collusion, Schiff Would Have Leaked It...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2018/07/22/gowdy_if_there_was_evidence_that_president_trump_commited_any_crime_adam_schiff_would_have_leaked_it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Trey Gowdy told FNC's Bret Baier on FOX News Sunday that while there are documents he has not seen, he knows that if there were any evidence that President Trump committed any crime with regard to Russia "Adam Schiff would have leaked it."  Schiff, the top Democrat on the House Intelligence Committee, said this week that President Trump is compromised by the Russians, offering possible recordings of his meeting with Putin as evidence.   "I have not seen one scintilla of evidence that this president colluded, conspired, collaborated, with Russia. And neither has anyone else, or you can rest assured, Adam Schiff would have leaked it," Gowdy said. "That is why they have moved on from collusion on to obstruction of justice, which is now their current preoccupation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Clinton dinner with Weinstein after election...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5976133/PICTURED-Hillary-Clinton-having-dinner-Harvey-Weinstein-election-loss.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of Hillary Clinton having dinner with longtime pal Harvey Weinstein weeks after her election loss have emerged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUPERGIRL' to feature TV's first trans superhero...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/supergirl-feature-first-ever-transgender-superhero-2357819</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transgender activist and actor Nicole Maines will play Nia Nal in the fourth season of the show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at Mormon Church Leaves 1 Dead...</title>
      <link>https://fox13now.com/2018/07/22/two-people-injured-in-shooting-at-lds-church-in-fallon-nevada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox13now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FALLON, Nevada -- One person is dead and another injured after a shooting Sunday at a Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints meetinghouse in Fallon, Nev.  The shooting took place at the church located at 750 West Richards Street during services according to Kaitlin Richins, a spokeswoman for the City of Fallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest aircraft has GLASS floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cntraveler.com/story/the-worlds-largest-aircraft-will-have-luxurious-bedrooms-and-glass-floors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cntraveler.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Airlander 10 could take up to 19 passengers on three-day expeditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP Governor Touted As Potential DEM 2020 Candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/07/21/conservatives-wonder-there-any-republican-left-baker-moderate-republicanism/AEH1hTPFdgVkE3kYHkkJiK/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlie Baker’s record would be good for a Democrat. But he’s a Republican, and some conservatives are fuming he’s too far to the left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron cites 'ART OF DEAL' in negotiation pushback...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-turning-trump-tricks-against-him--e1fe83d1-d045-4747-afa9-01905696f59d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using his own set of predictable negotiating tricks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March honors Warsaw's Jews, activist who warned of genocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/march-honors-warsaws-jews-activist-warned-genocide-175505329.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Israel's ambassador to Poland has joined Warsaw residents in recalling the first mass deportations of Jews from the Warsaw Ghetto and in honoring a Jewish activist who took his own life while despairing the world's indifference to the Holocaust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostalgic for Brazil's dictatorship, Bolsonaro looks to presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nostalgic-brazils-dictatorship-bolsonaro-looks-presidency-135624300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angry Brazilians long for a return to order, and former army officer Jair Bolsonaro, a fan of the dictatorship that stretched from the 1960s to the 1980s, hopes to ride that wave into the presidency. Often labeled a Brazilian Donald Trump, Bolsonaro, 63, actually seems to enjoy offending his critics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High risk of 'losing control' of AIDS epidemic: experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/high-risk-losing-control-aids-epidemic-experts-164118164.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AIDS epidemic risks resurging and spiralling out of control unless billions of extra dollars are pumped into prevention and treatment, experts warned Sunday on the eve of a major world conference. An alarming rate of new infections, coupled with an exploding population of young people in hard-hit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The French village that is so rich the local will pay no taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-village-rich-local-pay-145451094.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State auditors have told a French village near the Spanish border that it is “too rich” to continue taxing residents and should cancel council and property taxes this year. Le Perthus, a community of 586 people, earns more than £700,000 a year from parking fees alone, equivalent to nearly £1,200 per</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censors jump into action as China's latest vaccine scandal ignites...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/censors-jump-action-chinas-latest-vaccine-scandal-ignites-130244024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese censors on Sunday deleted articles and postings about the vaccine industry as an online outcry over the country's latest vaccine scandal intensified. Regulators said last week that they had halted production of a rabies vaccine at a large pharmaceutical company in the northeast after finding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  STANDOFF AT LOS ANGELES TRADER JOE'S...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/21/kcal9-employee-tells-harrowing-story-of-being-held-hostage-inside-trader-joes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lynne Westafer spoke for about 20 minutes and related the fear and fright many inside were feeling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrist Dems begin arguing against far-left agenda... </title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/article215241865.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centrist Democrats met this week seeking to convince potential presidential candidates they don’t have to embrace key policies of the party’s liberal base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE:  'MAMMA MIA!' Flops, Hits All The Wrong Notes...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/mamma-mia-here-we-go-again-equalizer-2-summer-weekend-box-office-1202430132/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;6th Update, Sunday AM: With chart In a box office defeat that no one anticipated, Denzel Washington’s first sequel ever, Equalizer 2, stole most of the No. 1 money away from Universal’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is he handing off key cases?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/why-is-mueller-handing-off-key-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something has been going on with Robert Mueller's investigation of people thought to have played significant roles in the Trump-Russia affair. The special counsel, assigned to investigate "any links and/or coordination between the Russian government and individuals associated with the campaign of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY IN A HOUSECOAT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/what-is-she-wearing-hillary-clinton-looks-like-hell-at-ozyfest-in-new-york-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Central Park raccoons die from viral 'zombie' outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/21/dozens-of-raccoons-die-from-viral-zombie-outbreak-in-central-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen Central Park raccoons have died in an ongoing viral outbreak that causes “zombie” behavior in the critters, authorities determined. Of 26 raccoons found dead inside the park sin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dust Storm Invades Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/weather/dust-storm-invades-las-vegas-heat-wave-coming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Light sprinkles and intermittent showers are possible Saturday evening after gusts kicked up dusts in the morning, according to the National Weather Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US fighter jet intercepts plane near Trump resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article215313405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Air Force F-16 fighter jet on Saturday intercepted a small plane near Donald Trump's private golf resort in New Jersey, where the president is currently staying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINCLAIR fumbles imperil mega-merger...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/398149-sinclairs-fumbles-imperil-mega-merger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FCC's rejection of the deal is a striking reversal of fortune for the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TARGETS APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-targets-apple-with-push-into-advanced-smartphone-screens-1532260804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOE Technology Group, a supplier of screens for iPads and MacBooks, now wants to provide Apple with advanced organic light-emitting diode, or OLED, smartphone screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense bill to end Cabinet's direct control of nuclear agency...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/22/trump-administration-control-national-nuclear-secu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bill being negotiated in Congress would essentially end the Trump administration’s direct supervision of an agency that oversees the nation’s nuclear weapons stockpile. The Senate-approved bill would remove the National Nuclear Security Administration from direct control of the Energy Department, where it’s been since its creation in 2000, and empower it to act nearly on its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How long will Mueller investigation go on?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/22/politics/robert-mueller-russia-investigation-length/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week's indictments could be the high point for his team. Or it could be simply the crest of one of several coming waves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractor rampages through downtown Denver in police pursuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/22/tractor-pursuit-through-downtown-denver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Denver Police squad cars pursued a tractor through downtown Denver on Friday night before finally stopping it at 15th and Market streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Russian agent met with Obama Treasury, Fed officials...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-russia-butina-exclusive/exclusive-accused-russian-agent-butina-met-with-u-s-treasury-fed-officials-idUKKBN1KC0DE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused Russian agent Maria Butina had wider high-level contacts in Washington than previously known, taking part in 2015 meetings between a visiting Russian official and two senior officials at the U.S. Federal Reserve and Treasury Department.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
