<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SOON IN EVERY COUNTRY?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/28/coronavirus-latest-updates-outbreak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Friday, more than 83,700 cases of coronavirus have been reported, resulting in at least 2,859 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE MARKET MELTDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/dow-futures-fall-100-points-after-another-massive-rout-amid-coronavirus-fears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures pointed to more losses early Friday, after suffering a tumble that sent them more than 10% below their record highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY: SCHOOLS MAY NEED TO BE CLOSED...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/485114-white-house-chief-of-staff-claims-press-covering-coronavirus-to-take</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House acting chief of staff Mick Mulvaney on Friday downplayed the threat of the coronavirus but acknowledged likely school closures and disruptions to public transportation in the United States as a result of the outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not eating enough fruit and veg linked with increased risk of anxiety disorders...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/not-eating-enough-fruit-vegetables-linked-increased-risk-100725503.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Canadian research has found that eating less than three portions of fruit and vegetables per day appears to be linked to a higher risk of having an anxiety disorder. From the data, the researchers found that participants who ate less than three portions of fruit and veg per day had at least a 24</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli ex-general takes third jab at ousting Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israeli-ex-general-takes-third-jab-ousting-netanyahu-034526946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former armed forces chief Benny Gantz will take a fresh shot at unseating Israel's veteran Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Monday after two previous electoral showdowns ended in deadlock. The 60-year-old has been in the public eye since first declaring political ambitions and running against</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTBREAK GETTING BIGGER</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200228131609-4wyiy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/ (WRAPUP 10, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):WRAPUP 10-Coronavirus outbreak 'getting bigger', says WHO, warning of spread worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico confirms first cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a7d2aaac19fc3022ba686ba91e7d4395</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico's assistant health secretary announced Friday that the country now has two confirmed cases of the new coronavirus. Hugo Lopez-Gatell said one of the patients is in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazi cautionary dramas wade into political, factual disputes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/53222429335d067a738081756723c401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Hollywood mustered its creative forces in the 1940s when Adolf Hitler's Nazi Germany sought to conquer the world, with Humphrey Bogart standing up to the fascist regime in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Biden Campaign On The Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/02/28/810135605/joe-bidens-campaign-is-on-the-line-in-south-carolina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president got some promising results in polling leading into the primary this week. But even with a win, he still has lots of catching up to do to hope to win the nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss govt bans all events over 1,000 people...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/swiss-government-bans-all-events-over-1000-people-2020-02-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Swiss government announced an immediate ban Friday on all “public and private” events in the country involving more than 1,000 people as a measure to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputies shared graphic photos of Kobe Bryant crash scene, sources say...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-02-27/kobe-bryant-photos-lost-hills-sheriff-deputies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. Sheriff's Department says it is looking into reports that deputies shared graphic images of the Kobe Bryant helicopter crash scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new burger chef makes $3 an hour and never goes home. (It's a robot)...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/technology/story/2020-02-27/flippy-fast-food-restaurant-robot-arm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robotic arms like Flippy from Miso Robotics are getting cheap enough to make financial sense for low-wage work. But there's an argument in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey to allow Syrian refugees free access to Europe after troop attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/turkey-to-allow-syrian-refugees-free-access-to-europe-after-troop-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey said Friday that it ordered troops stationed along the Syrian border to stand down and allow refugees to cross into the European Union after a Syrian government airstrike killed 33 Turkish troops in what was seen as a major escalation in the conflict, a  report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Tom Brady open to new home in free agency...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28793123/sources-tom-brady-open-new-home-free-agency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is set on entering free agency and believes the process could lead to a new team, sources told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Near Mystery Case Worry and Wonder...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/28/its-scary-residents-near-mystery-coronavirus-case-worry-and-wonder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Thomas Fuller and Nicholas Bogel-Burroughs VACAVILLE, Calif. — In the parking lot of a big-box store, Rick Lodwick tossed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE CANCELS MORE EVENTS</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11061770/pope-francis-cancels-second-day-engagements-ill-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE Francis cancelled events for the a second day in a row today after falling ill. The Vatican said the 83-year-old pontiff had decided not to go ahead with official audiences after he skipped a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOG TESTS POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11060913/dog-coronavirus-test-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PET dog of a coronavirus patient has tested positive for the deadly disease. The owner of the dog, Yvonne Chow Hau Yee, who lives in Hong Kong with her beloved Pomeranian, tested her pet pooch …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The wizard that was Warhol...</title>
      <link>https://www.spectator.co.uk/2020/02/the-wizard-that-was-warhol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spectator.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1983 I was sent to New York to interview Johnny Rotten and I took the opportunity to call on Andy Warhol. The Factory was in the phonebook; and the receptionist, Brigid Berlin, said that Andy was…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of Super Tuesday, thousands attend Bernie rally in Richmond gym...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Sanders-rallies-supporters-in-Va-capital-ahead-15090429.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. - The thousands of people who showed up to a rally for Sen. Bernie Sanders five days before the Super Tuesday Democratic primaries did not come to size up the presidential candidate.  They were all in for Sanders, I-Vt., who was trounced in Virginia by Hillary Clinton four years ago, but who was tied for the lead with former New York mayor Mike Bloomberg in the most recent poll for this year's contest.  "I think that this candidate represents the best chance for substantive change that I've seen in my lifetime," said Kristin Reed, 41, a Virginia Commonwealth University professor. "This is really not just an election. This is a movement."  Also in the crowd was Zhue Azuaje, 27, who works for the American Civil Liberties Union in Richmond. "As a queer, Hispanic, immigrant woman, his campaign has really spoken to me," she said. "He has such a strong, diverse base."  Sanders began his remarks by apologizing to those who had to be turned aside from the huge gymnasium in the Arthur Ashe Junior Athletic Center. Campaign officials said the fire marshal estimated that 4,700 people attended the event.  "We will defeat the most dangerous president in the modern history of this country," he said, calling President Donald Trump a "pathological liar" who is running a "corrupt administration," and is "moving this country into an autocratic-type society."  "Trump, you're not going to get away with it," Sanders said to enormous cheers. "We're going to defeat you."  As he has throughout his two presidential campaigns, Sanders promised sweeping changes on many fronts, including education, immigration and criminal justice. On the last of those alone, he said he would end mass incarceration, private prisons and the "destructive war on drugs." He said on his first day in office, he would sign an executive order to legalize...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces growing crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/28/politics/donald-trump-coronavirus-miracle-stock-markets/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is hoping for a "miracle" that will make the coronavirus disappear but tanking stock markets and signs the disease is stalking America are delivering their verdict on his scattershot management of the crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California patient with UNKNOWN ORIGIN in serious condition...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/28/health/coronavirus-us-updates-california-patient/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California patient who tested positive for the coronavirus days after being hospitalized is in serious condition and intubated, California Rep. John Garamendi told CNN's Erin Burnett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKET MELTDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/28/stock-market-live-updates-dow-loses-3200-points-and-counting-on-week-bond-yields-collapsing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average, S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq points to losses at the open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of Girl Cheerfully Getting Abortion at PLANNED PARENTHOOD Draws Horror...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/02/27/tiktok-video-of-laughing-girl-having-abortion-at-planned-parenthood-draws-horror/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A widely viewed TikTok video shows a girl apparently having fun as she heads to Planned Parenthood for an abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans growing nervous about economy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/485078-republicans-growing-nervous-about-2020-economy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans who have been counting on a roaring economy to power President Trump and GOP congressional candidates on Election Day are growing nervous because of the economic havoc wreaked by the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pets face quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pet-dog-quarantined-hong-kong-low-levels-coronavirus-080902393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All pets of people in Hong Kong infected with the coronavirus will be quarantined, with one dog already in isolation, the city's authorities said Friday. The canine has been placed in quarantine for 14 days as a precaution but has no "relevant symptoms", Hong Kong officials said Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HITS MEGACITY LAGOS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nigeria-braces-coronavirus-hits-megacity-lagos-062857721.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Nigeria's economic hub Lagos scrambled for hygiene products Friday, after the chaotic megacity of 20 million announced the first confirmed case of new coronavirus in sub-Saharan Africa. Health Minister Osagie Ehanire said in a statement overnight that the infected person was an Italian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC ominous scenario: Healthcare systems 'overwhelmed'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cdc-outlined-ominous-hypothetical-scenario-214633263.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what the US could face in the coming months if the coronavirus spreads, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many exposed?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-bracing-spread-coronavirus-212128258.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California said Thursday it was monitoring some 8,400 people for the new coronavirus, after officials confirmed a woman had contracted the disease without traveling to outbreak-hit regions. Governor Gavin Newsom said travelers arriving from affected areas were being monitored and sought to reassure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I could fall to my death:' tightrope walker Wallenda readies to cross active volcano...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200227224041-5xefc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WALLENDA/VOLCANO (TV, PIX):'I could fall to my death:' tightrope walker Wallenda readies to cross active volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower: Feds helping evacuees lacked protection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c80d86633aa077b04ca430606c1e10fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A government whistleblower has filed a complaint alleging that some federal workers did not have the necessary protective gear or training when they were deployed to help...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA says Chinese ship fired laser at American aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a1b50c60545ae703817aa5a8fef730f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A Chinese Navy ship fired a laser at a U.S. surveillance aircraft flying over the Philippine Sea west of Guam, the Navy said Thursday, acknowledging the incident more than a week...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>56 COUNTRIES EXPOSED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d1a054f19cf1f33b4ee22c244603ebe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A deepening health crisis became an economic one too Friday, with the virus outbreak sapping financial markets, emptying shops and businesses, and putting major sites and events off...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California abnormally dry after low-precipitation winter...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/046e612fb07d262163e7ce8e7e9a5cd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A dry beginning of the year has left most of California abnormally parched, as officials brace for the possibility of an early and more intense wildfire season amid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle-area high school shuttered...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/27/bothell-high-school-closed-over-coronavirus-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suburban Seattle high school was closed Thursday after a staffer’s family member was placed in quarantine for showing symptoms of possibly contracting the new virus that started in China - an action health officials say is unnecessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force changes service anthem to gender-neutral lyrics...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/27/air-force-changes-service-anthem-gender-neutral-ly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force changed lyrics in its service anthem by dropping gender references that exclude women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPY AGENCIES MONITOR INDIA</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/china-health-usa-intelligence/u-s-spy-agencies-monitor-coronavirus-spread-concerns-about-india-sources-idUSL2N2AR1YG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. intelligence agencies are monitoring the global spread of coronavirus and t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School requires kids to dance with anyone who asks. Mom fighting for daughter's right to say 'no'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-middle-school-requires-kids-to-dance-with-anyone-who-asks-one-mom-is-fighting-for-her-daughters-right-to-say-no/ar-BB10sDxR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli scientists: Will have vaccine in weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/HEALTH-SCIENCE/Israeli-scientists-In-three-weeks-we-will-have-coronavirus-vaccine-619101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once the vaccine is developed, it will take at least 90 days to complete the regulatory process and potentially more to enter the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House GAGS govt health experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8052775/White-House-GAGS-government-health-experts-speaking-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government health experts now must coordinate their media appearances through Vice President Mike Pence's office under a new White House directive for dealing with coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scope of undetected U.S. spread unknown...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/02/27/a-single-coronavirus-case-exposes-a-bigger-problem-the-scope-of-undetected-u-s-spread-is-unknown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s clear that the virus is spreading undetected in the United States. But how broadly that is occurring is an utter mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman took 550x usual dose of LSD, with surprisingly positive consequences...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/27/health/lsd-overdoses-case-studies-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accidental drug overdoses can be life threatening but for two women who took massive hits of LSD the experience was life changing -- in a good way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Gov Says State Only Has 200 Testing Kits...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/02/27/gov-newsom-coronavirus-testing-kits-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Gavin Newsom said Thursday the state is monitoring about 8,400 people for the coronavirus, a day after a Solano County patient was identified as the first coronavirus case in the U.S. from unknown origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New witnesses implicate CIA operative, DEA official in murder plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/2020/02/27/enrique-camarena-dea-agent-murder-narcos-mexico/2566023001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities assess new witness claims that a DEA official and CIA operative were tied to DEA agent Enrique Camarena's 1985 murder in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panicked passengers get family kicked off flight over coughing daughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/463636/family-kicked-off-flight-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FAMILY of five say they were kicked off a plane just before takeoff over fears their coughing toddler could be infected with coronavirus. Canadian Emmanuel Faug, his wife Clémentine Ferraton and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to stop providing security for Harry, Meghan...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-royals-canada-idUSKCN20L2KH?taid=5e581b2809d31b0001388971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada will no longer provide security for Prince Harry and Meghan Markle, the C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHARK TANK' Star Loses $400K In Email Scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/barbara-corcoran-loses-388700-dollars-phishing-scam-shark-tank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Lesson learned: Be careful when you wire money!" she tweeted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Daily Life Could Change in USA...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/02/27/coronavirus-us-spread-daily-life-effects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How could the possible spread of coronavirus change our daily lives? Schools, businesses, hospitals and first responders could all be impacted, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army of 100,000 Chinese Ducks on Standby to Combat Locust Swarms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/army-of-100000-chinese-ducks-on-standby-to-combat-locust-swarms/ar-BB10s7K0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY cuts kissing scene from MULAN to appease Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8050961/Disney-cut-kissing-scene-Mulan-China-said-doesnt-feel-right-Chinese-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An early cut of the film featured Mulan sharing a kiss with her love interest, Chen. Disney has decided to remove the scene after their Chinese executives deemed it inappropriate, the director said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg releases new heart info; Calls on Sanders to do same...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/27/politics/michael-bloomberg-heart-health/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg's campaign disclosed new information on Thursday about the health of the presidential candidate's heart, and called on Bernie Sanders, who suffered a heart attack last year, to release the same data -- a clear attempt to bring the issue of the Democratic frontrunner's health to the forefront in the 2020 race for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA MONITORING 8,400</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/california-is-monitoring-8400-people-for-the-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski snubs French Oscars fearing 'lynching'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/polanski-snubs-french-oscars-fearing-lynching-161052163.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial film director Roman Polanski told AFP on Thursday he would not attend the French Oscars because he fears a "public lynching" by feminist activists. The veteran is at the centre of a storm of protest after his new film about the Dreyfus affair, "An Officer and a Spy"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange extradition hearing paused until May...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/assanges-uk-extradition-hearing-paused-until-may-165709477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British judge on Thursday paused Julian Assange's extradition hearing following four days of intense legal wrangling over Washington's request for the WikiLeaks founder to stand trial there on espionage charges. Judge Vanessa Baraitser, who will ultimately rule on the controversial case, ordered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infects Iranian Vice President, Kills Ambassador To Vatican...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/iranian-vice-president-infected-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could hit 80% of Brits in 'worst case scenario'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11041657/coronavirus-could-kill-500000-brits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR in five Brits could become infected by deadly coronavirus — with up to 500,000 killed, according to a doomsday scenario set out in official papers seen by The Sun. Ministers are now considerin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALPERIN: Murderers Treated More Fairly Than Canceled People...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/media/2020/02/mark-halperin-metoo-cancel-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disgraced pundit is now portraying himself as a victim. Of cancel culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>700 ASKED TO ISOLATE IN NY</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/02/26/coronavirus-update-de-blasio-cuomo-outline-preparations-in-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Health Department says 700 people in the state have been asked to voluntarily self-isolate for two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie's New Coalition Put to Test in SCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-sanders-coalition-put-test-164038803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders is investing heavily in South Carolina, visiting often and building a solid organization. But the question remains whether his newfound front-runner status and momentum will be enough to attract the coalition of minority voters he needs to do well there.Saturday’s Democratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Stolen Hearse With Body In Back Crashes After LAPD Chase On Freeway...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/02/27/lapd-pursuit-ends-in-wreck-on-110-freeway-in-south-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday evening, a Lincoln Navigator was stolen from in front of a Pasadena church. It contained a casket with a woman's body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Picks Top AIDS Official for Response...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pence-picks-top-u-aids-163417283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Vice President Mike Pence has selected the State Department’s top AIDS official, Deborah Birx, to join his coronavirus response team, his office announced on Thursday.Birx is a career government official who was nominated by former President Barack Obama in 2014 as the U.S. global AIDS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branson's Wealth Falls to Earth as VIRGIN GALACTIC Sputters...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/branson-wealth-falls-earth-virgin-150006098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wearing a black suit and harness, Richard Branson once leaped from the roof of a Las Vegas casino to launch one of his ventures.His fortune headed in the same direction this week.The value of the British billionaire’s stake in Virgin Galactic Holdings Inc. has fallen about $1.1 billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'UNCONVENTIONAL' ARMY EXERCISE SET FOR UNDISCLOSED SITES IN NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article240651992.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vexed by how to contain virus, countries take tough steps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1631a414cfba8ae39dee4b82748b129b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Saudi Arabia cut travel to Islam’s holiest sites, South Korea toughened penalties for those breaking quarantines and airports across Latin America looked for signs of sick...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty shelves hit USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.khon2.com/local-news/worries-over-panic-buying-arise-as-some-supply-shelves-at-stores-empty-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khon2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supplies were flying off the shelves Wednesday, with some shoppers taking pictures of empty shelves at stores across Oahu. This comes after a message from the Health Department to stock up on neces…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of gay killer: Why pop culture suddenly thirsty for queer blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/article/gay-serial-killers-murderers-tv-film-gianni-versace-dont-fuck-with-cats-9362656</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical staff exposed?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8051701/CDC-took-four-days-test-person-unknown-origin-coronavirus-case.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC reportedly took four days to test a person with the first confirmed case of coronavirus where the origin of the disease is unknown because they 'didn't fit the criteria'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus threatening to end world air-travel boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/coronavirus-raises-worries-about-a-broad-slowdown-in-air-travel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus will be a test for US airlines that have posted 10 consecutive years of profits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appeals court rules tech platforms can censor content...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/484916-federal-appeals-court-rules-tech-platforms-are-free-to-censor-content</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal appeals court on Wednesday ruled that internet giants like Google and Facebook can censor content on their platforms, rebuking arguments from conservatives who claim the tech companies violate users' First Amendment rights&amp;nbsp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearse with body in back stolen from church...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/hearse-carrying-body-stolen-from-california-church/5970854/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mortuary's Lincoln Navigator with a body in the back was stolen from a church in California, sheriff's deputies say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Arrested For Vile Cow Manure Battery...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/cow-manure-attack-672985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 27--A Florida Man was arrested yesterday on a felony battery charge after allegedly dumping a bucket of cow manure over the head of a victim, police report. According to a complaint affidavi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg already airs more ads than Hillary in all of '16...</title>
      <link>http://mediaproject.wesleyan.edu/releases-022620/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mediaproject.wesleyan.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts say should be prepared to see overnight boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/coronavirus-could-explode-in-the-us-overnight-like-it-did-in-italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for a serious test of broken American health infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO official slams Trump's 'ignorant and incoherent' response...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/461542/world-health-organization-official-lashes-out-donald-trumps-incoherent-ignorant-coronavirus-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOP WHO adviser has claimed Trump made “ignorant” and “incoherent” remarks during a news conference detailing the administration’s response to the coronavirus outbre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS: 14% of patients who recovered test positive again...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/coronavirus-bombshell-14-patients-who-21588972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recovered coronavirus patients discharged from hospitals in China's Guangdong province have later tested positive for the virus again - and nobody knows why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Joe holds wide lead ahead of primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/484901-poll-biden-holds-wide-lead-in-south-carolina-ahead-of-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden holds a wide 20-point lead over his closest rivals in South Carolina just days before the state’s Democratic presidential primary,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools shut, travel curbed as world races to fight...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200227142704-o5sk0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/ (WRAPUP 9, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):WRAPUP 9-Schools shut, travel curbed as world races to fight coronavirus</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
