<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pope writes to controversial nun, thanks her for 50 years of LGBTQ ministry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/pope-francis-writes-to-controversial-nun-thanking-her-for-50-years-of-lgbtq-ministry/ar-AASxYoi?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans adopted millions of dogs during the pandemic. Now what do we do with them?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/americans-adopted-millions-of-dogs-during-the-pandemic-now-what-do-we-do-with-them/ar-AASwPtf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Friday brings more than 2,600 flight cancellations as disruption stretches into third week...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Friday-brings-more-than-2-600-flight-16758178.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flight disruptions stretched into their third week on Friday with snow in the Northeast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODEL:  Wave peak mid-January...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2617194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Florida’s rocketing number of COVID-19 cases likely will peak by mid-January as the highly contagious omicron variant potentially infects most of the state’s population during this wave alone, according to disease modelers with the University of Florida’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffs of Maryland hospitals, stressed and sickened, know 'cavalry' isn't coming...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/staffs-maryland-hospitals-stressed-sickened-183300655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE — As COVID-19 hospitalizations climb into uncharted territory, fueled by the highly contagious omicron variant, Maryland’s medical work force is increasingly diminished by illness and exposure, burnout and turnover. Gov. Larry Hogan has responded with pleas for people to get vaccinated and boosted and wear masks to spare the hospitals. The state opened several testing sites near ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida breaks daily record again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-florida-breaks-daily-183700861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida reported 76,887 new COVID-19 cases on Friday, the highest daily number of the pandemic, and the number of hospital patients with the virus passed 9,000, according to data from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control. The increase in cases comes as a record 151,725 tests are being reported on average per day as of Dec. 30, the most recent data available for testing rates. The state’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes to Block Biden Mandate?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/07/politics/supreme-court-biden-vaccine-testing-mandate-covid-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court's conservative majority on Friday appeared ready to reject one of President Joe Biden's most aggressive attempts so far to combat the spread of Covid-19 -- a vaccine or testing requirement aimed at large businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POITIER DEAD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sidney-poitier-dead-214e66b7e52909bdc64465e9ff4a1339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sidney Poitier, the groundbreaking actor and enduring inspiration  who transformed how Black people were portrayed on screen, and became the first Black actor to win an Academy Award for best lead performance and the first to be a top box-office draw, has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic scenes in main city...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-59912794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BBC reporter sees the aftermath of protests and deadly violence in Kazakhstan's biggest city Almaty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman horrified by fellow plane passenger's text: 'We have Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/07/woman-divides-reddit-after-spying-on-covid-passengers-text/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A female passenger divided critics on Reddit after purporting to spot a fellow passenger’s text, in which they claimed to have contracted COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Investors Try to Turn Private Islands Into Blockchain Utopias...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3n38x/cryptocurrency-investors-try-to-turn-private-islands-into-blockchain-utopias</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptoland and Satoshi Island believe they'll become paradises where the cryptoeconomy can flourish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have archaeologists finally discovered long-lost temple of Hercules?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/article-691828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin STILL hasn't handed cellphone to cops despite search warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10377455/New-Mexico-New-York-police-work-Baldwin-phone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Mexico authorities on Thursday said they were working with police in New York to obtain material from Alec Baldwin's iPhone relating to an on-set fatal shooting of a cinematographer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew rape accuser 'unlikely to accept $5m pay off'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4414286/prince-andrew-virginia-roberts-unlikely-pay-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew’s rape accuser Virginia Roberts Giuffre is unlikely to accept a $5million (£3.7million) pay off because she wants to “send a message”. The Duke is currently waiting on tenterhooks for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom charged after teen found quarantining in car trunk...</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/news/local/2022/01/07/mom-charged-after-14-year-old-found-in-car-trunk-at-cy-fair-isd-drive-thru-covid-testing-site-das-office-confirms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mother has been charged after authorities said a child was found in the trunk of a car at a Cy-Fair ISD drive-thru COVID testing site, Harris County District Attorney’s Office confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sotomayor Exaggerates Severe Cases Among Children...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/07/sotomayor-severe-covid-children-oral-arguments-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court heard oral arguments Friday on whether to prevent the Biden administration's vaccine mandate for private workplaces from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Drives Racial Rationing of Therapeutics...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/coronavirus/food-and-drug-administration-drives-racial-rationing-of-covid-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In New York, racial minorities are automatically eligible for scarce COVID-19 treatment, regardless of age or underlying conditions. In Utah, "Latinx ethnicity" counts for more points than "congestive heart failure" in a patient’s "COVID-19 risk score"—the state’s framework for allocating monoclonal antibodies. And in Minnesota, health officials have devised their own "ethical framework" that prioritizes black 18-year-olds over white 64-year-olds—even though the latter are at much higher risk of severe disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fingerprints Could Lead To Treatment For Disorders?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gene-causes-humans-fingerprints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say this gene -- responsible for the circular, wavy, or winding patterns on your fingertips -- also fuels limb development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala admits 'level of malaise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10379439/Kamala-Harris-admits-level-malaise-two-years-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris told PBS 'there is a level of malaise' in the country amid the coronavirus pandemic, invoking a word associated with Jimmy Carter's speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIDNEY POITIER DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4414838/sidney-poitier-dead-lilies-of-the-field-actor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LILIES of the Field actor Sidney Poitier, the first black man to win a Best Actor Oscar, has passed away at 94. The Academy Award winner’s death was confirmed on Friday by Bahamas Minister of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swimsuit model stalked with APPLE AirTag...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/brooks-nader-sports-illustrated-swimsuit-model-says-apple-airtag-used-to-track-her-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sports Illustrated Swimsuit model Brooks Nader says she was tracked with an Apple AirTag a stranger slipped into her coat at a Manhattan bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIVIL RIGHTS ADVOCATE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10379329/Sir-Sidney-Poitier-dead-94.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poitier's trailblazing acting career saw win an Oscar in 1964 for Lilies of the Field. His cause of death is not yet known. Twice-married, he had four daughters with his first wife and two with his second wife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Tulip: Inside FACEBOOK's Secretive Push To Build Holland's Biggest Data Center...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/amansethi/operation-tulip-inside-facebooks-secretive-push-to-build</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a wild twist, Facebook demanded that its data center be designated a project of “national importance.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST BLACK BEST ACTOR OSCAR WINNER</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/07/beloved-actor-sidney-poitier-dead-at-94/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary actor Sidney Poitier, whose 71-year career included iconic roles in the classic Hollywood films “A Raisin in the Sun,” “Guess Who’s Coming to Dinner” and “Uptown Saturday Night,” has died…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayor taps younger brother as deputy police commissioner...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/07/adams-taps-younger-brother-bernard-as-a-deputy-nypd-commissioner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernard Adams, a 56-year-old retired NYPD officer, said he will oversee governmental affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seaweed Emerges As Latest 'Weapon' Against Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/seaweed-extract-prevent-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors are hopeful their discovery will lead to a new drug that can stop new COVID variants from spreading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quebec to require vaccine proof for cannabis, liquor shoppers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-59915459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The measure is just one of several the province is taking to stem the rising tide of new cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 bodies stuffed into SUV outside Mexico palace...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/ten-bodies-stuffed-into-an-suv-and-parked-outside-governors-palace-in-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe tightens screws on unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/unwelcome-just-everywhere-europe-tightens-100027622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From mandating COVID-19 shots for everyone over 50 to excluding the uninoculated from more venues, European countries get tougher on the unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Planned Parenthood Clinic Up in Flames. It Was Arson...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjbjxm/planned-parenthood-east-tennesee-fire-arson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in Tennessee are offering a reward of up to $10,000 for information that leads to prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Gov to require all health care workers to get boosted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/omicron-variant-coronavirus-news-01-07-22/h_4a709d47776865488df42e8bc479da3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Countries around the world are grappling with a surge in Covid-19 cases, leading to increased restrictions in many places. Follow here for the latest news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant spots 'v-shaped UFO' from AIRBUS cockpit......</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4414855/v-shaped-ufo-flies-above-passenger-jet-planes-cockpit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a flight attendant spotted a V-shaped UFO flying above an Airbus A230 passenger jet. The extraordinary footage was captured from the cockpit at 39,000ft by a sky-watchin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's 'mini-Nato' intervenes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20220107-russia-s-mini-nato-intervenes-in-kazakhstan-amid-growing-turmoil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with mounting unrest, Kazahkstan's government appealed overnight to the Collective Security Treaty Organisation (CSTO) for military aid against what it called "terrorist groups". Here is what y…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online troll arrested after threatening Piers Morgan...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tv/17244088/piers-morgan-and-son-death-threats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIERS Morgan last night insisted “We must draw a line on trolls” as it emerged a suspect has been arrested for making death threats against him. Officers from two of the country’s biggest police fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men convicted of Ahmaud Arberys murder to be sentenced... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/07/us/ahmaud-arbery-sentencing-killers-mcmichael-bryan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three White men who chased and murdered Ahmaud Arbery in south Georgia returned to court Friday to learn whether they'll spend their lives in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITIGROUP to Fire Unjabbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/citigroup-confronts-vaccine-holdouts-in-no-jab-no-job-mandate-1.1704463</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citigroup Inc. was the first major Wall Street bank to impose a strict Covid-19 vaccine mandate: Get a shot or face termination. With its deadline fast approaching, the company is preparing for action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA checkpoints close as personnel infected...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/588707-arizona-tsa-checkpoints-close-due-to-covid-19-staffing-issues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport will be temporarily closing several security checkpoints starting Friday due to Transportation Security Administration (TSA) staffing issues tied to the COVID-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's 'Death Trap' Underground Tunnel Hit With Traffic Jam...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/technology/elon-musks-death-trap-underground-vegas-tunnel-hit-traffic-jam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Sure You Want to Live to 150?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2022/01/live-to-150-life-expectancy-extension/621190/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I accept a high probability that weather and climate will be the cause of my death.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis star breaks silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4414299/novak-djokovic-breaks-silence-claim-world-support-vax-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TENNIS star Novak Djokovic has finally broken his silence as the vaccine row continues while he remains holed up in a Covid quarantine hotel. The anti-vax World No 1 thanked his supporters “a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They need to process rapids, PCRs. They're out sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/07/covid-testing-staff-shortage-526701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the supply chain for once-scarce equipment remains intact, the sheer demand for testing is stretching sample collection sites and laboratory staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S runs out of hash browns...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220107-mcdonald-s-runs-out-of-hash-browns-in-some-taiwan-stores</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald's Taiwan said Friday some of its stores were running out of hash browns imported from the United States and would have to suspend sales due to "unstable global shipping supply".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA entrepreneur atest target of city's home invader burglars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10377617/Wealthy-LA-entrepreneur-latest-victim-citys-terrifying-home-invasion-robberies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mansion of wealthy LA entrepreneur, Florence Mirsky, co-founder of Koko Nuggz, was raided by three arm burglars at around 2a.m. Thursday after they zip-tied two housesitters, LAPD said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most expensive home in America lists for $295 million, may head to auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/07/most-expensive-home-in-america-lists-for-295-million-may-head-to-auction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Along with a record-setting price, the property known as "The One," in the Bel Air section of Los Angeles, comes with a history of drama, lawsuits and debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers partied maskless on charter flight to Mexico. Airlines refusing to fly home...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/canadian-influencers-partied-maskless-plane-084557583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three Canadian airlines have declined to accommodate the 100 party-goers after videos surfaced of their maskless bash in the skies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
