<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NRA shows signs of decline, even in Trump's America...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/national-rifle-association-decline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group’s own tax forms show a dip in revenue. And after decades of ever more deadly mass shootings, opponents of gun violence have been on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'BLADE RUNNER' and 'RUNNING MAN' predicted 2019 -- decades ago...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/02/how-blade-runner-and-the-running-man-predicted-our-lives-decades-ago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the future. Two classic science-fiction films — “Blade Runner” and “The Running Man” — are both set in 2019, and although the films envisioned a few details that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Maher Taking Heat for POPEYE'S Chicken Joke to Black Congressman...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/02/bill-maher-popeyes-chicken-racist-joke-black-congressman-will-hurd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Maher's at it again: he made yet another joke on his show many people are calling racist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unveils Pharaonic tomb, home to 50 mummies...</title>
      <link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2019/0202/1027143-egypt-pharaoh-tomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rte.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egyptian archaeologists have uncovered a tomb related to the Pharaohs containing 50 mummies dating back to the Ptolemaic era, in Minya, south of Cairo, the ministry of antiquities has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirchner comeback?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-argentina-election-fernandez-exclusiv/exclusive-argentinas-fernandez-plans-election-run-against-macri-sources-idUSKCN1PQ5RB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Argentine President Cristina Fernández de Kirchner intends to run for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA agent commits suicide at Orlando Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/florida/security-issue-at-orlando-airport-halts-flights-officials-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Transportation Security Administration agent was killed Saturday morning after jumping from a hotel balcony into the atrium of Orlando International Airport, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls for resignation build...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/428191-pelosi-calls-on-northam-to-step-aside-photo-is-contrary-to-fundamental</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) called on Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam (D) to "do the right thing" following a photo that surfaced Friday showing a man wearing blackface and another dressed in a Ku Klux Klan robe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto sees stock fall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/428083-beto-orourke-sees-stock-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O'Rourke has seen his stock fall in the last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS, RAMS ready for Super Bowl generation game...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/patriots-rams-ready-super-bowl-generation-game-015749625--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady will chase a record-breaking sixth Super Bowl crown on Sunday as the New England Patriots take on the Los Angeles Rams in a clash of the generations set to rewrite NFL history. Patriots star Brady, 41, will become the oldest quarterback ever to lift the title if he masterminds yet another</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy-plagued halftime show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/super-bowl-liii-halftime-controversy-continues-as-colin-kaepernick-attorney-attacks-adam-levine-1202548192/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversy surrounding Super Bowl LIII’s halftime show continues, as Colin Kaepernick’s attorney Mark Geragos called Maroon 5 frontman Adam Levine’s rationalization on his pa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northam backtracks after apology...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/northam-backtracks-on-whether-he-is-in-racist-photo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embattled Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam has said privately he does not think he is in the racist photo from his 1984 medical school yearbook, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considering facial recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/02/us/politics/ralph-northam-virginia-governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Northam, increasingly isolated over a yearbook photo showing two people in blackface and Ku Klux Klan robes, was calling fellow Democrats to say he did not think it was him in the photo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA GOV NOW SAYS NOT HIM IN PHOTO</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6660879/Democrat-Virginia-Governor-DENIES-hes-racist-yearbook-picture-featuring-blackface-KKK-robe.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Governor Ralph Northam now denies appearing in a racist photograph that he on Friday apologized for Senator Louise Lucas said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims yearbook mix up?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/02/politics/northam-racist-yearbook-photo/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam has told a source he now believes it is not him in a racist yearbook photo and, despite mounting pressure to resign, that he will not do so, according a top Virginia Democratic source who spoke to the governor on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIXIE DRAMA</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/347ad6bd706c48febcac1903b40dc24c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A Virginia Democrat who has spoken with Gov. Ralph Northam has told The Associated Press that the governor now does not believe he was in a racist picture in his 1984 medical yearbook and has no immediate plans to resign. The official was not authorized to speak on the record to detail a private conversation. The official told the AP on Saturday that Northam plans to address the issue with the public in the afternoon. Northam is calling Virginia Democrats to try and gain support. Nearly his entire political base has called for him to resign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WON'T RESIGN</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/virginia-democrat-says-gov-northam-wont-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) &amp;mdash; A Virginia Democrat who has spoken with Gov. Ralph Northam has told The Associated Press that the governor now does not believe he was in a racist picture in his 1984 medical yearbook and has no immediate plans to resign. The official was not authorized to speak on the record to detail a private conversation. The official told the AP on Saturday that Northam plans to address the issue with the public in the afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutiny at Central Bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-02-02/mutiny-breaks-out-venezuelas-central-bank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won't Resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/virginia-democrats-demand-northam-resign-but-add-that-he-does-not-plan-to-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran in 'successful test' of new cruise missile on revolution anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190202-iran-successful-test-new-cruise-missile-revolution-anniversary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran in 'successful test' of new cruise missile on revolution anniversary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First defection...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ad2a17edc5dd4421b2d28935ee66e9b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — A Venezuelan air force general defected from the administration of President Nicolas Maduro on Saturday and called on his compatriots to participate in protests against the socialist leader's rule. Gen. Francisco Yanez is the first high ranking officer to leave Maduro's government since Jan. 23, when National Assembly President Juan Guaido declared himself the country's legitimate leader. In a YouTube video, Yanez said: "The transition to democracy is imminent." He described Maduro as a dictator and referred to Guaido as his president, but refused to say whether he is still in Venezuela or has left the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Private Lunar Spacecraft Shoots for Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/43209-first-private-spacecraft-shoots-for-the-moon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The private space race is about to take another great leap as Israel sends a private lander to the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Superhuman' robots will outstrip mankind within 50 years, warns AI expert...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1080843/robot-news-latest-artificial-intelligence-ai-superhuman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROBOTS will be in a position to outstrip the abilities of mankind within half a century, an expert in artificial intelligence has warned, stressing it was vital to introduce safeguards to prevent mankind being “replaced”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to suspend nuke treaty after Trump pulls out...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/15881e8900db4c4eaae3d84bb2500041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Following in the footsteps of the U.S., Russia will abandon a centerpiece nuclear arms treaty but will only deploy intermediate-range nuclear missiles if Washington does so, President Vladimir Putin said Saturday. U.S. President Donald Trump accused Moscow on Friday of violating the 1987 Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces treaty with "impunity" by deploying banned missiles. Trump said in a statement that the U.S. will "move forward" with developing its own military response options to Russia's deployment of banned cruise missiles that could target Western Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran unveils long-range cruise missile on revolution anniversary...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190202084438-0lkva</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-REVOLUTION/ANNIVERSARY-MISSILES (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Iran unveils long-range cruise missile on revolution anniversary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'COONMAN'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ralph-northams-yearbook-page-shows-man-in-kkk-costume-and-another-apparently-in-blackface/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Northam's 1984 medical school yearbook page shows two men, one of whom is wearing a Ku Klux Klan costume and the other in what appears to be blackface</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIXIE DRAMA</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f902e4ea080f415eb2e09d1022110688</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam acknowledged Friday that he appears in a photo on his 1984 medical school yearbook page that shows a person in blackface and another wearing a Ku Klux Klan robe. The revelation of the photograph prompted state Republicans and two Democratic presidential candidates to call for his resignation. Northam quickly apologized. The Democratic governor confirmed in a statement that he was in the photo wearing a costume "that is clearly racist and offensive." Northam did not say which costume he was wearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YEARBOOK DRAMA: VA GOV 'DEEPLY SORRY'</title>
      <link>https://www.wric.com/news/virginia-news/gov-northam-confirms-controversial-yearbook-photo-i-am-deeply-sorry-for-the-decision-/1745988427</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wric.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A photo released on Friday afternoon of Governor Ralph Northam's 1984 yearbook page from Eastern Virginia Medical School shows two men, one in blackface and another in a KKK robe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Kaepernick Super Bowl ad rejected...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/cbs-rejects-pro-flag-anti-kaepernick-just-stand-super-bowl-ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran-owned apparel company’s pro-flag Super Bowl TV ad that punches back at Nike's promotion of Colin Kaepernick and his national anthem protests has been rejected by CBS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRET EASTON ELLIS:   'BLACK PANTHER' Oscar Nomination  About Race, Not Quality...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bret-easton-ellis-questions-black-panther-oscar-nomination-for-best-picture-does-it-really-deserve-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bret Easton Ellis thinks "Black Panther" may owe its Best Picture Oscar nomination to Hollywood's emphasis on diversity - not to its quality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lasers could beam messages directly to a listener's ear...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8335749/lasers-could-beam-messages-directly-to-a-listeners-ear-like-whispering-secret-from-afar-scientists-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LASERS could be able to beam messages directly to a listener’s ear, like “whispering a secret from afar”, according to scientists in the US. The laser interacts with water vapour …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 HOURS INTERNET CUT-OFF FOR KIDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8334713/official-guidelines-kids-social-media-use/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILDREN should be limited to just two hours-a-time on social media – new official advice will declare next week. In the first formal guidelines ever, the Chief Medical Officer will pile huge press…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Experiments To Gene-Edit Human Embryos...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/02/01/689623550/new-u-s-experiments-aim-to-create-gene-edited-human-embryos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite outrage over gene editing in China that affected the birth of twins, research is underway in the U.S. to assess the safety and effectiveness of CRISPR tools to edit genes in human embryos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKFACE OR KKK?</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/virginia/article_67fdd682-2662-11e9-a7d1-c7ed70e09b50.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The photo, from the Eastern Virginia Medical School 1984 yearbook, led to calls for the Democratic governor's resignation from both sides of the aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake University Part Of ICE Sting; 130 Foreign 'Students' Arrested...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/02/01/fake-farmington-hills-university-leads-to-130-arrests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At first glance it all seemed real. The University of Farmington boasted that its “innovative curriculum combines traditional instruction and distance learning with full-time professional experiences.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX and FOX Legal War Over Executives Heading To Trial...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/netflix-fox-lawsuit-poaching-executives-trial-date-1202547835/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox and Netflix’s long legal dust-up over the streamer’s snatching of two executives almost three years ago is heating up as the former attempts to get the upcoming trial pushed back and the sparri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Restaurant Owner Apologizes For 'MAGA' Hat Ban...</title>
      <link>http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/02/01/san-mateo-restaurant-apologizes-trump-maga-hat-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Mateo restaurant owner has apologized after saying he would ban patrons who wear "Make America Great Again" hats to his establishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: VICE, BUZZFEED and the New-Media Reckoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/vice-media-cuts-250-jobs-or-10-of-workforce-11549033923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice Media’s cut of 250 jobs, or 10% of its workforce, is the latest digital media retrenchment amid an increasingly difficult online-ad market and pressure from investors who expected red-hot returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Northam Refused to Shake Black Opponent's Hand...</title>
      <link>https://bigleaguepolitics.com/watch-ralph-northam-refuses-to-shake-his-black-opponents-hand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bigleaguepolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After missing recruit goal, ARMY hopes rap video will attract Gen-Z...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/the-army-needs-to-recruit-more-gen-z-ers-and-it-s-turning-to-recruiters-rap-to-do-it-1.566927</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army is revamping the way it recruits future soldiers after missing its recruiting goal in 2018 for the first time in more than a decade, and the service is – at least in part – turning to rap music to pique the interest of Generation Z.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What APPLE Censors for China Exposed...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/02/01/apple-apps-china-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The site shows which apps — from human rights groups, the New York Times, and virtual private networks — have been removed from Apple's app store in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS: Jewish Republican accuses Muslim Dem of anti-Semitism, she accuses him of Islamophobia...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/a-jewish-republican-accused-a-muslim-democrat-of-anti-semitism-she-accused-him-of-islamophobia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reps. Lee Zeldin, R-N.Y., and Ilhan Omar, D-Minn., traded accusations of antisemitism and Islamophobia in a week-long Twitter spat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist has organs 'stolen' in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/travel/world-travel/north-america/man-who-died-in-mexico-flown-home-without-brain-stomach-and-heart/news-story/6474b0c9a1131613c48d4101a23da44c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of a Korean man who died in Mexico of “natural causes” has been flown home with missing organs, prompting his widow to speak out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech A.I. Devices Predict Winner...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/01/who-will-win-the-super-bowl-according-to-siri-google-and-alexa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I asked Siri, Google Assistant, Alexa and Cortana who will win the Super Bowl. Here's what they said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Competitive Eating Queen: Downs 501 wings in 30 mins!</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2816647-all-hail-molly-schuyler-the-dark-queen-of-competitive-eating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hang on, folks. I've just received word. Molly Schuyler has landed. She is on her way. I repeat, she is en route...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
