<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Success Driven by Hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquiremore.com/p/social-media-success-is-driven-by</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquiremore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expressing animosity towards outgroups drives engagement, new research finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest Tax Increase in San Fran History Now Funding $60,000 Tents for Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/06/25/critics-warned-the-largest-tax-increase-in-san-francisco-history-would-be-ill-spent-its-now-funding-60000-tents-for-the-homeless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco politicians are raising eyebrows at the high costs of an emergency program that provides secure camping sites to the city's homeless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takedown of Iran Media Sites Extends Thorny Precedent...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/us-iran-media-sites-takedown-doj-press-freedom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Free speech advocates raised concerns after the Justice Department seized more than 30 domains this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stem cells for Covid mostly shot in dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/25/for-now-stem-cells-for-covid-19-are-mostly-a-shot-in-the-dark/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some researchers, and a few charlatans, are turning to stem cells as a treatment for Covid-19. So far there's no solid proof that they work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids Test Positive on ROYAL CARIBBEAN Cruise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/two-kids-test-positive-for-covid-on-royal-caribbean-cruise/ar-AALpwvs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royal Caribbean Cruises Ltd. said two unvaccinated children on the Adventure of the Seas turned up positive for Covid-19 following routine testing that’s required before returning home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine-linked heart condition tends to 'resolve quickly'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210625180116-f4fw9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SCIENCE (GRAPHICS):COVID SCIENCE-Vaccine-linked heart condition tends to resolve quickly; Delta variant fuses cells to infect more efficiently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregonians Receive Ominous Letters for Flying 'Black Lives Matter' Flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/oregon-residents-receive-ominous-letters-flying-black-lives-matter-flag-1604265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Thank you for flying the BLM flag. It will make it easier to identify who is a socialist, racist, woke and un-American when the fighting breaks out," an anonymous letter said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida to send 50 law enforcement officers to Texas border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-to-send-50-law-enforcement-officers-to-texas-border/ar-AALs9g1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BUILDINGS AT RISK</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9723841/Map-report-predicting-condo-collapse-reveals-Miami-Beach-spots-risk-collapse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The report that detailed that the Champlain Towers South building was sinking before its horrific collapse had described other areas in Miami Beach where buildings could be at risk of collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Acquires Encrypted Messaging App...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epnapp/amazon-acquires-encrypted-messaging-app-wickr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wickr is a popular encrypted messaging platform used by journalists, criminals, governments, and businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Worst day ever' in pigeon racing history as 5,000 birds vanish...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/25/worst-day-ever-for-pigeon-racing-as-5000-birds-vanish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bird handlers were devastated after a mind-boggling 5,000 homing pigeons seemingly disappeared during a race across the UK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police thwart multiple terror attacks on Tel Aviv Pride parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/police-arrest-armed-man-on-his-way-to-attack-pride-parade-672021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The police made arrests in two incidents where people bearing weapons approached the parade area. Other non-violent disruptors were also arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAfee death sparks conspiracies...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3156537/john-mcafee-death-sparks-activated-dead-mans-qanon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHN McAfee’s death has sparked wild conspiracies that the tech guru activated a so called “dead man’s switch” to expose the government. Prominent QAnon supporters say the m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE boss says company 'is of China and for China'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-57606588</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sportswear giant was recently hit by a backlash over statements on Xinjiang and the Uyghurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN:  Prosecutors Already Have Enough Evidence to Indict Donald...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/michael-cohen-tells-jimmy-kimmel-that-manhattan-prosecutors-already-have-enough-evidence-to-charge-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen told Jimmy Kimmel on Thursday that Manhattan prosecutors investigating the Trump Organization have the evidence needed to press criminal charges -- whether or not the company's executives flip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wurzburg horror: At least 3 dead after violent assault... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1454668/Wurzburg-attack-Germany-knife-latest-update-Police-city-injured-suspect-shot-terror-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEVERAL people have been wounded following reports of a knife attack in the German city of Wurzburg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Republicans move away from capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/americas-continued-move-toward-socialism-84a0dda7-4b8d-483a-8c4e-0c2e562c4e67.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socialism is getting more popular, and capitalism is fading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson calls Joint Chiefs chairman a 'pig,' 'stupid'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/560209-tucker-carlson-lashes-out-at-milley-not-just-a-pig-hes-stupid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Tucker Carlson sharply criticized the chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff on Thursday, calling him a "pig" and "stupid" and saying he got his job because he was obsequious and told his superiors what</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is BUZZFEED Really Worth $1.5 BILLION?!</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/buzzfeed-ecommerce-analysis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed announced plans to go public via a SPAC on Thursday -- and in one neat move, redefined itself as a tech rather than a content company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Justice Dept suing GA over voting laws...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ga-state-wire-georgia-voting-rights-laws-voting-c552e88d294e5f35e2eea595177bc4b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department is suing Georgia over the state's voting laws, a person familiar with the matter said Friday. The announcement will be made later Friday by Attorney General Merrick Garland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top GOP pollster: To win, we need Trump to disappear...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/top-gop-pollster-to-win-we-need-trump-to-go-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is some good news for House and Senate Republicans in the latest Battleground Civility Poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Seattle and Portland may smash all-time temp records... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/111-degrees-forecast-in-portland-as-life-threatening-heat-looms/968046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All-time records will be shattered across the Northwest as an extreme heat wave sends temperatures to dangerously high levels. Seattle is forecast to hit triple digits too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAX 113&amp;#8457;!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2021-06-22-northwest-dangerous-record-heat-late-june</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's increasingly likely this heat wave will rewrite the record books in places not accustomed to such extreme heat. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colosseum's underground labyrinth restored to eerie splendor...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210625-colosseum-s-underground-labyrinth-restored-to-eerie-splendour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colosseum's underground labyrinth restored to eerie splendour</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE takes down China 'internment camp' videos...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210625132416-55sa5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atajurt Kazakh Human Rights' channel, which published nearly 11,000 videos on YouTube totaling over 120 million views has been blocked for violating policy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressmen Squirm as Gaetz Continues to Roam...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/congressmen-squirm-world-class-sleazeball-001238698.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastMatt Gaetz is currently stuck somewhere between a Greek tragedy and one of Shirley Jackson’s dark short stories.Every day Congress is in session, he walks the marbled halls like any other lawmaker. He votes. He attends committee hearings. Questions witnesses. Even pops up on the Senate side with his fiancé from time to time.But all the while, the sword of Damocles hangs over Gaetz: Any day could be his last as a free man for a very long time.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liam Neeson's surprising second act...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/the-surprisingly-durable-second-act-of-liam-neeson/ar-AALr3JH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix’s “The Ice Road” is the latest release from Liam Neeson, who has reshaped his career as an old-school action hero since “Taken.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia launches Mediterranean drills amid rift with Britain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-europe-russia-government-and-politics-bb56dbd5334210b8013fc998f6f108a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The Russian military on Friday launched sweeping maneuvers in the Mediterranean Sea featuring warplanes capable of carrying hypersonic missiles, a show of force amid a surge in tensions following an incident with a British destroyer in the Black Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Scientist Readying for First Contact...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5gdpb/meet-the-scientist-who-is-preparing-for-humanitys-first-contact-with-aliens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Garrett, director of the Jodrell Bank Centre for Astrophysics, talks about the effort to prepare for contact with alien life in Motherboard’s “Space Show.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAfee widow says he was not suicidal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/john-mcafee-europe-business-technology-c3a6940808a8dd86a59ed71df0ff3fc2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANT ESTEVE SESROVIRES, Spain (AP) — The widow of John McAfee, the British-American tycoon who died in a Spanish prison this week while awaiting extradition to the United States, said Friday that her husband was not suicidal when she last spoke to him hours before he was found dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin traders 'vanish with $3.4 BILLION'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15390502/bitcoin-brothers-vanish-with-2-5billion-in-investor-funds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO South African brothers who launched a bitcoin business from their bedroom and gathered £2.5billion in funds have vanished in what is suspected to be the biggest crypto heist in history. Raees a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly shooting at swanky Hollywood Hills party...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3155902/blue-jay-shooting-hollywood-hills-party-one-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE person was allegedly killed and five were hurt as three men tried to rob a home in Hollywood Hills. Officers responded to reports of a shooting at a multi-million dollar home just before 2am. W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-life Tarzan lived 41 years not knowing women existed, ate rat heads...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/real-life-tarzan-lived-41-24396739</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ho Van Lang, 49, now lives in a small Vietnamese village where he is adapting to living among other people. He and his family fled civilisation during the Vietnam war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key inflation indicator posts biggest year-over-year gain in three decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/25/key-inflation-indicator-rises-3point4percent-in-may-from-a-year-earlier-as-expected.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key inflation indicator that the Federal Reserve uses to set policy rose 3.4% in May, the fastest increase since the early 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Most say restrict abortion after 1st trimester...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-us-supreme-court-abortion-religion-health-2c569aa7934233af8e00bef4520a8fa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A solid majority of Americans believe most abortions should be legal in the first three months of a woman’s pregnancy, but most say the procedure should usually be illegal in the second and third trimesters, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA caravan tried to run Biden bus off road. Now sued under anti-KKK act...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-caravan-of-trump-backers-tried-to-run-a-biden-bus-off-a-road-now-they-e2-80-99re-being-sued-under-an-anti-kkk-act/ar-AALrdrP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A White House staffer, former Texas state representative and Biden campaign workers are suing several members of the “Trump Train” caravan, as well as San Marcos, Tex., law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv defies virus to party with Pride...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210625-tel-aviv-defies-virus-to-party-with-pride</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tel Aviv defies virus to party with Pride</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 DEAD, 159  MISSING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/florida-condo-collapse-285cbfbfca14594b6f69ff3301e7a487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — About 160 people were still unaccounted for Friday a day after an oceanside condominium building collapsed into a pile of rubble, and searchers combing through a twisted, shifting pile of concrete and metal feared the death toll of at least four could go much higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man admitted storming Capitol. Then told FBI his pastor had come with him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-florida-man-admitted-storming-the-capitol-feds-say-then-he-told-the-fbi-his-pastor-had-come-with-him/ar-AALrccq </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange fiancée urges Biden to free WIKILEAKS founder...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210625075709-ib8pj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WIKILEAKS-ASSANGE/MORIS (PIX, TV):Assange's fiancée urges Biden to free WikiLeaks founder to show U.S. has changed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Normalizing' UFOs. Retired Navy pilot recalls Tic Tac encounter...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210625023847-hni7q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-UFOS/PILOT (TV, PIX):'Normalizing' UFOs - retired U.S. Navy pilot recalls Tic Tac encounter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauvin could face decadeslong sentence in Floyd death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/derek-chauvin-sentencing-23c52021812168c579b3886f8139c73d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Former Minneapolis police Officer Derek Chauvin learns his sentence Friday for murder in George Floyd' s death, closing a chapter in a case that sparked global outrage and a reckoning on racial disparities in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 DEAD, 99  MISSING</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/biden-approves-florida-emergency-declaration-deadly-building-collapse/story?id=78482598</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden approved a Florida emergency declaration after a deadly building collapse left three dead and up to 99 missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC gets green light to fly passengers to space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/25/virgin-galactic-receives-faa-license-to-fly-passengers-to-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic announced on Friday that the Federal Aviation Administration granted the company with the license it needs to fly passengers on spaceflights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test to detect 50 types of cancer...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/blood-test-detect-50-types-230100925.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The test is based on a type of DNA that is shed by tumours into the bloodstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Seemed Like Dem Activists. They Were Secretly Conservative Spies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/25/they-seemed-like-democratic-activists-they-were-secretly-conservative-spies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHEYENNE, Wyo. — The young couple posing in front of the faux Eiffel Tower at the Paris hotel in Las</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Alito bristles at conservative Court's incremental course...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/560147-justice-alito-bristles-at-conservative-supreme-courts-incremental</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Samuel Alito has drawn attention for his fiery criticism of Supreme Court rulings, with some court watchers especially struck by the degree of barely concealed hostility he directed at fellow conservative justices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debut Date Set For Horror Classic...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/halloween-kills-trailer-debut-date-set-for-horror-classic-1234781462/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official trailer for the latest installment in the Halloween franchise, Halloween Kills, is on the loose. In 2018, David Gordon Green’s Halloween, starring icon Jamie Lee Curtis, earned more th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Simulates Cyberattack That Brings Down Utilities Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41243/the-national-guard-just-simulated-a-cyberattack-that-brought-down-utilities-nationwide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's Cyber Yankee exercises simulated the increasingly likely scenario of cyberattacks crippling massive sections of the nation's utilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 DEAD, 99  MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3147725/miami-beach-apartment-block-mass-casualties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment an apartment in Miami Beach collapsed, leaving at least one person dead and 99 others reported missing, as “banging” was heard beneath the rubble. Dozens wer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUILDING SINKING FOR DECADES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/collapsed-miami-condo-had-been-sinking-into-earth-at-alarming-rate-since-1990s-researchers-say/ar-AALoUP0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The building had been sinking at an alarming rate - about 2 millimeters a year - according to a 2020 study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside extraordinary effort to save Trump from covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inside-the-extraordinary-effort-to-save-trump-from-covid-19/ar-AALooCP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excerpt from the book ‘Nightmare Scenario’ details how Trump's illness was far more severe than the White House acknowledged. Advisers thought it would alter his pandemic response. They were wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI BEACH CONDO HORROR</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9720381/Eleven-story-Miami-Beach-apartment-building-collapses-sparking-huge-search.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A huge emergency search and rescue operation is underway after the beachfront condo tower, Champlain Towers South, collapsed at about 1.30am on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan says need to prepare for military conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/24/asia/taiwan-foreign-minister-china-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's escalating military intimidation of Taiwan shows the self-governed island "needs to prepare" for a possible military conflict, Taiwan's Foreign Minister Joseph Wu said in an exclusive interview with CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURFSLIDE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/miami-building-collapses-25ee9ff94dd07d2a0ae3da742a6cb8dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — A beachfront condo building partially collapsed Thursday outside Miami, killing at least one person and trapping others in the tower that resembled a giant fractured dollhouse, with one side sheared away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Speaks Out Again, Apologizes For Pretending Everything Was OK...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/britney-spears-conservatorship-court-instagram-post-1234781345/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out Britney Spears didn’t say all she had to say yesterday in court about the restrictive conservatorship that has ruled her life and career since 2008. Just over 24 hours after telling…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER halts anti-smoking drug after finding carcinogen...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/pfizer-halts-distribution-of-anti-smoking-drug-after-finding-carcinogen-671996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
