<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Thiel Says He 'Underinvested' in Bitcoin, Slams Central Banks at Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/peter-thiel-says-he-underinvested-in-bitcoin-slams-central-banks-at-event/ar-AAPLA4J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Thiel, the technology billionaire and conservative political donor, praised cryptocurrencies and slammed central banks during an appearance on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney becomes Republican Trump foil...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/577704-cheney-becomes-gops-trump-foil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Liz Cheney is using her platform on the special committee investigating the Jan. 6 attack to take direct aim at Donald Trump — and become a foil to the former president and de facto leader of the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Phil, CBS sued after teen allegedly sexually assaulted at Utah center...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/dr-phil-cbs-sued-teen-235849972.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who alleges she was sexually assaulted at a Utah ranch is suing the popular TV doctor after recommending that she be treated there for suicidal thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan, SKorea never did full lockdowns. It left lessons on how to coexist with virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Japan-and-South-Korea-never-did-full-lockdowns-16550763.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - In Japan, the newly minted prime minister has vowed to create a path into the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'TRUTH' Social Hacked Within Hours of Announcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/trump-truth-social-hacked-within-hours-announcement-1641137</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president announced he is launching a new social media platform that will soft launch in November, before a planned nationwide rollout in early 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELTICS wiped from NBA broadcasts after player slams Tibet abuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/china-wipes-boston-celtics-from-nba-broadcasts-after-enes-kanter-slams-tibet-abuses/ar-AAPLJkz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese social media was filled with a flood of angry fans calling for a boycott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen. warns of Beijing's growing threat in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/oct/20/gen-david-thompson-space-force-commander-warns-chi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is threatening to overtake the U.S. military as the most dominant force in space, says the second in command of the now 3-year-old U.S. Space Force, who warns that Washington must dramatically accelerate its rollout of critical new technologies if it wants to retain superiority over the futuristic war-fighting domain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW UK LOCKDOWN WITHOUT 'BOOSTERS'?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/oct/20/javid-vows-to-protect-nhs-as-he-says-covid-infections-could-hit-100000-a-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health secretary rejects calls for ‘plan B’ measures despite predicting infections could hit 100,000 a day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to Eliminate Testing Option for Workforce...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/nyc-to-mandate-vaccines-scrap-testing-option-for-workforce/ar-AAPK3cI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City said it would require all municipal workers to be vaccinated against Covid-19 and eliminate a test-out option in a move that immediately drew ire from a powerful police union that said it would bring legal action against the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exit Plan Ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2021/10/senator-joe-manchin-democratic-party-exit-plan-biden-infrastructure-deal-exclusive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He could pull the trigger if he doesn't get his way on the Build Back Better bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP, UP AND AWAY:  STOCKS HIT ALL-TIME HIGH!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/19/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow jumped to a record on Wednesday as investor sentiment was boosted by better-than-expected earnings reports and a new record for bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BULLSH*T'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/577623-manchin-on-party-switch-its-bull</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) on Wednesday dismissed a report that he is actively thinking about dropping out of the Democratic Party as "bullshit" and "rumors."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK BOWS TO THE COMMUNISTS:  APPLE removes YAHOO app in China after request...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/20/yahoo-news-app-one-of-the-last-sources-of-western-news-in-china-is-removed-from-apple-store-amid-censorship-drive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese internet users have lost one of their last avenues to foreign news after the Yahoo Finance app disappeared from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN HEALTH FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16486075/queen-urged-rest-cancel-northern-ireland-trip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen sparked health fears by cancelling her first royal duties in 15 years yesterday. Her Maj, 95 — due to visit Northern Ireland — has been told by docs to rest for up to a week instead.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 gas gallon...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/wheels/news/gas-prices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gas prices took off in October. They're 44% higher than the average 2021 price. If prices stay high, sales of big SUVs and pickups may suffer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In First, Surgeons Attach Pig Kidney to Human -- and It Works...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/19/in-a-first-surgeons-attached-a-pig-kidney-to-a-human-and-it-worked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surgeons in New York have successfully attached a kidney grown in a genetically altered pig to a human patient and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon case tests Congress' power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-congress-82628f5b0bbd711ddcf3ebbf50f79dac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. House is expected to hold Steve Bannon in contempt of Congress. It's up to the Justice Department, and the courts, to determine what happens next. As lawmakers ready a Thursday vote to send a contempt referral to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Employee Walkout Grows Tense as Trans Rights Protesters Clash With Chappelle Supporters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arts-and-entertainment-los-angeles-elliot-page-dave-chappelle-a80a7a9267520c5bbc8f0b755302b5b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Critics and supporters of Dave Chappelle's Netflix special and its anti-transgender comments gathered outside the company's offices Wednesday, with “Trans lives matter” and “Free speech is a right” among their competing messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight Over Military Order Heats Up as Deadlines Loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-10-20/pentagon-squares-off-with-congressional-republicans-over-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A political fight looms as vaccine mandate opponents prepare for the Defense Department’s deadlines to come into effect next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Epstein's Ranch had computer rooms to spy on guests...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3865943/epsteins-zorro-ranch-had-computer-rooms-the-size-of-houses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein’s notorious Zorro Ranch had three computer rooms “the size of houses” to spy on famous guests including Prince Andrew, one of the pedophile’s victims has claimed. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-Year-Old Drew 'Offensive Sketch.' Cops Handcuffed Her...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvngvm/black-10-year-old-handcuffed-by-honolulu-cops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultimately, the child was held for over four hours by either school staff or police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Employee Walkout Grows Tense as Trans Rights Protesters Clash With Chappelle Supporters...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/netflix-employees-stage-walkout-protest-dave-chapelle-special-the-closer-transphobic-1235093535/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Netflix employees and supporters gathered in the shadow of the streaming giant’s Los Angeles headquarters on Wednesday to protest Dave Chappelle’s standup special “The Closer.” Bu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisis not seen since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10109363/Supply-chain-crisis-unseen-WWII-bring-disaster-Christmas-Resellers-jack-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's hottest toys are already selling out, and half of Americans haven't even started their shopping yet, a survey found, while recent shoppers were already striking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA record profit despite parts shortage, ship delays...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-earnings-elon-musk-tesla-inc-4085ff56d41a3e3e55c31439c7435fc3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Record electric vehicle sales last summer amid a shortage of computer chips and other materials propelled Tesla Inc. to the biggest quarterly net earnings in its history. The company said Wednesday that it made $1.62 billion in the third quarter, beating the old record of $1.14 billion set in the second quarter of this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mossad's New Boss is Gadget-Loving Killing Machine..</title>
      <link>https://www.spytalk.co/p/mossads-new-boss-is-a-gadget-loving</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spytalk.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Barnea warned Iran the “long arm of Mossad” isn’t finished with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male Infertility Cure? Scientists Create New Sperm Using Monkey Stem Cells...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/male-infertility-stem-cells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team used embryonic stem cells collected from rhesus macaque monkeys to produce immature sperm cells called round spermatids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 people rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/tv/more-100-people-rally-outside-netflix-protest-dave-chappelle-s-n1281994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming giant has drawn fierce internal criticism and public scrutiny since Chappelle’s special, “The Closer,” debuted Oct. 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireball raced across Midwest sky. 'Not natural fireball,' group says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-fireball-raced-across-the-midwest-sky-except-it-was-not-a-natural-fireball-group-says/ar-AAPL7D2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say fireballs frequently appear in Earth's atmosphere, but the one seen over the Midwest apparently was not a meteor, one group says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER:  'Much Worse' Than Thought -- 'Just Unbelievable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jim-cramer-says-astounding-inflation-much-worse-than-thought-just-unbelievable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers are "astounding" according to Cramer, who was discussing the topic at the top of CNBC's news all day on inflation numbers and their affect on both consumer goods and investment markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Giant to Change Name?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/facebook-name-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report in the Verge says Facebook wants to be known as a metaverse-building company, not a social media company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metro offers subway riders involved in derailment $21 credit...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/tracking-metro-24-7/2021/10/metro-offers-riders-involved-in-derailment-21-smartrip-credit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metro is offering the riders who were on board the Blue Line train that derailed on Oct. 12 SmarTrip credit for future rides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold War-Era Air Raid Siren Mysteriously Blares In CA Neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/10/19/east-sac-loud-siren-cold-war-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was one of dozens of civil defense sirens installed across the city back in the 1940s to warn people of an imminent emergency like a dam break or nuclear war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student Forced To TAPE Mask To Face...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/19/face-masks-colorado-springs-tape/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A student in Academy School District 20 said she was forced to take her mask to her face at school in Colorado Springs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings were in North America in 1021, well before Columbus, researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/tree-rings-radioactive-carbon-signs-vikings-north-america-rcna3383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vikings from Greenland — the first Europeans to arrive in the Americas — lived in a village in Canada’s Newfoundland exactly 1,000 years ago, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parkland school shooter blames POT for '18 massacre...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10111259/Accused-Florida-school-shooter-set-plead-guilty-2018-Parkland-massacre.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nikolas Cruz has pleaded guilty to killing 14 students and three staff dead in a mass shooting at a high school in Parkland in 2018 - the deadliest attack ever at a US high school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walter Reed on lockdown for bomb threat... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/montgomery-county/2021/10/walter-reed-on-lockdown-for-bomb-threat-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shelter in place order has been issued for the Bethesda Navy base that houses Walter Reed National Military Medical Center for the investigation of a bomb threat at the hospital’s lobby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban behead women's volleyball player; Post photos on social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3896327/taliban-behead-womens-volleyball-player-head-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONSTER Taliban militants beheaded a women’s volleyball player and posted photos of her decapitated head on social media. A coach from the all-girls team confirmed that Mahjabin Hakimi w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorsey Mocks Metaverse Plan, Says Dystopian...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/jack-dorsey-mocks-mark-zuckerbergs-metaverse-plan-saying-its-dystopian/ar-AAPJPf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg wants Facebook to be a "metaverse company," and Dorsey responded to a tweet about the metaverse being "a dystopian corporate dictatorship."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*CK Joe Biden' Chant Drowns FOX Postgame Show One Day After They Muted 'F*CK YOU A-Rod'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/fck-joe-biden-chant-drowns-fox-alcs-postgame-show-one-day-after-they-muted-fck-you-a-rod/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After muting as many “F*CK YOU A-ROD” chants as they could on Monday, shouts of “F*CK Joe Biden” drowned the ALCS postgame show on Fox Tuesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghouliani turns Abe Lincoln...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-rudy-giuliani-cosplaying-as-abe-lincoln-is-somehow-more-unsettling-than-that-sounds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani with an Abe Lincoln filter. Exactly what we've all been waiting for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If chickenpox shot lasts 20 years, why not Covid ones?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/if-the-chickenpox-vaccine-lasts-20-years-why-not-the-covid-19-shot-682382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will the third booster shot be our last? Israeli doctors explain the science behind it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Crown Jewel Of American Retail, Rampant Crime Has Taken Luster Out Of Chicago's Magnificent Mile...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/michigan-avenue-magnificent-mile-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Police have issued a formal warning after continued robberies on and around the city’s Magnificent Mile, at a time when stores continue to leave while others fight to stay in business after big pandemic hits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blasts closure of restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article255144327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We refuse to become the vaccination police.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW MANY WILL BE REQUIRED?</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/how-many-boosters-will-we-need-israel-says-too-soon-to-know-1.1653686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Israel told a panel of U.S. vaccine experts weighing a potential Covid-19 booster dose from Pfizer Inc. and BioNTech SE on Friday that it’s unclear how long the benefit of such a shot would last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarasota Named Best Place to Retire...</title>
      <link>https://money.usnews.com/money/retirement/articles/what-makes-sarasota-the-best-place-to-retire </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's why this Florida beach retirement spot is No. 1 for the second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS THREATENS TO BACK RESTRICTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/uk-news/3896631/four-key-restrictions-boris-johnson-could-bring-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAJID Javid will tonight dangle the prospect of a return to restrictions unless Brits get their boosters to tackle the Covid surge. Mandatory masks, working from home and vaccine passports are all …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Accused of Crimes Against Humanity in Covid Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bolsonaro-accused-of-crimes-against-humanity-in-covid-probe/ar-AAPKBqp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil senators said Jair Bolsonaro should be charged for nine crimes, including charlatanism, malfeasance and crimes against humanity in their conclusion of a probe into the government’s handling of the pandemic that’s unlikely to have any short-term impact on the president’s political fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toothpaste Will Fly as GOOGLE Drones Test Delivery in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/toothpaste-will-fly-as-alphabet-s-drones-test-delivery-in-texas/ar-AAPKR69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Alphabet Inc.’s drone-delivery operation is expanding to a Walgreens in suburban Dallas where it will make airborne deliveries of toothpaste and other goods to residents of nearby towns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Draws Late-Night Comedy Crowd With 'GUTFELD!'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/fox-news-gutfeld-greg-late-night-comedy-1235093369/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News has drawn a big crowd for years with shows that skewer liberals and the perceived excesses of the left. Now the cabler is seeing strong returns for its experiment with Greg Gutfeld as host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's still very, very good to be DURAN DURAN...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/still-very-very-good-duran-120037916.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Set to release their 15th album, Duran Duran's Simon Le Bon and John Taylor talk recovering from COVID, their favorite bad review and plastic trousers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX workers stage walk-out over Chappelle trans comments...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211020105832-wwsdb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public figures, trans activists and supporters join 'Team Trans' Netflix employees in protest against "harmful content" after release of comedy special said to ridicule trans experiences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How controversy put streamer on blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/How-the-controversy-over-Dave-Chappelle-s-special-16548080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Netflix endures another week of the maelstrom created by Dave Chappelle's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Isn't Hitting the Panic Button...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/10/progressives-primary-kyrsten-sinema-arizona/620422/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator from Arizona doesn’t seem rattled by progressives’ threats to primary her—and it’s not clear she should be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary Cancer Treatment 'Wakes Up' Immune System To Destroy Tumors.</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cancer-treatment-destroy-tumors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breakthrough cancer treatment "jump starts" a patient's natural defenses by merging chemotherapy, immunotherapy, and tumor-fighting techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY Loses Bid for Secrecy in Dr. Luke-Kesha Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/kesha-dr-luke-lawsuit-sony-secrecy-1235034004/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the 7-year-old libel suit over a rape accusation nears trial, a New York judge is opening the books on pop music dealmaking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BITCOIN NEW RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/bitcoin-jumps-to-new-record-high-above-65000-after-landmark-us-etf-launch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin notched a fresh all-time high on Wednesday as investors cheered the successful launch of the first U.S. bitcoin futures exchange-traded fund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX could make Musk first trillionaire, says MORGAN STANLEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/oct/20/spacex-could-make-elon-musk-world-first-trillionaire-says-morgan-stanley</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of world’s richest person’s fortune so far has come from electric car company Tesla</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walkouts and strikes hit hospitals in pandemic hot spots...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/20/hospitals-labor-shortage-covid-delta-516303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been at least 30 strikes of health care workers so far this year, according to a tracker from Cornell University’s School of Industrial and Labor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WANTED: 80,000 truck drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/19/economy/trucking-short-drivers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trucking industry is short 80,000 drivers, a record high, Chris Spear, President and CEO of the American Trucking Associations, tells CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic ordering making things worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/retailers-manufacturers-over-ordering-amid-supply-chain-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retailers and manufacturers are overordering or placing orders too early as they panic over the supply chain crisis, and that's not helping, experts told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Shortages Next Supply-Chain Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-hoarding-food-shortages-next-120000053.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In Denver, public-school children are facing shortages of milk. In Chicago, a local market is running short of canned goods and boxed items.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureA $30 Billion Fortune Is Hiding in China’s Silicon ValleyThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightHate-Speech Case Forces Japan to Confront Workplace RacismBut there’s plenty of food. T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the new NFL, teams scoring on two-minute drives like never before...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/in-the-new-nfl-teams-are-scoring-on-two-minute-drives-like-never-before/ar-AAPKcSD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As NFL games wind down, the improbable has become the expected, and offenses are lighting up the scoreboard with unprecedented frequency,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Predicts Difficult Winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-k-s-boris-johnson-predicts-difficult-winter-as-covid-deaths-rise/ar-AAPHweN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson predicted a difficult winter due to coronavirus and other pressures on the National Health Service, as his government acknowledged worsening data in its pandemic response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IN-N-OUT BURGER clashes with San Fran over shot mandate: 'We refuse to become vaccination police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-n-out-burger-clashes-with-san-francisco-over-vaccine-mandate-e2-80-98we-refuse-to-become-the-vaccination-police-e2-80-99/ar-AAPKeoU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As San Francisco requires proof of vaccination to dine indoors, In-N-Out Burger is refusing to become the "vaccination police."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier with 'Hitler mustache' thrown out of military after Capitol riot charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Soldier-with-Hitler-mustache-thrown-out-of-16547809.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Army reservist charged in the Justice Department's sweeping investigation of the U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Tudor Jones says inflation worse than feared; Biggest threat to society...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/paul-tudor-jones-says-inflation-could-be-worse-than-feared-biggest-threat-to-markets-and-society.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire hedge fund manager Paul Tudor Jones believes that inflation is here to stay, posing a major threat to the markets and the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record out-of-stocks, shipping delays expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/holiday-shopping-2021-record-out-of-stocks-shipping-delays-ahead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts warn shoppers can expect to find record out of stocks as they scan retail websites and may face prolonged shipping delays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired pope hopes to soon join friends in afterlife...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pope-francis-religion-pope-benedict-xvi-84fc17d61798b96cb712b432cd4da5e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Retired Pope Benedict XVI has said he hopes to soon join a beloved professor friend in “the afterlife,” in a sign that the 94-year-old pontiff is not only accepting his eventual death but welcoming it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin keeps Russian workers home for week as deaths soar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-russia-europe-vladimir-putin-bcb1c48ff55f0b2276d3696baba2084c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin on Wednesday backed the Cabinet’s proposal to declare a non-working week and keep Russian workers away from their offices as coronavirus deaths surged to another daily record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JABS FOR KIDS IN WEEKS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-coronavirus-vaccine-bf6e5c8725aca6c757b129dad8f96926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Children age 5 to 11 will soon be able to get a COVID-19 shot at their pediatrician's office, local pharmacy and potentially even their school, the White House said Wednesday as it detailed plans for the expected authorization of the Pfizer shot for younger children in a matter of weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems push IRS bank reporting plan amid uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-to-scale-back-treasury-e2-80-99s-irs-bank-reporting-plan-amid-gop-uproar/ar-AAPFE2r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration has faced an uproar over the plan from Republicans and industry groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's COVID outbreak grows as cities race to trace infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211020081849-6h7pu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHINA (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China's COVID-19 outbreak grows as cities race to trace infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can see through you: CEOs' language under machine microscope...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211020045902-qbyf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-INVESTMENT/NLP (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-AI can see through you: CEOs' language under machine microscope</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
