<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Deaf man sues porn site over lack of closed captioning...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/01/16/pornhub-sued-class-action-deaf-demand-closed-captioning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pornhub just got sued because it lacks closed captioning in videos, making it hard to watch for the deaf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff takes on Trump, calling him 'erratic hothead.' Now he's feeling the heat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/adam-schiff-takes-on-trump-calling-him-an-erratic-hothead-now-hes-feeling-the-heat/ar-BBZ3GVd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury brings back the 20-year bond to pay for the ballooning deficit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/17/treasury-brings-back-the-20-year-bond-to-pay-for-the-ballooning-deficit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Treasury Department is issuing a 20-year bond for the first time in 34 years to help pay for the ballooning $1 trillion dollar budget deficit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's shortest man dies at 27...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/worlds-shortest-man-dies-nepal-27-172725938.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's shortest man who could walk, as verified by Guinness World Records, died Friday at a hospital in Nepal, his family said. Khagendra Thapa Magar, who measured 67.08 centimetres (2 feet 2.41 inches), died of pneumonia at a hospital in Pokhara, 200 kilometres from Kathmandu, where he lived</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 more linked to neo-Nazi group arrested in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be1f537775593d49415a008f2639f39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Three men linked to a violent white supremacist group known as The Base were charged with conspiring to kill members of a militant anti-fascist group, police in Georgia announced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein jury seated after prosecutors accuse defense of excluding white women...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200117210846-qqnzx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-HARVEY WEINSTEIN/JURY (PIX):Weinstein jury seated after prosecutors accuse defense of excluding white women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother and daughter 'psychics' get prison time in fraud case...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/crime/fl-ne-broward-pysching-sentenced-for-million-dollar-fraud-20200117-zj7edl5yoveotog5qmigyxcgee-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They claimed they were “white squaw Cherokee Indian” spiritual healers, and used eggs filled with snake embryos to convince their victims that they were cursed, authorities say. But on Friday, the mother and daughter pair of Annie Marie Vwanawick, 74, and April Miller, 44, both of Broward, were sentenced to prison for defrauding two victims with their spiritual scams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon continues training Saudis on military bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/extreme-vetting-trump-administration-continue-training-saudis-military-bases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to screen airline passengers from China for new illness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e42ddf6414d214a8d86a8ba153d82a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Three U.S. airports will screen passengers arriving from central China for a new virus that has sickened dozens, killed two and prompted worries about an international outbreak,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DREAM TEAM</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a0f6c7518ce72e63374ddc9e01eeb18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has assembled a made-for-TV legal team for his Senate trial that includes household names like Ken Starr, the prosecutor whose investigation two decades...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Manhattan's Skyscrapers Are Empty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/01/american-housing-has-gone-insane/605005/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately half of the luxury-condo units that have come onto the market in the past five years are still unsold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun Violence Surging In Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/01/17/794510796/why-gun-violence-is-surging-in-toronto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, more than 760 people were shot. Canada has tighter gun laws than in the U.S., and officials and gun control advocates are trying to figure out why the surge is happening and how to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg assembling fundraising experts to recruit wealthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/17/bloomberg-makes-push-to-recruit-wealthy-donors-but-not-to-take-their-money.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of the Bloomberg team's targets are backing other candidates, but the effort could potentially put pressure on the donors to withhold funds from other contenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New software flaw could further delay BOEING MAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/new-software-flaw-could-further-delay-boeings-737-max/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Boeing Co. has identified a new software flaw in the grounded 737 Max that will require additional work, possibly further delaying the plane's return to service. The company alerted the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration and is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Considers Changes to Law Banning Overseas Bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-considers-changes-to-law-banning-overseas-bribes/ar-BBZ46FI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President regrets wading into 'that f***ing vaping thing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-hhs-azar-vaping-policy-14475d0f-07db-4e33-ac25-b512562ab419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's one of Trump's few health care accomplishments heading into 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style legend Jean-Paul Gaultier retires from fashion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jean-paul-gaultier-retire-fashion-designer-185054835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French designer Jean-Paul Gaultier shocked the fashion world Friday by saying his next Paris haute couture show will be his last. "Rest assured, haute couture will continue with a new concept," said the designer, who made pop history by putting Madonna in a conical bra, invented the "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two iPhones or the privacy of billions: Why APPLE vs. FBI matters...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/two-iphones-or-privacy-billions-why-apple-vs-fbi-matters-n1118001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI's efforts to push Apple to unlock phones have caused alarm among technology industry veterans and academics who see a broader effort to reduce privacy and introduce digital back doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rolls back Michelle Obama lunch program on her birthday...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/policy/article239402203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Dems go to war with FACEBOOK, Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/tech/democrats-facebook-war/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few years ago, then President Barack Obama was appearing at dinner and on stage with Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg, and Nancy Pelosi was heaping praise on COO Sheryl Sandberg for "inspiring women across the world to believe in themselves."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes to consider faithless electors, ahead of 2020 vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6f415b0b39decbd05f58ec5a08195e79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court said Friday it will decide ahead of the 2020 election whether presidential electors are bound to support the popular vote winner in their states or can opt for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX name dropped...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/entertainment/ct-ent-disney-fox-rename-20200117-ytbvfutodrdd3jc3ww5uk7ax2q-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20th Century Fox film studio will become 20th Century Studios, and Fox Searchlight Pictures will become simply Searchlight Pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers at U.S. airports to be screened for new, potentially deadly Chinese virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/new-virus-prompts-u-s-health-officials-begin-airport-screenings-n1117911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screening will only take place at the airports with direct or indirect flights from Wuhan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avalanche Reported Near Lake Tahoe; Several Missing...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/17/alpine-meadows-placer-county-avalanche-people-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several people are unaccounted for after an avalanche at Alpine Meadows on Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why SKoreans flipping out over US ambassador's mustache...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/17/asia/harry-harris-mustache-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might just be the most bizarre criticism of a US ambassador in recent memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Census kicks off in remote Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be84b23d6c8fd94e6fb935bd4fecb257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — The 2020 Census kicks off Tuesday in remote Alaska. U.S. Census Bureau Director Steven Dillingham will be there to conduct the first count in the Bering Sea community of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers at U.S. airports to be screened for new, potentially deadly Chinese virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2020/01/17/coronavirus-us-airports-screening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new virus has sickened dozens in China, and two people have died. Cases have spread to Thailand and Japan. There are no known cases in the U.S., but health experts are concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure building on vulnerable senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/politics/impeachment-trial-resolution-mcconnell-susan-collins/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It had been weeks since the House of Representatives passed articles of impeachment, and back home senators were getting pushed on what they believed a fair impeachment trial would look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Considers Changes to Law Banning Overseas Bribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-17/white-house-considers-changes-to-law-banning-overseas-bribes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China birthrate hits lowest level since country was founded...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/01/17/asia/china-birthrate-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's birthrate in 2019 hit its lowest level since the founding of the People's Republic in 1949, according to official statistics released by Beijing Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteorite or Volcano? New Clues to Dinosaurs' Demise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/meteorite-or-volcano-new-clues-to-the-dinosaurs-demise/ar-BBZ1Q3o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Starr Bashed Trump During Hearings, Praised Witnesses Against Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trumps-new-lawyer-panned-presidents-poor-judgement-on-impeachment-said-testimony-against-him-doesnt-look-good/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's new lawyer, former independent counsel Ken Starr, served as an analyst for Fox News during the House impeachment proceedings against the president. And in that role, he h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEWINKSY:  Are you f---ing kidding me?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/17/politics/monica-lewinsky-ken-starr-senate/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement that former independent counsel Ken Starr is joining President Donald Trump's impeachment defense team surprised many on Friday, but one person, apparently, had an especially notable reaction to the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem compares self to Manchester Arena bomber on new track...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2020/jan/17/eminem-manchester-arena-bomb-attack-salman-ramadan-abedi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relatives hit back at ‘disrespectful’ rapper over lyrics referring to terror attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>560-POUND ISIS fanatic dubbed 'Jabba the Jihadi ' is arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/268806/monstrous-40-stone-isis-jihadi-dubbed-jabba-the-hutt-is-arrested-sparking-stream-of-internet-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MASSIVE 40-stone jihadi dubbed “Jabba the Jihadi” has been nicked by Iraqi forces— sparking a stream of hilarious internet memes. Hate preacher Abu Abdul Bari had to be loaded onto a flatbed truc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Woman burned in random bleach attack in NYC subway station...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/woman-becomes-target-of-unprovoked-bleach-attack-in-nyc-subway-station-police/2261025/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 37-year-old woman was the victim of an unprovoked attack when another woman threw bleach at her face in a Manhattan subway station Thursday afternoon, police said. The woman was standing near the subway booth at 7th Avenue and West 14th Street when a 30-year-old woman threw liquid at her, police said. The victim suffered minor burns, according to the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can cast tie-breaking vote?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/history-shows-chief-justice-john-roberts-could-cast-tie-breaking-n1117506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief justice has offered no clues about how he would approach the question of witnesses, but judges typically rule in favor of allowing relevant testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline forces woman to take pregnancy test to stop 'birth tourism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article239389563.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaf man sues porn site over lack of closed captioning...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/report-deaf-man-sues-pornhub-over-lack-of-closed-captioning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An adult video website is reportedly the target of a lawsuit over an alleged lack of closed captioning for its videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic City struggles to keep street lights on...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/atlantic-city-going-in-wrong-direction-hard-rock-ceo-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hard Rock CEO Jim Allen said the company is willing to be part of the solution in Atlantic City but is not encouraged by recent developments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe Might Ban Face Recognition From ALL Public Places...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90453208/the-eu-might-ban-facial-recognition-tech-for-five-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasoning is that facial recognition tech is so new, yet rolling out so quickly, we simply can’t know all the risks and drawbacks associated with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Heiress Backs Bill That Would Tax DISNEY Over CEO Pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90453156/abigail-disneys-new-crusade-fixing-the-ceo-to-worker-pay-gap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under California’s proposed tax rules, companies that make over $10 million in taxable income in the state would be liable for higher tax rates based on the pay disparity between the company’s regular employees and its CEO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Drone Swarms Over Colorado: Mysterious Objects Secret Military Craft?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/usaf-intelligence-expert-claims-drones-21287021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Mike Turber has suggested the mysterious drone swarms seen over Colorado and Nebraska may not be drones at all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW RATINGS SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2020/01/16/rachel-maddow-ratings-largest-audience-ever-lev-parnas-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Maddow’s exclusive sit-down with the controversial Lev Parnas delivered her eponymous MSNBC program’s largest audience ever on Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's culture minister sparks outrage by echoing Goebbels...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-51149224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The minister uses parts of a speech by Nazi Germany's propaganda boss but calls it a coincidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders supporters threaten to stay home if nominate centrist...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/people-will-sit-at-home-sanders-supporters-threaten-to-stay-home-if-democrats-nominate-a-bland-centrist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa — Bernie Sanders supporters in Iowa are warning that a lack of enthusiasm for Joe Biden could bring the same result the nomination of another milquetoast Democrat did four years ago: electing Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drivers say sniper shooting at cars on highway in eastern NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article239345368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors scrutinizing whether Comey illegally disclosed classified secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/justice-dept-investigating-years-old-leaks-and-appears-focused-on-comey/ar-BBZ23bs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge military exercise could jam GPS for planes flying in Southeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article239372348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi slam reflects rising tensions between social media giant and Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Pelosi-s-Facebook-slam-reflects-rising-tensions-14983267.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Nancy Pelosi's attacks on Facebook highlight how furious Democrats have become with the social network.  The most powerful Democrat in the House accused the company with an office in her home district of cozying up to President Donald Trump during a Thursday news conference.  "All they want are their tax cuts and no antitrust action against them," Pelosi said when asked whether Facebook was too powerful. "And they schmooze this administration in that regard because so far that's what they have received."  The House speaker's words highlight how tensions between the tech titan and Democrats have escalated in the week since Facebook defied Democrats' calls andannounced it wouldn't police the accuracy of ads run by politicians on their site.  Democrats warned the policy will benefit Trump in 2020, especially because his campaign has already been able to run unchecked ads making misleading claims about former vice president Joe Biden.  For years, Facebook and other large Silicon Valley companies were widely viewed as Democratic darlings. But concerns that Facebook didn't do enough to prevent Russian interference during the 2016 election marked a key turning point, and the company's positions on fighting falsehoods have only strained it further.  Pelosi also ripped Facebook as "shameful," "abusive," "irresponsible" and intent on being "accomplices for misleading the American people with money from God knows where."  Pelosi's vitriol is in line with recent attacks on Facebook from leading Democratic presidential candidates. Her remarks were prompted by recent comments that Pete Buttigieg, the former mayor of South Bend, Indiana, made to The New York Times editorial board about Facebook's unbridled power. "No one company and no one person should have the kind of power...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR, DERSHOWITZ JOIN TEAM TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/17/trump-impeachment-defense-to-include-ken-starr-alan-dershowitz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's lawyers Ken Starr and Alan Dershowitz will defend him of against an impeachment charge of abusing power by pressuring Ukraine to investigate former Vice President Joe Biden, a leading contender for the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Coup'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/grammy-deborah-dugan-recording-academy-ouster-coup-1203470424/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED: As the music industry reeled in the wake of Deborah Dugan’s sudden removal from her post as president/CEO of the Recording Academy on Thursday — a mere five months after she’d taken charge…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Drone Swarms Over Colorado: Mysterious Objects Secret Military Craft?</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/202001171078055130-drones-colorado-mysterious-objects-be-secret-military-craft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past several months, people in Colorado have reportedly flooded authorities with information about large drones, raging through night sky there. Although local officials have said there is nothing unusual or criminal about them, commentators are not ready to leave it at that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT HAPPENS WHEN FED STOPS PUMPING?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/debate-over-whether-call-qe-110000007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In the court of investor opinion, the verdict is in. The Federal Reserve is guilty of quantitative easing.Never mind that Chairman Jerome Powell tells everyone his efforts to shore up funding markets are “in no sense” QE. Try as policy makers may, they’ve lost the ability to convince people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You're bunch of dopes and babies': Inside Trump stunning tirade against generals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-called-his-generals-a-bunch-of-dopes-and-babies-in-a-fit-of-rage-book-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new book by Washington Post reporters sheds new light on Trump’s incredible temper tantrum at his top military brass, who he also called “losers.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T under pressure to defy Maduro censors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5247995bc15a8b6bf479bf5af42f411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Last April, as a military uprising roiled Venezuela, Nicolás Maduro’s socialist government ordered pay TV providers to immediately cease transmission of CNN and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Break up big tech's monopoly': Smaller rivals join growing chorus...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tech-antitrust/break-up-big-techs-monopoly-smaller-rivals-join-growing-chorus-ahead-of-congress-hearing-idUSKBN1ZG17J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In April 2019, Tile.com, which helps users find lost or misplaced items, suddenl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Satanic' sect kills pregnant woman and six children in violent 'exorcism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/satanic-sect-kills-pregnant-woman-21298394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bodies of seven people, including a child as young as one, were found in a mass grave after families were held against their will in a church in Panama</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH GETS BIGGER: VALUE TOPS $5 TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/16/big-tech-worth-over-5-trillion-with-alphabet-joining-four-comma-club.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet became the fourth U.S. technology company to reach $1 trillion in market value, as Big Tech becomes an ever bigger part of the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 BILLIONAIRES HEADED TO DAVOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/davos-world-economic-forum-2020/dalio-dimon-and-117-other-billionaires-set-to-descend-on-davos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richest 119 attendees have $500 billion of combined net worth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicted To Bomb Terribly At Box Office...</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/dolittle-movie-2020-box-office-predictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This certainly isn't Marvel!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers ferry Chinese migrants to Florida in yachts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/feds-smugglers-ferry-chinese-migrants-204941696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities have thwarted two separate attempts by smugglers to bring Chinese migrants illegally into the U.S. through Florida aboard yachts. Three men are facing human smuggling charges in federal courts in Miami and Fort Lauderdale. The Miami Herald first reported they are accused of ferrying a total</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foes Sue to Force Zuckerberg to Sell Majority Stake...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-foes-sue-force-zuckerberg-024127971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc. was sued by four potential competitors who accuse it of anticompetitive behavior and who asked a judge to order Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg to give up control of the social media behemoth.The companies also said if Facebook isn’t forced to sell its WhatsApp and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa Group To March Alongside Pro-Gun Protesters In Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/16/antifa-group-march-pro-gun-protesters-virginia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A diverse gathering of pro-gun protestors set to descend upon Virginia's capital on Monday could include an unlikely ally, a local antifa group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Who's going to Super Bowl LIV?</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001097083/article/qb-index-championship-sunday-who-needs-sb-liv-the-most</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers is hunting for a second ring. A Lombardi Trophy would do wonders for Ryan Tannehill's career. Which of the four Championship Sunday QBs needs to win Super Bowl LIV the most? See how they rank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nations dawdle on agreeing rules to control 'killer robots' in future wars...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200117101055-stqv4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nations are investing in developing lethal autonomous weapons systems which can identify, target, and kill a person all on their own - but there are no international laws governing their use</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: BERNIE, BIDEN TIED...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200116232846-rwbm2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/DEMOCRATS-POLL (PIX):POLL-Sanders climbs, now tied with Biden among registered voters</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
