<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: NEW MEX...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-TWx4GjID6A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live coverage of President Donald Trump holding a campaign rally in Rio Rancho, New Mexico. Â» Subscribe to NBC News: http://nbcnews.to/SubscribeToNBC Â»...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge tosses lawsuit over SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER's  'hate' group labels...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/sep/16/judge-amy-berman-jackson-tosses-lawsuit-over-south/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge has thrown out a lawsuit that accused leaders of the Southern Poverty Law Center of trying to financially destroy one of the organizations that it has labeled as a hate group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS leader calls for more terror attacks on West... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9939894/isis-leader-abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-audio-message/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“BADLY injured” ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi has released a new message calling for more deadly attacks on the West – four months after he emerged from the shadows. The latest speec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next to Cali, raising money, but keeps details secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global/2019/sep/16/trump-california-fundraiser-secret-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous visits to the San Francisco Bay area ended with physical confrontations between supporters and demonstrators</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein sex slave tried to swim shark-infested waters to escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/09/13/prosecutors-must-probe-jeffrey-epsteins-trafficking-network/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of torture, suddenly there was a sliver of hope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu fights for MORE after decade in power... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election/israels-netanyahu-fights-for-new-term-after-decade-in-power-idUSKBN1W12UY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu faced a battle for political survival ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECLARES NEW YORK TIMES 'DEAD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/09/16/trump_everybody_involved_in_kavanaugh_story_at_new_york_times_must_resign_destroyed_old_gray_ladys_virtue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a campaign rally Monday night, President Donald Trump denounced 'The New York Times' for a recent controversial report on Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh. Trump accused reporters of destroying the Old Gray Lady's "virtue" and ruining her reputation. President Trump campaigns in Rio Rancho, New Mexico at the Santa Ana Star Arena: PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP: They will do whatever they can to demean you, to libel you. They try to blacklist, coerce, cancel or destroy anyone who gets in their way. Look at what they are doing today to Justice Kavanaugh. Kavanaugh.  Did you see the New York Times? Did you see what they are doing? Did you see what Democrats -- they're calling for his resignation. They are calling for his impeachment. And the woman involved said she did not know anything, but they still -- the New York Times had to put out a major apology and change their story. The woman said, I do not remember that. And they still want him to be impeached. And I just put out a statement -- and he is a great man, by the way. A great talent. A great, brilliant man, Brett Kavanaugh.  I just put out a statement on social media that said -- I do not think they will do it, but they should, for the good of the nation. I called for the resignation of everybody at the New York Times involved in the Kavanaugh smear story. And while you are at it, the Russian witch hunt hoax, which is just as phony a story.  They've taken the Old Gray Lady -- you know, the New York Times, for years, the Old Gray Lady, so prestigious. They have taken the Old Gray Lady and broken her down, destroyed her virtue, and ruined her reputation. She can never recover and will never return to greatness under current management. The Times is dead. Long live the New York Times. Long live the New York Times. I do want it to live, but they have to change their ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Rivals Slug It Out in Second Election This Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-rivals-set-to-slug-it-out-in-the-second-election-this-year/ar-AAHouFP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 YEARS OF TRUMP TAX RETURNS SUBPOENAED...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/8-years-of-trump-tax-returns-are-subpoenaed-by-manhattan-da/ar-AAHo5K0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Scientist Keeps Receiving Packages of Serial Killers' Hair...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/us/why-this-scientist-keeps-receiving-packages-of-serial-killers-e2-80-99-hair/ar-AAHovNB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T accused of faking DIRECTV accounts to boost numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.law.com/newyorklawjournal/2019/09/16/investors-claim-att-created-fake-streaming-service-accounts-to-hide-failure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.law.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to an amended complaint filed last week in Manhattan federal court, AT&amp;T management overreported the number of customers who had signed up for the company's $35-per-month product, leading investors to believe it was well-positioned to compete with cheaper online streaming services such as Netflix and Hulu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of 'JOKER' and Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/defense-joker-1239858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Phillips' bravura work dares to confront the things we're most afraid to see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren, before huge  crowd, touts self as heir to female pioneers... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Warren-before-huge-NYC-crowd-touts-herself-as-14444940.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Sen. Elizabeth Warren hailed the political power of female-led organizing in a speech Monday night that invoked the deadly 1911 Triangle Shirtwaist Factory fire to argue that outrage can spark positive change - and to make the case for her own presidential ambitions.  Warren, D-Mass., has long faced doubts from some Democratic leaders and voters who wonder if she would be able to defeat President Donald Trump, because of her outspoken liberal message and voters' possible reluctance to embrace a woman as president. Monday's speech, and the big crowd it attracted, was in part an attempt to rebut such doubts by arguing that liberal women have won big change before.  "I wanted to give this speech here - but not because of the arch behind me or the president this square is named for," Warren said, reading from a teleprompter in Washington Square Park, blocks from where the Triangle fire killed more than 140 workers, including many young immigrant women.  "We're not here today because of famous arches or famous men," she said. "In fact, we're not here because of men at all - we're here because of some hard-working women."  The comments were a more direct nod to gender than most of her public remarks to date, which typically focus on the ways in which powerful interests have tilted the country's government toward elites.  The event, which the campaign said attracted more than 20,000 people and was easily among her largest crowds, had been heavily promoted by the Warren campaign in the preceding days. It came as the campaign enters a new phase in which voters will be paying closer attention and the field is narrowing, and as Warren is looking for new ways to show off her momentum.  She has started holding large rally-style events in an effort to demonstrate that she enjoys enthusiastic grass-roots support from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says voting more important than sex!</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Netanyahu-has-unusual-pre-election-pitch-14443365.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - In battling to extend his run as Israel's longest-serving prime minister, Benjamin Netanyahu has warned voters of many a hazard, from unrest in the occupied territories to nuclear weapons in Iran. In the hours before the polls were to open Tuesday, he warned of another one: election day sex.  Voting day is a national holiday here and Netanyahu's ruling Likud party posted a last-minute video beseeching supporters not to waste it by going to the beach, lounging on the couch or - as suggested by a shot of four feet intertwining beneath the sheets - engaging in a bit of weekday whoopee. While you're enjoying yourself, the ad ends, "the left is getting ready to take over the government."  It was part of closing pitch that could seem strange to American political consultants who seek to convey an air of building momentum at the end of a campaign. By contrast, Netanyahu's final message has been: I'm losing.  The final public polls showed the race between Netanyahu and former army chief of staff Benny Gantz too close call or even slightly favoring Likud. (It is illegal to release new survey results in the final three days of the campaign.) But in hopes of motivating his base to go vote for the second time in five months, Netanyahu has been waging an all-out, all-is-lost campaign.  Showing his legendary ability to dominate the narrative, the prime minister was ever-present on national television and radio over the campaign's final weekend, sparring with the "hostile media," warning of widespread voter fraud in Arab neighborhoods and claiming that the country's recent run of security and growth was in fact slipping away. Israelis, who have heard the apocalyptic tone before, call it Netanyahu's "oy gevalt" campaign.  "Netanyahu is extremely competent at increasing the turnout of his political base," Yohanan Plesner,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aims to turn state red...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-campaign-rally-new-mexico-democrat-leaning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just hours after New York City prosecutors went on the offensive by subpoenaing his tax returns, President Trump took the stage in Democratic-leaning New Mexico on Monday night for a campaign rally that demonstrates his own aggressive tack going into the 2020 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREFOX Owner Wants To Create New Internet Without Ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90403645/mozilla-and-creative-commons-want-to-reimagine-the-internet-without-ads-and-they-have-100m-to-do-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The funds would support projects using a new “web monetization” protocol, including open source tools and individual creators</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>