<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Dystopian'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/video-south-dakota-teachers-scrambling-092649863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The teachers were seen stuffing cash in their clothes and helmets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Could Possibly Go Wrong? Biggest Economic Risks '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/economy/what-could-possibly-go-wrong-these-are-the-biggest-economic-risks-for-2022-11639376012236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists have struggled to see ahead in the pandemic. They’re upbeat about next year, but could easily get blindsided again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD'S FIRST OMICRON DEATH IN UK</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10303843/Omicron-makes-40-new-Covid-cases-London-Boris-Johnson-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NHS leaders said No10 needs to be prepared to introduce stricter curbs than Plan B - which includes work from home and face masks - if Omicron is on the brink of overwhelming the NHS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force discharges 27 for refusal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/13/air-force-discharged-vaccine-524167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force gave its forces until Nov. 2 to get the vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg husband mocks Biden restarting student loan payments: 'No thank you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/buttigiegs-husband-biden-admin-restarting-student-loan-payments-next-month-no-thank-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg's husband, Chasten, appeared less than enthusiastic about having to repay his student loans, writing, "no thank you," in an Instagram story on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR porn use on rise as female users triple...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4264878/vr-porn-on-the-rise-more-female-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRTUAL reality porn is rising in popularity, according to a new study. Researchers interviewed thousands of people from the UK and US and found over 83% of VR headset users in the study had watche…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA to reimpose statewide indoor mask mandate for month...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/california-mask-mandate-covid-19-pandemic-rules/11335487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is reimposing an indoor mask mandate for counties that don't already have their own such measure in place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Altering Weather to 'Fight Droughts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dg3kb/scientists-are-altering-weather-to-fight-droughts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of evidence to support the effectiveness of cloud seeding has grown in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS:  Workers Threatened With Firing If They Left...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/kentucky-tornado-factory-workers-threatened-firing-left-tornado-employ-rcna8581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;heard the warning sirens and wanted to leave the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: At least 74 dead, over 100 still missing in tornado aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/13/kentucky-tornado-aftermath-dozens-dead-over-100-still-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 64 people are dead and more than 100 still missing in Kentucky after tornadoes ravaged the area, Gov. Andy Beshear said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA GETS 1ST OMICRON CASE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10305599/China-detects-case-Omicron-hundreds-thousands-placed-quarantine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in the northern city of Tianjin confirmed the case in an individual who entered the country from an undisclosed overseas location, according to the Tianjin Daily newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside abandoned sex dens...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/13/inside-the-abandoned-sex-dens-jeffrey-epstein-shared-with-ghislaine-maxwell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never-before-seen photos of the estates the perv shared with his “lady of the house” have come to light amid the ongoing trial of Maxwell, who is charged with grooming many of the late …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid tension, Southern Baptist women lead where they can...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-baptist-6c5ea89af77883048855b41e4bc30963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jacki King, the women’s minister at Second Baptist Church in Conway, Arkansas, first felt a call to ministry as a college student. She decided to follow it, giving up her pre-med major and her spot on a college softball team for ministry training at a small Bible school with a mostly male student body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway bans serving of alcohol in bid to halt outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211213191518-an8m4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NORWAY-OMICRON (URGENT):Norway bans serving of alcohol in bid to halt Omicron outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools draw up emergency plans over fears they could shut...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/politics/17022820/schools-close-again-after-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCHOOLS have been told to make sure all their Covid contingency plans are up to scratch in case Omicron forces them to push the panic button. No10 today said there’s “no plans” fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>48 Congressmen violated federal conflicts-of-interest law...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/conflicted-congress-key-findings-stock-act-finances-investing-2021-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insider's new investigative reporting project reveals the depths of lawmakers' conflicts-of-interest, potential self-dealing, and violations of a federal corruption law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don's new social site forces users to donate to reserve usernames...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/trump-social-media-reserve-username-fee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People are receiving texts inviting them to reserve a username for Donald Trump's new social media platform—for a fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech removes drone threat from Pope mass...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/exclusive-israeli-tech-removes-drone-threat-from-pope-mass-688639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIRD of 20 to 30-year-olds using Buy Now Pay Later schemes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10305465/Almost-20-30-year-olds-using-Buy-Pay-Later-schemes-shopping.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial schemes, which are now provided by most household name retailers, let UK customers their shopping in monthly instalments interest-free rather than upfront.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Transitory' was 'worst inflation call in history' of Fed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/13/el-erian-says-transitory-was-the-worst-inflation-call-in-the-history-of-the-fed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calling inflation "transitory" was a historically bad move for the Federal Reserve, according to Allianz chief economic advisor Mohamed El-Erian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even worse start overseas...</title>
      <link>https://showbuzzdaily.com/articles/behind-the-us-worldwide-weekend-box-office-12-12-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets jabbed 10 times  -- in one day!</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/national/health/coronavirus/127245863/covid19-man-receives-up-to-10-vaccines-in-one-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man is believed to have been paid for the jabs and to have visited several vaccination centres. Health officials are &amp;quot;very concerned&amp;quot;, and are investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ORDERS STATE DEPT TO ISSUE PASSPORTS ONLINE...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/biden-executiv-order-government-modernize</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The order will direct 17 agencies to overhaul the way they interact with Americans, including allowing them to apply for things like passports online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKER DEAD AFTER WARNING WAREHOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/world/amazon-worker-trying-to-warn-colleagues-one-of-first-identified-victims-among-70-dead-in-tornadoes/ar-AARIUWp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clayton Cope, 29, wanted to warn his coworkers the storm was coming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says he will fly  Noah's ark spaceship packed full of animals to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10304483/Elon-Musk-named-Time-Magazines-2021-Person-Year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk has been named Time magazine's 2021 Person of the Year for 'creating solutions to an existential crisis' and 'for driving society's most daring and disruptive transformations.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors relive horror; 'All could hear was screams'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10303237/Deadliest-storm-Kentuckys-HISTORY-kills-94-identified-victims-including-judge-43-little-boy-Devastating-pictures-survivors-picking-remains-homes-Putin-sends-condolences.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Survivors of a deadly tornado that killed at least 94 people on Friday night spoke out on Sunday about what they experienced, with many sharing their stories inside a candle factory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Blood From Athletes Could Keep Brains Of Sedentary People Healthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/blood-alzheimers-couch-potatoes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists identified a brain-boosting protein in the blood of active mice. When injected into sedentary mice, the couch potatoes saw the same improvements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad beaten to death while putting up Christmas decorations...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article256551311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men armed with blunt objects attacked the man in his front yard, outlets report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight Attendants Blame Airport Drinking for Stoking Mask Anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-12-13/flight-attendants-blame-airport-drinking-for-stoking-mask-anger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers Sent to Quarantine Camps in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-require-quarantine-camp-134217885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong will require inbound travellers from the United States to spend seven days at a government quarantine camp, after a passenger coming from the US tested positive for the Omicron variant of Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sad' Christmas tree brings town together...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/nation-world/national/article256529971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Even Charlie Brown’s Christmas tree looked better than this sad spruce.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooter opens fire on Walk of Fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4259900/hollywood-walk-fame-shooting-gunman-vicente-fernandez/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GUNMAN opened fire on the Hollywood Walk of Fame as fans gathered to mourn the late Mexican singer Vicente Fernández, reports say. Cops said they received calls of a shooting that occurred on the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WEST SIDE STORY' LATEST BOXOFFICE BUST...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/12/11/box-office-calamity-for-oscar-buzzed-west-side-story-disney-overreach-on-high-priced-tix-discouraging-hard-hit-audiences</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  WALLACE OUT AT FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/end-of-an-era-chris-wallaces-departure-from-fox-news-sets-off-a-media-and-political-firestorm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The political mediaverse was electrified by Chris Wallace's surprise announcement that he's leaving Fox News effective immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Oz ending show after 13 seasons amid senate run...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/dr-oz-show-canceled-1235061640/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The show will be replaced by a new series hosted by Daphne Oz titled 'The Good Dish.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets vaccinated 10 times  -- in one day!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-gets-vaccinated-up-to-10-times-in-single-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man allegedly got vaccinated against COVID-19 as many as 10 times in a single day. Here's why:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Moviegoing conditions remain impaired'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/west-side-story-box-office-debut-soft-1235131508/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Audiences didn’t open their wallets to see the infamous rivalry between the Sharks and the Jets play out on the big screen. “West Side Story,” Steven Spielberg’s remake of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Globes Nominations Prove DOA With Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/golden-globes-nominations-hfpa-scandal-1234889846/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if you held a Golden Globes and no one was there, or really cared? Mired in controversy and canceled for 2022 by NBC, that is the thorny question and reality facing the Hollywood Foreign Press…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX IN PHILLY TO EAT OUT</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/covid-19-vaccination-philadelphia-restaurants-indoor-dining-philly-vaccine-mandate/11334019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia officials announced Monday that proof of a COVID-19 vaccine will soon be required to eat inside a restaurant or food establishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES Analysis: If Awards Show Announces Noms But Nobody Cares, Have They Really Voted?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/golden-globes-nominations-nobody-cares/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hollywood Foreign Press took time out from their self-improvement push to release nominations that aren't likely to have any impact on this awards season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin admits moonlighted as taxi driver after collapse of Soviet Union...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4261913/putin-moonlighted-taxi-driver-soviet-union-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has revealed he moonlighted as a taxi driver after the fall of the Soviet Union.  The now billionaire Russian president said the economic turmoil in the early 1990s triggered by…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does 'Sex Guru' With Million Followers Go on Run?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sex-guru-still-preaching-million-025824283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyTo hear him tell it, there isn’t much that self-proclaimed “godman” Paramahamsa Nithyananda can’t do with his alleged supernatural powers. Want to hear a cow or monkey speak Sanskrit? He’s your man. Heal the blind? Check. ESP, stop sunrise, see through walls? The swami says he can do all these and more. And if you swear your fealty to him and start making donations, he’ll teach you how to do them too.Nithyananda, who claims to be the physical embodiment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi will stay around to lead through next election -- and beyond?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/12/politics/nancy-pelosi-house-democrats-leadership-2022/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi will stay until at least after the midterm elections, extending her nearly 20-year run as the House's top Democrat after she turns 82 and, perhaps, beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hawaii ultra-luxury real estate market smashes records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/13/hawaiis-ultra-luxe-real-estate-is-smashing-records-heres-whats-selling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The volume and the velocity of Hawaii's real estate market have shattered every record and historical norm previously held," said Hawaii Life CEO Matt Beall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New telescope can 'look back in time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/james-webb-space-telescope-60-minutes-2021-12-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Pelley reports on the James Webb Space Telescope, due to launch December 22. Scientists hope it will be able to see the universe's first stars and galaxies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake anyone? AI synthetic media tech enters perilous phase...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211213055748-k9gqz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laws specifically aimed at online abuse using deepfake technology have been passed in some jurisdictions, including China, South Korea, and California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her INSTA Handle Was 'Metaverse.' Last Month, It Vanished...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/13/her-instagram-handle-was-metaverse-last-month-it-vanished/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY, Australia — In October, Thea-Mai Baumann, an Australian artist and technologist, found herself sitting on prime internet real estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious case of map and disappearing Taiwan minister at U.S. democracy summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/curious-case-map-disappearing-taiwan-minister-us-democracy-summit-2021-12-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video feed of a Taiwanese minister was cut during U.S. President Joe Biden's Summit for Democracy last week after a map in her slide presentation showed Taiwan in a different color to China, which claims the island as its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waited, panicked, prayed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211213013839-wy0qf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/TORNADOES-MAYFIELD RESIDENTS (PIX, TV):Tales of survival: Mayfield residents waited, panicked, prayed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At AMAZON Site, Twister Collided With Peak Delivery Season...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/12/at-amazon-site-tornado-collided-with-companys-peak-delivery-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every day as Christmas nears, Amazon’s share of online sales typically rises, as customers turn to the e-commerce giant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo lands 130 miles away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/photo-from-kentucky-home-hit-by-fornado-found-in-indiana-74cb89f25f533d45257cd9240b6acf9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Katie Posten walked outside Saturday morning to her car parked in her driveway, she saw something that looked like a note or receipt stuck to the windshield. She grabbed it and saw it was a black and white photo of a woman in a striped sundress and headscarf holding a little boy in her lap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don, O'Reilly Play to Empty Seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/donald-trump-bill-oreilly-tour-begins-empty-seats-florida-live-arena-1658541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Empty seats were seen at the FLA Live Arena in Sunrise, Florida, for the first stop of Trump and O'Reilly's "History Tour."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME NAMES MUSK PERSON OF YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/person-of-the-year-2021-elon-musk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visionary. Showman. Iconoclast. Troll. How Elon Musk is reshaping our world—and beyond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC crew robbed in Oakland...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/585511-nbc-news-crew-robbed-in-oakland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NBC Sports crew working on assignment in Oakland, California was robbed at gunpoint Saturday morning, according to a report from The Mercury News,&amp;nb</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members of Congress publicly blast FACEBOOK but quietly invest in tech giant...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/congress-holding-stocks-facebook-twitter-disney-fox-news-2021-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers held stock in news companies, television networks, and social-media giants, an Insider investigation found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Loves Poking the Bear. Will SEC Claw Him?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-12-13/tesla-ceo-elon-musk-can-t-stop-taunting-the-sec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>São Paulo has fully vaccinated 100% of adults. Will it be enough?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/s-c3-a3o-paulo-says-it-has-fully-vaccinated-more-than-100-percent-of-its-adults-will-it-be-enough-to-stop-omicron/ar-AARLmir</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel writer's bad review of MICHELIN-starred restaurant went viral. Chef responded with images of horses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-travel-writer-s-bad-review-of-a-michelin-starred-restaurant-went-viral-the-chef-responded-with-images-of-horses/ar-AARLeqf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady caps NFL milestone game with game-winning overtime TD pass...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/brady-caps-nfl-milestone-game-222047194.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tampa Bay's superstar quarterback Tom Brady nabbed yet another NFL passing record Sunday, but he saved his best for last in the Buccaneers' 33-27 overtime triumph over the Buffalo Bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 panel to vote on holding Meadows in contempt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/steve-bannon-donald-trump-presidential-elections-capitol-siege-elections-e59a77b5b4259276163219f009ab6459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House panel investigating the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES announces noms to skeptical Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-business-arts-and-entertainment-golden-globe-awards-tom-cruise-aef0f54303558fb04ba325331e368258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Hollywood Foreign Press Association will announce nominations to the 79th Golden Globes on Monday morning. But will Hollywood care? The press association, often ridiculed, even by its own hosts, this year went from punchline to pariah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim at critical crossroads decade into rule...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-seoul-economy-96537a68bbbcce440bd5e63bc409542a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — Too young. Too weak. Too inexperienced. Since taking power following his father’s sudden death 10 years ago this week, Kim Jong Un has erased those widespread doubts that greeted his early attempts to extend his family’s brutal dynastic grip over North Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey's Central Bank intervenes as currency hits record low...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-middle-east-turkey-recep-tayyip-erdogan-efdeb09244e84b72278d27812adca795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — The Turkish currency dipped to an all-time low Monday amid another anticipated interest rate cut later this week and after the S&amp;amp;P credit rating agency downgraded its outlook for Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis police spending RISES as defund movement fades...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/minneapolis-police-spending-rises-as-defund-movement-fades/600126143/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some council members lamented the increase, though they made few efforts to reduce it. They focused instead on trying to increase funding for violence prevention and mental health services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 warns Russia of 'massive consequences' if invades Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/g7-warns-russia-of-e2-80-98massive-e2-80-99-consequences-if-ukraine-invaded/ar-AARK9IC </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDakota teachers competed for $1 bills on hockey rink. Critics called game 'terrible' and 'dehumanizing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/sd-teachers-competed-for-241-bills-on-a-hockey-rink-critics-called-the-game-e2-80-98terrible-e2-80-99-and-e2-80-98dehumanizing-e2-80-99/ar-AARLg53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials struggle to count dead: 'Sill finding bodies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/kentucky-officials-struggle-to-count-the-dead-after-tornadoes-e2-80-98we-e2-80-99re-still-finding-bodies-e2-80-99/ar-AARKmSG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dystopian'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/south-dakota-teachers-classroom-funding-b1974857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The teachers were seen stuffing cash in their clothes and helmets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>75% of town gone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/13/us/kentucky-tornadoes-storms-monday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who had their lives ripped apart in mere moments by violent and unforgiving tornadoes over the weekend are now dealing with a new reality -- seeking the basic needs of food and shelter while surrounded by devastation and uncertainty over the fate of their neighbors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strangers find family mementos miles away...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Prom-photo-baby-pic-Strangers-find-family-16696801.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brad Hale was getting ready to leave his house Saturday when he noticed something white...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Beto show Dems how to lose less badly in rural America?</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/politics/can-beto-orourke-show-democrats-how-to-lose-less-badly-in-rural-america/article_a8ee6fa3-5bc6-5b9a-ba12-74bb1db07833.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DE LEON, Texas — Nobody expects Beto O'Rourke to win Comanche County in the Texas gubernatorial race — least of all, Beto O'Rourke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock-Market Bravado Tested as Bonds Flash Policy Danger...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/stock-market-bravado-tested-as-bonds-flash-fed-policy-danger-1.1694378</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fastest inflation print in nearly 40 years is rattling nerves on Wall Street where economically sensitive trades are hitched to an ultra-accommodative Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Lawyers Plan to Call 35 Defense Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/ghislaine-maxwell-s-lawyers-plan-to-call-35-defense-witnesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell’s Lawyers Plan to Call 35 Defense Witnesses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: 'If necessary to get another boost, just have to deal with it'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/585462-fauci-if-it-becomes-necessary-to-get-yet-another-boost-then-well-just-have</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House medical adviser Anthony Fauci on Sunday said health officials will "have to deal with it” if it is determined that another COVID-19 booster shot is necessary to protect against the virus,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robberies. Drought. Tent Camps. LA's Next Mayor Faces Litany of Crises...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/12/robberies-drought-tent-camps-los-angeless-next-mayor-faces-a-litany-of-crises/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Peter Nichols has lived for 22 years in a two-bedroom Cape Cod in the Fairfax District, in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Tornadoes kill dozens in 5 states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tornadoes-business-arkansas-kentucky-mayfield-b6ef6a901cc2e4552e760a36c749937c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAYFIELD, Ky. (AP) — Rescuers were forced to crawl over the dead to get to the living at a Kentucky candle factory walloped by a tornado, part of an unusual cluster that killed dozens in the Midwest and South and flattened whole towns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images, expert suggest Iranian space launch coming...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/iran-space-launches-nuclear-deal-72a010e26d3ff0395fd09b7c1b3e51d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Iran appears to be preparing for a space launch as negotiations continue in Vienna over its tattered nuclear deal with world powers, according to an expert and satellite images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALLACE OUT AT FOX</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-chris-wallace-to-leave-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Wallace is leaving Fox News.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
