<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Tucker Carlson Undergoes Emergency Back Surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvn8q8/tucker-carlson-pumped-full-of-fentanyl-emerges-with-new-understanding-of-the-opioid-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I just thought that was the most interesting fucking thing that had ever happened to me,” he said after emergency back surgery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  'Climate Change' Protestors Confront Manchin Driving Maserati: 'We Want to Live!'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/joe-manchin-maserati-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin (D-WV) was loudly confronted by numerous Sunrise Movement climate change activists on Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW:  BUT BIDEN DID BETTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msnbc.com/rachel-maddow/watch/in-2021-elections-biden-out-performs-past-30-years-of-first-year-presidents-125338693867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Maddow points out the pattern in recent history of first year presidents going all the way back to George H.W. Bush losing the governorship of Virginia and New Jersey to the opposing party, and since Democrats actually won New Jersey, losing in Virginia doesn't necessarily warrant a freak out no matter what the Beltway media says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two dead after drug dealers open fire at five-star Hyatt in Cancun...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10167287/Gunmen-storm-five-star-Hyatt-hotel-Cancun.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people believed to be drug dealers have reportedly died following a shooting at a five-star hotel in Cancun that is popular with American tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst who aided Trump-Russia dossier charged with lying...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/04/arrest-illustrates-how-steele-dossier-was-political-dirty-trick-by-hillary-clinton/https://nypost.com/2021/11/04/arrest-illustrates-how-steele-dossier-was-political-dirty-trick-by-hillary-clinton/https://nypost.com/2021/11/04/arrest-illustrates-how-steele-dossier-was-political-dirty-trick-by-hillary-clinton/https://nypost.com/2021/11/04/arrest-illustrates-how-steele-dossier-was-political-dirty-trick-by-hillary-clinton/https://nypost.com/2021/11/04/arrest-illustrates-how-steele-dossier-was-political-dirty-trick-by-hillary-clinton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to deflect asteroid in test of 'planetary defense'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211104-nasa-to-deflect-asteroid-in-test-of-planetary-defense</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1998 Hollywood blockbuster "Armageddon," Bruce Willis and Ben Affleck race to save the Earth from being pulverized by an asteroid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: High Schoolers Accused Of Murdering Spanish Teacher...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nohema-graber-iowa-high-school-teacher-killed-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nohema Graber had been reported missing several hours before her body was discovered in a nearby park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How white women propelled win...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/how-white-women-helped-propel-republicans-victory-virginia-n1283153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats dismissed Glenn Youngkin's emphasis on schools, but it may have helped cost them an election in a state they were favored to win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Questions Grounds for Keeping Jan. 6 Docs Secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/judge-questions-trump-s-grounds-for-keeping-jan-6-documents-secret/ar-AAQkxrz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A federal judge on Thursday expressed skepticism about Donald J. Trump’s attempt to block from release a wide range of documents related to the Capitol riot, signaling that she might be open to allowing a congressional committee scrutinizing the violence to pore over hundreds of files that the former president wants to keep secret. At a hearing by video conference, Judge Tanya S. Chutkan of the U.S. District Court for the District...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANCUN: Resort guests told to shelter in place amid reports of active shooter...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/cancun-mexico-hotel-shooting/11199155/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staff at the Hyatt Ziva Riviera Cancun hotel in Mexico on Thursday told guests to seek shelter amid reports of an active shooter at the resort, a person staying at the hotel confirmed to ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials Warn Of Kids Selling New Psychedelic Street Drug 'Paint'...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/04/citrus-heights-mesa-verde-new-drug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;School officials in Citrus Heights are warning parents about students selling a new street drug. It’s a pill with psychedelic effects and is known to be highly addictive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANCHIN:  This country is center-right...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/joe-manchin-suggests-we-re-a-center-right-country-here-s-what-the-data-show/ar-AAQkmK3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More Americans say they're "conservative" than "liberal" or "progressive." But that's not the whole story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe rights body's pro-hijab campaign sparks outcry in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20211104-europe-rights-body-s-pro-hijab-campaign-sparks-outcry-in-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Plunges 21%...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/barstool-sports-portnoy-violent-sex-allegations-stock-1235105157/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED: Shares of Penn National Gaming fell more than 20% Thursday, after the publication of an article in which several women alleged that they had “violent and humiliating” sexual en…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARSTOOL Portnoy Accused of 'Disturbing' Sexual Encounters...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/barstool-founder-dave-portnoy-accused-of-disturbing-sexual-encounters-in-new-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent report from Business Insider featured damning accusations of Barstool founder Dave Portnoy having disturbing sexual encounters with young women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu Shots Hard To Find As Demand Surges...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/11/04/flu-shots-hard-to-find-bay-area-influenza-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flu season is here, but the vaccine to protect you may be difficult to find as the demand surges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admits Saying N-Word...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/11/04/suns-owner-robert-sarver-accused-of-repeatedly-using-n-word/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suns owner Robert Sarver is being accused of using the N-word on multiple occasions ... and is admitting he said it once while quoting a player.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Robert Sarver's 17-year tenure as owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/32440987/phoenix-suns-robert-sarver-allegations-racism-misogyny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ESPN investigation, featuring interviews with more than 70 current and former Suns employees, reveals accusations of racism and misogyny against owner Robert Sarver -- and a toxic workplace many employees believe his behavior emboldened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Town Built to Resemble LEGOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/european-town-built-resemble-lego-blocks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architecturaldigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The architects allowed nostalgia guide their creative decisions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioter who bragged she wouldn't go to jail gets prison term...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-crime-texas-prisons-social-media-0f9e470c9871a2f5f1440df76ee23671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A real estate agent from suburban Dallas who flaunted her participation in the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan city on edge as lead water crisis persists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-environment-and-nature-michigan-poverty-12586348a94d5d57de7de6e15df23421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BENTON HARBOR, Mich. (AP) — Shortly after sunrise on a recent Saturday in Benton Harbor, Michigan, residents began lining up for free bottled water so they could drink and cook without fear of the high levels of lead in the city’s tap water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air taxis promised to fly above potholes of Rome...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211104-air-taxis-promised-to-fly-above-potholes-of-rome</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With streets filled with potholes, buses erupting in flames and soul-crushing traffic on the ground in the Eternal City, some say the only way is up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton Treasury Chief Sounds Alarm on Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/clinton-treasury-chief-sounds-alarm-on-inflation-biden-administration-still-not-fully-recognizing-the-gravity-of-the-situation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Treasury Secretary Larry Summers on Thursday advised the Biden administration to take the threat of rising inflation more seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Removed After Joke In Courtroom About Black Man Shot By Police...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/11/04/kyle-rittenhouse-trial-juror-removed-joke-jacob-blake-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors said the juror asked a courtroom deputy "Why did the Kenosha police shoot Jacob Blake 7-times? Because they ran out of bullets," saying the joke shows poor taste, and showed racial bias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Necrophiliac murderer confesses he had sex with 99 corpses...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3998557/bedsit-murder-david-fuller-sex-bodies-morgue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MONSTER who had sex with at least 99 corpses in hospital mortuaries – including children as young as nine – today admitted murdering two women and raping them as they were dying. Davi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor uncovers link between noses, penis size...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/3988708/doctor-true-mans-nose-reveal-big-penis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you’re planning on getting the tape measure out to measure your soldier then think again. One doctor said the age old rumour of whether or not you can tell how big a man’s penis is b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mediterranean Diet BAD For You? Experts Warn Could Weaken Immune System...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mediterranean-diet-pesticides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors say fruit, vegetables, and whole grains are the source of most of these toxins when they come from traditional farming techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF THE BILLIONAIRES:  COURT REJECTS BEZOS CHALLENGE TO MUSK NASA DEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/bezos-nasa-musk-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin first appealed the NASA decision through the U.S. Government Accountability Office. When that didn't pan out, the Bezos-backed space outfit took to the courts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narrow NJ victory does little to ease anxieties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/murphy-e2-80-99s-narrow-win-in-new-jersey-does-little-to-ease-democratic-anxieties/ar-AAQic8q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Phil Murphy won his fight for reelection Wednesday night, but the margin appeared likely to be slight. Despite the victory, a Republican surge statewide alarmed Democratic leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: RAIDERS Player In Deadly Crash Was Driving At 156 MPH!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/raiders-release-receiver-henry-ruggs-iii-following-fatal-car-accident-and-pending-felony-dui-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say Ruggs was going 156 mph prior to crash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NON-TRUMP CANDIDATES SURGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republicans-elections-youngkin-trump-b132a704-505d-4b54-a9bc-a8c273715514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are thriving despite Trump's tactics and antics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans sees Youngkin as blueprint for future...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/579907-republicans-see-youngkin-win-as-blueprint-for-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are eyeing Glenn Youngkin’s successful campaign for the Virginia governor’s mansion as a roadmap for the 2022 midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS SOUND ALARM...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/03/reeling-from-surprise-losses-democrats-sound-the-alarm-for-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Reeling from a barrage of unexpected losses, an array of Democrats on Wednesday pleaded with President Biden and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck driver who knocked out longtime Dem leader spent $153 on campaign...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/ed-durr-steve-sweeney-nj-senate-president/11198116/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey's longtime state Senate president Steve Sweeney has lost reelection, falling to Republican Ed Durr, who spent less than $200 on the race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zap Away Negative Thoughts?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/brain-stimulation-mental-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stimulating the brain's internal capsule both improves mental function and helps patients dealing with conditions like depression focus their thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-stakes hearing in Trump effort to block release of presidential docs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/04/politics/trump-records-hearing-january-6/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The power Donald Trump holds as a former president will be put to the test on Thursday, as a federal judge is set to hear arguments on whether Trump can keep secret records from his White House about his attempt to overturn the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Shows U.S. Destroyer Standoff With Iranian Vessels Over Oil Tanker...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42987/video-shows-u-s-destroyers-very-intimate-standoff-with-iranian-vessels-over-seized-oil-tanker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's raid on an oil tanker resulted in an incredibly close encounter between its gunboats and a U.S. Navy destroyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bardot fined for 'savages' jibe against French Indian Ocean island...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211104-bardot-fined-for-savages-jibe-against-french-indian-ocean-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French screen legend turned animal rights activist Brigitte Bardot was on Thursday fined 20,000 euros ($23,000) by a court on France's Indian Ocean island of La Reunion over a 2019 diatribe where she…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Claim to Improve Brain Function With Implants...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/scientists-brain-function-implants-ai</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This could be a totally new approach in treating mental illness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst who aided Trump-Russia dossier arrested...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-arrests-john-durham-9d2344081036235309346ad95b14a8bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A Russian analyst who helped provide information for a dossier of research used during the Trump-Russia investigation has been arrested as part of an ongoing special counsel investigation, a person familiar with the matter said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Natalie Wood assaulted by Kirk Douglas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-lifestyle-movies-los-angeles-hollywood-2edc063a1a5529bd6cd7fdca096672cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For decades, it's been one of Hollywood's darkest rumors: A teen-age Natalie Wood was sexually assaulted by a top movie star more than twice her age when she met with him at a hotel in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RUST' film armorer says someone may have put bullet in gun...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/alec-baldwin-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-movies-84daca775fdcc3a391d4416e8a18e59f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman in charge of weapons on the movie set where actor Alec Baldwin fatally shot cinematographer Halyna Hutchins said Wednesday night that she had inspected the gun Baldwin shot but doesn’t know how a live bullet ended up inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Jake Paul Fight His Way Out of Trouble?</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/11/08/can-jake-paul-fight-his-way-out-of-trouble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A polarizing social-media star seeks an unlikely second act in boxing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi From Hell at Center of Gruesome Cult Murders...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rabbi-hell-center-gruesome-cult-090120927.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sander Koning/AFP via Getty ImagesJERUSALEM—A Jerusalem judge says that Eliezer Berland, one of Israel’s most infamous cult leaders, who repeatedly slipped through the hands of law enforcement by fleeing the country and securing reduced jail sentences through plea deals, has implicated himself in two gory unsolved murders dating back to 1986.Following the arrests in recent weeks of seven of Berland’s followers, the defrocked rabbi, a convicted sex offender, was arrested on Monday at a prison in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ammo Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/11/03/ammo-shortage-minnesota-deer-hunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DNR has already sold more than 220,000 deer-hunting licenses, but those hunters might have a hard time finding some of the supplies they need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 1 Black Juror Chosen for Trial Over Ahmaud Arbery Killing...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/03/only-1-black-juror-is-chosen-for-trial-over-ahmaud-arberys-killing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK, Ga. — After a grueling process that lasted two and a half weeks, a jury was selected on Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Grave concern' over Covid in Europe as German cases soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211104-grave-concern-over-covid-in-europe-as-german-cases-soar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization expressed "grave concern" Thursday over the rising pace of coronavirus infections in Europe, as Germany registered its biggest daily increase since the start of the pand…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat 'Sticker Shock' Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/meat-sticker-shock-looms-as-3-000-bonuses-fail-to-end-worker-shortfall-1.1676898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recruiting is only getting harder for a U.S. industry that demands grueling work and has the taint of deadly Covid outbreaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5-year-olds have to show vax cards in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2021/11/03/5-year-olds-soon-have-to-show-vaccine-cards-in-san-francisco-1392237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco Health Officer Susan Philip said the requirement won't kick in for at least two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA mandates shots or tests for big companies by Jan. 4...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-business-health-medicaid-29c2262c336bcfc38da2d14b251daf51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of millions of Americans who work at companies with 100 or more employees will need to be vaccinated against COVID-19 by Jan. 4 or get tested for the virus weekly under government rules that took effect Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK first to authorize Covid pill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-europe-health-pandemics-17905e9505a5ff50f2436b2bcb22f59f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain granted conditional authorization on Thursday to the first pill shown to successfully treat COVID-19 so far. It also is the first country to OK the treatment from drugmaker Merck, although it wasn't immediately clear how quickly the pill would be available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto addiction: Hidden epidemic?</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2021-11-crypto-addiction-hidden-epidemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Matt Danzico began seeing cryptocurrency logos in the packaging of grocery store items, he knew he had a problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China has debated attacking Taiwan-controlled islands, official says...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211104114342-6j7mo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/ (PIX, TV):China has debated attacking Taiwan-controlled islands, Taiwan official says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal Beaten Unconscious, Suffers Broken Ribs In Attack By 16-Year-Old Girl At School...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/04/principal-knocked-out-attacked-assaulted-patricia-lampron-henderson-inclusion-school-dorchester-boston/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dr. William W. Henderson Inclusion School in Dorchester will be closed Thursday after a principal and another staff member were attacked by a student during dismissal Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu hopes for comeback dim as Israel passes budget...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-elections-middle-east-benjamin-netanyahu-tel-aviv-ff814fb157de978e694a6dafd501599c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Former Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu watched from the sidelines Thursday as the government that toppled him after 12 years in power passed a national budget, dealing a major blow to his hopes of a swift return to the country's top office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black, Latino voters often pick Dems. But Republicans of color just won 2 big 'firsts' in Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/latino-and-black-voters-have-long-preferred-democrats-but-republicans-of-color-just-achieved-2-big-firsts-in-virginia/ar-AAQibXp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winsome Sears is the first Black woman elected to statewide office in Virginia, and Jason Miyares is the first Latino to reach that milestone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden urges swift action as Dems scramble to deflect voter anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-urges-swift-action-as-democrats-scramble-to-deflect-voter-anger/ar-AAQig4X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president did not take responsibility for Tuesday’s losses, saying “people are upset and uncertain” but that the passage of his agenda would help them and the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force says 8,500 miss deadline...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-b145976254f6deab1ae3130cf8159b00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nearly 8,500 active duty members of the Air Force and Space Force have missed the deadline for getting COVID-19 vaccinations, including 800 who flatly refused and nearly 5,000 with pending requests for a religious exemption, the Air Force said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer says Ghislaine jail conditions rival Hannibal Lecter...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/579997-lawyer-says-ghislaine-maxwells-jail-conditions-rival-hannibal-lecter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer representing Jeffrey Epstein associate Ghislaine Maxwell claimed that she has endured jail conditions similar to what fictional character Hannibal Lecter experienced in the 1991 film "The Silence of the Lambs."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carville blames 'stupid wokeness'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/579991-carville-blames-stupid-wokeness-for-democratic-losses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic political strategist James Carville blamed his party's recent losses and weak performance in state elections on "stupid wokeness" on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Prices Near Record High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-food-prices-getting-closer-090000591.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global food costs jumped last month, extending a march toward a record and piling more inflationary pressure on consumers and governments.Most Read from BloombergSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItChina’s Climate Goals Hinge on a $440 Billion Nuclear BuildoutAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’Results on Key Ballot Initiatives, From Policing to the EnvironmentInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideA U</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is world protesting so much? New study claims to have answers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/why-is-the-world-protesting-so-much-a-new-study-claims-to-have-some-answers/ar-AAQiLfy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of protests around the world more than tripled in less than fifteen years, often prompted by demands for "real democracy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court signals it's likely to bolster right to carry concealed gun in public...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/majority-of-supreme-court-appears-to-think-ny-gun-law-is-too-restrictive/ar-AAQi4qu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Supreme Court justices indicated Wednesday that they believe Americans generally have a right to carry a handgun outside the home for self-defense and that a New York law requiring special justification for getting such a permit is too restrictive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study finds 28 million extra years of life lost...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Covid-study-finds-some-28-million-extra-years-of-16591095.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 28 million extra years of human life were lost in 2020, a year marked by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China rapidly expanding its nuke arsenal, Pentagon says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/03/china-is-rapidly-expanding-its-nuclear-arsenal-pentagon-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington has previously called on China to join the U.S. and Russia in a new arms control treaty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay-to-view autopsy organizer defends $500 event...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-pay-view-autopsy-organizer-015530405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organizer of a pay-to-view autopsy in the United States defended the event Wednesday, after an outcry by the family of the dead man who did not know he would be dissected in front of a live audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey weighs 'outlaw' bid for TX gov...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/matthew-mcconaughey-weighs-outlaw-bid-053111254.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis, sex and politics combine in Chinese #MeToo scandal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-tennis-media-social-media-4c0e8bffa89475a545e86112d8efba6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Chinese authorities have squelched virtually all online discussion of sexual assault accusations apparently made by a Chinese professional tennis star against a former top government official, showing how sensitive the ruling Communist Party is to such charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former 'RUST' crew member speaks out about safety concerns...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/News/video/rust-crew-member-speaks-safety-concerns-80944141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lane Luper, a crew member on the movie set of &amp;quot;Rust,&amp;quot; who had quit and left the production the day before the fatal shooting death of Halyna Hutchins, discusses his safety concerns on set.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
