<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GAS HITS 7-YEAR-HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/27/business/memorial-day-gas-prices/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nasty surprise awaits the 34 million drivers expected to hit US roads this Memorial Day weekend — the highest gas prices in seven years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicious Brawl Erupts At ASTROS Game...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/no-love-lost-fans-brawl-during-dodgers-astros-game-wednesday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a hostility between the two teams since the sign-stealing scandal broke in January of 2020, when Major League Baseball revealed that the Astros cheated during their 2017 title run in which they beat the Dodgers in the World Series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimon Sharpens Criticism of Biden Tax Hike Proposal...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dimon-sharpens-criticism-biden-tax-182949093.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. Chief Executive Officer Jamie Dimon has twice in this hearing before a congressional committee sharply criticized President Joe Biden’s proposed tax hikes, which are aimed at people making more than $400,000 and at corporations.He has previously questioned them, but today said that that level of tax increases would be four times bigger than the GOP’s 2017 tax cuts and called that “a mistake.”“The tax increase is actually four times what the tax decrease was from 2017,” he said. “You all know the phrase the devil is in the details, well the details here are all that matter, not the top line of 28%.”His main warning is about global competitiveness. He warns of capital going overseas and other economic problems and says it would make his bank less competitive globally.“If you want to have a healthy, growing, competitive America against the rest of the world, you need a global, competitive tax rate,” he said. “It would be detrimental to a lot of companies, it would push a lot of capital overseas.”Dimon isn’t against all taxes. In yesterday’s Senate Banking hearing he said the U.S. should impose a carbon tax.For more on Wall Street CEOs Testify Before U.S. House Committee, click here for our TOPLive blog.More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever Colorado River water shortage now almost certain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/27/weather/lake-mead-colorado-river-shortage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Lake Mead sunk below a key threshold this week, new projections show continued declines in the key reservoir's supply that could trigger a shortage declaration and water cuts in some states next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-styled satanist beheaded cellmate, but guards didn't notice...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/self-styled-satanist-beheaded-his-cellmate-in-central-california-prison-but-guards-didnt-notice-reports-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convicted killers shared the same cell at Corcoran State Prison. But on the morning of March 9, 2019, only one was still alive. Jaime Osuna, 31, had decapitated and dissected the body of his ce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientology secrets spill into open in Masterson rape case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/celebrity/scientology-s-secrets-spill-into-open-in-danny-masterson-rape-case/ar-AAKrWqd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women who have accused Danny Masterson of rape testified that Scientology officials tried to stop them from reporting the alleged attacks to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Making Play for Puerto Rico?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-republicans-think-gop-can-win-in-puerto-rico/ar-AAKrBlp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rick Scott believes Puerto Rico will achieve statehood — and the Florida Republican rejects arguments by some in his party that the Caribbean island territory would elect Democrats to Congress in perpetuity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel vs. Hamas was world's first AI war...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/gaza-news/guardian-of-the-walls-the-first-ai-war-669371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IDF used artificial intelligence and supercomputing during the last conflict with Hamas in the Gaza Strip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No longer confined to fringe, theories move mainstream...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20210527-no-longer-confined-to-the-fringe-ufo-theories-move-into-the-mainstream</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subject of UFOs in the US is getting serious treatment from mainstream media and heavyweight politicians. Next month Congress is set to review a report from the director of national intelligence…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON unveils 'ZenBooth' for overwhelmed employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/amazon-zenbooth-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online retail giant Amazon has unveiled a small booth designed to let overwhelmed warehouse employees "focus on their ... well-being."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors treating Trump Org like it's the mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-york-prosecutors-are-treating-the-trump-organization-like-it-s-the-mob/ar-AAKrT18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much like the mob, the Trump Organization is run by family members and loyalists who've been around for decades. Prosecutors want them to "flip."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will this be the summer of sex?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20210525-are-we-heading-towards-a-summer-of-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that vaccines are rolling out, some are trumpeting plans to make up for a year of isolation. So, is a hedonistic summer in the offing? Not so fast, say experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods' golf future cloudy after crash: 'More painful than anything'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/27/tiger-woods-rehab-process-is-the-most-painful-thing-hes-experienced/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods has never experienced pain like this before. As the golf icon continues his rehab and recovery after a horrifying single-car crash in February, he discussed the post-accident process in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNICKS Fan Banned After Spitting On HAWKS Player...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/trae-young-spit-knicks-fan-banned-indefinitely/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Knicks have announced that the fan who spit on Hawks guard Trae Young has been banned indefinitely from MSG.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest Crypto Conference Coming To Miami...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/worlds-largest-bitcoin-conference-miami-wynwood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you bought into the cryptocurrency craze yet or is it all a bit too confusing? Well get ready because Miami is about to be taken over by Bitcoin 2021, the world’s largest cryptocurrency conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC presenter dies from blood clot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tv/15088900/lisa-shaw-dead-44-bbc-presenter-covid-vaccine-astrazeneca/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “BRILLIANT” BBC radio presenter died in hospital aged 44 after having the AstraZeneca Covid vaccine, her family said today. Lisa Shaw’s devastated relatives told of their heartb…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Tanning salon customer finds dead body on sun bed after woman had two-hour session...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2969273/tan-salon-customer-dead-body-sun-bed-austria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SHOCKED tanning salon customer found a dead woman on a sun bed after she had visited the solarium in Austria for a two-hour session. The client made the grim discovery of the 50-year-old woman in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OOOP:  LeBron accidentally reveals top secret  APPLE headphones...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2968402/lebron-james-beats-earbuds-apple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBRON James has been pictured wearing what appear to be Apple’s highly anticipated “Beats Studio Buds” headphones. Rumours about the Beats earbuds have been circulating for a whi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTuber arrested for tying dog to helium balloons...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/youtuber-arrested-tying-dog-helium-24198814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTuber Guarav Sharma has been detained under animal cruelty laws after tying his pet Pomeranian dog to a bunch of helium balloons and letting it float away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Walsh: My Radio Show Was Canceled By Trump-Supporting Boss!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/radio/just-in-joe-walsh-says-his-radio-show-was-canceled-by-big-trumper-network-boss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never-Trumper Joe Walsh said on Wednesday he lost his radio show because his network is run by a Donald Trump supporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS workers say they are treated like 'coffee-making robots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/starbucks-workers-say-they-are-treated-like-coffee-making-robots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people who work at Starbucks say customers are ordering increasingly complicated drinks that are sapping their will to continue working at the coffee giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Defund police' candidate has car stolen...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/atlanta-defund-the-police-backer-has-car-stolen-by-kids-in-broad-daylight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Atlanta city councilman – who is aiming to be the city's next mayor – had his car stolen by children in broad daylight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime-Tracking App CITIZEN Scraps Plans For 'On-Demand' Police Force...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/citizen-app-peter-thiel-palantir-security-force/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company tested out giving users the ability to summon their own personal police force. This week it pulled the plug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Philly Steakhouse Ripped Over $100 Minimum Per Person Requirement...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/26/philadelphia-steak-48s-100-minimum-policy-social-media-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fancy steakhouse has enacted a strict dining policy that has social media sizzling with criticism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR TRAVEL BOOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/memorial-day-travel-airline-industry-avelo-breeze/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline travel expert says the industry is "recovering faster and better than many expected."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case for Swimming in Wild...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/05/roger-deakin-waterlog-why-wild-swimming/618974/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man’s journey through public waterways—whether sparkling or dirty or algae-filled—challenges us to look differently at the commons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS-ROYCE Boat Tail May Be Most Expensive New Car in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/rolls-royce-boat-tail-may-120200931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 19-foot convertible features crockery from Christofle of Paris, a proper refrigerator and a giant parasol at the back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Wing Scarcity Forcing Restaurants To Pull From Menus...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/chicken-wing-shortage-denver-colorado-restaurants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Denver-area restaurants are removing items from menus or even temporarily closing because they don't have enough chicken wings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: First-Born More Likely To Suffer Heart Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/how-many-siblings-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First-born children generally had a lower risk of non-fatal cardiovascular and coronary events than their younger siblings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys adopt 'accent' of other species when in shared territory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/may/27/monkeys-adopt-accent-of-other-species-when-in-shared-territory-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian Amazon primates found to adapt their calls to get along better with their neighbours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long bath almost as good as long run...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/may/26/hot-tub-health-kick-why-a-long-bath-is-almost-as-good-for-you-as-a-long-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have discovered that prolonged immersion in a piping hot bath has many of the same medical benefits as aerobic exercise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Public transit worker fatally shoots 9, then kills self at San Jose rail yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/active-shooter-near-northern-california-rail-yard-authorities-say-n1268623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A public transit employee, Samuel Cassidy, opened fire on co-workers at the Santa Clara Valley Transportation Authority before taking his own life, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: WIZARDS Star Restrained After Fan Dumps Popcorn On Him...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/26/russell-westbrook-sixers-fan-popcorn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westbrook had to be restrained by multiple people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to Propose $6 Trillion Budget...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/27/biden-to-propose-6-trillion-budget-to-boost-middle-class-and-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden will propose a $6 trillion budget on Friday that would take the United States to its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime boss shakes govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210527-crime-boss-s-wild-claims-shake-turkish-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crime boss's wild claims shake Turkish government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physician warns Tokyo Olympics could spread variants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tokyo-olympic-games-coronavirus-pandemic-health-sports-793b0a9b231b2a148e38beb924f0000a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A physician representing a Japanese medical body warned Thursday that holding the postponed Tokyo Olympics in two months could lead to the spread of variants of the coronavirus. Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-rooted racism, discrimination permeate military...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-racial-injustice-race-and-ethnicity-discrimination-business-4e840e0acc7ef07fd635a312d9375413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Stephanie Davis, who grew up with little, the military was a path to the American dream, a realm where everyone would receive equal treatment. She joined the service in 1988 after finishing high school in Thomasville, Georgia, a small town said to be named for a soldier who fought in the War of 1812.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia Claims Expose Erdogan Vulnerability...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/erdogan-supports-interior-minister-against-corruption-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mafia Claims Expose Erdogan’s Political Vulnerability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Oz, Births of Tasmanian Devils Are Milestone After 3,000 Years...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/27/in-australia-births-of-tasmanian-devils-are-a-milestone-after-3000-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia — Pink, hairless, deaf and blind, the roughly month-old joeys were but the size of a shelled peanut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seychelles Mysteries Pit Anti-Vaxxers Against Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/seychelles-e2-80-99s-covid-mysteries-pit-anti-vaxxers-against-scientists/ar-AAKqFfe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases in the world’s most vaccinated nation are ticking up, forcing researchers to wage war against misinformation on whether jabs are effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT president: Orwell's 1984 could happen in 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-57122120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech executives warned that democracy has to win the AI arms race, in a new BBC Panorama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!  7 MILLION AUSTRALIANS ORDERED INTO NEW COVID LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527003449-ixaur</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Australia's Victoria state to enter COVID-19 lockdown after fresh outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-official who revealed UFO project accuses Pentagon of 'disinformation' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/26/ufo-whistleblower-ig-complaint-pentagon-491098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lue Elizondo's IG complaint asserts that officials have tried to discredit him after he went public in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents flee Melbourne...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9623007/Melbourne-Covid-residents-flee-Victoria-head-Sydney-ahead-imminent-five-day-lockdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An announcement by Acting Victorian Premier James Merlino about the probable lockdown is expected to come at about 9am on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!  7 MILLION AUSTRALIANS ORDERED INTO NEW COVID LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527001417-slw29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (URGENT):Australia's Victoria state to enter snap one-week COVID-19 lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S:  World Faces Longer Supply Shortage as Factories Squeezed...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-faces-longer-supply-shortage-002059342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Eric Li’s factory making glass lampshades for companies including Home Depot Inc. is being stretched to its limits with sales doubling their pre-pandemic level.But like many Chinese manufacturers, he doesn’t plan to expand operations -- a reticence that could slow the pace of China’s economic growth this year and prolong a shortage of goods being felt around the world as demand picks up.Surging prices of raw materials means “margins are compressed,” explains Li, owner of Huizhou Baizhan Glass Co. Ltd., in the southern Chinese province of Guangdong, which makes about $30 million in annual revenue. With the global economic recovery still uneven, “the future is very unclear, so there is not much push to expand capacity,” he adds.The combination of higher input prices, uncertainty about export prospects and a weak recovery in domestic consumer demand meant Chinese manufacturing investment from January to April was 0.4% below the same period in 2019, according to official statistics (comparing to 2019 strips out the distortion of last year’s pandemic data).Due to the vast size of China’s manufacturing sector, that poses a risk both to the nation’s growth -- which is currently predicted to reach 8.5% in 2021, according to a Bloomberg tally of economists’ estimates -- and to a global economy that’s grappling with supply shortages and rising prices.Falling ProfitsWeaker-than-expected investment could have a “sizable” impact on GDP growth this year, said Citigroup Inc.’s China economist, Li-gang Liu. Lower investment may dent imports of capital goods and equipment from developed economies like Japan and Germany, “which in turn could drag their economic recovery and rebound as well,” he added.AnHui HERO Electronic Sci &amp; Tec Co. Ltd. is one of those companies feeling the squeeze. Based in the eastern province of Anhui, the company manufactures capacitors used to make electronic circuits, with sales mainly in the domestic market. Jing Yuan, the founder, says orders are up as much as 30% year-on-year, but profits are down 50% due to increasing materials costs that are not easily passed onto clients.The company is under “huge cash pressure” as it needs to pay half a month in advance of delivery in order to secure copper and other metals, which they previously paid for months after receiving, he said. “The commodity issue has to be addressed by the government,” he added.What Bloomberg Economics Says...Chinese industry is absorbing significant cost pressures from rising commodity prices -- damping the inflationary impact for the rest of the world. Will it last? Our analysis of gross margins suggests it could for a while longer: downstream industries -- where the cost crunch is most severe -- still have a small cushion.David Qu, China economistFor the full report, click here.Input shortages mean some manufacturers aren’t able to make use of their existing facilities, so expansion would be of little use. Chinese electric vehicle maker Nio Inc. suspended production at one of its factories last month, due to a shortage of microchips.Modern Casting Ltd., which makes iron and steel products in Guangdong, issued a note to clients this month saying it would not be able to meet its current orders due to high raw material costs. A member of staff who answered the phone at the company’s office confirmed the note, but declined to give further details.Growth TransitionOn top of the higher input costs, Chinese companies face a bumpy transition toward domestic consumer spending to sustain its post-pandemic recovery.Exports, China’s strong-suit last year, may begin to slow as vaccine roll-outs cause consumers in wealthy countries to shift spending back to services. Meanwhile, the growth rate of Chinese consumer spending has yet to fully recover.Investment sentiment among Chinese small and medium-sized enterprises is below levels seen even in 2018-9 when uncertainties from the U.S.-China trade war were a brake on expansion plans, according to a regular survey of more than 500 Chinese companies by Standard Chartered Plc.“Demand is still mainly underpinned by exports, so domestic companies are aware that this is not sustainable,” said Standard Chartered’s China economist, Lan Shen.While some export-oriented sectors have been pushed to their limits, large amounts of slack remain for manufacturers targeting Chinese consumers due to subdued domestic demand.Retail sales growth was 4.3% in April on a two-year average basis, which strips out base effects from the pandemic, less than half pre-pandemic growth rates. Overall capacity use at China’s manufacturers fell to 77.6% in the first quarter from 78.4% in the previous three months, with the automotive sector hit hardest by overcapacity following three years of declining sales volumes.Even for electric vehicles whose sales are surging, most companies have already built their capacity and will now focus on incremental upgrades. “The majority of the investment has been done,” said Jochen Siebert of JSC Automotive Consulting.China ordered state-owned companies to expand last year, with their investment growth of 5.3% in 2020 from the prior year easily outstripping the 1% increase in private investment. But for a sustainable pick-up in investment, the market, not the state, needs to feel confident.Carsten Holz, an expert on Chinese investment statistics at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, estimates that privately-owned companies have accounted for 87% of manufacturing investment in 2015, the most recent year of available data. They are more sensitive to input costs.“There is a pandemic plus insecurity about future trade given a new U.S. administration, neither of which is conducive to investment that relies on long-term growth prospects,” Holz said.Mixed PoliciesTransport bottlenecks are also a challenge for export-oriented manufacturers. Gordon Gao, who exports gardening products from China, said that he has had to reject 80% of orders this year due to port delays. In one case, an order placed before mid-February could only be shipped three months later when a client finally secured a container.Beijing has tried to improve conditions for private companies by ordering a crackdown on speculation to curb commodity prices and easing access to bank loans.Yet the government continues to gradually withdraw fiscal and monetary stimulus measures introduced amid the pandemic last year. It set a relatively unambitious target of “above 6%” growth for this year, and the Communist Party’s Politburo signaled last month it would prioritize reforms to control house prices and debt growth.“The policy stance has definitely shifted away from supporting growth and back toward de-risking the financial sector,” said Adam Wolfe, an economist at London-based Absolute Strategy Research. “The risks for economic growth seem tilted to the downside, especially for capital-intensive, construction-linked sectors.”For manufacturers such as Li, a longer period of domestic growth and control over input prices will be needed before capacity expansion is on the cards. While his company of 200 workers took on new permanent staff before the pandemic, for now he’d rather pass the risks of investment on to others.“I wouldn’t do that now, I would rather hire some temporary workers and outsource the rest,” he said.More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile rolls out mobility pass for vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/chile-loosen-restrictions-those-vaccinated-against-covid-19-2021-05-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chileans fully vaccinated against COVID-19 will be allowed to move more freely within the country, the government said on Monday, although the nation's borders will remain closed through mid-June to tamp down a fresh spike in infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite controversy, Chris Cuomo secure at CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/with-his-star-status-secure-at-cnn-chris-cuomo-skirts-controversy-again/ar-AAKpInA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although some colleagues privately gripe about his involvement in his brother’s politics, the prime-time host remains a ratings star — and a favorite of CNN President Jeff Zucker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Public transit worker fatally shot 8, then killed himself at San Jose rail yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/public-transit-worker-fatally-shot-8-then-killed-himself-at-san-jose-rail-yard-authorities-say/ar-AAKposP?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooter was a Valley Transportation Association employee, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos assures shareholders they're in good hands at final meeting as CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/26/jeff-bezos-final-shareholder-meeting-as-amazon-ceo-highlights-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos on Wednesday capped off his last shareholder meeting as CEO of Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayoral candidate shot dead after sharing her location on FACEBOOK Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mayoral-candidate-shot-dead-mexico-24193982</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alma Barragán, 61, was shot dead in Mexico's most dangerous state after she revealed her location to the killers during a Facebook Live video while campaigning to become mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Throws Down With Jamie Dimon Over Bank Fees...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/bunch-of-baloney-elizabeth-warren-throws-down-with-jamie-dimon-over-chase-raking-in-massive-overdraft-fees-during-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) got into a heated showdown with the man who is, arguably, the banking industry's most well-known figure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin rules out making it compulsory...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210526-putin-rules-out-compulsory-coronavirus-vaccinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin rules out compulsory coronavirus vaccinations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALDEN puts stamp on TRIBUNE with new debt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-a1ddfd98054a1e77175cf62fec4d2718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hedge fund Alden Global Capital closed its deal for Tribune on Monday. It wasted little time installing new leadership and saddling the newspaper chain with $278 million in debt it took on for the acquisition, according to regulatory filings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Execs sent to white male reeducation camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/lockheed-martin-put-executives-through-training-to-unlearn-white-male-privilege-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consulting firm claims that the ‘roots of white male culture’ include traits such as ‘a can-do-attitude’ and ‘hard work.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA cuts million$ from LAPD...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-cut-millions-lapd-george-120039767.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One year after George Floyd's murder, the L.A. City Council finalized a plan to spend $90 million on communities of color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garcetti picked for ambassador to India...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/biden-picks-l-a-mayor-garcetti-as-ambassador-to-india-source-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is expected to announce he is nominating former senior State Department official Nicholas Burns to serve as his ambassador to China and Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti to be his…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federer on Retirement -- and Becoming Switzerland's New Tourism Ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/roger-federer-retirement-wimbledon-switzerland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We kind of thought he already was Switzerland's tourism ambassador?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors investigating Trump tell witness to prepare for grand jury testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/26/politics/donald-trump-grand-jury/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan prosecutors pursuing a criminal case against former President Donald Trump, his company and its executives have told at least one witness to prepare for grand jury testimony, according to a person familiar with the matter -- a signal that the lengthy investigation is moving into an advanced stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKHEED's Woke-Industrial Complex...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/lockheed-martins-woke-industrial-complex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s largest defense contractor sends key executives on a mission to deconstruct their “white male privilege.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELECTION CARNAGE: 88 Mexican politicians, political candidates murdered since September...</title>
      <link>https://www.telesurenglish.net/news/Mexico-Moroleon-Mayoral-Candidate-Shot-to-Death-20210526-0005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telesurenglish.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eighty-eight politicians have been murdered since the start of the electoral process in Sep. 2020.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dershowitz sues NETFLIX over documentary...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-dershowitz-netflix-epstein-documentary-20210526-xz3vphyypjcs7jhjn4gog6rb6e-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alan Dershowitz sued Netflix Wednesday over a Jeffrey Epstein documentary that he says bolstered “false allegations of sexual misconduct.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Culture of Fear at Firm Managing Bill Gates' Fortune...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/26/a-culture-of-fear-at-the-firm-that-manages-bill-gatess-fortune/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 27 years, Bill Gates has entrusted the management of his enormous wealth and the endowment of his giant foundation</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
