<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 is wily virus. Can humans outsmart it?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/covid-19-is-a-wily-virus-can-humans-outsmart-it/article_b61b2ed7-a2c3-5f7a-b6a9-501d9e4f9c1e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To prevent a dangerous new virus from having its way with humankind, you might take a page from the Chinese warrior king Sun Tzu, and think like the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packed Bars Serve Up New Rounds Of Contagion...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/packed-bars-serve-up-new-rounds-of-covid-contagion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials are pointing to reopened bars as a cause of local spikes in coronavirus cases. Bars are tailor-made for the spread of the virus, with a cacophony of conversations that require raise…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASES HIT NEW HIGH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bc6644329af546be3b06763da8abd29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of confirmed new coronavirus cases per day in the U.S. hit an all-time high of 40,000 Friday — eclipsing the mark set during one of the deadliest stretches in late April — in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Disconnect Between Prices And Profits In Stock Market History?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/biggest-disconnect-between-prices-and-profits-stock-market-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Leaving and not coming back': African Americans head overseas...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2020/06/26/blaxit-black-americans-leave-us-escape-racism-build-lives-abroad/3234129001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feeling cornered and powerless in the face of persistent racial and economic struggles in the USA, some Black Americans decide to settle abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris Shadow Campaign for VP...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/06/kamala-harris-shadow-campaign-vice-president/613225/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator from California seems like the obvious choice to be Joe Biden’s running mate. So why is she keeping mum about her thinking?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamers Muzzling Controversial Documentaries?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/are-streamers-muzzling-controversial-docs-1299790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half a dozen hot-button docs have been pulled from platforms or dropped by digital distributors in the past year, angering filmmakers and viewers: "People do not like to be told they cannot see a film."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Male #MeToo Stigma and Fear of Coming Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/hollywoods-male-metoo-stigma-fear-coming-forward-1299702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two years into the movement, male victims grapple with consequences after speaking out, from mockery to job offers drying up: "I've never been so vulnerable in my life."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporations grapple with slavery reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/corporations-slavery-reparations-d2bca054-cf0a-4fa7-af6e-10490a49e308.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reparations debate has moved from the political realm to the corporate one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm young Black man who used to oppose Black Lives Matter'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200625151308-mzg0y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The #BlackLivesMatter movement opened my eyes to the extent of anti-Black racism in the United States today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Venezuelans take extraordinary steps to beat water shortage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a883de87f3cd5a5da370080cd3200012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela’s economic collapse has left most homes without reliable running water, so Caracas resident Iraima Moscoso saw water pooling inside an abandoned construction...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama ICU beds 82% full...</title>
      <link>https://abc3340.com/news/local/82-of-alabamas-icu-beds-full-as-covid-19-cases-soar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc3340.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the last 24 hours, the state of Alabama&amp;rsquo;s seen a record increase in COVID-19 cases with more than 1,100 cases added in a single day. UAB&amp;rsquo;s Dr. Jeanne Marazzo attributes the surge to the relaxation in people&amp;rsquo;s efforts to social distance and wear masks. &amp;ldquo;We are giving the virus more of an opportunity to jump from one person to another,&amp;rdquo; she said. 82 percent of Alabama&amp;rsquo;s ICU beds are now full, according to Dr. Don Williamson with Alabama&amp;rsquo;s Hospital Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't be a sheep': Sheriffs rebel against masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Don-t-be-a-sheep-Sheriffs-rebel-against-new-15368271.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after Gov. Jay Inslee, D, ordered Washington state residents to cover their faces in public, a Republican sheriff in a rural swath of the state's southwest suggested they should be doing no such thing.  "Here's what I say," Lewis County Sheriff Robert Snaza told the crowd outside a church Tuesday, carrying a megaphone and sporting his green and beige uniform but no face mask. "Don't be a sheep."  Few of the people cheering on Snaza covered their faces either, according to video of the scene taken by the Daily Chronicle of Centralia, Wash. Indeed, the words on a billboard above the crowd seemed to capture their feeling about the pandemic: "Oh, no! A virus. Quick - burn the bill of rights."  With coronavirus infections rapidly spreading across the American South and West and more states making masks a requirement, dozens of sheriffs like Snaza are staging a rebellion against state governments. An adherence to their interpretation of Constitution, they say, comes before any kind of public health advice.  Since April, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has said people should cover their faces in public to stop the spread of the coronavirus, which has killed more than 122,000 people in the United States to date. But Snaza said he did not believe masks were effective, arguing they should be optional instead.  "My frustration is we continue to listen to the governor's requests without asking questions, without saying: 'Well wait a minute, there's the other side to this,' " Snaza told Oregon Public Broadcasting.  He is not alone. In Nevada and North Carolina on Thursday, multiple sheriffs said their Democratic governors' mask requirements were "unconstitutional and unenforceable." After five California counties ignored a similar directive, Gov. Gavin Newsom, D, threatened to withhold state funds. Another...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: India, China massing troops in border showdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/india-china-deployed-large-numbers-border-showdown-foreign-183951578.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India acknowledged for the first time Thursday that it has matched China in massing troops at their contested Himalayan border region after a deadly clash this month. The neighbours have blamed each other for a June 15 battle in the Ladakh region in which 20 Indian soldiers were killed while China suffered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major gunfight breaks out in upscale Mexico City neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200626113001-dyamy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/:Major gunfight breaks out in upscale Mexico City neighborhood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car crashes deadlier as drivers speed during lockdowns...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200626112931-nf9qa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TRAFFIC-CASUALTIES (INSIGHT):INSIGHT-Car crashes deadlier as drivers speed during lockdowns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal raves take off across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200626102955-g1xtf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/LOCKDOWN-PARTIES (TV):As lockdown eases, illegal raves take off across Europe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Warns of Re-Lock...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/06/25/newsom-warns-of-another-shutdown-due-to-growing-coronavirus-cases-leaving-local-businesses-in-jeopardy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as businesses across the state are beginning to reopen, Gov. Gavin Newsom is warning of another shutdown if current coronavirus numbers don't improve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis council puts plan to abolish police in motion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/198e18397e404ef9411f2efcdf7754c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The Minneapolis City Council votes Friday on a proposal to change the city charter to allow elimination of the city's police department, a radical move supported by a majority...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New taxes coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Governments-eye-new-taxes-on-cigarettes-homes-15368171.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cash-starved cities and states across the country are starting to weigh whether to raise taxes on homes, cigarettes, local businesses and global tech giants, hoping to rake in new revenue that might help them close the massive budget shortfalls created by the coronavirus pandemic.  The increases that have been proposed - and in some cases adopted - reflect the growing desperation on the part of government leaders nationwide. Many have found that recent spending cuts, furloughs and layoffs haven't been enough to shore up their sagging finances, forcing them to consider more politically noxious and economically risky moves in the middle of an economic crisis.  "No politician wants to lead with raising taxes," said Mark Mazur, the director of the Urban-Brookings Tax Policy Center. "When they get there, it's because they've run out of other options."  Philadelphia increased fees on parking and raised wage taxes on workers who reside outside the city. Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot, D, said this month she couldn't rule out a property tax increase to cover her city's $700 million budget shortfall. From New York to Seattle, other states and municipalities have considered a wide array of prospective rate hikes in response major drops in once-reliable sources of income - and months of failed attempts to get Congress to authorize more federal aid.  Nashville leaders even took the eye-popping step in June to increase property taxes by about 34 percent, a move meant to help pay down rising public education costs - and one that quickly sparked a public outcry.  The city's rates long had been historically low, according to Bob Mendes, an at-large member of the Nashville Metro Council who helped craft the budget blueprint. An increase helped pave the way for the city to close an anticipated $216 million financial hole in the 2021 fiscal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PASSION OF CHRIST' Screenwriter Teases Mind-Blowing Sequel...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/entertainment/films/1300833/Passion-of-the-Christ-2-Resurrection-screenwriter-Randall-Wallace-Mel-Gibson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PASSION OF THE CHRIST 2 screenwriter Randall Wallace has shared another update on Mel Gibson's biblical sequel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No amount of money' can undo damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8456819/Trump-family-say-no-money-undo-damage-Mary-Trumps-book.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their application for a temporary restraining order, the Trumps said that they would suffer 'irreparable harm' if Mary's book is released next month as planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL GATES: USA 'not even close' to doing enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/25/us/bill-gates-coronavirus-town-hall-us/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gates says the current coronavirus picture, both globally and in the US, is "more bleak" than he would have expected and warns that making people take the vaccine may prove more of a hurdle than developing and distributing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial-Recognition Backlash Brews After Fury Over Police Conduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/facial-recognition-backlash-brews-after-fury-over-police-conduct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial-Recognition Backlash Brews After Fury Over Police Conduct</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House set for historic vote on DC statehood...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/504632-house-set-for-historic-vote-on-dc-statehood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is poised to pass legislation Friday that would make Washington, D.C. the 51st state, the first time such a bill has ever been approved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Doomsday Bunkers Become New Normal?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/26/could-doomsday-bunkers-become-the-new-normal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first tenant for one of Frank Woodworth’s underground bunkers wasn’t a human, it was a seed. “A couple of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARVILLE: NO CHANCE OF RE-ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.msnbc.com/11th-hour/watch/james-carville-there-is-no-chance-trump-will-be-re-elected-86029381572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran Democratic strategist James Carville says he believes it's more likely that Trump decides to drop out of the 2020 race than Trump wins re-election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music reckons with racial stereotypes and its future...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c34fd394a0275f0726cb5bb231f70833</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — When country singer Rissi Palmer was working on her debut album, she wanted a song like Gretchen Wilson’s “Redneck Woman,” a song that would introduce her and tell her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Arizona lost control of the epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/How-Arizona-lost-control-of-the-epidemic-15367484.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX - A drive-up testing site equipped for several hundred people in West Phoenix was swarmed on Saturday by about 1,000 people, leaving some baking in their cars for hours.  A nearby testing station has already reached capacity for this weekend, appointments vanishing within minutes. Hospitals are filling up. Restaurants are again shutting down, more than a month after Arizona reopened its economy under the mantra "Return Stronger."  Arizona has emerged as an epicenter of the early summer's coronavirus crisis as the outbreak has metastasized, flaring across new parts of the country and, notably, infecting more young people.  Maricopa County, which includes Phoenix, is recording as many as 2,000 cases a day, "eclipsing the New York City boroughs even on their worst days," warned a Wednesday brief by disease trackers at Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, which observed, "Arizona has lost control of the epidemic."  But physicians, public health experts, advocates and local officials say the crisis was predictable in Arizona, where local ordinances requiring masks were verboten until Gov. Doug Ducey, a Republican, reversed course last week. State leaders did not take the necessary precautions or model safe behavior, these observers maintain, even in the face of compelling evidence and repeated pleas from authoritative voices.  "We have failed on so many levels," said Dana Marie Kennedy, the Arizona director of AARP, who said her organization has yet to receive a response to four letters outlining concerns to the governor. She is working on a fifth.  Neither the governor's office nor the state health department responded to requests for comment.  At critical junctures, blunders by top officials undermined faith in the data purportedly driving decision-making, according to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO NOVEMBER ELECTION RESULTS FOR WEEKS?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2020/06/25/wait-weeks-to-tally-novembers-votes-one-ex-official-says-that-could-be-generous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Counting mail-in ballots in New York and Kentucky could take until next week, and delays could be longer in November with higher turnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT IGNORES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-ignores-virus-spike-as-us-cases-surge-toward-records/ar-BB15YpgG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Sagging Popularity Drags Down Republican Candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/poll-shows-trump-dragging-down-gop-senate-candidates/ar-BB15X7H9?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:  BIDEN LEADS IN TEXAS!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/fox-news-poll-shows-biden-leading-in-2016-trump-states-of-georgia-florida-north-carolina-and-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News poll shows Biden leading in 2016 Trump states of Georgia, Florida, North Carolina and TEXAS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA mayor urges residents to stay home... </title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/la-mayor-urges-residents-to-stay-home-as-coronavirus-cases-spike/article_eec6bc87-1949-517e-a86e-d5e34d419621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Amid record-setting spikes in newly confirmed coronavirus infections, Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti urged Angelenos to continue staying home as much as possible — even as the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL IN THE FAMILY:  Trumps LOSE attempt to gag Mary Trump from publishing tell-all book...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/judge-tosses-trump-family-attempt-to-block-mary-trumps-tell-all?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Queens County Surrogate Court Judge cited “several improprieties” in Robert Trump’s attempt to block niece Mary’s tell-all, slated to be published this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady AGAIN defies virus rules to work out with teammates...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1039711/tom-brady-defies-coronavirus-rules-team-workout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOM Brady again defied coronavirus safety advice to practice with his Tampa Bay Buccaneers teammates, despite the fact that two players recently tested positive for the virus. After getting flack f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden Now Leads in ALL Key Battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/showing-strength-with-white-voters-biden-builds-lead-in-battleground-states/ar-BB15WSW0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER 1.5 MILLION JOBLESS CLAIMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/25/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jobless claims totaled 1.48 million last week as unemployment related to the coronavirus pandemic remained stubbornly high. Economists surveyed by Dow Jones had been expecting 1.35 million claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noose and concern for Wallace 'was real': NASCAR president...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/noose-concern-wallace-real-nascar-president-194246795--nascar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASCAR president Steve Phelps said Thursday that the noose found in the garage of Bubba Wallace &amp;quot;was real&amp;quot; and while the series&amp;#39; only black driver wasn&amp;#39;t targeted in a hate crime, officials&amp;#39; concern for him was warranted. Phelps held a conference call with reporters on Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe COVID-19 can damage the brain...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200625214519-dg2oh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAIN (PIX):Severe COVID-19 can damage the brain, preliminary study finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVERNORS BACKTRACK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/778da4a2da7e5d9d12e6105c012b8cf9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The coronavirus crisis deepened in Arizona on Thursday, and the governor of Texas began to backtrack after making one of the most aggressive pushes in the nation to reopen, as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task force tracking big spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-says-coronavirus-going-away-his-own-task-force-disagrees-n1232061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New internal data obtained by NBC News show the White House is closely tracking big virus spikes around the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODEL: Phoenix could see 28,000 new infections a DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8459417/Data-shows-23-counties-seeing-uncontrollable-COVID-growth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A color-coded data map, compiled by spatial analytics company Esri, shows how the US is faring in terms of infections by tracking the number of new COVID-19 cases on a county level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Lines Form At DOLPHINS Stadium Test Site...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/06/25/coronavirus-testing-hard-rock-stadium-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Florida's number of coronavirus continues to surge, there has been an increase in the number of people wanting to be tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress test finds some banks could be stressed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/25/fed-puts-restrictions-on-bank-dividends-after-test-finds-some-banks-could-be-stressed-in-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move signals that the unprecedented nature of the coronavirus pandemic, and the difficulty in forecasting what the future holds for banks, is making the Fed cautious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA TOO</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-06-25/florida-s-desantis-doesn-t-plan-to-move-to-next-phase-of-opening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to offer more 'context' on virus posts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-seeks-offer-more-context-virus-posts-193736510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook said Thursday it was looking to add notifications about the source of coronavirus-related posts and will warn users when they share stories that are more than 90 days old. Facebook Vice President John Hegeman said in a blog post the social media giant would be seeking to direct people to "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy investigating LSD ring...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/navy-warns-of-increase-in-personnel-taking-lsd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy disclosed on Thursday that it has seen an increase in its personnel purchasing, using, and distributing the hallucinogenic drug LSD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan prosecutor pick ducks questions about Barr's job offer...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/25/jay-clayton-sdny-bill-barr-339888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay Clayton — the chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission — made the remarks in a congressional hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobbyist Jack Abramoff Charged in Crypto-Currency Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/amp/news/articles/2020-06-25/lobbyist-abramoff-charged-in-crypto-currency-case-u-s-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORAD intercepts 2 Russian aircraft near Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://wpta21.com/2020/06/25/norad-intercepts-2-russian-aircraft-that-came-near-alaska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wpta21.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNEAU, Alaska (AP) — Military officials say two Russian aircraft were intercepted after they came within 50 miles of Unimak Island along Alaska’s Aleutian chain. The commander of the North American Aerospace Defense Command says Wednesday’s incident marked the fifth time this month that such an intercept has taken place. NORAD says the Russian aircraft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precinct commander quits in protest...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/25/bronx-nypd-precinct-commander-is-quitting-in-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Brea, a Bronx NYPD precinct commander, is quitting in protest of how the department is handling police reform, The Post has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong-un death rumors resurface; Japan reveals 'suspicions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11954967/kim-jong-un-dead-rumours-japan-suspicions-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN has revealed it has “some suspicions” about the health of the periodically missing North Korean dictator Kim Jong-un.   The country’s defence minister made the bombshell comment at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON buys Seattle arena naming rights, will call it 'Climate Pledge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/sports/hockey/amazon-buys-naming-rights-to-keyarena-will-call-it-climate-pledge-arena/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arena, home to the city’s incoming NHL franchise and WNBA's Storm, will be powered 100% by renewable electricity and seek to achieve a zero carbon footprint. NHL Seattle CEO Tod Leiweke said the arena aims to produce zero waste,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trumps LOSE attempt to gag Mary Trump from publishing tell-all book...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8460807/Trumps-LOSE-attempt-gag-Mary-Trump-judge-dismisses-petition-protective-order.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump family have lost their attempt to gag their niece from writing a tell-all book about them. A judge ruled that their application to stop Mary was 'fatally defective' and dismissed it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY changing 'Splash Mountain' ride tied to Jim Crow film...</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/entertainment/2020/06/25/disney-changing-splash-mountain-ride-tied-to-jim-crow-film/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid calls to change the Splash Mountain theme park ride because of its ties with “Song of the South,” the 1946 movie many view as racist, Disney officials said Thursday it was recasting the ride to make it based on “The Princess and the Frog,” the 2009 Disney film with an African American female lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan: 1 in 3 pilots have fake licenses...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/06/25/business/pakistan-fake-pilot-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 30% of civilian pilots in Pakistan have fake licenses and are not qualified to fly, the country's aviation minister revealed Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing, Tracking Still Plagued by Delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2020-06-25/virus-testing-tracking-still-plagued-by-reporting-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Used Missile With Long Blades to Kill Qaeda Leader in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-s-used-missile-with-long-blades-to-kill-qaeda-leader-in-syria/ar-BB15WcHZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe coronavirus resurgences alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53175459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If left unchecked the resurgences will "push health systems to the brink once again", the WHO warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to secure virus 'red zone' in southern Italy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thepeninsulaqatar.com/article/25/06/2020/Army-to-secure-virus-red-zone-in-southern-Italy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepeninsulaqatar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The army was being sent in to secure a virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone footage catches huge great white lurking below surfers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1030159/footage-white-shark-prowling-six-surfers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS chilling footage shows a great white shark prowling just feet away from six oblivious surfers as they wait to catch a wave.  The drone footage, filmed by a local teenager, shows the fears…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNEAKY:  Your iPhone has hidden map of EVERYWHERE you go...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1035842/iphone-map-location-tracking-significant-settings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOUR iPhone keeps track of your real-world movements – which you can view on a map. The little-known feature is buried deep within your iPhone settings, and shows your exact movements over the past…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS PAUSES REOPENING</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/texas-governor-pauses-state-s-reopening-due-spike-new-covid-n1232118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The last thing we want to do as a state is go backwards and close down businesses," Gov. Greg Abbott said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Weigh Scrapping Football Season...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/ncaafb/colleges-weigh-scrapping-football-season-in-threat-to-a-cash-cow/ar-BB15XkPj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare red rainbow forms...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/red-rainbow-forms-over-birmingham-22249706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A red rainbow formed over Birmingham this month, with sky-watchers claiming the beautiful dome is so rare you are lucky if you witness it first-hand just once in your lifetime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece woos tourists with pledge of 'maximum' safety...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/greece-woos-tourists-pledge-maximum-virus-safety-153554991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece has taken every possible care to shield tourists from COVID-19 as it prepares to open additional airports to travellers on July 1, Prime Minister Kyriakos Mitsotakis said Thursday. With a quarter of the nation's economy dependent on tourism, the government faces an urgent challenge to reassure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury sent $1.4 BILLION in payments to DEAD PEOPLE...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report/botched-testing-1-200-for-the-dead-watchdog-audits-virus-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government’s quick action to issue stimulus payments in the wake of the coronavirus crisis led to more than a billion dollars of fraudulent payments, while slow action to address the health risks might have worsened the outbreak, according to a report by a government watchdog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incessant Fireworks Keeping Minneapolis Residents On Edge Amid Gun Violence...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/06/24/incessant-fireworks-keeping-minneapolis-residents-on-edge-amid-gun-violence-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a time when gun violence is becoming more common across Minneapolis, the consistent sound of fireworks is increasing fear and anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston facing 'apocalyptic' July 4...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/houston-facing-apocalyptic-july-4-134936261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Houston’s Covid-19 outbreak is accelerating at an exponential pace that will swamp the fourth-largest U.S. city’s medical infrastructure by the Independence Day holiday, less than two weeks away, a leading disease specialist warned.Even as Houston-area intensive-care wards approach full</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTBREAK:  TEXAS GETS REALITY CHECK...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/covid-19-gives-texas-reality-143042609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The Texas Medical Center in Houston is the largest health care complex in the world, so vast it describes itself, accurately, as a “medical city.” About 106,000 people work there, traversing 50 million square feet of property. If TMC were a stand-alone business district, it would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China could get coronavirus bailout from by U.S. taxpayers?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/how-scarce-us-taxpayer-money-could-wind-up-in-chinas-coffers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American taxpayer dollars intended to help countries weather the global downturn could flow into Chinese Communist Party coffers, U.S. officials and analysts fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/24/us-hits-highest-single-day-of-coronavirus-cases-at-36358-breaking-april-record.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grim milestone reported on Wednesday surpasses the peak that was hit in late April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED STATES OF INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-surge-map-7714f8d1-5ba1-46f8-9bf3-5d59938f2c95.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the grimmest map since Axios began tracking the weekly changes in coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 store  opens at Miami mall...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/entertainment/covid-19-essentials-pop-up-offers-in-demand-supplies-for-pandemic-in-one-place/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 essentials. No, we’re not about to list off a bunch of items. COVID-19 Essential is the name of a new pop-up store in Aventura....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: World putting America in quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/921833/world-putting-america-quarantine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus is making the U.S. a pariah state and reshuffling the international order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WON'T FOLLOW NJ MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/06/24/president-trump-wont-follow-new-jersey-quarantine-mandate-during-upcoming-trip-white-house-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump recently traveled to Arizona, one of the states designated by New Jersey as a hotspot requiring quarantine. Trump will visit his Bedminster golf club this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Sexual Abuse Epidemic Rocking Gaming World...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-wild-west-of-twitch-video-game-streaming-where-sexual-abuse-runs-rampant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple women come forward to The Daily Beast to share their stories of sexual harassment and abuse on the popular video game-streaming platform, where victims have no recourse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops' use of military-grade speakers at protests prompts backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-orlando-george-floyd-protests-lrad-opd-20200625-vke7xwiggbg23llwetr4eggsz4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often described by critics as an acoustic weapon, the LRAD device was created for the military after the attack on USS Cole in 2000. It has since been marketed to domestic law enforcement and public safety agencies as a super-powered bullhorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saharan Dust Turns Skies Gray from Gulf Coast to Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/african-dust-turns-skies-gray-from-the-gulf-coast-to-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;African Dust Turns Skies Gray from the Gulf Coast to Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC Cops Caught on Tape Talking About 'Slaughtering' Black People...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/504454-3-north-carolina-police-officers-fired-after-conversation-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three police officers in North Carolina have been fired after they were heard on camera making racist comments, including the use of racial epithets and references to “slaughtering” Black people, police said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court 2020: Major rulings on abortion, Trump's tax returns still to come...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/supreme-court-2020-major-rulings-152456132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at the major Supreme Court rulings of 2020 and the pending cases yet to be decided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Adults Than Ever Live With Parents or Grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/06/25/more-adults-than-ever-live-with-parents-or-grandparents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record 32 million American adults were living with their parents or grandparents in April, according to the latest American</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo artist sees bump in desire to erase hateful skin art...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ca3686e2f5113a82a065626d2a07e86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELLOWS FALLS, Vt. (AP) — A Vermont tattoo artist who has long offered free removal or covering of hateful skin art like swastikas, SS lightning bolts or the words “white power” says he’s seen an...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
