<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NC teacher killed in shootout with Mexican drug cartel after stash house heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsoctv.com/news/local/sheriff-popular-union-county-coach-killed-shootout-with-mexican-drug-cartel/P4M26CUMNVGTHPE7KRIQMQC42M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsoctv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Union County teacher and coach was killed in a shootout last week with a Mexican drug cartel, according to the Alamance County Sheriff’s Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'How can democracy function if we can't talk to one another?' U.S. justices ask...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-justices-idUSKBN2C12VN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two U.S. Supreme Court justices from opposite ends of the ideological spectrum are calling on Americans to learn to talk civilly to each other or risk lasting damage to the nation's democratic system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biz Forced to Pay $136,000 After Prohibiting Employees, Customers From Wearing...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/04/14/liberty-tax-service-lynn-covid-fine-osha/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii 'train to nowhere' rakes in taxpayer cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/14/hawaiis-train-nowhere-rakes-taxpayer-cash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’d be forgiven for wondering what a light rail system in Honolulu has to do with crushing the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World struggles to maintain immunization drives after mounting side effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2021/04/14/coronavirus-covid-live-updates-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To date, more than 45 percent of the eligible U.S. population has received at least one vaccine dose though the number of new cases continued to trend upward at an average of 11 percent over the past week. At least 562,000 people have died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone images show shocking growth of child migrant facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/new-images-expansion-migrant-facility-in-donna-texas-as-crisis-rages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New images show the extent to which the migrant facility in Donna, Texas has expanded in recent weeks as authorities scramble to find space to house an overwhelming surge of underage people coming across the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ABCNEWS names Kimberly Godwin new president...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-walt-disney-abc-news-kimberly-godwin/cbs-news-executive-kimberly-godwin-to-lead-abc-news-idUSKBN2C12SK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News executive Kimberly Godwin has been named president of Walt Disney Co's ABC News, the media company said on Wednesday, becoming the first Black woman to lead the news division of a major broadcast television network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy running on stimulus-fueled high. What will happen when it wears off?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/14/policy-and-fiscal-risk-could-hamper-a-long-term-economic-recovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The path beyond this rocket-fueled year looks far less clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soars in debut, valued at $86 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/14/coinbase-to-debut-on-nasdaq-in-direct-listing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coinbase held its direct listing Wednesday on the Nasdaq, luring public market investors who've been waiting to get into the cryptocurrency exchange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland trooper shoots, kills white teen who had airsoft gun...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/shooting-occurs-near-maryland-state-190731044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Maryland State Police trooper responding to a pair of 911 calls shot and killed a teenager who was pointing what investigators determined was an airsoft gun at him, authorities said Tuesday. The shooting occurred after state police received two 911 calls about someone acting suspicious, Superintendent Woodrow Jones II told a news conference. A second caller gave a street address for the suspicious person that was a short distance from the Leonardtown barracks, but the caller hung up before identifying themselves, Jones said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Correspondents' Association cancels dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/14/white-house-correspondents-dinner-cancelled-481502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the second year in a row that the annual event has been axed because of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ABCNEWS names Kimberly Godwin new president...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/04/14/business/media/abc-news-president-kimberly-godwin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her new role is just one of several changes in the world of broadcast news as the industry adjusts to a drastically changed news cycle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to pull US troops from Afghanistan, end 'forever war'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-troop-withdrawal-afghanistan-september-11-d2c7426736f9f530e0e62f2295a44d28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said Wednesday he will withdraw remaining U.S. troops from the "forever war” in Afghanistan, declaring that the Sept. 11 terror attacks of 20 years ago cannot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving seat open during flight reduces transmission up to 57%...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/covid-leaving-seat-open-during-flight-reduces-transmission-by-up-to-57-percent-665161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A laboratory model showed that leaving the middle seat in each airplane aisle vacant reduced COVID transmission by 23% to 57%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Defensive Player Of Year Accused Of Unprovoked Nightclub Assault...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/04/14/aaron-donald-assault-lawsuit-todd-hollis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pittsburgh attorney says he is planning to file assault charges against former Pitt Football star Aaron Donald.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potter arrested, charged with 2nd degree manslaughter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/14/officer-kimberly-potter-charged-in-daunte-wright-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Potter, the former Minnesota police officer who fatally shot Daunte Wright after mistakenly drawing her gun instead of her Taser, was arrested Wednesday and will be charged with second-deg…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noisy environments can have detrimental effect on plants, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/apr/14/noisy-environments-have-detrimental-effect-plants-new-mexico-study-finds-persistent-noise-natural-gas-wells</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Persistent noise from natural gas wells in New Mexico disrupted birds that feed on and distribute pinyon seeds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERCOT Emergency Warning Shocks Texans On Mild April Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2021/04/14/ercot-emergency-warning-shocks-texans-on-mild-april-day/?sh=286640347b64</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were a few scattered thunderstorms over a small portion of northwest Texas, but otherwise the state experienced calm weather on a very mild spring day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas set to come out of Covid better than ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/las-vegas-new-casinos-attractions-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New casino resorts, innovative restaurants, expanded convention space and one-of-a-kind cultural destinations characterize the latest iteration of Las Vegas, which continues to reinvent itself in the face of adversity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is obsessive coronavirus cleaning over?</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/coronavirus/2021/04/is-the-time-of-obsessive-coronavirus-cleaning-over/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you still obsessively cleaning to try to fend off the coronavirus? A local scientist says it’s time to stop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI quietly accessing hundreds of American computers hacked via MICROSOFT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/fbi-might-gone-ahead-fixed-microsoft-email-server-rcna680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not updating your critical software? The FBI might just do it for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors: No charges for officer in Capitol riot shooting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-politics-shootings-veterans-cef4da2291ce3c98b0d232220bd288e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal prosecutors will not charge a police officer who shot and killed a woman as she climbed through the broken part of a door during the insurrection at the U.S. Capitol on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCRABBLE ban on racial slurs angers top players...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/scrabble-bans-racial-slurs-b929572.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three prominent members of the global Scrabble players’ organisation quit in response to the changes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Navy Celebrates New $2 Billion Ship With Ceremonial Twerking...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9468717/Bizarre-video-shows-dancers-twerking-Commissioning-new-Australian-Navy-ship-Sydney.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of scantily clad women twerking has launched a new ship. The ceremony was attended by the Governor General and head of the Navy in Sydney on the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX show to teach viewers how to fall asleep...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/netflix-show-to-teach-subscribers-how-to-fall-asleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming giant has released a trailer for a new series from meditation app Headspace that attempts to explain how not to be awake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W BUSH TO BREAK SILENCE IN TV INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/george-w-bush-calls-not-passing-immigration-reform-one-of-his-biggest-regrets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preview: In an interview for "CBS Sunday Morning," the former president talks politics, painting, and his new book, "Out of Many, One: Portraits of America's Immigrants."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ELLEN' Talk Show Drops to All Time Low Ratings; Now Under Million Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/04/14/afternoon-emergency-ellen-degeneres-daytime-talk-show-drops-to-all-time-low-ratings-down-11-in-one-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen DeGeneres is really having a serious problem now. Maybe that’s why she keeps flipping $40 million houses. For the week of April 4th, Ellen’s afternoon talk show hit an all time lo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Penthouse Offered for Sale at $241 Million!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/london-penthouse-offered-for-sale-for-dollar241-million-by-entrepreneur-nick-candy/ar-BB1fEaA6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A penthouse at the One Hyde Park project in London’s upscale Knightsbridge district is being offered for sale for 175 million pounds ($241 million), according to a person with knowledge of the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain fog: How trauma, uncertainty and isolation have affected our minds and memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/apr/14/brain-fog-how-trauma-uncertainty-and-isolation-have-affected-our-minds-and-memory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a year of lockdown, many of us are finding it hard to think clearly, or remember what happened when. Neuroscientists and behavioural experts explain why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A minor investigation into the Bidens' Major problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-minor-investigation-into-the-bidens-e2-80-99-major-problem/ar-BB1fDmDU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s eating the first family’s youngest dog?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: REDEMPTION OF BIEBER...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/justin-bieber-cover-profile-may-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He made every mistake a child star can make, including the ones that nearly destroyed him. Now—fortified by God, marriage, and a new album, "Justice"—Justin Bieber is putting his life back together, one positive, deliberate step at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W BUSH TO BREAK SILENCE IN TV INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/entertainment/television/george-w-bush-today-show/73-8196f871-cf17-4c3e-9766-e2256bb90278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hoda Kotb will sit down with President Bush for his first live television interview in 3 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORYLINES:  Former 'BACHELOR' Comes Out As Gay on 'GMA'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Culture/bachelor-star-colton-underwood-gay/story?id=77057551&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_16_post_hero_card_hed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former "Bachelor" star Colton Underwood came out as gay in an exclusive interview with Robin Roberts on "Good Morning America."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADDRESS LEAK:  Enraged rioters force cop to flee her home after Daunte Wright shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2697369/daunte-wright-rioters-clash-cops-flashbangs-violence-minnesota/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A THIRD night of riots erupted following the death of Daunte Wright that lead to protesters burning down a police building and forcing a cop to flee her home after her address leaked. More than 60 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds seized his iPhone last winter!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/13/gaetz-bahamas-investigation-481273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents executed a search warrant and seized the Florida congressman’s iPhone last winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAILOUTS CONTINUE?</title>
      <link>https://www.fool.com/the-ascent/personal-finance/articles/biden-facing-pressure-to-include-a-fourth-stimulus-check-in-upcoming-infrastructure-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fool.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is working on a big stimulus bill. Will it include another COVID-19 relief check?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/13/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Goldman Sachs climbed 2% after the bank blew past analysts' expectations with record first-quarter net profits and revenues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Monkey Experiment Raises Questions...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/04/elon-musk-neuralink-monkey-demo-draw-skepticism-scientist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some scientists note that similar tech has been around for 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry as Video Shows Robodog Patrolling With NYPD...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/outcry-video-robodog-patrolling-nypd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I ain't never seen nothing like this in my life."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Fines Students $50 For Bareface...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/04/13/saint-josephs-college-fines-students-50-for-not-wearing-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saint Joseph’s College in Maine is giving $50 tickets to students who violate the school's face mask requirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE: Republican Rep Retires...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/04/14/kevin-brady-congress-texas-retirement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Montgomery County Republican has served in Congress for more than two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ULTIMATE SCHEMER</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/the-ultimate-schemer-cnbcs-jim-cramer-and-colleagues-reflect-on-the-dark-legacy-of-bernie-madoff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC's Jim Cramer reflected on Bernie Madoff's disgraced legacy as he and his colleagues reported on the financier's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>37,000 VICTIMS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/14/bernie-madoff-infamous-ponzi-schemer-dead-at-82/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Madoff, whose $65 billion Ponzi scheme made him one of the world’s most hated criminals and destroyed even his own family, died Wednesday at the secure federal medical center in Bu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan's powerful tribes on collision course with monarchy over alleged royal plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/jordans-powerful-tribes-collision-course-090014490.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jordan's tribes have long been the kingdom's bedrock and a source of support for the monarchy. But accusations of seditious scheming may change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There aren't sugar daddies.' Cuba's Miguel Díaz-Canel faces tough choices amid Castro exit...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/there-arent-sugar-daddies-cubas-miguel-d-az-canel-faces-tough-choices-amid-castro-exit/article_95b6321c-20a4-57a6-a132-58d5edadfacc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In nearly three years as Cuba's handpicked president, Miguel Díaz-Canel's public image has been a stark contrast to the military fatigues and starched suits of his predecessors, Fidel and Raúl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Average Woman Pops 4,153 Pimples In Lifetime!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/women-pop-pimples-pandemic-making-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average American woman pops a total of 65 pimples annually. That’s 4,153 zits in the average U.S. woman’s adult lifetime!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom male sex robot leaves female fan swooning...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/custom-male-sex-robot-strongest-23912637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A male Real Doll is being custom-built for a randy fan and a picture shows him in a tank top with stubble, short hair and strong jawline – impressing a married woman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former 'BACHELOR' Colton Underwood Comes Out As Gay In 'GMA' Interview...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/colton-underwood-gay-former-bachelor-good-morning-america-interview-robin-roberts-1234734036/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colton Underwood, the 2019 star of ABC’s The Bachelor heavily promoted during the season for his proclaimed virginity, has come out as gay in an interview with Robin Roberts on Good Morning A…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Two-Thirds Would Rather Work Out At Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/two-thirds-would-rather-exercise-at-home-than-gym/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one in five respondents said keeping up with a workout routine at home has led to better sex during lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia announces live-fire drills in Black Sea as US warship set to arrive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9469575/Ukraine-standoff-Russia-announces-snap-live-fire-drills-Black-Sea-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three missile ships, a frigate and a minesweeper will take part in live-fire drills in the Black Sea today, the Russian navy has said, as the first of two US warships deployed to the region is due to arrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J halt threatens to worsen 'hesitancy' problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Vaccine-pause-threatens-to-worsen-hesitancy-16099555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The pause in distribution of the Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine this week...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases on rise in 27 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/13/covid-19-cases-deaths-vaccinations-daily-update.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As U.S. Covid cases rise, the country is also administering vaccine shots aimed at preventing the spread of the virus at a faster pace than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO EXCHANGE GOES PUBLIC</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coinbase-stock-ipo-price-c3b802074ce4349b5bccf9ba43022800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street will be focused on Coinbase Wednesday with the digital currency exchange becoming a publicly traded company. Coinbase is making its initial public offering of stock with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMORGAN, GOLDMAN smash earnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/news/bank-stocks-jpmorgan-goldman-sachs-wells-fargo-earnings-q1-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JPMorgan and Goldman Sachs easily beat views, helped by loan loss reserves released and strong investment banking. Bank stocks were mixed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 test positive at India religious festival!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210414-over-1-000-test-positive-for-covid-19-at-india-religious-festival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 1,000 test positive for Covid-19 at India religious festival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors worried as younger patients fill beds in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210414-in-german-hospital-doctors-worried-as-younger-patients-fill-beds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In German hospital, doctors worried as younger patients fill beds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women detail drug use, sex and payments after late-night parties with Gaetz...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/14/politics/gaetz-parties-women-drug-use-sex-payments/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first thing some of the women were asked to do when they got to the house parties in the gated community in suburban Orlando was to put away their cellphones, according to two women in attendance who spoke to CNN in recent days. The men inside, a who's who of local Republican officials that often included Rep. Matt Gaetz, did not want the night's activities documented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN SACHS record earnings results...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/14/goldman-sachs-gs-earnings-q1-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expectations for Goldman Sachs are running high amid favorable conditions for many of the Wall Street businesses that the firm operates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study of public attitude toward press reveals distrust deeper than partisanship...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-media-tom-rosenstiel-journalists-915025bcab8f5910381eee11b5cb9d17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A study of the public's attitude toward the press reveals that distrust goes deeper than partisanship and down to how journalists define their very mission. In short:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Glacier in Alaska Moving 100 Times Faster Than Normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/glacier-alaska-moving-100-times-165646252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nature can be unpredictable at times, but some things are more reliable than others. Spring (usually) brings a lot of rain, birds migrate to warmer areas in the winter months, and glaciers move slow. These are trends that have been established and are expected, but they're not always universally true. Sometimes spring is dry, sometimes migratory birds like geese decide to stick it out in a cold area for an entire winter, and sometimes glaciers move really, really fast. As Earther reports, the National Park Service recently confirmed that a glacier near Denali National Park and Preserve in Alaska is moving up to 100 times faster than it would be expected to, and the rare event has caught the attention of scientists. It's not an entirely new observation, but it's incredibly rare to see a massive chunk of ice move at these speeds, and there are only a few places on Earth where it happens. Glaciers are almost always moving. They travel over the ground beneath them at an extremely slow pace and you wouldn't even know they were moving if you were standing on one. Over time, the masses of ice can carve and shape the landscape below, but it takes a very long time for this to happen. However, some glaciers abandon this, well, "glacial pace" in favor of a brief speed boost that still has scientists scratching their heads a bit. This phenomenon is called a glacial surge, and it's unique not just for its rarity but also the fact that it tends to only happen in certain areas, and Alaska happens to be one of them. They happen briefly and then stop, returning the glaciers to their normal slow crawl. A glacial surge requires an increase in speed of around ten times the normal glacial movement rate. In the case of the glacier currently cruising in Alaska, the speed is in the 50x to 100x range. Even when a glacier is moving this fast it's not exactly breaking any speed records. Remember, we're talking about frozen slabs that move as slow as less than two feet in an entire year. The glacier currently moving fast in Alaska — called the Muldrow Glacier — has experienced a number of surges in the past, with the most recent one occurring roughly 64 years ago. During that brief boost, the glacier pushed forward 4 miles in less than a year. It's a very interesting phenomenon and one that researchers still don't fully understand. It's believed that melting glacial ice may play a role in helping to speed these huge slabs up, but determining why these events happen at surprisingly regular intervals is still something that scientists are trying to explain. In any case, if you're in Alaska, it might be worth taking a trip to see a glacier moving faster than any other in the region if only to say that you saw it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Breyer Retire' campaign looms over Dems' tenuous majority...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/14/stephen-breyer-retirement-supreme-court-481197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neither Democratic lawmakers nor President Joe Biden are putting overt retirement pressure on the Supreme Court justice — but his future is on everyone's minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls to impeach Bolsonaro rising, but his grip on Brazil remains strong...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/calls-to-impeach-bolsonaro-are-rising-but-his-grip-on-brazil-remains-strong/ar-BB1fDxQY </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket Veteran Plots Cheaper Path Back to Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/a-rocket-veteran-plots-a-cheaper-path-back-to-space/ar-BB1fDwfG </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz associate said to be cooperating with prosecutors in probe of congressman...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/gaetz-associate-said-to-be-cooperating-with-prosecutors-in-investigation-of-the-congressman/ar-BB1fCxXn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Greenberg, a former tax collector for Seminole County, Fla., is said to be providing prosecutors evidence against Rep. Matt Gaetz in a sex trafficking investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISS cameras capture '400ft triangular UFO' soaring behind SPACEX craft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/iss-cameras-capture-huge-400ft-23910185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious object was spotted hurtling past SpaceX's Dragon capsule not far from the International Space Station. UFO fan "Mr MBB333" estimated it could be up to 400ft wide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular Exercise May Help Protect Against Severe Covid...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/14/regular-exercise-may-help-protect-against-severe-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More exercise means less risk of developing severe Covid, according to a compelling new study of physical activity and coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker Bitten By Viper at San Diego Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/worker-bitten-by-viper-at-san-diego-zoo/2574799/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Diego Zoo wildlife care specialist was bitten Monday by a venomous snake while they were in an area away from the public, an official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus surges fuel fears 100 days before Tokyo Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/virus-surges-fuel-fears-100-days-before-tokyo-olympics/ar-BB1fChEF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Olympic flame is on its way across Japan and athletes around the world are ramping up training, but 100 days before Tokyo 2020 opens, organisers still face monumental challenges. Despite the problems, Tokyo 2020 organisers say they are confident "we will be able to deliver a safe and secure Games."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixing and matching' corona vaccines will be trialed to see if alternating doses can boost immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9465841/Covid-vaccines-Moderna-Novavax-added-mix-match-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say mixing jabs is unlikely to pose any safety concerns, and that it could even lead to shots being more effective at preventing an infection with the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll: DC worst place in nation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/548011-dc-worst-place-in-america-americans-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans said in a recent poll by YouGov&amp;nb</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA efficacy falls to 90%...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/moderna-covid-vaccine-efficacy-falls-213129629.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US biotech company Moderna announced Covid vaccine is 90 percent effective against all forms of the disease and 95 percent effective against severe disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs banned from Chicago firehouses after one kills smaller pet walking near station...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dogs-banned-chicago-firehouses-one-210400663.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — The Chicago Fire Department will no longer allow dogs at firehouses after a firehouse dog killed a family pet near an Englewood fire station. A dog named Bones — believed by the Fire Department to be a mixed-breed stray taken off the street — was living at Engine 116 at 60th Street and Ashland Avenue when it got out and killed a small breed dog being walked in the area. “Any and all ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uruguay facing world-record Covid infection rate...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-uruguay-world-record-covid-infection.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uruguay has reported a 24-hour record coronavirus death toll, as it has gone from one of the least-affected countries to registering the most new daily cases per capita in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDs reach all-time high for 6th consecutive year...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/stds-reach-all-time-high-for-6th-consecutive-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sexually transmitted diseases have reached an all-time high in the U.S. for the sixth consecutive year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fed is 'overwhelmingly' white and male and needs to change, study says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/13/the-fed-is-overwhelmingly-white-and-male-and-must-change-study-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed has a "staggering" lack of diversity among its directors, according to a report Tuesday from a leading Washington think tank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J VAX HALT OVER CLOTS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-immunizations-coronavirus-pandemic-2dde2aacf486bab59844ef907a28cbce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. on Tuesday recommended a “pause” in use of the single-dose Johnson &amp; Johnson COVID-19 vaccine to investigate reports of rare but potentially dangerous blood clots,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert says cop was justified in pinning down George Floyd...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/derek-chauvin-trial-live-updates-14901d347ed2a6353e2c1db7bec1f9d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Former Officer Derek Chauvin was justified in pinning George Floyd to the ground because he kept struggling, a use-of-force expert testified for the defense Tuesday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Vincent seeks water, funds as volcano keeps erupting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-ralph-gonsalves-6801eeae1833f47ff95def4f198335f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KINGSTOWN, St. Vincent (AP) — Leaders of volcano-wracked St. Vincent said Tuesday that water is running short as heavy ash contaminates supplies, and they estimated that the eastern Caribbean...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
