<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fake FERRARI factory raided...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/792473/ferrari-lamborghini-supercar-fake-cheap-brazil-counterfeit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Best Day -- Was His First Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/mattberman/2020-democratic-primary-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And other things you can learn from new data on how many donors Democratic presidential campaigns got each day this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO:  Ebola outbreak now global emergency...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2019/07/ebola-outbreak-in-congo-declared-a-global-health-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The World Health Organization says the deadly Ebola outbreak in Congo is now an international health emergency after the virus spread this week to a city of 2 million people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia launches criminal case over gay couple's adoption...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-launches-criminal-case-over-gay-couples-adoption-172548071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Wednesday said it had opened an unprecedented criminal case accusing officials of negligence for allowing a gay couple to adopt two children. The Investigative Committee, which probes serious cases, said that Moscow social workers were suspected of criminal negligence for allowing the two</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force warns against storming Area 51 as 'event' reaches 1.5 million attendees...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/air-force-warns-storming-area-51-facebook-event/story?id=64389885</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force is warning people against storming Area 51 in Nevada, after a Facebook event page organizing a meet up at the "Alien Center tourist attraction" went viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Drudge's 'Future' Now Realized, And That Has Legacy Media Enraged...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/timothymeads/2019/07/15/matt-drudges-future-is-now-realized-and-that-has-legacy-media-enraged-n2550087</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth not absolute with AI deception technology...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/453395-truth-is-not-absolute-with-ai-deception-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal challenges may help resolve privacy and developmental concerns so that artificial intelligence can be a viable law enforcement tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK raises alarm after mother held by Iran is taken to mental ward...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-raises-alarm-mother-held-iran-taken-mental-153357016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London demanded the immediate release Wednesday of a jailed British-Iranian aid worker whose husband said she has been transferred to the mental ward of a public hospital in Tehran. Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe's case has roiled Britain's relations with the Islamic republic since her 2016 arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE HEAT TEMPS...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_heat.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food delivery droid wants to use bike lanes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/food-delivery-robot-wants-share-bike-lane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Refraction AI, founded by two researchers at the University of Michigan, joins a crowded field of self-driving delivery vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES GETTING BACK ON MOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/07/trump-and-nasas-uncertain-moon-plans/593986/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA wants to put people back on the lunar surface in 2024, but it doesn’t have the budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren gets big bucks from employees of tech companies she wants to break up...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/07/16/elizabeth-warren-tech-donations-facebook-google-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts senator came in second among the Democratic presidential candidates in donations from employees of Amazon, Apple, Facebook, and Google over the last three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion for hire: Americans embrace clothing rental services...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190717-fashion-hire-americans-embrace-clothing-rental-services</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion for hire: Americans embrace clothing rental services</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CBS EVENING NEWS' Ratings Slip On Norah O'Donnell's Debut As Anchor...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2019/07/17/cbs-evening-news-ratings-slip-on-norah-odonnells-debut-as-anchor/#b1fe2b015b09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ratings data compiled by Nielsen show O'Donnell's first night actually delivered lower ratings than the anchor she replaced, Jeff Glor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There's no justice in America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/792492/el-chapo-life-in-prison-sentence-trial-us-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball Coach Ejected for Fight over Robot Umpire...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/atlantic-league-coach-ejected-for-arguing-over-automated-strike-zone-just-one-inning-into-robot-umpire-era/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank Viola will go down as the first victim of the automated strike zone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters Line up at 4:00 AM for NC Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/07/17/watch-trump-supporters-line-up-at-400-am-for-greenville-nc-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump supporters began lining up early for the president's 2020 re-election campaign rally in Greenville, North Carolina, on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tied up wife's lover, cut off penis, deputies say...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/florida-dismemberment-275903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 17--A gun-toting Florida Man broke into the home of his wife’s lover and cut off the man’s penis with a pair of scissors, according to police who said that the intruder fled the residence with t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugs flow thru NM after checkpoints close...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/drugs-pour-in-from-mexico-as-border-patrol-forced-to-focus-on-migrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS CRUCES, New Mexico — Border Patrol highway checkpoints in the southern New Mexico region that normally seize seven figures of worth of drugs annually have not seized a dollar in nearly four months after being shuttered in late March, allowing drugs to flood into the country. Meantime, with the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House condemnation of Trump may just be beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/long-day-partisan-warfare-house-just-beginning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House’s long day of partisan warfare on Tuesday over President Donald Trump's tweets is likely only one chapter in a saga over the president’s language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tries to muster flotilla as Iran suspected of seizing tanker...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-tries-to-muster-a-flotilla-as-iran-suspected-of-seizing-tanker/ar-AAEsuyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EL CHAPO JAILED FOR LIFE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7255505/Mexican-drug-lord-El-Chapo-faces-sentencing-US-case.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. District Judge Brian Cogan granted prosecutors' request to jail El Chapo for life plus 30 years, the additional years for firearms offenses, in Brooklyn, New York, on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHILLY: 17 Teens Attack Man At Public Pool...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/07/16/17-kids-assault-45-year-old-man-vogt-rec-center-mayfair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen kids between the ages of 12 to 18 years old assaulted the lifeguard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Scaling Warehouse Shelves to Get Stuff to You Faster...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/robots-scaling-warehouse-shelves-stuff-140000673.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A logistics company partly owned by Related Cos., the developer behind Manhattan’s Hudson Yards, is searching for locations across North America to build its multistory robotic warehouses.Robots -- and humans -- started working this month at Quiet Logistics’ new 440,000-square-foot (41,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dump Treasurys, Liquidate Record Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-07-16/foreigners-dump-us-treasurys-liquidate-record-216-billion-us-stocks-13-consecutive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gates loses title as world's second richest person...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/07/17/bill-gates-overtaken-worlds-second-richest-person/1753467001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates lost his title as the world's second-richest person to French billionaire Bernard Arnault, says Bloomberg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce 'LION KING' Song Bombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/07/16/beyonce-faces-a-rare-failure-as-her-lion-king-song-is-shown-no-spirit-from-fans-bombs-on-charts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEDS AM UPDATE: Beyonce debuted the video for “Spirit” last night on ABC. The video already has 2 million views on YouTube. So does the original video. That’s a total of 4 million…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barefoot woman scaled face of Mount Rushmore. She almost made it to top...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-barefoot-woman-scaled-the-face-of-Mount-14101788.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She clung to the sheer rock face barefoot with no safety ropes or climbing gear in sight. To her left, the enormous stone head of George Washington protruded from the side of the granite mountain. An equally impressive likeness of Thomas Jefferson boxed her in from the right. About 15 feet above her was the top of Mount Rushmore.  National Park Service officials said it was at this point that Alexandria Incontro finally stopped climbing last Friday when she illegally scaled the historic sculpture while visiting the monument in South Dakota with her family, according to federal court documents.  On Monday, the 30-year-old from Omaha, Nebraska, pleaded guilty to climbing Mount Rushmore, records said. She was fined $1,000 and given a $30 fee.  "Ms. Incontro seemed like a nice person who was 'having a day' as it were," her lawyer, Thomas Harmon, told The Washington Post in an email late Tuesday.  A Park Service representative did not respond to a request for comment late Tuesday.  The calls came pouring in shortly after 7 p.m. Friday, according to an incident report. A person had gone beyond the barrier intended to keep visitors away from the sculpture and past the bright orange warning signs, witnesses reported. The woman was starting to scramble up the massive pile of loose rocks at the base of the sculpture.  When a federal officer and park ranger arrived, the unruly visitor, later identified as Incontro, was already steadily ascending, the report said. The ranger told Incontro to come down and she responded by saying something like, "Do you want me to come down fast or slow?" She then kept climbing, officials said.  The officer and ranger followed Incontro, trailing behind her as she climbed higher and higher without shoes, gear or safety equipment, the documents said.  By...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign purchases of American homes plunge 36%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/17/foreign-purchases-of-american-homes-plunge-36percent-as-chinese-buyers-flee.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenging conditions in the U.S. housing market, along with tighter currency controls by the Chinese government, cause a stunning drop in foreign demand for American homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tape shows Trump, Epstein discussing women at 1992 party...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/tape-shows-donald-trump-jeffrey-epstein-discussing-women-1992-party-n1030686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The November 1992 tape in the NBC archives shows Donald Trump with Jeffrey Epstein more than a decade before Epstein pleaded guilty to felony prostitution charges in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City Hopes 'Baby Shark' Song Will Drive Homeless From Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/article232770632.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOR FIGHT ERUPTS</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-floor-fight-pelosi-collins-condemn-trump-tweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Escalating tensions on Capitol Hill erupted into a contentious floor fight in the House of Representatives on Tuesday afternoon, as House Speaker Nancy Pelosi spoke in favor of a proposed resolution condemning "racist" comments by President Trump -- even as Republican leaders stood steadfast behind the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's top 100 hotels revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-7249241/The-Leela-Palace-Udaipur-India-voted-best-hotel-world-Travel-Leisure-readers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Readers of Travel + Leisure gave The Leela Palace Udaipur 98.89 out of 100 in the publication's annual 'World's Best 100 Hotels' awards, which earned it the top spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US official claims Mexican soldiers made 'incursion' onto American soil; 'Scuffle' with agent...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7254889/US-official-claims-Mexican-soldiers-incursio-American-soil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple members of the Mexican military crossed into the U.S. in the El Paso sector of western Texas at around 6.15 ET on Tuesday, National Border Patrol Council President Brandon Judd said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triple-digit temps threaten blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/07/16/heat-wave-could-cause-power-outages-new-york-city-chicago-d-c/1749257001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An upcoming heat wave could lead to power outages in the central and eastern U.S., includingÂ major metropolitan areas,Â experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: CHIMPANZEES BOND OVER WATCHING MOVIE TOGETHER...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/world/chimpanzees-bond-over-watching-movie-together-study-937577.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The research suggests human social bonding may have deeper evolutionary roots than previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY WARNING ISSUED OVER APP LETTING USERS TURN SELVES OLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/faceapp-app-download-challenge-privacy-warnings-old-filter-a9008306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tied up wife's lover, cut off penis, deputies say...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/florida-man-tied-up-wifes-lover-cut-off-penis-deputies-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say a Florida man held his wife&amp;#39;s lover at gunpoint and cut off the man&amp;#39;s penis before fleeing with the flailing appendage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu makes history as Israel's longest-serving leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a8a9d3c598954ca6803710e375117156</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hijab-wearing wrestler breaking barriers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/malaysias-phoenix-hijab-wearing-wrestler-breaking-barriers-035112809.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hijab-wearing, diminutive Malaysian wrestler known as "Phoenix" cuts an unusual figure in the ring, a female Muslim fighter taking on hulking opponents in a male-dominated world. Dressed in flame-patterned trousers, a black and orange hijab and top, Nor Diana uses sophisticated moves to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym, eat, repeat: Rise of muscle dysmorphia...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/jul/17/gym-eat-repeat-the-shocking-rise-of-muscle-dysmorphia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idealised male body has become bigger, bulkier and harder to achieve. So what drives a generation of young men to the all-consuming, often dangerous pursuit of perfection?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters Happiest Workers in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/firefighters-are-the-happiest-workers-in-america-1.1288266</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wary swimmers share waves with deadly sharks off Cape Cod...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wary-us-swimmers-share-waves-deadly-sharks-off-081123702.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the entrance to Newcomb Hollow Beach, at the tip of the Cape Cod peninsula, the picture of a great white shark reminds swimmers that the US shores of the Atlantic must be shared with the ocean's most feared predator. The great whites swim to this region in the northeastern United States to hunt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Leaders Head to Secretive Summer Camp to Ponder Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chinas-leaders-head-secretive-summer-090002130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The signs of summer have arrived in the northern Chinese resort town of Beidaihe: The umbrellas are out, the traffic controls are in place and the regional Communist Party chief has stopped by to make sure everything’s set for the most important of visitors.China’s so-called summer capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good playlist make food taste better?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-good-music-playlist-restaurant-153908860.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You've finally secured a table at the hottest new restaurant in town. For weeks it's been all over Instagram; everyone you know is talking about it. After thwarted efforts to arrive ad hoc (thanks to queues that stretch round the block), you're now here, and it's time to enjoy your meal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk wants to implant chips into human brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/tech/elon-musk-wants-hook-your-brain-directly-computers-starting-next-ncna1030631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla and SpaceX founder announced a goal of implanting chips into human brains as early as next year to create direct human connections to computers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Why Trump must acknowledge that he went too far this time...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/16/why-trump-must-acknowledge-that-he-went-too-far-this-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s déjà vu all over again. President Trump has given the hanging party a first-rate piece of rope to use against him. His tweet will not live in infamy, but his cringe-worthy “go back” language r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>76 billion opioid pills flooded USA as epidemic raged, federal data shows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2724e61adf014c59919b754b66138aa2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Republican support for Trump rises after racially charged tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-poll/republican-support-for-trump-rises-after-racially-charged-tweets-reuters-ipsos-poll-idUSKCN1UB2UD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Support for U.S. President Donald Trump increased slightly among Republicans aft...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession fears rise for middle-class families...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/16/more-middle-class-families-say-american-dream-is-out-of-reach-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Middle-class Americans are less optimistic about their financial standing than they were just six months ago, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>76 billion opioid pills flooded USA as epidemic raged, federal data shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/76-billion-opioid-pills-newly-released-federal-data-unmasks-the-epidemic/2019/07/16/5f29fd62-a73e-11e9-86dd-d7f0e60391e9_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six companies distributed and three companies manufactured the bulk of the pills that saturated the nation with opioids from 2006 to 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress orders Pentagon to reveal if it used diseased ticks for biological warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9522551/congress-pentagon-us-military-ticks-lyme-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Military chiefs have been ordered to reveal whether they used diseased TICKS in sick biological warfare experiments. A bill passed in the House of Representatives requires the Pentagon to invest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.3 Mag Quake Rumbles Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/bay-area-quake-strength-brentwood-contra-costa-14100146.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 4.3 quake rattled the Bay Area on Tuesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you're killing iguanas in Florida, do it in the 'kindest manner possible,' PETA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/news/20190712/peta-pipes-in-if-youre-killing-iguanas-do-it-in-kindest-manner-possible</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FWC wants people to humanely kill the invasive green iguanas, but PETA says try to regulate them first, then kill, but do so to 'avoid prolonged suffering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAYOR PETE LEADS DEM FUNDRAISING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/16/buttigieg-biden-warren-lead-2020-democratic-primary-fundraising-race.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders, Pete Buttigieg and Elizabeth Warren entered July with the most money on hand as they jockey for position in the 2020 Democratic primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants on defensive at antitrust hearing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/453390-tech-giants-on-defensive-at-antitrust-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four of the nation’s largest tech companies sought to reassure skeptical lawmakers that they are not a competitive threat to other companies as the House ramps up its antitrust investigation into Silicon Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans murders in Honduras stoke fears of backlash against LGBT...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190716214927-2038p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONDURAS-LGBT/MURDERS (FEATURE):FEATURE-Transgender murders in Honduras stoke fears of backlash against LGBT+ rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain send third warship to the Gulf as Iran threatens attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9522374/iran-threat-attack-britain-tanker-gulf-navy-third-warship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN’s supreme leader has threatened Britain with retaliation over the “vicious” seizure of an Iranian oil tanker near Gibraltar. As tensions escalate over the tanker row, it was revealed that the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats against members of Congress increasing, Capitol police chief says...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/threats-against-members-increasing-capitol-police-chief-sund-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Bennie Thompson has called for police board to re-examine safety procedures following Trump's Twitter attack on four Democratic women of color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-13 gang members indicted after 'medieval-style' killing spree in LA....</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/wielding-machetes-and-baseball-bats-ms--carried-out-medieval/article_a3bb05ba-a0fe-560a-a5db-e88a5fb7a892.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — MS-13 gang members in Los Angeles hacked to death seven people in the last two years, including a rival gang member who was dismembered and had his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEATWAVE BUILDS IN NORTHEAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/hottest-weather-of-season-on-tap-for-northeast-as-record-challenging-heat-wave-builds/70008824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California doesn't have enough doctors. To recruit them, the state is paying off medical school debt...</title>
      <link>https://napavalleyregister.com/news/local/california-doesn-t-have-enough-doctors-to-recruit-them-the/article_de24ccce-16b2-50e9-a1f0-44f1263c029b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;napavalleyregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — Bryan Ruiz’s hands were still shaking an hour after he learned the $300,000 in medical school loans he took out to become a dentist were being wiped away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in jail endured group strip searches. L.A. County to pay $53 million to settle suit...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/07/16/l-a-county-to-pay-53-million-to-settle-lawsuit-over-invasive-group-strip-searches-of-female-inmates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During her brief incarceration several years ago, Jessica Almaraz said she was ushered into a dirty bus garage with 60 or so other inmates at a women’s jail in Lynwood. The inmates, some of whom were menstruating, were told to remove their clothes, and lift and spread their body parts, in full view of one another. Deputies yelled degrading comments and profanities as they made their orders. Some laughed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI BANNED FROM SPEAKING</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/16/nancy-pelosi-criticism-donald-trump-violates-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House ruled Tuesday that House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s criticism of President Trump violates the chamber’s rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WNBA suspends star for domestic violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/wnba/2019/07/16/wnba-suspends-riquna-williams-10-games-for-domestic-violence/39692411/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Sparks guard Riquna Williams was arrested on April 29 and charged with two felony counts. Her criminal case is ongoing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell says 'uncertainties' increased chances of rate cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/16/feds-powell-says-uncertainties-have-increased-chances-of-a-rate-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speech comes as market participants are strongly anticipating a rate cut at the July 30-31 Federal Open Market Committee policy meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD Abruptly Aborts President 8 Months Into Term...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/planned-parenthood-terminates-presidency-after-eight-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Planned Parenthood announced on Tuesday that it has removed Leana Wen as president, after less than a year in the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/nc73225421/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robbers' New Weapon: Fake Marijuana To Make Victims Pass Out...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/07/16/deep-ellum-robbers-new-weapon-synthetic-marijuana-victims-pass-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two of the three victims didn’t even know what had happened to them until police on foot patrol woke them up on the street after they passed out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOTUS showcases first pure electric sports car...</title>
      <link>https://www.topgear.com/car-news/electric/lotus-evija-1972bhp-electric-hypercar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.topgear.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abused Victims While Serving Time, Lawyer Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-abused-victims-while-serving-time-in-florida-lawyer-brad-edwards-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney Brad Edwards says a new accuser has come forward to say Epstein took advantage of work release to prey on young women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBERLYFT pays drivers to protest bill making them employees...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1667396/uber-and-lyft-paid-drivers-to-protest-californias-ab5-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California bill could mean major changes for gig-economy employers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple Married 71 Years Dies On Same Day...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/07/16/amazing-love-story-couple-married-71-years-die-same-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Georgia couple married for 71 years both died on the same day, within just 12 hours of each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kim Gets His Luxury Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/16/world/asia/north-korea-luxury-goods-sanctions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong-un parades around in Mercedes-Benzes and a Rolls-Royce, despite sanctions intended to keep North Korea from importing luxury goods. We tracked how they get there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne to reporter: 'What's your ethnicity?'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/trump-adviser-kellyanne-conway-asks-reporter-what-s-your-ethnicity-n1030406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential counselor's unusual question came during a tense exchange with the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEYLAND becomes 'ghost town'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/16/disneyland-has-become-a-ghost-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To say that Disneyland’s new Star Wars-themed Galaxy’s Edge land is a big deal would be an understatement. The highly anticipated $1 billion, 14-acre immersive expansion was the biggest in pa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CNN analyst: Major news outlets 'Zionist orgs'...</title>
      <link>https://jewishinsider.com/2019/07/ex-cnn-commentator-at-progressive-summit-major-news-outlets-are-zionist-orgs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;jewishinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;T-shirts linking Zionism with racism sold at Netroots Nation conference</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
