<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fashion mogul Nygard consents to extradition to USA on sex trafficking charges...</title>
      <link>https://winnipeg.ctvnews.ca/peter-nygard-consents-to-extradition-to-united-states-1.5607086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;winnipeg.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former fashion mogul Peter Nygard has consented to being extradited to the United States to face charges including sex trafficking and racketeering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing historic challenge, Florida Dems stumble against DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facing-a-historic-challenge-Florida-Democrats-16501880.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. - To Kelly Smith, the case against Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Market Grapples With Surge in Get-Me-Away Demand...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/private-jet-market-grapples-with-surge-in-get-me-away-demand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even people who can normally afford to charter a private jet at a moment’s notice are being forced to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone Sensor Can Detect If High...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smartphone-high-on-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new AI system detects marijuana intoxication by examining smartphone user behavior before and after using cannabis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadband firm sues NETFLIX after traffic surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/skorea-broadband-firm-sues-netflix-after-traffic-surge-squid-game-2021-10-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korean Internet service provider SK Broadband has sued Netflix to pay for costs from increased network traffic and maintenance work because of a surge of viewers to the U.S. firm's content, an SK spokesperson said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority of Trump Voters Now in Favor of Seceding...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/shock-poll-majority-of-trump-voters-now-in-favor-of-seceding-from-the-union/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shocking new poll reveals that over half of Trump voters polled, and 41% of Biden voters, are in favor of blue and/or red states seceding from the union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Gauge Highest Since '91 as Americans Spend More...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inflation-gauge-hits-highest-since-125743783.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. personal spending growth accelerated by more than forecast in August, driven by goods purchases, while a closely watched measure of inflation exceeded estimates. Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsAn Unapologetic Old Boys’ Network Is Costing Australia BillionsThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtHSBC Bets Big on China as Pressure Mounts in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador mining bitcoin using energy from volcanoes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/el-salvador-just-started-mining-bitcoin-with-volcanoes-for-the-first-time-ever-and-theyve-already-made-269.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Salvador has mined 0.00599179 bitcoin, or about $269, with power harnessed from a volcano, in a first for the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta's Wealthiest, Whitest District Wants to Secede...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-10-01/buckhead-cityhood-vote-district-wants-to-secede-from-atlanta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some residents are pushing to make Buckhead its own city, the latest in a series of political ruptures by race and class across the metro area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last stand of Bob Baffert, horse racing's most successful and embattled trainer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/last-stand-bob-baffert-horse-103046549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Baffert has cultivated the story of a horse racing dynasty built from humble roots. He now faces scrutiny about short cuts he's alleged to have taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million bolivars become one as Venezuela recalibrates battered currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211001-a-million-bolivars-become-one-as-venezuela-recalibrates-battered-currency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A million bolivars become one as Venezuela recalibrates battered currency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man invited people into motel room. Then sacrificed them and set them on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/A-Texas-man-invited-people-into-his-motel-room-16501500.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside of the Mid City Inn in Euless, Texas, Jason Alan Thornburg was often seen reading...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-food chains close indoor seating as cities mandate jab checks...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001095910-p0smd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RESTAURANTS/VACCINES (PIX):Fast-food chains close some indoor seating as U.S. cities mandate vaccine checks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's most restrictive abortion law back in Texas court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-austin-texas-courts-lawsuits-a7961b629e913e1008f8e929c99fb310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — A federal judge on Friday will consider whether Texas can leave in place the most restrictive abortion law in the U.S., which since September has banned most abortions and sent women racing to get care beyond the borders of the nation's second-most populous state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can RNA Be Altered? Scientists Could Bend Strands Into Circles to Treat Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-10-01/can-rna-be-altered-scientists-could-bend-strands-into-circles-to-treat-cancer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors flock to biotech startup Orna Therapeutics on the promise of low-cost treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon's 300% Surge Throws Another Price Shock at World...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/silicon-300-surge-throws-another-032657665.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A metal made from the second-most abundant element on Earth has become scarce, threatening everything from car parts to computer chips and throwing up another hurdle for the world economy.Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsAn Unapologetic Old Boys’ Network Is Costing Australia BillionsThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtHSBC Bets Big on China a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PWC will allow ALL employees to work virtually, live anywhere they want...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/exclusive-pwc-tells-us-employees-they-need-never-return-office-2021-09-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accounting and consulting firm PwC told Reuters on Thursday it will allow all its 40,000 U.S. client services employees to work virtually and live anywhere they want in perpetuity, making it one of the biggest employers to embrace permanent remote work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Wants Greenland's Minerals. Greenlanders Wary...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/the-world-wants-greenlands-minerals-but-greenlanders-are-wary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NARSAQ, Greenland — This huge, remote and barely habited island is known for frozen landscapes, remote fjords and glaciers that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange Allure of Pool-Cleaning Videos...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/the-strange-allure-of-pool-cleaning-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some TikTok creators have become successful on the video platform by dancing, singing or performing everyday tasks. Miles Laflin has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Parisians Are Over FOGO...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/the-parisians-are-over-fogo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — On a recent sunny afternoon, a cluster of young women in short dresses and high boots crowded into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock, Bond, Real Estate Prices All Uncomfortably High...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/stock-bond-and-real-estate-prices-are-all-uncomfortably-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prices of stocks, bonds and real estate, the three major asset classes in the United States, are all extremely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Rape Accusations, Fraternities Face Protests and Growing Anger...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/after-rape-accusations-fraternities-face-protests-and-growing-anger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the University of Nebraska-Lincoln, hundreds of students protested outside a fraternity house in August after a student reported a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Month Later, Five Zebras Still on Run in Maryland...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/30/a-month-later-five-zebras-are-still-on-the-run-in-maryland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re still out there, roaming free. A month after they escaped from a farm in Maryland, five zebras have evaded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Afghans leaving U.S. military bases before resettlement...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/exclusive-giant-can-worms-some-afghans-leave-us-military-bases-before-2021-10-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something unexpected is happening at U.S. military bases hosting Afghan evacuees: Many hundreds of them are simply leaving before receiving U.S. resettlement services, two sources familiar with the data told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson, DISNEY Settle Explosive 'BLACK WIDOW' Suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/scarlett-johansson-disney-settle-black-widow-lawsuit-1235022598/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The settlement ends a back-and-forth PR battle pitting the CAA-repped star against the studio that was poised to have dramatic implications for all of Hollywood’s majors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Brazil election run-up, US-style Big Lie not ruled out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-election-run-us-style-012907270.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leftist former president Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva is the favorite in Brazil's elections one year from now but surprises along the way are not ruled out -- not even a dramatic US-style finale with charges of a rigged result.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flag-wearing man throws Molotov cocktail into Austin Dems HQ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-austin-texas-0d88e008e385feb7001be133f19c11c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — An arson investigation was underway after a man wearing an American flag bandanna threw a Molotov cocktail into the headquarters of the county Democratic Party in Austin. The incendiary device did not ignite when it was thrown at the Travis County Democratic Party headquarters at about 2 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne covid cases hit record DESPITE two months of lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-victoria-reports-record-new-covid-19-cases-2021-09-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melbourne's COVID-19 cases surged to record levels on Thursday with officials blaming illegal home gatherings to watch a key sporting event for the spike as a hard lockdown to combat the spread of the Delta variant neared two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Uprecedented efforts to intimidate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/justice-alito-says-the-supreme-court-didn-t-nullify-roe-v-wade-in-texas-abortion-decision-this-portrayal-feeds-unprecedented-efforts-to-intimidate-the-court/ar-AAP0PQi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The justice also said that recent claims about the court's decision-making are "false and inflammatory."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIEW TO A CHILL:  WILL AUDIENCES FLOCK TO BOND?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/the-new-james-bond-film-aims-to-steady-a-shaken-industry-but-no-one-seems-to-know-what-will-leave-audiences-stirred/ar-AAP0DRo?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As "No Time to Die" opens, the era of major movies debuting exclusively in theaters is finally back. But which genres can actually entice consumers is vexing Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ridley Scott, 83, Plans 'GLADIATOR' Sequel  After Napoleon!</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/sopranos-fever-sweeps-the-youth-pitt-clooney-reunion-ridley-scotts-new-gladiator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Bond suggestions; the Many Saints of Newark meaning; kids today love The Sopranos; Brad Pitt and George Clooney face off; Ridley Scott is planning a Gladiator sequel. All in today’s Movie News Rundown. But First: This short bonus episode of The Industry podcast looks at one man’s quest to fix Superman IV. It’s on Spotify and Apple and […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California returns land to descendants of original Black owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-09-30/newsom-signs-law-to-return-bruces-beach-black-family</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom authorizes returning the land known as Bruce's Beach to the descendants of a Black couple that had been run out of Manhattan Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major flea infestation shuts 2 Oakland schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/major-flea-infestation-shuts-2-oakland-schools</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two elementary schools in Oakland will be closed for the rest of the week due to an infestation of fleas that may have been caused by raccoons in the area, school officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oldest man who ever lived' dies at 127...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/oldest-man-who-ever-lived-25112382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natabay Tinsiew, who claimed to have been born in 1894, passed away in his remote village of Azefa on Monday as his family look for him to be officially recognised by the organisation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN PUSHES ELIMINATION OF DEBT CEILING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/30/yellen-lends-support-for-effort-to-remove-the-debt-ceiling-altogether.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said Thursday she would just as soon see the power over debt limits taken away from Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS To Slow Mail Delivery Beginning Friday; 'Will Be Slower Than In 1970s'; 'Disastrous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mail-delivery-slower-usps-october-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Postmaster General Louis DeJoy's 10-year plan is aimed at cutting costs. Critics call it "disastrous."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem civil war hits new heights...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/574814-democratic-civil-war-hits-new-heights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats engaged in a verbal war on Thursday, with progressives and centrists accusing one another of essentially sabotaging President Biden’s agenda and putting the party’s majorities in jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST LOOK: Scheindlin Returns to Courtroom In Trailer for New 'JUDY JUSTICE'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/reality-tv/news/judge-judy-scheindlin-returns-courtroom-trailer-new-show-judy-justice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Judy Scheindlin is back in the courtroom for the first look trailer at her upcoming [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIP-HOP HALFTIME FOR SUPER BOWL 2022...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/30/super-bowl-2022-halftime-performers-announced/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for the most stacked Super Bowl halftime performers lineup of all time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Month for Stocks Ends With Few Signs the Drama Is Over...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bad-month-stocks-ends-few-202428322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The end of the September in the stock market was a time of volatility, accelerated hedging and economic unease. It did not, however, spur an extreme reordering in trader sentiment, and to some of Wall Street’s old guard that’s worrisome.Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsAn Unapologetic Old Boys’ Network Is Costing Australia BillionsThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKHEED refuses  comment on video exposing mystery craft on secret testing base...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/09/30/lockheed-martin-skunk-works-chief-skunk-jeff-babione-national-defence-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockheed Martin Senior Executive Refuses To Comment On Odd-Shaped Aircraft That Surfaced In TikTok Video At Apparent Skunk Works Facility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Biden rules would limit arrest, deportation of migrants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-donald-trump-joe-biden-mexico-arrests-af64610730b9c603b592101e4a7ddfa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing bipartisan criticism over its approach to immigration, the Biden administration on Thursday announced new rules that require authorities to only pursue migrants who recently crossed into the country without permission or are deemed to pose a threat to public safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman arrested for felony grits attack...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/grits-attack-arrest-908572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 30--A Florida Woman is behind bars for allegedly striking her boyfriend in the head with a sauce pan “containing freshly cooked grits,” according to a felony complaint. Investigators say De</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid cases fall by 25%, fueling hope Delta has peaked...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-cases-infections-down-a8fef1a4-5215-4a91-9bdc-1874724e5698.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are still a lot of cases, but it's a significant improvement from this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Crazed Parents Make Bizarre Threat to Defund Own School...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mask-crazed-parents-make-bizarre-threat-to-defund-own-school/ar-AAP0uhP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As coronavirus outbreaks plague America’s schools, parents opposed to common-sense safety measures like mask mandates have resorted to bizarre and even violent tactics, perhaps most notoriously threatening to zip-tie an elementary school principal. Now, some parents enraged at a mandate in Ankeny School Community District near Des Moines, Iowa, are dangling a new, legal tactic, albeit one that risks sabotaging their own school system:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alito says Supreme Court not 'dangerous cabal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/30/politics/samuel-alito-notre-dame/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Samuel Alito on Thursday rejected criticism that the Supreme Court has improperly handled some of the cases that come to it as a part of its emergency docket without the benefit of a full briefing schedule and oral arguments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans Freak:  'Belichick Resorting to Biological Warfare'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/fans-freak-out-as-tom-brady-appears-noticeably-sick-before-clash-with-patriots-belichick-resorting-to-biological-warfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is gearing up for one of the most highly anticipated matchups of his career and football fans are freaking out after he appeared noticeably ill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarkozy sentenced to 1 year for illegal campaign financing...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210930-former-french-president-sarkozy-found-guilty-of-illegal-campaign-financing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French court Thursday imposed a one-year sentence on former president Nicolas Sarkozy after finding him guilty of illegal campaign financing for massive overspending on his 2012 re-election campaig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret State Dept Report Says Microwaves Didn't Cause 'Havana Syndrome'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/danvergano/havana-syndrome-jason-crickets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A declassified State Department report obtained by BuzzFeed News dismissed the theory that microwave weapons are behind the mysterious neurological injuries in diplomats worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military suicides rise 15%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-army-lloyd-austin-aa9971be75f6a78d9b6530d6ff3d6d72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The number of U.S. military suicides jumped by 15% last year, fueled by significant increases in the Army and Marine Corps that senior leaders called troubling. They urged more effort to reverse the trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congresswomen Share Their Abortion Stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5db7bk/congresswomen-share-their-abortion-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congresswomen testified as Texas’s abortion ban threatens to overturn Roe v. Wade and end abortion access as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China population could halve in next 45 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3150699/chinas-population-could-halve-within-next-45-years-new-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say previous estimates may have severely underestimated the pace of demographic decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin forcing debate about debt...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/09/30/joe-manchin-is-forcing-congress-to-think-about-the-deficit-good/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among Americans who aren't liberal pundits, the debt and deficit rank as major concerns. It's about time Congress noticed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire at secret Iran missile base...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/fire-in-iran-occurred-at-secret-irgc-missile-base-report-680760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday, Tel Aviv-based ImageSat International - ISI, a commercial servicer for satellite images - estimated that the facility was not just any military compound - it was a secret missile base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage mayor backs use of yellow stars by mask opponents...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/anchorage/2021/09/29/tensions-run-high-over-proposed-mask-ordinance-at-second-night-of-anchorage-assembly-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public testimony stretched until midnight and the Assembly did not vote on the ordinance. Another meeting is scheduled for Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMITH &amp; WESSON Moving From MA To TN Over Proposed Gun Laws...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/30/smith-and-wesson-massachusetts-tennessee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smith &amp; Wesson, one of the oldest gun manufacturers in the country, announced Thursday it is moving operations from Springfield to Tennessee due to gun laws in Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Combat Meth, California To Pay Drug Users To Stop Using...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/09/30/1040412804/to-combat-meth-california-will-try-a-bold-treatment-pay-drug-users-to-stop-using</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fatal drug overdoses, including from meth, have soared. California is preparing to roll out a controversial but proven treatment that involves paying stimulant users small sums of money not to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shakira says wild boars attacked her, stole purse in park...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/shakira-says-wild-boars-attacked-her-stole-her-purse-barcelona-n1280477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Look at how two wild boar which attacked me in the park have left my bag," Shakira told her more than 70 million Instagram followers as she held up her torn bag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Tom Brady Sounds Extremely Sick -- Doesn't Know Why...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/30/tom-brady-sounds-extremely-sick-hoarse-voice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady spoke to the media Thursday, though he didn't sound at all like Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who survived 1918 flu succumbs to corona...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Woman-who-survived-Spanish-flu-world-war-16498363.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She lived a life of adventure that spanned two continents. She fell in love with a World...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN 'toxic' workplace, workers claim in essay...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/30/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-essay-claims-toxic-workplace.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos' space company Blue Origin is described as a "toxic" workplace in an essay by 21 current and former employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COSBY: R. Kelly Was 'Screwed,' 'Railroaded' In Trial!</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/celebrities/news/2021/09/29/bill-cosby-r-kelly-verdict-comments-railroaded.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Wyatt spoke out on behalf of his 84-year old client.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Becomes Social Experiment For Behavioral Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-lockdown-social-experiment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study finds women tend to make significantly longer phone calls and follow government measures more closely than men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Stagehands Set to Begin Strike Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/e2-80-98about-power-not-reason-e2-80-99-as-locals-build-support-iatse-votes-on-strike-authorization-next-week/ar-AAOKniV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voting begins October 1 on a strike authorization vote that could lead to a production shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orban Foe Who'd Break the Law to Raze His Regime Leads Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/orban-foe-who-d-break-the-law-to-raze-his-regime-leads-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orban Foe Who’d Break the Law to Raze His Regime Leads Primaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How tech journalism turned against technology...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/tech-media-has-turned-anti-tech/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook want you to join them on the Metaverse. The Metaverse is the company’s Next Big Thing, and where they see the internet going: an online world of total wraparound experience, a lot more like the Lawnmower Man version than what we have now. They released a statement this week earmarking some $50 million towards [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIEW TO A CHILL:  WILL AUDIENCES FLOCK TO BOND?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rave-james-bond-reviews-raise-110742055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Rave reviews for the long-delayed James Bond movie “No Time to Die” could finally entice people away from Netflix and into theaters. Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionHSBC Bets Big on China as Pressure Mounts in LondonHow Los Angeles Became the City of DingbatsTiming can dictate the success or failure of a b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S sues to block AMAZON billboard off flagship store...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/macys-files-suit-to-keep-amazon-billboard-off-flagship-store</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looks like Amazon may be trying to encroach on Macy's territory in the heart of Midtown Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous FACEBOOK Whistleblower Speaks Out on '60 MINUTES'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/facebook-whistleblower-60-minutes-2021-09-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former employee, who recently filed anonymous federal complaints against Facebook, reveals her identity on 60 Minutes, Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Someone Betting Oil Will Soar to Record $200 a Barrel...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/commodities/energy/oil-gas/someone-is-betting-that-oil-will-soar-to-a-record-200-a-barrel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SORKIN: Rudin Got What He Deserves...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/09/aaron-sorkin-on-scott-rudin-scott-got-what-he-deserves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exclusive interview with Sorkin as his smash adaptation of 'To Kill a Mockingbird' reopens on Broadway, without its disgraced producer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Academic Success Often Leads To 'Vicious Cycle' Of Perfectionism, Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/school-success-perfectionism-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some students can't help but feel like they're fighting a never-ending scholarly battle just to prove they're "good enough."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem agenda hangs in balance...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-e2-80-99-agenda-hangs-in-balance-as-pelosi-biden-scramble-for-support-on-infrastructure-vote/ar-AAP0flj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expected House vote increasingly appears doomed: Liberal-leaning Democrats over the past day have reinforced their opposition to the measure, as they wage a broader, still-intensifying war with moderates over the fuller size and scope of Biden’s economic agenda.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
