<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Get COVID' Party Helped Overrun Alberta's ICUs...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvzq73/a-get-covid-party-helped-overrun-albertas-icus-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Partygoers were reportedly trying to “build up natural immunity” rather than get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrests after French soccer rocked by violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210923-arrests-after-french-football-rocked-by-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arrests after French football rocked by violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorillas shock onlookers with sex show at Bronx Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/23/gorillas-shock-onlookers-with-oral-sex-at-bronx-zoo-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say it’s quite common: Primates can be caught “performing every position and variation one can imagine.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When 'Ask app not to track,' some iPhone apps keep snooping anyway...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ask-app-not-track-iphone-161340829.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On your iPhone, you can now tap a button that says, "Ask app not to track." But behind the scenes, some apps keep snooping anyway. Say you open the app Subway Surfers, listed as one of the App Store's "must-play" games. It asks if you're OK with the app "tracking" you, a question iPhones started displaying in April as part of a privacy crackdown by Apple. Saying no is supposed to stop apps such as Subway Surfers and Facebook from learning about what you do in other apps and websites.Subscribe to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN BRINGS BACK HAND AMPUTATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/taliban-afghanistan-executions-punishments-ae174220-c2ec-41e4-8b40-6e3f06cec9ad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Quran will be the foundation of laws in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU pummeled for altering RBG abortion quote, replaces 'woman' with 'person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/aclu-ruth-bader-ginsburg-abortion-quote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) is raising eyebrows for altering a quote from the late Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg in order to be more inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLM Leader Promises National 'Uprising' Over 'Racist' Mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/new-york-blm-leader-promises-national-uprising-over-racist-vaccine-mandates-similar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses In Short Supply. Vax Mandate Could Make It Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/23/1039228806/nurses-are-in-short-supply-employers-worry-vaccine-mandate-could-make-it-worse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has ordered more than 17 million health care workers to get a COVID-19 vaccine. Some health care employers fear losing large numbers of workers who don't want the shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of horses in Del Rio suspended...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/23/use-of-horses-along-border-in-texas-suspended-white-house-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The use of horses among Border Patrol officials in Del Rio, Texas, has been suspended in the aftermath of images being shared that showed mounted Border Patrol agents using their horses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracy roils Kennedys after killer's release recommended...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-politics/article/rfk-jr-bobby-kennedy-sirhan-sirhan-parole-16474192.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recommendation for parole has sent shock waves through the Kennedy family, already...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both vaccinated? Oregon health officials say you can kiss on dates again...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/coronavirus/2021/09/both-vaccinated-oregon-health-officials-say-you-can-kiss-on-dates-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oregon Health Authority says "intimacy" is back on, if you're vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Legalizes Breakthrough Treatment: Magic Mushrooms...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/2021/09/23/magic-mushrooms-oregon-legalizes-breakthrough-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oregon will license and regulate psilocybin-assisted therapy by 2023. Some health care professionals aren't willing to wait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warrant issued for ex-NETFLIX exec accused of raping wife...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/23/diego-bunuel-former-netflix-exec-accused-of-assaulting-wife-wanted-by-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Post has confirmed a warrant is still active for former Netflix executive Diego Bunuel as the 46-year-old allegedly assaulted his wife Maggie Kim in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA 1st state to set quota limits for retailers like AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/newsom-signs-law-making-california-1st-state-to-set-quota-limits-for-retailers-like-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California on Wednesday became the first state to bar mega-retailers from firing warehouse workers for missing quotas that interfere with bathroom and rest breaks under a new law signed by Gov. Gav…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tears in the Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm/2021/09/23/scoop-tears-in-the-oval-office-494448</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Democrats announce a reconciliation revenue framework.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crusader mass grave in Lebanon sheds light on cruelty of medieval warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/crusader-mass-grave-in-lebanon-sheds-light-on-cruelty-of-medieval-warfare-680138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists managed to reconstruct the rest of 25 individuals, all men, and analyzed their wounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEPP SPEAKS:  No one is safe from cancel culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/johnny-depp-blasts-cancel-culture-from-literal-platform-more-strike-talk-r-i-p-melvin-van-peebles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp criticizes cancel culture as reporters hang on his every word; a strike by IATSE’s 150,000 members looks increasingly possible; R.I.P. to Melvin Van Peebles, an icon, revolutionary, and baadasssss. Cancelled: Johnny Depp bemoaned yesterday that “no one is safe” from cancel culture, while speaking into a microphone to a room filled with journalists.  “It […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen says Trump bluffing about running for office again...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com.au/michael-cohen-trump-bluffing-about-running-for-president-2024-2021-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen told Insider that Trump wants to keep raising money and retain some "semblance of power, importance, and relevance, none of which he has."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-coded tickets are key to escape...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/haitians-color-coded-tickets-key-033002097.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. authorities are allowing Haitian migrants at a massive camp in Texas who hold blue and yellow numbered tickets to remain in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At overrun ICU in Montana, 'problem is we're running out of hallways'...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/montana-icu-overrun-with-covid-patients-staffing-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billings Clinic in Montana is past the tipping point as it looks for places to add intensive care unit beds and is on the cusp of rationing care to deal with the surge of sick covid patients in a s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some dumped at gas station...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/biden-administration-releases-some-haitian-migrant-families-at-del-rio-gas-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas — Haitian migrant families who illegally crossed the southern border and lived in a makeshift camp beneath an international bridge are being released into the United States, contradicting the Biden administration’s claims that they would be removed from the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Multiple casualties' reported after shooting at Fort Meade... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3717748/fort-meade-shooting-multiple-casualties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“MULTIPLE casualties” were reported after a gunman reportedly entered a US Army building in Fort Meade Thursday morning, a spokesperson tells The Sun. Officials with the Fort Meade divi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To sue NYT and niece, The Don turns to low profile attorney from New Jersey...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/to-sue-the-new-york-times-and-his-niece-trump-turned-to-a-low-profile-attorney-from-new-jersey/ar-AAOJHGA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alina Habba, Trump’s new attorney, also replaced a longtime Trump lawyer in another defamation case brought by a former Apprentice contestant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: DOW jumps 500 points as comeback rally intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/22/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks were higher Thursday as fears around a crisis in China's property market eased and as the Fed kept current monetary stimulus in place for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREEDOM:  Sweden won the argument on Covid?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/anders-tegnell-sweden-won-the-argument-on-covid/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of all the celebrities that have been created during the course of the Covid-19 pandemic, Swedish State Epidemiologist Anders Tegnell is perhaps the most surprising. A softly-spoken official within the Swedish Health Agency, he has quietly been going about his work monitoring infectious diseases for years. But his decision, when Covid hit, to stick to [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US special envoy to Haiti resigns over migrant expulsions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/haiti-envoy-resigns-migrants-border-texas-8bdf813465adc48856eea352bd3bd6b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration’s special envoy to Haiti resigned in protest of "inhumane" large-scale expulsions of Haitian migrants to their homeland wracked by civil strife and natural disaster, U.S. officials said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. County sheriff's unit accused of targeting political enemies, vocal critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/la-county-sheriffs-unit-accused-of-targeting-political-enemies-vocal-critics/ar-AAOJMfp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little-known team of investigators in the L.A. County Sheriff's Department has pursued criminal investigations into some of Villanueva's most vocal critics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenya bans 'blasphemous' film about gay lovers...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210923-kenya-bans-blasphemous-film-about-gay-lovers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kenya bans 'blasphemous' film about gay lovers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican forces surround border camp...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-immigration-joe-biden-mexico-texas-98ca5cbe55bec23b01555cdf770ac373</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD ACUÑA, Mexico (AP) — A camp where more than 14,000 migrants had waited along the Texas border just days ago was dramatically smaller at dawn Thursday, while across the river in Mexico, Haitian migrants in a growing camp awoke surrounded by security forces as a helicopter thundered overhead .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domestic flight jab mandate? Not 'off table'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/09/23/domestic-flight-vaccine-mandate-not-off-the-table/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speculation is growing that the federal government may require proof of vaccination for domestic air travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Uncomfortable Question in France: Are We Still Great Power?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/23/an-uncomfortable-question-in-france-are-we-still-a-great-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — Beneath France’s angry outbursts about a secretive “knife-in-the-back” American deal to provide nuclear-powered submarines to Australia lay a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp, social posts helped lead migrants Del Rio...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-technology-united-states-del-rio-haiti-872d4b59f5f68f0a63b32704aa961021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas (AP) — For the final leg of his journey from Chile to the United States, Haitian migrant Fabricio Jean followed detailed instructions sent to him via WhatsApp from his brother in New Jersey who had recently taken the route to the Texas border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. special envoy for Haiti resigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-special-envoy-haiti-resigns-amid-deportations-report-2021-09-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. special envoy for Haiti, Ambassador Daniel Foote, has resigned, a senior State Department official said on Thursday, amid mass deportations of Haitians who fled recent political turmoil and natural disasters at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant drive-thrus slower and less accurate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/23/its-not-your-imagination-restaurant-drive-thrus-are-slower-and-less-accurate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drive-thrus became slower and less accurate in 2021, according to SeeLevel HX's annual report.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
