<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA to cut troops on Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bdcaae2eaf5f4d2b9cb8a5d8464be3c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. officials say the number of active-duty troops on the border with Mexico will drop from 5,600 to about 4,000, and their deployment will be extended through the end of January. Officials say the Department of Homeland Security submitted a formal request for the additional military support Friday. It hasn't been approved by Defense Secretary Jim Mattis. But military officials have been working with DHS for weeks to help craft a request that would be accepted by the Pentagon. President Donald Trump deployed the troops to the border in response to a caravan of migrants walking to the U.S. from Central America. Critics have called the deployment a political stunt before the midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: White Dallas Cop Indicted For Murder In Shooting Death Of Unarmed Black Neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/11/30/sources-former-dallas-police-officer-amber-guyger-indicted-for-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Dallas Police Officer Amber Guyger was indicted for murder in the shooting death of Botham Jean in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  NFL STAR BRUTALIZES, KICKS WOMAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2018/11/30/kc-chiefs-kareem-hunt-attacked-kicked-woman-surveillance-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TMZ Sports has obtained video of KC Chiefs running back Kareem Hunt attacking a woman in an Ohio hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal worker admits stealing $5,200 from greeting cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/communities/west/news/wauwatosa/2018/11/30/u-s-postal-worker-admits-stealing-money-mail-wisconsin/2160849002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas P. Gunderson pleads guilty to embezzling mail on Nov. 29.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETTE MIDLER: HANG TRUMP, FAMILY 'GOOD AND HIGH'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2018/11/30/bette-midler-fantasizes-trump-and-family-hanged-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Bette Midler fantasized about President Trump and his family being hanged "good and high" in a pro-Robert Mueller social media post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVOLT:  Employees pledge $200K to engineers who strike...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/419163-google-employees-pledge-200k-to-engineers-to-go-on-strike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google employees have pledged $200,000 to the company's engineers if they go on strike to protest its decision to release a censored search engine for China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swastikas Painted On LA Black Panther Mural...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/29/lapd-probes-swastikas-painted-on-mural-depicting-black-leaders-activists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police Thursday were investigating the scrawling of four swastikas on a South Los Angeles mural depicting black civil rights leaders and activists as a hate crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami warning canceled...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2018/11/30/tsunami-warning-issued-kenai-peninsula-communities-on-cook-inlet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday’s earthquake didn’t create a big wave in Cook Inlet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PALIN:  Family Intact, House Not...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/SarahPalinUSA/status/1068578031176957952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“🙏🏼 for Alaska. Our family is intact - house is not... I imagine that’s the case for many, many others. So thankful to be safe; praying for our state following the earthquake.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC clerk stalls marriage over 'foreign' New Mexico ID card...</title>
      <link>https://www.lcsun-news.com/story/news/local/2018/11/29/las-cruces-resident-prove-new-mexico-statehood-washington-dc/2149376002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lcsun-news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former candidate for New Mexico Secretary of State had to convince staff in a Washington, D.C., marriage bureau New Mexico is in fact one of the 50.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabinet Secretary Calls Congressional Critic Drunk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6447723/Zinke-responds-Democratic-congressmans-resignation-demand-calling-DRUNK.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It’s hard for him to think straight from the bottom of the bottle,' Zinke said in a statement he posted on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs who surrender medical license in one state still practice in others...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/11/30/medical-board-license-failures-doctor-malpractice-move-states/2159948002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surrendering a medical license in one state resulted in far more lenient discipline by medical boards, and sometimes no punishment at all, in another</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Intel Committee has made criminal referrals to Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/30/richard-burr-intel-criminal-referrals-michael-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Burr suggests referral was made against Michael Cohen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio station pulls 'Baby It's Cold Outside' amid #MeToo...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2018/11/30/radio-station-stops-playing-baby-its-cold-outside-amid-me-too-movement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND - A Cleveland radio station has stopped playing “Baby It's Cold Outside" this holiday season after it says listeners voiced concern about the song’s predatory undertones amid the “Me Too” movement. WDOK Christmas 102.1 pulled the song from its around-the-clock rotation of Christmas music this week after receiving a call from a listener who suggested it is inappropriate in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Trump Jr.'s Testimony Conflicts With Cohen's Account...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/11/30/672188201/trump-jr-s-2017-testimony-conflicts-with-cohen-s-account-of-russian-talks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's son told the Senate that negotiations over a Trump Tower in Moscow concluded before his father's campaign took off. The president's former attorney said otherwise in court Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO exercises cyber defences as threat grows...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/nato-exercises-cyber-defences-threat-grows-161421627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The activity is taking place just 50 kilometres (30 miles) from the border with Russia, seen by the West as the biggest cyber threat after a string of attacks blamed on the Kremlin. Targets have included world sports bodies, the US Democratic Party and the world chemical weapons watchdog in the Netherlands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial recognition deployed at marathon to stop cheats...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/facial-recognition-deployed-china-marathon-stop-cheats-050110393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial recognition will be deployed at a marathon on Sunday in China to crack down on cheating, state media said, after a half-marathon was blighted by widescale flouting of the rules. Running and marathons are fast becoming popular in China, with participants sporting the latest trendy gear and wearable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM worker blames Trump for job cuts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/419086-laid-off-gm-worker-blames-trump-for-losing-her-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who has spent the past 20 years working at the General Motors plant in Lordstown, Ohio, said in a recent interview that she blames President Trump for the planned closure of GM's sole assembly plant in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military claims EMP attack would wipe out America, 'democracy, world order'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/military-warns-emp-attack-could-wipe-out-america-democracy-world-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an extraordinary and sobering report meant to wake the nation up to a growing threat, a new military white paper warns that an electromagnetic pulse weapon attack like those developed by North Korea, Russia and Iran could essentially wipe out the United States, kill or displace millions and even…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican governors raise concerns about midterm losses...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/30/trump-midterms-republican-party-governors-rga-1034609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican governors say the president and the party has to find a way to appeal beyond a narrowing conservative base to avoid losing in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE OBAMA BESTSELLING BOOK OF YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/michelle-obama-becoming-memoir-2018-best-seller-ea7f80d6-000b-45ad-aa73-260aae0606c7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's sold more than 2 million copies in the U.S. and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dominatrix specializes in turning 'white, right-wing men' into socialists...</title>
      <link>https://womenintheworld.com/2018/11/30/dominatrix-specializes-in-turning-white-right-wing-men-into-socialists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;womenintheworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing wave of sex-positive feminists are working to usher in what they describe as a “pleasure revolution” in which women’s sexuality is embraced, rather than stigmatized, by both individuals a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA CELEBRATE COHEN PLEA...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-media-giddy-cohen-plea-turning-gun-trump-prez-next-just-begi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Today is a good day for Donald Trump to resign’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug lord who changed his face testifies against El Chapo...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/el-chapo-trial-drug-lord-who-changed-his-face-testifies-n942116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was the third former drug dealer to testify so far at the trial in federal court against notorious drug lord Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires, Rising Crime Fueling LA Gated Community Craze...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/wildfires-rising-crime-fuel-las-gated-community-craze-1163999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire fears from Malibu to Bel Air are adding to the allure of self-contained neighborhoods for A-listers — from Arnold Schwarzenegger to the Kardashians — who are already concerned about rising crime and the "Next Door effect" on anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLUES OF MUELLER</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/muellers-coming-attractions-1543587088-55f4cf5c-6338-4bce-8b38-4f70710f17c1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every twist of the investigation shows that Mueller knows far more than we thought he did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champs Elysees braces for return of France's 'yellow vest' protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests/champs-elysees-braces-for-return-of-frances-yellow-vest-protesters-idUSKCN1NZ1WN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workmen erected metal barriers and plywood boards on the glass-fronted facades o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Americans Rank Financial Security Over Love in Relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/affluent-americans-rank-money-higher-than-love-when-coupling-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Americans Rank Financial Security Over Love in Relationships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miley Cyrus wild new music video includes strip club full of priests...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/miley-cyrus-new-music-video-mark-ronson-nothing-breaks-like-a-heart-priests-police-a8660376.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space war brewing? Russia announces will establish lunar colony...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6446333/Is-space-war-brewing-Russia-announces-establish-lunar-colony-2040.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement was made at a joint meeting of the Moscow-based Scientific and Technical Council of Roscosmos and the Space Council of the Russian Academy of Sciences (stock image).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Implants to Treat Depression...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-propose-new-way-to-depression-with-brain-imp-1830745317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years, doctors have explored an unorthodox method to address cases of depression that haven’t responded to other treatments: sending precise electrical shocks directly to areas of a patient’s brain, otherwise known as deep brain stimulation (DBS). While the technique has shown some promise, its positive effects tend to be inconsistent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' loses Trump-bump glory...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2018/11/30/saturday-night-live-lost-its-trump-bump-glory-pete-davidson-alec-baldwin/2135741002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Saturday Night Live' was on a ratings and critical high for more than a year after the 2016 election, but the show's reliance on Trump jokes and its series of controversies has turned the 44th season into a mess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia scrambles troops amid fears of COUP to topple Crown Prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/745522/saudi-arabia-mohammed-bin-salman-coup-military-g20-riyadh-crown-prince</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality series chronicles love lives of 'extreme' couples: Adult babies, vampires, man who has sex with CAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6440489/Bizarre-new-reality-series-documents-lives-extreme-couples.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We tv's docuseries Extreme Love is based on the digital series of the same name and takes an intimate look at unusual couples around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack among biggest ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/news/marriott-hit-hack-ranks-among-biggest-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nashville police union: AMAZON getting 'corporate welfare'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0a82b2c4d5ed4095b9bd4a1544f4615a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Nashville's police union is blasting the city's plans to award up to $15 million in incentives for Amazon's new facility, calling it "corporate welfare." A Nashville Fraternal Order of Police news release this week called for support of a resolution to block Amazon's incentives until city employees receive cost-of-living adjustments. Nashville has proposed up to a $15 million cash grant based on each job Amazon creates within the next seven years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Corpse smuggler' arrested with 50 human skeletons in luggage...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/indian-corpse-smuggler-arrested-50-human-skeletons-luggage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian police are investigating a skeleton smuggling gang after a man was caught with skulls and bones of 50 different people on a train.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.4-million-year-old tools could upend human origin story...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/24-million-year-old-tools-found-algeria-could-upend-human-origin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists in Algeria have discovered stone tools and cut animal bones that may be up to 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel stalks President abroad -- AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/30/trump-mueller-g20-argentina-1034614</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s anger over the probe threatens to overshadow his G-20 trip, which will feature several important policy-related events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beat Down in WAWA: Older Woman Viciously Attacked, Spit On...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/11/28/caught-on-camera-2-young-women-accused-of-beating-up-another-woman-at-cherry-hill-wawa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two young women are accused of beating up another woman and knocking her to the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cure for HIV in sight...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/30/cure-for-hiv-world-aids-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medical research enters a new era to find ways to eradicate HIV from infected populations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oz denies Proud Boys founder visa for 'bad character'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/419054-proud-boys-founder-denied-visa-to-australia-for-bad-character</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The founder of the far-right “Proud Boys” group was denied a visa to tour Australia after failing the character test,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Substitute Teacher Tapes Student To Chair...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/29/aaco-substitute-teacher-tapes-student-to-a-chair-when-he-wouldnt-return-to-his-seat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long-term substitute teacher at an Anne Arundel County Public School is no longer at the school after she was reported by a parent for taping a student to a chair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 SECRET GOOGLE Maps locations you're not allowed to see...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/7865105/google-maps-secret-locations/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOGLE Maps has a bold mission to document every corner of Earth – but some places are so secret they’re not allowed to be snapped. From military bases, mysterious islands and even a random h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington's new power standoff - Trump, Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ba955302de0d437d8be9f26637447d37</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — They haven't spoken in days, not since President Donald Trump called to congratulate Nancy Pelosi on Democrats' election night win. But they don't really need to. Trump and Pelosi go way back, from the time she first showed up at Trump Tower fundraising for the Democrats long before he would become president or she the House speaker. Two big-name heirs to big-city honchos — Trump and Pelosi each had fathers who were political power players in their home towns — they've rubbed elbows on the Manhattan social scene for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High tension G20 opens, dominated by Trump quarrels...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/high-tension-g20-opens-dominated-trump-quarrels-doc-1b80h13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jay-Z Goes After Kanye for Trump Support on New Track...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jay-z-goes-after-kanye-west-for-trump-support-on-meek-mill-album-champions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hov has spoken. And he didn’t hold back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White SAfricans lose legal fight against plans to seize their land...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6446421/White-farmers-legal-fight-stop-land-given-black-South-Africans-without-compensation-thrown-out.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa's High Court rejected a legal challenge on Friday brought by a group representing white farmers against President Cyril Ramaphosa's plans for land expropriation without compensation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moved island!?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/745482/seismic-event-the-hum-earthquake-unsolved-mystery-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARRIOTT database breached on 500 million guests...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/30/marriott-says-its-starwood-database-was-breached-onapproximately-500-million-guests-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marriott said the Starwood guest reservation database was breached, potentially exposing information on about 500 million guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian city to fine LGBT for being 'public nuisance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181130-indonesian-city-fine-lgbt-being-public-nuisance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary does little to dampen speculation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/418991-clinton-does-little-to-dampen-2020-speculation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton is increasingly weighing in on critical political events, keeping her name in the news and doing little to dampen speculation that she might once again run for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRINDR president says marriage 'between man and woman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/29/grindr-apps-president-calls-marriage-holy-matrimony-between-man-and-woman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After backlash within gay dating company, Scott Chen says he ‘supports gay marriage’ and was voicing his personal feelings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump denies working on real estate project during campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cohen-says-trump-stayed-involved-in-moscow-tower-project-during-campaign-1543539269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen told special counsel Robert Mueller he lied to Congress to play down President Trump’s involvement during the 2016 campaign in efforts to build a Trump Tower in Moscow, raising the pressure on his former boss as investigators probe his business relationship with Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Ex-Lawyer Admits Lies... </title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/eb753c198a8f43c9adad6a9f3bdcc285/michael-cohen-pleads-guilty-lying-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's former lawyer, Michael Cohen, confessed in a surprise guilty plea Thursday that he lied to Congress about a Moscow real estate deal he pursued on Trump's behalf during the heat of the 2016 Republican campaign. He said he lied to be consistent with Trump's "political messaging."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Moscow is going to be huge'...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/d80b3f2ba0c546ef9abb0e5c81277f89/behind-cohen-plea-trumps-longtime-dream-moscow-tower</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump for decades dreamed of building a Trump Tower in the heart of Moscow, a plan that flared and fizzled several times over the years, most recently when his presidential campaign was gaining momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warnings grow over unsanitary conditions in Tijuana shelter...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/warnings-grow-over-unsanitary-conditions-210321336.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico (AP) — Aid workers and humanitarian organizations expressed concerns Thursday about unsanitary conditions at the sports complex in Tijuana where more than 6,000 Central American migrants are packed into a space adequate for half that many people and where lice infestations and respiratory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New warning to federal employees: No talk of 'Resistance' or opinions about impeachment at work...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/federal-employees-are-warned-not-to-discuss-trump-%E2%80%98resistance%E2%80%99-at-work/ar-BBQh3QR?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will stock market end 2018 in red?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/29/its-now-up-to-president-trump-to-rescue-the-stock-market-from-ending-2018-in-the-red.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump meets his counterpart Chinese President Xi Jinping in Agentina this weekend, and a lot is riding on whether he can turn down the temperature on trade wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Found Dead on TX Ranches This Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/11/29/217-migrants-found-dead-on-texas-border-area-ranches-in-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents received information from a rancher about the remains of a deceased person found 50 miles from the Texas-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Communist China Home to So Many Billionaires...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2018/11/29/communist-china-billionaires-jack-ma/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s official now that Jack Ma, chairman of the Chinese e-commerce giant Alibaba Group Holdings Ltd., is a member of the Communist Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES PAGE ONE FRIDAY:  USA has little to show for stalled nuker talks with NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-pol-us-norkor-nuclear-20181122-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly six months after President Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un embraced at a historic Singapore summit and made vague promises of peace and prosperity, talks have flatlined and Pyongyang has taken no significant steps to reduce its nuclear arsenal or capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INDIVIDUAL 1'</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Trump-Individual-1-is-newly-cast-as-center-of-13432906.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In two major developments this week, President Donald Trump has been labeled in the parlance of criminal investigations as a major subject of interest, complete with an opaque legal code name: "Individual 1." New evidence from two separate fronts of special counsel Robert Mueller III's investigation casts fresh doubts on Trump's version of key events involving Russia, signaling potential political and legal peril for the president. Investigators have now publicly cast Trump as a central figure of their probe into whether Trump's campaign conspired with the Russian government during the 2016 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOONAN: Reflections on Impeachment, 20 Years Later...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/reflections-on-impeachment-20-years-later-1543535342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a tragedy for Bill Clinton, Monica Lewinsky and America. He could have averted it by apologizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside futuristic restaurant, where robot has replaced bartender...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Inside-a-futuristic-restaurant-where-a-robot-has-13432560.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With architecture dating back to the Middle Ages, Prague is a city whose modern identity is still defined by its many layers of ancient history, much of which remains gloriously intact. And yet, it is here - among a city of Baroque palaces, ornate, Renaissance-era chapels and cobblestone streets - that one of the first flashes of the future has suddenly, randomly emerged. It has been dubbed "Cyberdog." Though the name conjures images of an Eastern European Internet Cafe frequented by backpackers, it actually belongs to a newly opened wine bar. Unlike other wine bars in the Czech capital, however, this one has a new twist: It is staffed by a robotic bartender who serves drinks ordered via a smartphone app, according to Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants stage hunger strike at Mexican border...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-caravan/handful-of-caravan-migrants-launch-hunger-strike-at-u-s-border-idUSKCN1NZ074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A handful of the thousands of Central American migrants camped out at the U.S.-M...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO sighting in Texas? Mysterious 'cigar-shaped' object in sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/UFO-sighting-in-Texas-Keller-resident-mysterious-13432076.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was the oddest thing I've ever seen," said the person who recorded the sighting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-third in caravan being treated for health issues...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/caravan-migrants-suffer-from-respiratory-infections-tuberculosis-chickenpox-other-health-issues-tijuana-government-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tijuana’s Health Department is warning that migrants who came with the caravan are suffering from respiratory infections, tuberculosis, chickenpox, and other health issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian tanks just 11 MILES from Ukraine border amid fears of imminent invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/745416/russia-ukraine-war-vladimir-putin-petro-poroshenko-tanks-invasion-black-sea-kerch-strait</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bombshell email dossier that could save Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6444461/Rape-sex-assault-case-against-Harvey-Weinstein-thrown-accusers-lied.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein had been ‘vilified’ by a ‘vicious media assault’, his team said, and evidence ‘never critically examined or investigated’ because of the public pressure to prosecute him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire Dems invite Beto...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/29/beto-orourke-invited-to-new-hampshire-as-2020-speculation-heats-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Beto O'Rourke's team is heeding requests from top Democratic Party organizations to visit the key primary state of New Hampshire as the former Texas Senate nominee consider a run for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Sheryl Sandberg requested research on Soros...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/emails-show-sheryl-sandberg-aware-facebooks-definers-george</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Facebook maintains that Sandberg was not directly involved in a public relations firm's opposition research on Soros, it now acknowledges that she did in fact request research on the billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Republican Plan Drafted to Counter Trump Probes in House...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/secret-gop-plan-drafted-to-counter-trump-probes-in-u-s-house#gs.w3Cdwkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€˜Investigations â€“ My Plan to Counterâ€™: A Trump Ally's Secret Plan to Fight House Democrats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Employees Debated Burying Conservative Media In Search Results...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/29/google-censorship-conservative-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Let's make sure that we reverse things in four years'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel stalks President abroad -- AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/29/trump-mueller-russia-probe-g20-summit-michael-cohen-1034193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House aides hope the G-20 summit will showcase the president's deal-making skills. But Mueller's latest move threatens to overshadow any achievements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops indicted for beating undercover colleague during protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/st-louis-police-officers-indicted-accused-of-beating-an-undercover/article_4a82d209-b3cd-565e-9a97-309cf1c2a5af.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three officers accused of kicking and beating an undercover officer during a night of police protests, and another officer lied to a grand jury to cover it up, prosecutors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB to design and build homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90271599/exclusive-airbnb-will-start-designing-houses-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airbnb wants to get into the housing business in a big way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army to increase lethality by wearing AR combat goggles...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/microsoft-hololens-us-military-contract/#FrKpIftCrgqm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will there be employee blowback?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T 3-Tiered Streaming Service to Battle NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-t-will-spend-2019-whittling-down-debt-1543528870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T, trying to reassure investors it can capitalize on its big acquisition of Time Warner, plans to offer three versions of a new streaming video service next year that will feature original movies and television series from Warner Bros., Turner and HBO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spider milk -- more nutritious than from cow?</title>
      <link>https://www.popsci.com/jumping-spider-milk-protein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popsci.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spider milk may sound like a fictional substance, but scientists in China have found at least one species of creepy crawlers that produces a milk-like fluid to nourish its young.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US University Insuring Against Drop in Chinese Students...</title>
      <link>https://www.insidehighered.com/news/2018/11/29/university-illinois-insures-itself-against-possible-drop-chinese-enrollments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insidehighered.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign is paying $424,000 to protect itself in case of a falloff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted ads from internet coming to TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90273586/targeted-ads-are-coming-to-cable-via-your-smart-tv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nielsen is testing a way to replace cable TV ads with targeted ads from the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB TROUBLES: MIC Shuts Down, Reliant On Socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/the_new_gatekeepers/mic-layoffs.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,000-year-old ring may have belonged to Pontius Pilate...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/2000-year-old-ring-engraved-with-pilate-may-have-belonged-to-notorious-ruler/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uncovered 50 years ago at the Herodian palace near Bethlehem, a simple copper-alloy ring is now given a good cleaning -- and a second look by skeptical scholars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floyd Mayweather, DJ Khaled Charged By SEC In Crypto Probe...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/29/floyd-mayweather-dj-khaled-sec-crypto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former boxing champ Floyd Mayweather Jr. and music producer DJ Khaled have settled with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for failing to disclose payments they received for promoting investments in cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: Inmates say porn ban violates constitutional rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/politics/2018/11/28/iowa-department-corrections-prison-porn-ban-federal-lawsuit-inmates-sex-pornography-reading-rooms/2135895002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During legislative debate on the issue, Sen. Rich Taylor opposed the ban, saying it ignores male inmates' sex drive. "This is a bad idea," he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans artist sues over Chicago's definition of female breast...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-transgender-woman-bea-sullivan-knoff-20181129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The performance begins with Bea Sullivan-Knoff emerging on stage with a brown paper bag over her head. It says, on all four sides, "Touch Me."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani would 'love' court battle over info sharing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-pol-manafort-confidential-mueller-trump-giuliani-20181129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort’s lawyers shared confidential information about Robert Mueller’s investigation with President Trump’s legal team, Rudy Giuliani said Thursday — an extremely unusual move that legal experts argued could be criminal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan stealth jets on carrier could upend Asia power balance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/asia/japan-f-35-fighter-aircraft-carrier-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan is preparing an order for roughly 100 US-designed F-35 stealth fighter jets in a deal that could potentially upend the balance of power in Asia, according to sources familiar with the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery ballot could sway control of Alaska state govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/politics/alaska-legislature/2018/11/27/alaska-division-of-elections-certifies-tie-in-critical-fairbanks-house-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One “unusual” ballot cast for Democratic candidate Kathryn Dodge remains uncounted, pending a Friday recount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colonel wings clipped after flying F-16 for romantic rendezvous...</title>
      <link>https://vtdigger.org/2018/11/26/flying-fraternity-guard-commanders-wings-clipped-secret-rendezvous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;vtdigger.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST gate agent mocks 5-year-old's name, posts boarding pass on social...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/travel/oc-southwest-gate-agent-mocks-5-year-old-girls-name/4784236/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest Airlines gate agent in Orange County posted a 5-year-old girl's boarding pass on social media to mock her unique name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie 'Reaganesque' Reshaping of Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/the-run/articles/2018-11-29/bernie-sanders-20-the-hurdles-to-recapturing-the-magic-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak in Congo now world's second biggest...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/ebola-outbreak-in-east-congo-now-worlds-second-biggest-idUSKCN1NY2LY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ebola outbreak in eastern Congo is now the second biggest in history, with 4...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Plane Makes Emergency Landing in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/angela-merkels-plane-experiences-technical-defect-en-route-to-g20-summit/a-46514663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel's plane had to turn around and land in Cologne after only an hour in the air due to a defect. The plane has experienced several issues in the past few months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Fires Commentator Who Called For Elimination Of Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/exclusive-cnn-fires-marc-lamont-hill-following-israel-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising Rates Killing Housing Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-29/rising-rates-are-killing-housing-market</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
