<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Robot tail to balance human body, stop from falling over...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/robot-tail-developed-balance-out-18838128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The robotic tail is designed to help the wearer to stay balanced when moving quickly or carrying heavy objects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS SWARM MCCONNELL HOME; THREATEN TO 'STAB MOTHERF*CKER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/far-left-protesters-descend-on-mitch-mcconnells-home-threaten-to-stab-the-motherfker-in-the-heart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgusting harassment caught on camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Cold, Hard Math Tells NETFLIX Could Crash 70%...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenmcbride1/2019/08/06/the-cold-hard-math-tells-netflix-could-crash-70/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s official... it’s the beginning of the end for Netflix (NFLX). As you may have heard, the online video company made a troubling announcement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug lord who tried to escape prison disguised as daughter found 'HANGED' in cell...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7327323/Brazilian-inmate-nearly-escaped-jail-dressed-woman-hanged.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian drug dealer Clauvino da Silva, 42, who tried to escape from a decade-long drugs sentence by disguising himself as his own daughter, has been found dead in his cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINK crew in miracle escape after private jet crash-lands, bursts into flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7326301/Private-jet-carrying-Pinks-manager-crew-crash-lands-bursts-flames-Denmark.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The manager and other staff of the US artist Pink, who had given a concert in Oslo the night before, were among the 10 passengers and crew who all escaped without injuries at Aarhus airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside documentary that's inspiring militant vegan movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7325015/Vegan-documentary-Dominion-horrific-viewers-sit-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominion, a documentary released in 2018, uses drone footage and hidden cameras to film farms in Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT SELL-OFF 'LEHMAN-LIKE'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/06/nomura-a-second-market-sell-off-could-be-lehman-like.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buckle up because the next sell-off could be even more violent, according to Nomura.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel laureate Toni Morrison dead at 88...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/11910324b8c848af823a4b19a3e1bc7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS TIPPING POINT?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/456277-texas-faces-turbulent-political-moment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a quarter century, Texas Republicans have run a ruby-red state, building a conservative bastion where government is limited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro says criminals will 'die like cockroaches' under new laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/06/jair-bolosonaro-says-criminals-will-die-like-cockroaches-under-proposed-new-laws </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil’s president calls for security forces and citizens who shoot alleged offenders to be shielded from prosecution</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-stakes dispute turns nasty, pits 5G technology against weather forecasting...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/will-5g-satellite-deployment-undermine-noaa-weather-forecasting/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dispute within the federal government has FCC officials saying 5G technology can be safely developed, while NASA and National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration officials contend that could threaten the work of polar-orbiting satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH SEA: US carrier sails into disputed waters amid new flare-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2019/08/06/us-carrier-sails-into-disputed-waters-amid-new-flare-ups/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy flew a small group of Philippine generals, officials and journalists Tuesday to the USS Ronald Reagan, where fighter jets landed and took off by catapult with thunderous blasts. The nuclear-powered carrier, which was brimming with about 70 supersonic F18 jets, spy planes and helicopters, was en route to Manila.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At time of transformation and tumult, film academy prepares to elect new president...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/movies/story/2019-08-05/motion-picture-academy-president-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscars: On Tuesday, the academy's board of governors will elect a new president to replace John Bailey. Who might they choose?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLD SOARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.kitco.com/news/2019-08-06/Gold-Prices-Pause-Bulls-Remain-Strong.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kitco.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Technical Analyst Jim Wyckoff prepares investors with an overview of how the markets opened and closed. What moved metal prices? How do the technicals look? By looking at important developments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed thugs return to streets to attack demonstrators...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1681557/armed-thugs-in-white-attack-protesters-in-hong-kong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incidents are eerily similar to the violent gang attack against anti-government protesters last month in the suburb of Yuen Long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strip club empire pledges to send erotic dancers to Area 51...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/06/strip-club-empire-pledges-to-send-erotic-dancers-to-area-51/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top adult entertainment company in Nevada is reportedly set to storm Area 51 next month — with strippers. “Come September 20, we’ll be there,” Ryan Carlson, director of operations at Déjà…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez rips McConnell over pic of men in 'Team Mitch' shirts 'groping &amp; choking' her cutout...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/05/aoc-rips-mcconnell-over-pic-of-young-men-in-team-mitch-shirts-groping-choking-cutout-of-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez called out Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell on Monday night after a photo surfaced on social media, showing a group of young men “groping and choking&amp;#8221…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog Falls From 6-Story Building, Crashes Through Car Sunroof -- Survives!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/05/dog-jumps-off-building-crashes-through-sunroof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dog's owner says they were returning from a walk when the dog ran up a flight of stairs and got onto the roof through a door that had been left open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Tut 'cursed' golden sarcophagus pictured outside tomb first time ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9662770/tutankhamuns-sarcophagus-curse-coffin-restoration-egypt/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KING Tutankhamun’s sarcophagus has been pictured outside his tomb for the first time since its discovery 100 years ago. The Egyptian boy king’s gold-plated coffin – believed by some to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing warns of financial chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china/china-says-u-s-currency-manipulator-labeling-could-cause-chaos-in-financial-markets-idUSKCN1UW04S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's central bank said on Tuesday that Washington's decision to lab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA LABELS CHINA 'CURRENCY MANIPULATOR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/05/trump-blasts-china-yuan-drop-as-currency-manipulation-1634502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time Treasury designated any country as a currency manipulator was in the early 1990s, when China was named.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 89% young feel lives meaningless...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/poll-89-per-cent-of-uk-gen-zers-say-their-lives-are-meaningless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Societal malaise of nihilism evident in survey results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Bites Back at Anti-Graft Leader Who Taunted Putin Allies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kremlin-bites-back-anti-graft-104224967.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For years, opposition leader Alexey Navalny embarrassed Russia‘s leadership with YouTube videos exposing their lavish lifestyles and dubious wealth, and the Kremlin put up with it. Now President Vladimir Putin’s patience appears to have run out.With Navalny in prison and riot police brutally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECESSION WARNING</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yield-curve-blares-loudest-u-153828113.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The latest eruption in the U.S.-China trade dispute pushed a widely watched Treasury-market recession indicator to the highest alert since 2007.Rates on 10-year notes sank to 1.714% on Monday, completely erasing the surge that followed President Donald Trump’s 2016 election. At one point</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey Responds to Mass Shootings in 'Looking for America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/lana-del-rey-looking-for-america-867851/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer previews a brand new song she wrote with Jack Antonoff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most would rather lose job to robot than human...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2212417-most-people-would-rather-lose-their-job-to-a-robot-than-another-human/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people would prefer a robot to take their job if they had to lose it, but they would prefer to see another human step in if a co-worker was going to lose theirs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cord-Cutting Speeds Up As TV Providers Scramble to Boost Profits...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/tv-cord-cutters-us-accelerating-study-emarketer-1229346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of households without a traditional pay-television subscription could soon equal those that have one, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran unveils new missiles; Warns of 'mother of all wars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7325835/Iran-warns-mother-wars-Britain-joins-task-force-Strait-Hormuz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's defence ministry unveiled what it described as three precision guided air-to-air missiles on Tuesday, after President Hassan Rouhani warned of the 'mother of all wars' if the country is attacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Fear 'Extinction in Suburbs' Over Gun Control...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/republicans-fear-extinction-in-the-suburbs-over-gun-control-1.1297594</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder, 'gay-hunters' strike terror in Russia's LGBT community...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/murder-gay-hunters-strike-terror-russias-lgbt-community-023743858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When LGBT activist Yelena Grigoryeva found her name on a hit list of a "gay-hunting" group, she did not appear to take the threat seriously. The group called itself "Pila", meaning "saw", after the series of Hollywood horror films of the same name, in which a serial killer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galveston officers on horseback seen leading handcuffed man with rope...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/5445603/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the officers led him around the corner to 21st and Market, where the mounted patrol unit was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge study explores genetics of PTSD in more than 165,000 veterans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/huge-study-explores-genetics-of-ptsd-in-more-than-165000-us-veterans/ar-AAFnOZY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged for midair meltdown challenges law, saying it was just rudeness...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/08/05/texas-man-charged-mid-air-meltdown-challenges-law-saying-just-rudeness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When does being a jerk rise to the level of becoming a felony when you're 30,000 feet in the air? A federal judge intends to decide the matter....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dayton killer drove to slaughter with best friend...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7324839/Connor-Betts-shot-best-friend-mass-shooting-driving-Dayton.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chance Betts, 24, was the man in the car with Betts and his sister Megan before the gunman killed nine outside Ned Peppers Bar, DailyMail.com can reveal. He is critically ill but is cops' key witness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUTURES DOWN MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/dow-futures-fall-implying-a-200-point-drop-on-tuesday-as-trade-war-fears-batter-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stock futures fell on Monday night, adding to Wall Street's losses from its worst day of 2019 amid intensifying trade-war fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godson of 'El Chapo' testifies about 'hit' put on him in Chicago jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/criminal-justice/ct-sinaloa-cartel-lieutenent-sentencing-chicago-20190805-m4viapclzjauxoodzm7weklcge-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesus Beltran Leon, who prosecutors say worked directly with the sons of Sinaloa boss Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman, is scheduled to be sentenced Monday in federal court in Chicago to importing thousands of pounds of narcotics into the U.S. on behalf of the cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech vows to fight white nationalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tech-companies-say-theyre-ready-to-fight-white-nationalist-terror-2d221935-3d78-4091-bece-cb216294a874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The companies believe concerted action could work, but doubt the White House is serious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio lawmaker blames 'drag queen advocates' in rant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/05/ohio-lawmaker-candice-keller-blames-gay-marriage-drag-queen-advocates-for-dayton-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawmaker in Ohio blamed the breakdown of the “traditional American family,” gay marriage and “drag queen advocates” for the Dayton massacre in a since-deleted Facebook rant. Sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS IN 'PORNOGRIND' BAND THAT RELEASED SONGS ABOUT RAPING AND KILLING WOMEN...</title>
      <link>https://news.vice.com/en_us/article/j5yekp/exclusive-dayton-shooter-was-in-a-pornogrind-band-that-released-songs-about-raping-and-killing-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Menstrual Munchies released albums like "6 Ways of Female Butchery" with cover art showing the rape and mutilation of female bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake ride-share driver cleans out bank accounts of victims...</title>
      <link>https://herald-review.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/fake-ride-share-driver-cleans-out-bank-accounts-of-victims/article_983d4539-0ba2-5b7f-9f4f-dd997ac8356f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;herald-review.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Authorities said a parolee with a long history of identity theft and credit card scams masqueraded as a ride-share driver downtown and cleaned out the bank accounts of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retaliation '11' on Scale of 1 to 10...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-retaliation-11-scale-1-123135905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. Analysts continued to warn about the dangers of an escalating trade war on Monday, as China moved to strike back at the U.S., hitting U.S. stocks and boosting Treasuries. Semiconductors,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurls devaluation back in Trump's face...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-hits-back-trump-weaker-041855645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. China responded to President Donald Trump’s tariff threat with another escalation of the trade war on Monday, letting the yuan tumble to the weakest level in more than a decade and asking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -767</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ba7d32105b6c4b0a932f6e44f3c54e48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA:  Must not let racist views become normalized...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/873dcdec893c43d2b22f6aaa0e574dca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Republican retirement highlights party's growing peril in TX...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7def26496545425a9bc83453f9147b00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds face challenges in stopping domestic terror attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/05a358527d994a47b40950dacb37cba9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TO VISIT EL PASO...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190805223505-y7gd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEXAS-SHOOTING/ (UPDATE 7, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 7-Two more Texas shooting victims die in attack, Trump to visit El Paso</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil deforestation climbs 67% through July as gov't attacks data...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190805200950-3ic5u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-ENVIRONMENT/ (PIX, GRAPHICS):Brazil deforestation climbs 67% through July as gov't attacks data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halts new agricultural purchases......</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190805172900-mc8jo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA-AGRICULTURE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China halts purchase of U.S. farm products</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN COMPARES TRUMP TO THE KKK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7324427/Biden-compares-Trump-Ku-Klux-Klan-claims-president-abandoned-national-unity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden claimed Monday that Donald Trump's use of a 'dog whistle' to subtly support racists makes him an heir to the Ku Klux Klan, the infamous white supremacist hate group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Anxious, Fearful Of Violence In Public Places 'The New Normal'...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/08/05/feeling-anxious-nervous-in-public-places-following-mass-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you find yourself looking for the nearest exits, or scouting out hiding places in public, you're not alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market's 'everything bubble' finally popping?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/is-the-stock-markets-everything-bubble-finally-popping-this-chart-might-have-the-answer-2019-08-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stock market is in shambles to start the week, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average dropping more than 700 points after China retaliated against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH LOSES $162B IN VALUE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/big-tech-plunges-in-market-rout-led-by-slump-in-apple-microsoft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the stock market's worst day of 2019, the biggest tech companies got hammered, losing more than $160 billion in combined market cap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MAGA bomber' sentenced to 20 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/05/maga-bomber-cesar-sayoc-sentenced-to-20-years-in-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Manhattan federal judge has sentenced “MAGA bomber” Cesar Sayoc to 20 years in prison, with five years’ supervised release. Judge Jed Rakoff said Monday the sentence was “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US prosecutors accuse Honduran president of drug conspiracy...</title>
      <link>https://cbs2iowa.com/news/nation-world/us-prosecutors-accuse-honduran-president-of-drug-conspiracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbs2iowa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) &amp;mdash; U. S. federal prosecutors have accused the Honduran government of essentially functioning as a narco-state, with the current and former presidents having received campaign contributions from cocaine traffickers in exchange for protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama attacks Trump's rhetoric in wake of El Paso, Dayton...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7324085/Obama-slaps-Trump-rhetoric-normalizes-racist-anti-immigration-sentiments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama forcefully denounced the rhetoric that Donald Trump has employed while in office to describe immigrants and minorities on Monday in a rare public rebuke of his successor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE sheds $45.7 BILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7321465/Asian-stock-tumble-3rd-day-China-lets-yuan-sink.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global shares fell sharply Monday after China let its currency to sink to an 11-year low against the dollar, fueling concern that Beijing is using the yuan as a weapon in an escalating tariff war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Deep Space Signals Can Now Be Picked Up In Real Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/mysterious-deep-space-signals-can-now-be-picked-up-in-real-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence has been able to tune in to the odd energy known as Fast Radio Bursts and observe them as they reach Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague-Infested Fleas Spark Warnings In CO...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/08/02/plague-fireworks-dicks-sporting-goods-park-commerce-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tri-County Health Department confirms plague-infected fleas have been infecting and killing prairie dogs at numerous areas in Commerce City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult Film Use of Copyright Suits Has Judges Seeing Red...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/porn-purveyors-use-of-copyright-lawsuits-has-judges-seeing-red</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porn producers, sellers account for lionâ€™s share of copyright-infringement lawsuits in U.S. -- and judges may have seen enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER PAN bus driver locked passenger in luggage compartment...</title>
      <link>https://wxow.com/news/national-news-from-the-associated-press/2019/08/05/bus-driver-arrested-for-locking-woman-in-luggage-compartment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wxow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — A bus driver has been charged with locking a passenger in the vehicle's luggage compartment. Connecticut State Police got a 911 call at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6-year-old thrown from 10th floor of London's Tate Modern gallery...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190805-boy-thrown-londons-tate-modern-french-tourist-visiting-uk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boy thrown from London's Tate Modern is French tourist visiting UK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline monitoring passengers via onboard cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/cathay-pacific-onboard-camera/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong airline Cathay Pacific has revealed it is monitoring passengers via cameras on its aircraft, re-opening an uncomfortable debate over surveillance aboard airplanes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compostable bowls contain cancer-linked 'forever chemicals'...</title>
      <link>https://newfoodeconomy.org/pfas-forever-chemicals-sweetgreen-chipotle-compostable-biodegradable-bowls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newfoodeconomy.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Smartphone Games Better For Stress Relief Than Mindfulness Apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/digital-relaxation-smartphone-games-better-for-stress-relief-than-mindfulness-apps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Besides the obvious irony associated with using a smartphone to quell anxiety, a surprising study out of the United Kingdom has found that playing smartphone video games may be better for mental health than mindfulness apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Latinos, devastating new low in era marked by hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/for-latinos-el-paso-is-a-devastating-new-low-in/article_638123c8-374c-5350-858c-2912e655926f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working with immigrants for 30 years, Pablo Alvarado has lived through decades of antagonism toward Latinos. It came in political waves that washed over California, Arizona and other states. There</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAYS 'FAKE NEWS' LEADS TO RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/456142-trump-says-fake-news-has-contributed-greatly-to-the-anger-and-rage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday said "fake news" has contributed to growing "anger and rage" in the country in the wake of two mass shootings over the weekend, marking the second time he has criticized media coverage in the aftermath of a trag</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART Evacuated After Man Calls Store, Threatens To Shoot It Up... </title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/08/05/florida-man-accused-threatening-massacre-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida man is accused of threatening to shoot up a Walmart store, one day after 20 people were killed at a Walmart in El Paso, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both pilots on UNITED flight arrested for intoxication...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/2-united-pilots-held-for-alleged-intoxication-before-flight-to-newark</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Scotland say two pilots have been arrested on suspicion of being under the influence of alcohol or drugs before a scheduled flight to New Jersey.  The flight, United Airlines 162 to Newark, New Jersey, was due to leave Glasgow Airport at 9 a.m. on Sunday. It was canceled after the arrests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Latinos, devastating new low in era marked by hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-05/mood-in-latino-community-in-wake-of-shootings-in-el-paso-and-gilroy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massacre of 20 people by a man who reportedly wanted to shoot "as many Mexicans as possible" marks what appears to be one of the deadliest hate crimes ever against Latinos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malibu wanted to crack down on huge mansions. But fire losses could bring even bigger homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-04/malibu-scraps-anti-mansionization-plan-woolsey-fire-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the estimated 650 homes that burned inside Malibu city limits, just 113 replacement plans have been approved, and only 12 have received permits to start construction, records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BLAMES INTERNET, VIDEO GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/trump-video-games-toledo-shooting-8chan-el-paso-press-conference-today-a9040066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BATWOMAN' Star Hopes Groundbreaking Lesbian Superhero Appeals to Everyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ruby-rose-batwoman-1229120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CW drama features the first out lesbian superhero to have her own show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does Brady do it? Starts with science, ends with something less precise...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/How-does-Tom-Brady-do-it-It-starts-with-science-14280905.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At this point it's fair to say that Tom Brady's personal science project is going well. He just celebrated his 42nd birthday with a new two-year contract extension, and he apparently runs faster than he did at 22, his legs limber and alive, which is to say nothing of that ring-heavy throwing arm. In his 20thNFL training camp, he's so radiant with health that he looks like he's got spring water for blood and years left.  Clearly, scoffers who called Brady quackish owe him an apology. He was right, and they were wrong. He was way ahead of his time in perceiving the evils of an NFL culture based on heavy weightlifting and painkillers and ditching them for a range of unconventional training methods. His elastic, tenacious body is the empirical proof, more convincing than any lab result. Of all of Brady's time-defiant feats, maybe the most impressive one is his physical resilience over the past decade from the age of 32 onward: In nine of his past 10 seasons he has started all 16 games. The only thing that could keep him off a field was NFL Commissioner Roger Goodell's tyrannical suspension in 2016. So laugh at Brady's avocado-chia smoothies if you want, but his habits line up with everything scientists know about anti-aging and avoiding illnesses such as arthritis.  None of it, however, explains how Brady keeps his mind right. How does he fight mental burnout and keep summoning the readiness to go through another August training camp? Years of success do not breed freshness in a quarterback. They breed expertise, regulation, know how. The wild raw physical music of a Patrick Mahomes is gone and so is the humbleness that begs to learn. What's left is pure tedious process. Mental exhaustion is what really gets most veteran quarterbacks, not the physical inability to perform. They get sick of it and choose liberation. What...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet people working to kick Chicago out of Illinois...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/lifestyles/ct-life-illinois-state-secession-movement-0801-20190801-iesnu74ogvfjxfk35sn72lq7ya-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at the movement to split Chicago from the rest of the state — why it's not as crazy as you think it is, and how the secession plan reflects Illinois' rural-urban divide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services sector slips to worst growth in 3 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bb56f8243df34f79898512711edbc8a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After El Paso, why Trump could lose Texas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/456173-texas-dem-leader-after-el-paso-why-trump-could-lose-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Director of the Texas Democrats Manny Garcia discusses the weekend's violence in El Paso and Democrats Push to turn Texas Blue in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's going on between Lindsay Lohan and crown prince of Saudi Arabia?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/05/whats-going-on-between-lindsay-lohan-and-the-crown-prince-of-saudi-arabia/?_ga=2.25761149.1513688566.1565009911-1964899810.1565009911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wild rumor hit town that Lohan and Mohammed bin Salman have gotten close, and that he’s been flying her around in his jets and showering her with presents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Patron Urinates Into Nightclub Ice Maker...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/ice-cold-relief-018452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 5--A nightclub patron relieved himself into a commercial ice maker early Saturday, according to Florida police who arrested the intoxicated urinator for disorderly conduct. Investigators say t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Californians forced to live in cars, RVs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/aug/05/california-housing-homeless-rv-cars-bay-area</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the state grapples with a housing crisis, thousands of people around the San Francisco Bay Area are sleeping in their vehicles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing number of people stop bathing; Trust bacteria to do job...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/aug/05/i-dont-smell-meet-the-people-who-have-stopped-washing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of people are eschewing soap and trusting bacteria to do the job instead – and an entire industry has sprung up to accommodate them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect storm brewing for market correction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/02/perfect-storm-building-for-market-correction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With new risks from trade wars, stocks head into the final weeks of summer vulnerable to a pull back or even a correction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns of copycat attacks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/456168-fbi-warns-of-copycat-attacks-in-wake-of-mass-shootings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is warning of the potential for copycat attacks by domestic extremists after two mass shootings rocked the country over the weekend, including one that appeared to be motivated by animus toward Hispanics and immigrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying car gets off ground -- for minute...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/tech/japan's-nec-shows-'flying-car'-hovering-steadily-for-minute</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese electronics maker NEC Corp on Monday showed a &amp;quot;flying car,&amp;quot; a large drone-like machine with four propellers that hovered steadily for about a minute. The test flight reaching 3 meters high was held in a gigantic cage, as a safety precaution, at an NEC facility in Abiko, Chiba Prefecture.…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
