<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FEINSTEIN BACKS BIDEN, SNUBS 'BRAND NEW' KAMALA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-congress-feinstein-20190103-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Dianne Feinstein said she supports former Vice President Joe Biden in the 2020 presidential field, which could make things awkward with fellow Californian and possible 2020 contender Sen. Kamala Harris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Hunting Foreign Buyers for Sovereign Debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/china-is-hunting-for-foreign-buyers-for-its-sovereign-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Is Hunting for Foreign Buyers for Its Sovereign Debt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany entices illegal migrants to leave with bribes... </title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/germany-entices-illegal-migrants-to-leave-with-bribes-free-rent-for-a-year-at-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 20,000 airport repatriations were scrubbed this year as rejected asylum-seekers vanished before departure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends conservatives for tweets about brussel sprouts, 'drunk' Don Lemon...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/03/newsbusters-daily-wire-conservative-suspended-twitter-brussels-sprouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Come on, Jack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers leap from UBER as driver has heart attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Passengers-leap-from-car-as-Uber-driver-has-heart-13505898.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Uber driver had a heart attack while driving, forcing two passengers to jump out of the car on a Northern California highway. The Press Democrat reports the 50-year-old male driver was stricken ill Wednesday while driving on the middle lane of Highway 101 in Petaluma. California Highway Patrol Officer Matt Pinheiro says the car drifted off the road onto the shoulder, slowing to about 5 mph when the passengers "ended up exiting the vehicle at a slow roll." Rancho Adobe Fire Protection District battalion chief Mike Weihman says the passengers apparently leapt from the moving vehicle to avoid a potential crash into nearby trees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Mulls Jim Webb as Next Defense Secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/03/us/politics/jim-webb-defense-secretary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Webb’s views align closely with President Trump’s drive to pull American troops from the Middle East and confront China more aggressively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confused Speaker botches speech...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/confused-pelosi-botches-speaker-speech-i-think-i-skipped-a-couple-of-pages-im-not-sure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the conclusion of her first speech to Congress after becoming House Speaker again, Nancy Pelosi realized she “skipped a couple pages” of her remarks. “As we take the oath of office today,” Pelosi said, “we accept responsibility as daunting and demanding as any previous generations of leadership have faced. “Guided by the vision and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man trapped in BURGER KING bathroom sues to regain free meals for life...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article223872735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Portland, Oregon, Burger King offered Curtis Brooner, 50, free burgers for life after he spent an hour trapped in a dirty restroom, but a corporate manager canceled the deal, a lawsuit says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>51-year-old mom accused of abusing her infant triplets...</title>
      <link>https://www.lehighvalleylive.com/bethlehem/2019/01/bethlehem-mom-accused-of-abusing-her-infant-triplets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lehighvalleylive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say the triplets, who were eight weeks old at the time, had broken bones and signs of head trauma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Bibi Must Quit If Indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Netanyahu-must-quit-if-indicted-majority-of-Israelis-say-in-Post-poll-576278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Likudniks don't want Benjamin Netanyahu to go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women navigate toxicity, other barriers in esports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6762c27de8f1434fb5a8e14649d2a50b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Susie Kim thinks the women gamers are out there. As general manager for a championship esports team, she would know. She's not surprised none of them are on her roster. The Entertainment Software Association reported this year that 45 percent of U.S. gamers are female, yet women make up a scant portion of the professional esports player pool. Executives for games like "League of Legends" and "Overwatch" say they are eager to add women to pro rosters, where players can make hundreds of thousands of dollars. Yet LoL's Championship Series hasn't had a female gamer since 2016, and the Overwatch League's inaugural season featured just one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skier saw 'afterlife' after dying for 20 MINUTES in avalanche before coming back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8034586/near-death-experience-ski-accident-austria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRITISH skier who ‘died’ for 20 MINUTES after being trapped in an avalanche revealed today how she “saw a peaceful forest” while experiencing the “afterlife”. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London airports order military-grade anti-drone equipment...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-drones-gatwick/gatwick-and-heathrow-airports-order-military-grade-anti-drone-equipment-the-times-idUSKCN1OX1KX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London's Gatwick and Heathrow airports have ordered military-grade anti-dro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to indict model Bar Refaeli for tax evasion, perjury, money laundering... </title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Police-to-indict-Bar-Refaeli-parents-for-tax-evasion-576237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supermodel and her parents expected to face charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian 'BATWOMAN' Series Moving Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ruby-rose-led-batwoman-pilot-a-go-at-cw-1172794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Nutter, who helmed 'Game of Thrones, 'Arrow' and 'The Flash,' is on board to direct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI IN CONTROL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6554789/Back-Pelosi-poised-reclaim-Speaker-gavel-8-years-minority.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi, grinning broadly and standing out on the House floor in hot pink, was elected Speaker of the House on Thursday. as Democrats returned to power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: EAGLES Fans Ready For Another Magical Run By Backup QB...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/01/02/eagles-may-be-underdogs-again-but-nick-foles-has-fans-feeling-confident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Optimism is high among Eagles fans and with Nick Foles at the helm, it's easy to see why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE BLAMES CHINA</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/apple-entering-dark-chapter-iphone-sales-are-slowing-n954221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is definitely the most defining period for Tim Cook in his career as CEO,” said one analyst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF man arrested in New Year's Eve sex assault of 99-year-old woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/crime/article/Man-charged-with-sexually-assaulting-99-year-old-13504453.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man captured after a New Year's Eve sex assault in San Francisco's Chinatown had attacked a 99-year-old woman in her apartment at the Ping Yuen housing project, officials said Wednesday. The suspect, identified by police as 26-year-old Teandre Howard-Kidd, was charged on Wednesday with sexual assault, residential burglary and elder abuse. He is scheduled for arraignment in San Francisco Superior Court on Thursday. The attack happened around 12:35 p.m. at the storied public housing development on the 800 block of Pacific Avenue known to locals as the Pings, police said. Staff members quickly provided police with surveillance footage of the suspect from one of the many security cameras in the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Vending Machines: PEPSI Testing Delivery Bots...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/food-drink/article223863645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PepsiCo is testing a way to bring snacks directly to college students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feinstein signals support for Biden over Kamala...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/feinstein-signals-2020-support-for-biden-over-harris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Dianne Feinstein said Thursday that it would be difficult not to support former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. if he runs for president in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE shifting billion$ to tax haven Bermuda...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-taxes-netherlands/google-shifted-23-billion-to-tax-haven-bermuda-in-2017-filing-idUSKCN1OX1G9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google moved 19.9 billion euros ($22.7 billion) through a Dutch shell company to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional ghost hunters investigate haunting of US battleship...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article223864065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of nationally known professional ghost hunters intends to spend part of Saturday night aboard the USS North Carolina, to find proof of ghosts that haunt the decommissioned battleship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting depression: Phone apps to monitor teen angst...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/21d8615133864b43bfe071ddfaf55a53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising suicide rates and depression in U.S. teens and young adults have prompted researchers to ask a provocative question: Could the same devices that some people blame for contributing to tech-age angst also be used to detect it? The idea has sparked a race to develop apps that warn of impending mental health crises. Call it smartphone psychiatry or child psychology 2.0. Studies have linked heavy smartphone use with worsening teen mental health. But as teens scroll through Instagram and Snapchat, tap out texts or watch YouTube videos, they also leave digital footprints that might offer clues to their psychological well-being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI IN CONTROL...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pelosi-poised-become-house-speaker-making-history-again-053957706--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi knew this moment would come, even if others had their doubts — or worked to stop her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Bar Refaeli suspected of tax evasion in Israel... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/model-bar-refaeli-suspected-tax-evasion-israel-142109842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's most famous model Bar Refaeli is suspected of tax evasion and will be called into a hearing ahead of her possible indictment, authorities said Thursday. The 33-year-old could be charged pending the hearing, while her parents are also suspected of money laundering, a justice ministry statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX 'MASKED SINGER' STARTS STRONG...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/masked-singer-reveals-huge-premiere-ratings-antonio-brown-fox/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox's new quirky competition "The Masked Singer" revealed itself to 9.2 million viewers on Wednesday night. That is a huge number for Fox</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Army targets millennials in new recruitment drive...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/03/army-targets-snowflakes-binge-gamers-millennials-new-recruitment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Army recruitment campaign seeks to target gamers and millennials stuck in 'boring jobs'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Malley Endorses Beto...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/03/omalley-2020-endorses-orourke-1078587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He promoted O’Rourke as part of a “new generation” of leaders that can unify and heal the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim congresswoman to be sworn in on Thomas Jefferson's Quran...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article223866655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Muslim Congresswoman elect Rashida Tlaib from Detroit Michigan will be sworn in with Thomas Jefferson’s Koran. The Palestinian-American joins Minnesota’s Ilhan Omar as the first female Muslims in the US House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake pastor smuggled drugs into jails using bibles...</title>
      <link>https://www.kwtx.com/cw12tv/content/news/Sheriff-Fake-pastor-carrying-drug-filled-Bible-visited-jail-503847341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kwtx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A search of the Bible he toted revealed Suboxone strips inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC News Veteran Leaves Network, Says Media Have Become 'Prisoners'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/nbc-news-veteran-leaves-network-says-media-have-become-prisoners-of-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"NBC (like the rest of the news media) could no longer keep up with the world," Bill Arkin, a 30 years veteran of NBC says in a memo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg halts FACEBOOK stock sale as value plummets over privacy gaffes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8112733/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-stock-selloff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILLIONAIRE Mark Zuckerberg has halted the sale of his Facebook stock after the company’s value collapsed last year. The controversial 34-year-old has seen his company fall from grace, and fa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American detained in Moscow 'charged with espionage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/03/moscow-spy-charges-ex-marine-arrested-after-usb-drive-pickup-paul-whelan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Whelan had drive with classified list of names when detained, claims news agency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Using AMAZON's Facial Recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/01/fbi-trying-amazons-facial-recognition-software/153888/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The software allows the FBI to go through video surveillance footage much faster than agents can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK PLUNGES 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/03/apple-stock-falls-after-cutting-q1-guidance-on-weak-iphone-sales.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has lost about $450 billion in market value since its peak of about $1.1 trillion last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Took Credit for Stock Records. Deserve Blame for Plunge?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-03/the-president-owned-the-trump-bump-are-we-in-the-trump-slump?srnd=businessweek-v2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pack of teens beats NYC man to steal iPhone...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-assaulted-in-iphone-robbery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four men are wanted by the NYPD for assaulting a man in order to steal his iPhone in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listen Up, This Podcast Will Just Take a Minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/listen-up-this-podcast-will-just-take-a-minute-11546264801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overwhelmed by the choices, some listeners are loading up podcasts that don’t last much longer than a commercial break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two more Puget Sound orcas predicted to die in critically endangered population...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environment/i-am-worried-and-i-am-afraid-two-more-puget-sound-orcas-predicted-to-die-in-critically-endangered-population/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two southern resident killer whales are ailing and are not expected to live, according to the lead demographer of the orca population that frequents Puget Sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy SEAL to Face Court-Martial Over Murder of Young ISIS Fighter...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/Decorated-US-Navy-SEAL--to-Face-Court-Martial-for-Charges-Including-Premeditated-Murder-in-Death-of-Young-ISIS-Fighter-503810871.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decorated Navy SEAL will face Court-martial for charges, including premeditated murder in the death of a young ISIS fighter in Iraq, NBC 7 has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunar base?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-china-moonlanding-20190102-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Chang'e-4 lunar lander is just part of an ambitious long-term space exploration plan that includes colonizing and commercially exploiting the solar system and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent unrest sweeps India as first women to enter temple forced into hiding...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/kerala-protests-sabarimala-temple-bjp-communist-violence-women-ban-supreme-court-a8709476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp, Amber Heard Legal Documents Shed New Light on Abuse Accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/johnny-depp-amber-heard-legal-documents-shed-new-light-dual-abuse-accounts-1171081 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stars' volatile relationship, and previously unreleased testimony from their 2016 divorce, is expected to be central to Depp's defamation lawsuit against U.K. tabloid The Sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW DIVES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/03/tech-shares-dive-after-hours-after-apple-warning-nasdaq-etf-loses-nearly-2-percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks fell sharply on Thursday after Apple warned first-quarter sales would be less than it previously expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S Clerk Brawls With Man In Spat Over Straw...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/01/02/brawl-mcdonalds-tampa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is under arrest after authorities say he grabbed the shirt of a Florida McDonald's employee and tried to pull her over a counter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns Iran against space launches, ballistic missiles...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190103133455-hiyb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/ (URGENT):U.S. warns Iran against space launches, ballistic missiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National housing crisis brewing?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-national-housing-crisis-is-brewing-What-13505365.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Housing is sputtering. Home sales, home-building and homeownership have gone flat, and the rise in home prices threatens to stall out. Things aren't likely to get better soon, particularly for lower- and middle-income households struggling to make the rent and become homeowners. That is, unless policymakers act. Housing statistics are clear. Sales of new and existing homes have gone sideways over the past year, as has new single- and multifamily home-building. Housing prices are still rising in much of the country, but the pace of growth is throttling back, and some builders are cutting prices to move houses. Homeownership, which collapsed during the housing crash a decade ago, is just off bottom, and foundering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary opposition vows 'year of resistance' to Orban...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190103-hungary-opposition-vows-year-resistance-orban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungary opposition vows 'year of resistance' to Orban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcism, Demonic Possession Now Tools in Culture Wars...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/01/pope-francis-exorcism-demonic-possession-culture-wars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a data-driven science, exorcism is the definition of bullshit, but as a social movement with people behind it, the devil and his works are very real and now apparently need to be confronted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can expect 'different world'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/03/nancy-pelosi-trump-can-expect-different-world-new-congress/2391622002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi plans to confront Donald Trump on manyÂ fronts, from investigating the deaths of child migrants to protecting Robert Muellerâ€™s probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won't rule out indictment, impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/news/nancy-pelosi-says-she-won-t-rule-out-indictment-impeachment-t146197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As she prepares to resume her role as House speaker, Nancy Pelosi told TODAY she isn't ruling out the idea that Trump could be indicted or impeached while in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Army puts out recruitment call to all snowflakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/calling-all-snowflakes-your-country-needs-you-7g3tv2gqm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The army has a new generation in its sights for its latest recruitment campaign. Instead of hardened gym goers it is targeting gaming addicts and “phone zombies” in the hopes of boosting the number...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal revolt on first day...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Liberal-revolt-threatens-to-derail-House-13503434.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democratic leaders are set to advance sweeping internal rules changes Thursday that would attempt to bring more sunshine to congressional governance and defuse a pair of political powder kegs that wreaked havoc on GOP leaders over the past eight years. But in their first day of power in the new Congress, Democrats must stave off a liberal rebellion after prominent Democrats said they would oppose the entire rules package that has been carefully assembled by Rep. Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., and a top lieutenant. Rep. Ro Khanna of California and Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Women Film Directors See Numbers Shrink...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/women-comprised-just-8-percent-directors-top-2018-films-1172727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new "Celluloid Ceiling" report from San Diego State University finds that while women made incremental gains in other behind-the-scenes roles in 2018, the percentage of directors who were women was down three percent from 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested at Mar-a-Lago; Was there to talk 'trillions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.floridatoday.com/story/news/2019/01/02/palm-beach-police-arrest-mar-lago-trespasser/2469856002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.floridatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man wanted to talk to Trump about his $6.3 trillion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Economic Collapse Has Lessons for America's Socialists...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/venezuela-economic-collapse-has-lessons-for-america-s-socialists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelaâ€™s Lessons forÂ American Socialists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roe v. Wade at stake as 116th Congress convenes?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/roe-wade-stake-116th-congress-convenes/story?id=60033788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress reconvenes for the 116th session Thursday in the wake of political shake-ups that could bring changes to abortion legislation and the look of Roe v. Wade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorean Diplomat in Rome Disappears...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/north-korean-diplomat-in-rome-disappears-11546515512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jo Song Gil, Pyongyang’s interim ambassador to Italy until late last year, has gone into hiding along with his wife, a development that presents embarrassment for Pyongyang as it negotiates nuclear disarmament with the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientology murder mystery as 'church employee' stabbed to death at complex...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8108737/scientology-sydney-church-stabbed-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SCIENTOLOGY employee has been stabbed to death today by a teenager outside the group’s mega church in Australia. A 16-year-old has been arrested after two men were allegedly stabbed in the drivew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Home Prices Fall Under $1 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/manhattan-home-prices-fall-under-1-million-as-sellers-cut-deals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buyers seeking bargains send median to three-year low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Took Credit for Stock Records. Deserve Blame for Plunge?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-president-owned-the-trump-bump-are-we-in-the-trump-slump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Took Credit for Stock Market Records. Does He Deserve Blame for the Plunge?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi breaks with Justice: Trump can be indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nancy-pelosi-speaker-of-the-house-speech-3fc7ccca-ff47-4fe9-bf2f-a3c4d05c30c2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As speaker, she plans to maintain the unyielding posture she's taken with the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI IN CONTROL...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/688ca14bb55642bc825a29bdc3ca1eda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi knew this moment would come, even if others had their doubts — or worked to stop her. Pelosi is poised to be elected Thursday as House speaker, the only woman who has held the office and now one of few elected officials who will be returning to it. The last time a speaker regained the gavel was more than a half-century ago. The California Democrat has spent her political career being underestimated, only to prove the naysayers wrong. In this case, it was by winning back the Democratic majority and amassing the votes for the speaker's job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A real roasting: Coffee startup set to overtake STARBUCKS in China...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/real-roasting-coffee-startup-luckin-set-overtake-starbucks-111401100.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After only a year in business, startup Luckin Coffee said Thursday it will open 2,500 stores this year to dislodge Starbucks and become China's largest coffee chain. The company said it plans to have more than 4,500 stores in China by the end of 2019, taking it past the US coffee giant, which has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naming names: Reckoning underway in Catholic Church...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/naming-names-reckoning-underway-us-catholic-church-104146078.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Over the past four months, Roman Catholic dioceses across the U.S. have released the names of more than 1,000 priests and others accused of sexually abusing children in an unprecedented public reckoning spurred at least in part by a shocking grand jury investigation in Pennsylvania</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'lifts mysterious veil' by landing probe on far side of moon...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190103095508-voxif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-MOON/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-China 'lifts mysterious veil' by landing probe on far side of the moon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's growing anger with Fed chief poses market risks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/423607-trumps-growing-anger-with-fed-chief-poses-market-risks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump would likely find himself in murky legal waters if he attempts to dismiss Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, but experts say the bigger concern is that any move on that front would ignite a chain of calamities that could derai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio host Michael Savage hit with death threats, heads to secret location...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/2/michael-savage-target-death-threats-i-own-3-guns-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City, state and federal agencies are taking a look at a vicious, hateful email sent a restaurant frequented by talk radio icon Michael Savage that threatens to shoot up the establishment if he’s not denied future service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CANCER BREATHALYZER...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/jan/03/uk-scientists-test-breathalyser-for-detecting-early-cancers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major study at Addenbrooke’s hospital could lead to cancer detectors in GPs’ surgeries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hackers Threaten To Reveal 'Secret' Data Linked To 9/11 Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/9-11-attacks-september-11-attack-hackers-threaten-to-reveal-secret-data-linked-to-9-11-attacks-1971754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hacker group has threatened to reveal "secret" data related to September 11 attacks in the US after claiming to have got access to a large cache of confidential files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Bernie Sanders, Claims of Sexism Hang Over 2020 Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-bernie-sanders-claims-of-sexism-in-2016-campaign-hang-over-2020-bid/ar-BBRIM7i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles unveils earthquake warning app...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6550265/Los-Angeles-unveils-earthquake-warning-app.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) - Los Angeles has released an earthquake warning app that could give LA County residents precious seconds to drop, cover and hold on in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Male model who is suing Bruce Weber for 'soliciting sex' sent the fashion photographer nude images...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6548467/Male-model-suing-Bruce-Weber-soliciting-sex-exchange-work-sent-photographer-nude-pics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In documents filed on Wednesday, Bruce Weber hits back at the allegations being made by Jason Boyce and dismisses the lawsuit as nothing more than a money grab by a failed model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22,000 Minors 'Illegally Crossed' Border in December......</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/01/02/22k-minors-illegally-crossed-border-in-december-says-dhs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOfficials with the Department of Homeland Security say that 22,000 minors "illegally crossed the border" in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APOLOGIZES, VOWS TO 'DO BETTER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/sanders-on-reports-of-harassment-in-2016-campaign-well-do-better-next-time-c6881299-e710-4b7e-80dd-7e6b840b8b89.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He said he wasn't aware of the allegations at the time: "I was a little bit busy running around the country..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren headed to Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/423578-warren-headed-to-iowa-after-announcing-white-house-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) will visit Iowa this weekend for a series of events, days after announcing she is forming an exploratory committee for a White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump invokes Vatican's 'biggest wall of all'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/423609-trump-suggests-vatican-proves-border-wall-is-moral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday suggested that a border wall can't be immoral because there are walls around the Vatican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Suicide Prevention Program Raises Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://smartinvestor.business-standard.com/market/Compnews-563632-Compnewsdet-Facebooks_new_role_as_global_arbiter_of_mental_distress_is_a_tricky_one.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;smartinvestor.business-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Market News from one of the most comprehensive financial news networks in India, it provides daily insight of the stock market, industry news, business news, economy news, loans &amp; credit card news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit Claims 'Southern Poverty Law Center' Abetted Theft, Spread Lies to Destroy Lawyer for Thought Crime...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/lawsuit-claims-splc-abetted-theft-spread-lies-to-destroy-lawyer-for-thought-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Says Left-wing smear group should lose non-profit status, face RICO prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone finds time for best-and worst-dressed list amid scandal...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/01/02/roger-stone-finds-time-for-best-and-worst-dressed-list-amid-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He expects to be indicted any minute by Robert Mueller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Ratings Rebound;  'SUNDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL Eyes No. 1 Finish...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/football-ratings-rebound-2018-snf-eyes-8th-no-1-finish-2018-19-season-1202528319/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the national anthem controversy took a toll on NFL ratings last fall, pushing down TV ratings, the games’ performance recovered in 2018, with the main football franchises posting year-t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freshman class not asking permission...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/politics/nation/democratic-congress-freshmen-tensions-nancy-pelosi-20190101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before the start of the new Congress, the Democratic freshman class is unified, but tensions have emerged that could test Nancy Pelosi's leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl 'cries blood' after contracting mystery illness on cruise...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8107438/jordyn-walker-girl-bleeding-eyes-mystery-illness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TEENAGE girl was left blind with blood pouring from her eyes after contracting a mystery illness on family cruise. Jordyn Walker’s face was left swollen – with medics having to remove…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: He 'Will Fold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/ann-coulter-trump-will-fold-on-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest orders purification ritual...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/india-kerala-hindu-temple-women-religion-11079646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women secretly entered one of Hinduism's holiest shrines on Wednesday, breaching a blockade around the Sabarimala temple where devotees have ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW PERMANENTLY BLIND, MEDICAL NIGHTMARE BAFFLES DOCTORS...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/state-and-regional/my-whole-face-just-turned-purple-missouri-teen-goes-blind/article_33b4107a-b8b0-5642-8fcc-ffc675d8a87b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twice in the past 18 months, Jordyn Walker has dealt with painful facial swelling and an illness that has taken away her senses and left doctors baffled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico finds Flayed god temple; Priests wore skins of dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e4e92bc35ead46309f632ec12df8ddf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican experts have found the first temple of the Flayed Lord, a pre-Hispanic fertility god depicted as a skinned human corpse, authorities said Wednesday. Mexico's National Institute of Anthropology and History said the find was made during recent excavations of Popoloca Indian ruins in the central state of Puebla. The institute said experts found two skull-like stone carvings and a stone trunk depicting the god, Xipe Totec. It had an extra hand dangling off one arm, suggesting the god was wearing the skin of a sacrificial victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: GIRL LOSES SENSES AFTER RETURNING FROM CRUISE...</title>
      <link>https://fox4kc.com/2018/12/31/smithville-15-year-old-faces-medical-mystery-with-positivity-and-determination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox4kc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SMITHVILLE, Mo. -- Imagine feeling perfectly healthy one day, then winding up in the hospital with crippling pain and swelling the next. It's the dilemma facing a Northland 15-year-old right now. And doctors are baffled as to why it's happening. Jordyn Walker enjoyed a family cruise last summer. But when she came back to the states, her medical nightmare began. It started with stomach pain and bloody stools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Pacific garbage patch device breaks, entire system towed back to port...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2019/01/02/ocean-cleanup-device-great-pacific-garbage-patch-breaks/2465082002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 60-foot chunk of the Ocean Cleanup device in the Great Pacific Garbage Patch has broken off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stoneman Douglas commission calls for arming teachers in tough final report...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/parkland/florida-school-shooting/fl-ne-stoneman-douglas-commission-report-20181231-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state commission investigating the shooting at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School unanimously approved its report Wednesday. Now the focus shifts to Gov.-elect Ron DeSantis and the state Legislature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road rage starts with teens egging cars -- ends with mom dead, 14-year-old facing murder charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article223816880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deputies in Harris County, outside of Houston, say three teen boys in an SUV were egging cars when a driver started chasing them, causing a wreck in Aldine that killed a mother on New Year’s Day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President invokes Vatican's 'biggest wall of all'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=12185091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump falsely claims Mexico is paying for wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS PANIC: STILL NO HOST!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/why-oscars-still-doesnt-have-a-host-1172331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hollywood Reporter's awards columnist breaks down the challenges — and possibilities — facing the Academy as it nears a record-late date for announcing a host or hosts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUCH!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6547487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a scathing op-ed Tuesday, Romney referred to President Donald Trump as 'the incumbent.' His niece, Ronna Romney McDaniel, is the Republican Party's chairwoman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drop costs Buffett big bucks, adding to struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/buffetts-berkshire-set-to-lose-about-2point8-billion-on-apples-after-market-drop-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Apple's more than 10 percent drop in share prices Wednesday, Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway could be down about $2.8 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daughter warns: She'll 'cut head off' and you won't even know you're bleeding...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/pelosis-daughter-warns-shell-cut-your-head-off-and-you-wont-even-know-youre-bleeding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presumptive incoming House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s daughter issued a warning to President Trump on Wednesday as her mother and other top Democrats met with president to discuss the government shutdown. “She’ll cut your head off and you won’t even know you’re bleeding,” Alexandria Pelosi, a documentary filmmaker, told CNN. ﻿ “That’s all you need to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Rare Cut to Sales Guidance, Blames Performance in China ...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-revises-guidance-sees-lower-revenue-in-fiscal-1st-quarter-11546465050</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple lowered its sales outlook for its fiscal first quarter, a rare revision to its guidance, blaming slowing sales of smartphones and other devices in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 18 month search for missing body, cops blame GOOGLE MAPS mistake...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/national/queensland/news/coroner-hits-out-at-police-use-of-google-maps-printouts-in-search-for-missing-man/news-story/0d005d8018e694433313ab2b941c7df4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Darrell Simon set off on his usual morning bike ride from his partner’s bushland home in November 2014, there was an excruciating wait for answers which lasted more than 18 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  STOCK MARKET 'GLITCH' IN DECEMBER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/trump-says-stocks-will-rise-once-trade-battle-settled-calls-last-months-market-decline-a-glitch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said there was a "glitch" in the stock market last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeks After 'Blockbuster' Assange-Manafort Scoop, No Evidence Emerges...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/02/five-weeks-after-the-guardians-viral-blockbuster-assangemanafort-scoop-no-evidence-has-emerged-just-stonewalling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. media is very adept at being outraged when they’re denounced as “fake news.” They should think more about why that attack resonates for so many.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Quizzes Brother On Detained American's 'Fake News' Social Post...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/02/cnn-grills-brother-of-detained-american/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whelan could face up to 20 years in prison in Russia if convicted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warship spotted carrying 'next gen' hypersonic superweapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8105762/china-warship-railgun-superweapon-picture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHINESE warship carrying a terrifying next generation hypersonic railgun suggests Beijing has beaten the world in developing the superweapon. Rumours first circulated last year when images shared…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez bashes 'bad economics' of Dem budget rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/budget-rules-sow-discord-among-democrats-as-new-congress-set-to-open-2019-01-02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are clashing over rules for the new Congress before it even opens, with three members slamming a budget provision they say will hamper their plans for health care and other priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious red sphere spotted flying off SC coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.greensboro.com/news/north_carolina/is-it-a-ufo-multiple-people-report-seeing-flying-red/article_9283f0dc-5c64-5e71-b4d7-e618776e0755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greensboro.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Carolina woman says she filmed a possible UFO off South Carolina’s Kiawah Island on Christmas Eve, and other witnesses are stepping forward on social media to report they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contentious meeting on border security in WH Situation Room...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-meets-with-congressional-leaders-in-situation-room-amid-partial-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has called for congressional leaders to return to the White House on Friday, top Republicans said shortly after a hotly anticipated, contentious closed-door meeting on border security in the Situation Room concluded Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300-foot tall dust wall devours rural town...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1066318/australia-news-latest-dust-storm-new-south-wales-dubbo-boona-mount-new-year-eve-nye-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPECTACULAR footage has been released of a red dust storm covering Dubbo in New South Wales, Australia, on New Year’s Eve, causing the cancellation of fireworks due to the poor weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK DROPS 7%... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/apple-warns-on-q1-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple lowered its guidance for its Q1 following disappointing iPhone sales and trade tensions between the U.S. and China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women describe alleged abuse by nuns: 'Secret not yet told'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/women-describe-alleged-abuse-by-nuns-the-secret-not-yet-told/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trish Cahill says a nun plied her with drugs and alcohol while teaching her how to have sex with a woman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE lowers revenue guidance citing weak iPhone sales in China...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2019/01/02/apple-revenue-iphone-tim-cook-letter-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Apple have been in a slump the past few months and a new letter from Tim Cook will likely make things worse. In a letter to investors released this afternoon, Cook relayed that Apple was …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
