<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>U.S. 5th Fleet seizes weapons shipment from stateless dhow in Arabian Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-5th-fleet-seizes-weapons-shipment-stateless-dhow-arabian-sea-2021-05-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy’s Fifth Fleet said on Saturday that the guided-missile cruiser USS Monterey (CG 61) seized an illicit shipment of weapons from a stateless dhow in international water of the North Arabian Sea on May 6-7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools Open, but Many Families Hesitant to Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/schools-are-open-but-many-families-remain-hesitant-to-return/ar-BB1gwVLI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pauline Rojas’s high school in San Antonio is open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80% Who Refuse Vaccine Say NOTHING Can Change Their Minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/whopping-80-percent-who-refuse-covid-vaccine-say-nothing-can-change-their-minds-but-theres-good-news-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A whopping 80 percent of people who say they won’t get vaccinated also say that there is nothing that can change their minds in a new poll — but there’s some potentially good news in the poll, as well. In a new The Economist/YouGov poll, respondents who said they don’t intend to get the Covid […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden faces struggle to hold Senate, Dem divisions resurface...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-biden-faces-a-struggle-to-hold-the-senate-democrats-e2-80-99-divisions-resurface/ar-BB1gvMd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In crucial Senate races in Pennsylvania, North Carolina and elsewhere, the Democratic coalition that came together to elect Biden is fracturing again — with big implications for his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abbas voices full support for rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.i24news.tv/en/news/israel/diplomacy-defense/1620420142-abbas-voices-full-support-for-palestinians-rioting-in-jerusalem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.i24news.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OF GAS PRICE SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9558509/Fears-gas-price-surge-ransomware-attack-shuts-Americas-key-fuel-pipeline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack on Colonial Pipeline took place Friday, and affected some of its information technology systems. Operations remain shutdown as of early Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Study Mysterious Behavior of Cats Sitting on Squares...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7eexj/scientists-have-studied-the-mysterious-behavior-of-cats-sitting-on-squares</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cats love sitting on any square object, as if drawn by some primordial instinct. A new study shows that the square can even be an optical illusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fire breaks out near Iran nuke power plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/massive-fire-breaks-out-near-irans-bushehr-nuclear-power-plant-report-667581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cause of the fire is still unknown, according to Iranian media reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British royal offers to sell access...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210509-british-royal-offers-to-sell-access-to-putin-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British royal offers to sell access to Putin: report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to 'firmly' defend Russian interests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210509-putin-on-wwii-victory-day-vows-to-firmly-defend-russian-interests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin on WWII Victory Day vows to 'firmly' defend Russian interests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC teacher caught sucking topless man's nipple during ZOOM class...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/08/nyc-teacher-caught-sucking-topless-mans-nipple-during-zoom-class/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teacher Amanda K. Fletcher allegedly performed an “inappropriate sexual act” on a Zoom class at Columbia Secondary School for Math, Science, and Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Mediocre...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/09/billionaire-elon-a-musk-see-on-mediocre-episode-of-snl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even if it was an average episode of “Saturday Night Live,” the host was a Musk see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Humility and hubris...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-elon-musk-business-technology-arts-and-entertainment-0563502b7b60d00bd65158031697444c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk showed a combination of humility and hubris as he opened his highly anticipated hosting gig on “Saturday Night Live.” The 49-year-old Tesla CEO, SpaceX founder and one of the world’s richest men opened his monologue by mocking his monotonal speaking style, saying no one can tell when he's joking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin tells Red Square parade that Nazi ideas persist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-government-and-politics-24387d1bd5aa5a7a90896529ef6a0cfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin marked the anniversary of the end of World War II in Europe with a speech warning that Nazi beliefs remain strong. Speaking to the annual military parade on Moscow's Red Square, Putin on Sunday decried “attempts to rewrite history, to justify traitors and criminals, on whose hands lies the blood of hundreds of thousands of peaceful people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson's phone number breach fails to prompt tighter security...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/boris-johnson-phone-number-breach-sparks-no-uk-rethink/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solutions are out there, but ministers have not been keen to embrace them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Age of Scandals Weakens American Christianity...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/how-american-christendom-weakens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An age of scandals reveals how institutions of the faith can fundamentally oppose the faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street parties celebrate end of Spain's state of emergency...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-spain-lifestyle-coronavirus-pandemic-health-e0ee913b5dd19d3dac5310eac1a512d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA, Spain (AP) — Impromptu street celebrations erupted across Spain as the clock struck midnight on Saturday, when a six-month-long national state of emergency to contain the spread of coronavirus ended and many nighttime curfews were lifted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Delivers Self-Deprecating 'SNL' Opening Monologue...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/ok-that-was-actually-funny-elon-musk-joined-by-his-mom-delivers-self-deprecating-snl-opening-monologue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk delivered a self-deprecating opening monologue on Saturday Night Live, making fun of many aspects of his persona and getting plenty of laughs from the audience. Musk’s selection as the night’s host was controversial, with even several SNL cast members publicly voicing their disapproval. Musk’s seeming attempt to crowdsource ideas […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogecoin plunges nearly 30% during appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/08/dogecoin-price-plummets-as-elon-musk-hosts-saturday-night-live-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Elon Musk hosted SNL, the price of dogecoin fell off a cliff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama dog Bo dies from cancer...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2021/05/obama-dog-bo-once-a-white-house-celebrity-dies-from-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama’s dog Bo died Saturday after a battle with cancer, the Obamas said on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-year-old, 2 women shot in Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/toddler-woman-shot-new-york-s-times-square-police-say-n1266765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The girl was toy shopping when she was struck, New York police Commissioner Dermot Shea said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists train bees to identify infection...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/552486-scientists-train-bees-to-identify-coronavirus-infection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Dutch scientists are enlisting the help of an unusual group of participants for a new kind of rapid COVID-19 test: bees that have been specially trained to detect the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBERATTACK SHUTS TOP U.S. PIPELINE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210508152642-o9z7n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PRODUCTS/COLONIAL PIPELINE (UPDATE 6, PIX):UPDATE 6-Cyber attack shuts down top U.S. fuel pipeline network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Neanderthals Weren't Cannibals, So Who Ate Them?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/these-neanderthals-werent-cannibals-so-who-ate-them-stone-age-hyenas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME — When a Neanderthal skull was discovered in a cave on the property of a beachfront hotel south of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Separate Worlds of Bill and Melinda Gates...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/the-separate-worlds-of-bill-and-melinda-gates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates and Melinda French Gates were stuck at home. When the pandemic hit last March, the couple retreated to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson Urges 'Step Back' From 'Sexist' HFPA...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/scarlett-johansson-hfpa-statement-criticism-diversity-inclusion-reform-1234752398/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scarlett Johansson has joined the outcry against the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, adding her voice to fellow Avenger Mark Ruffalo, who spoke out on Friday. They unite with numerous publicis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walls closing in on Gaetz?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/may/08/matt-gaetz-florida-sleazy-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigation into Florida congressman is reported to have grown beyond sex trafficking allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W Virginia factory center stage in supply chain crisis, showing economy's strains...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/west-virginia-factory-is-center-stage-in-supply-chain-crisis-as-u-s-economy-seeks-to-rebound-from-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scene inside one plant illustrates the deepening production challenges roiling American industry as it shakes off the pandemic. Parts shortages, price spikes, port delays, labor trouble - all are complicating the economy's rebound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In small NH town, 2020 election still rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-new-hampshire-campaign-2016-election-2020-house-elections-e50dfae66446197767bd255882d19439</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDHAM, N.H. (AP) — Meetings of the Windham Board of Selectmen are usually as sleepy as they sound — a handful of residents from the New Hampshire town, a discussion of ambulance fees, maybe a drainage study...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLDPLAY Chris Martin says lockdowns forced him to re-evaluate fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/may/07/coldplay-chris-martin-lockdowns-forced-re-evaluate-fame</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frontman says Covid pandemic means he has tried ‘to not attach too much to being a pop star’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Suspended Over Photos Showing Them Not Wearing Masks Off-Campus...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/07/umass-amherst-students-suspended-masks-outside-off-campus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three UMass Amherst students said they are not being treated fairly after they were suspended for not wearing masks at an off-campus outdoor event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild VIP Group-Sex Party About to Invade NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-wild-vip-group-sex-party-is-about-to-invade-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On May 15, SNCTM—an exclusive sex club—is set to host an 80-person bash in Downtown Manhattan. Masks are not optional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Internet Turned on Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/05/08/elon-musk-snl-saturday-night-live-host-internet-controversy-485781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unlikely, polarizing SNL hosting stint for the mogul reveals the boundaries and tensions of our ever-present culture wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did DeSantis violate First Amendment with FOXNEWS-only bill signing?</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/florida-politics/2021/05/07/did-desantis-violate-first-amendment-with-fox-news-only-bill-signing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts said the Florida governor likely ran afoul of the U.S. Constitution with his staged event in West Palm Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The origin story of Medina Spirit, Derby winner born on patch of Florida dirt and sold for $1,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/the-origin-story-of-medina-spirit-a-derby-winner-born-on-a-patch-of-florida-dirt-and-sold-for-241000/ar-BB1gvbQi </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In India's surge, religious gathering attended by millions helped spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/In-India-s-surge-a-religious-gathering-attended-16161841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI - As coronavirus cases in India shot upward last month, millions of people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney effort to turn Republicans from Trump threatens her ambitions. She says it's only beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Liz-Cheney-s-effort-to-turn-Republicans-from-16161868.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Liz Cheney had been arguing for months that Republicans had to face the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young causing Florida to have among highest hospital rates in country...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/younger-patients-causing-florida-to-have-among-the-highest-covid-hospital-rates-in-country/article_d0232b9b-f2ff-5a15-8236-702f84555174.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — As state and local officials drop mandates on COVID-19 restrictions, the virus continues to circulate throughout Florida, sending increasingly younger people to the hospital at rates that are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones? Lasers? New study suggests ways park service could clean Gateway Arch...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/drones-lasers-new-study-suggests-ways-park-service-could-clean-gateway-arch/article_349f30df-911e-5625-833d-d4f4301157f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS — The Gateway Arch gradually is losing some of its silver sheen, as a variety of forces — from salt to body oils to graffiti — take a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tried to track robbery victim by attaching iPhone to his car, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Florida-man-tried-to-track-his-robbery-victim-by-16161191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He'd been at the Millenia Mall in Orlando, Fla., for less than an hour when he allegedly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm as German anti-maskers co-opt Nazi resister Sophie Scholl...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210508-alarm-as-german-anti-maskers-co-opt-nazi-resister-sophie-scholl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alarm as German anti-maskers co-opt Nazi resister Sophie Scholl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese rocket debris set for uncontrolled plummet back to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210508-chinese-rocket-debris-set-for-uncontrolled-plummet-back-to-earth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Debris from parts of China’s Long March 5B rocket is set to crash down to Earth this weekend – but space agencies do not know when or where.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA and LaPierre's Fate Lies in Hands of TX Bankruptcy Judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-08/nra-and-lapierre-s-fate-lies-in-hands-of-texas-bankruptcy-judge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association, long a feared power broker, will learn its fate next week in a court ruling that could hobble the gun rights group and imperil the three-decade reign of its controversial boss, Wayne LaPierre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON warehouse employee dies at site of unionization drive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/07/amazon-employee-dies-at-bessemer-alabama-warehouse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon declined to share further details about the situation, noting that it was a personal medical incident.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
