<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>24 other businesses targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9564961/Hackers-launched-cyberattacks-24-companies-Colonial-Pipeline-shutdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two dozen other victims - who have not been named - were also affected by the ransomware attack, Bloomberg reported. The Colonial Pipeline was shut down on Friday,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF releases footage of retaliatory strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/idf-releases-footage-of-strike-on-hamas-members-launching-rockets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC limits reviews of vaccinated but infected, spurring concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/cdc-limits-review-of-vaccinated-but-infected-draws-concern/ar-BB1gx1au?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Federal health officials this month decided to limit how they monitor vaccinated people who have been infected with Covid-19, drawing concern from some scientists who say that may mean missing needed data showing why and how it happens. At the end of April, more than 9,000 Americans were reported to be infected after being vaccinated, according to the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. While that’s a tiny percentage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv opens up citywide bomb shelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/tel-aviv-opens-up-citywide-bomb-shelters-following-rockets-launched-667800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cities of Givatayim, Ramat Gan and Bnei Brak have made similar announcements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Hamas fires over 150 rockets into Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/cogat-announces-closure-of-gaza-border-crossing-over-rocket-fire-667730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of roads and train lines in southern Israel were closed due to security concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tinderbox burst into flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/dont-let-the-jerusalem-tinderbox-become-an-inferno-analysis-667763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rockets will pound Israel, and a Hamas or PIJ cell in the West Bank or from Gaza could attack the IDF or Israeli civilians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 other businesses targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9564219/Gas-stations-begin-run-fuel-cyberattack-Colonial-Pipeline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motorists in Atlanta on Monday night were complaining that gas stations were empty, as a consequence of the shutdown of the 5,500-mile Colonial Pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Resistance Is Ready'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/israel-jerusalem-violence-palestinians-wounded-2021-05-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's army said it launched airstrikes on Gaza, in response to rockets fired by Hamas militants after hundreds of Palestinians were hurt in clashes at a religious site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis to hold NEWSMAX town hall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/552717-desantis-to-hold-newsmax-town-hall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax announced Monday that Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) will hold a town hall on the channel later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly contagious variant emerges in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/10/highly-contagious-brazilian-covid-19-variant-emerges-in-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new mutation of the highly-contagious Brazilian COVID-19 variant, dubbed P2 or P.1.1, has emerged in Florida, health officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  NBC will not air GOLDEN GLOBES...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/golden-globes-canceled-nbc-2022-hfpa-1234753314/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There will be no Golden Globes on NBC in 2022, as the besieged Hollywood Foreign Press Association continues to falter in reforming itself to the satisfaction of Hollywood studios and stakeholders.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endangered wolves to be housed at Ted Turner ranch in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nm-state-wire-ted-turner-new-mexico-wolves-lifestyle-c0e4fd9d9ef2b74f5ad8eb78fecf1046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — One of Ted Turner’s ranches in southern New Mexico will be the new home for a pair of Mexican gray wolves and their pups as federal wildlife managers look at more options for boosting the genetic diversity of the endangered species...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy set to rout Cheney and move past 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/05/10/mccarthy-needs-to-rout-cheney-to-move-past-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANALYSIS — McCarthy hopes that ousting Cheney will satisfy pro-Trump GOP voters and allow him to move on to attacking Democrats’ failings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime becomes defining issue of NYC mayor race...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-crime-mayoral-race-defining-issue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some candidates for mayor of New York are making crime above and below ground in the city a campaign issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech's next move: Private cities without govt control...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/10/tech-bros-next-move-private-cities-without-government-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dominating Silicon Valley in the past two decades, hiking up rent prices in the area and filling the streets with flannel vests and wool sneakers, they’re now spreading into other regio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN: Hollywood just now realizes the awards are ridiculous?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/10/hollywoods-hypocritical-protest-of-the-golden-globes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such perfect timing, now that viewership has tanked and there is seemingly no awards show — not the Oscars or the Grammys or the CMAs or the SAGs or anything, really — that America wants to see.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN 63% APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-coronavirus-approval-rating-efcc859a21a0ab6c43dfb4157987bf80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is plunging into the next phase of his administration with the steady approval of a majority of Americans, according to a new poll from &lt;a href="https://apnorc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ground-breaking AI now predicting earthquakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/groundbreaking-ai-used-predict-earthquakes-24080538</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tool, called DeepShake, is being developed in the US to give several seconds of advance notice that earthquakes are on the way. It uses a deep neural network, a form of AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Man attacked mom with taser on Mother's Day...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/mothers-day-shocker-521903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 10--The most shocking Mother’s Day gift this year was the handiwork of a Wisconsin man, records show. During a disturbance yesterday afternoon, a 43-year-old woman was tased in the neck by her s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Spouse With Heart Disease Doubles One's Risk Of Developing Too...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/having-spouse-heart-disease-doubles-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men in particular, face a higher risk of developing heart disease if their wife smokes and has a history of strokes, the researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC attacker posing as cop, pepper spraying victims, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/dc-attacker-posing-as-cop-pepper-spraying-victims-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the past three years, a suspect has reportedly been dressing as a police officer and pepper spraying people in Meridian Hill Park in Northwest D.C., according to residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA OKs jab for 12-year-olds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/10/pfizer-covid-vaccine-fda-clears-use-in-kids-ages-12-to-15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA granting use of the shot in younger age groups will allow middle school-aged students to get vaccinated before school starts this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates known for 'womanizing,' naked pool parties, biographer says...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/10/bill-gates-womanizer-held-nude-pool-parties-biographer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates’ wild lifestyle was well known among his inner circle — but newspapers like the New York Times hid the unflattering reports, James Wallace wrote in the 1997 Gates biography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 APPLE suppliers in China have links to forced labor programs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/7-apple-suppliers-china-links-181145842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suppliers, which provide Apple with crucial parts like iPhone glass, have used thousands of forced laborers, The Information found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Restaurant Temporarily Closes for Cicada Invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2021/05/10/cicadas-close-michelin-starred-dc-restaurant-little-pearl-capitol-hill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little Pearl has gone dark for a month on Capitol Hill, citing (in part) the swarm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK GOVT GREEN LIGHTS CASUAL SEX...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9563525/Casual-sex-allowed-17-Government-gives-green-light-people-meet-inside.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Casual sex will be allowed again for the first time this year as part of the Government's latest lifting of lockdown measures, with people from different households allowed to meet inside from Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting erupts at immigration office in Florida, leaving 'one dead'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2860393/uscis-shooting-orlando-one-dead-immigration-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SHOOTING at the United States Citizenship and Immigration Services has allegedly left one dead. A photograph from the scene showed a barrier surrounding what is reportedly a body. Lieutenant Dieg…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian spy unit suspected of directed-energy attacks on American personnel...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/10/russia-gru-directed-energy-486640</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIA Director William Burns is now receiving daily briefings on the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US ship fires warning shots in encounter with Iranian boats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/persian-gulf-tensions-middle-east-iran-government-and-politics-e8c06d358419b7de6dbc3a72a1fa7cc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A U.S. Coast Guard cutter fired two volleys of warning shots Monday as a group of 13 Iranian fast boats sped toward U.S. Navy vessels in the Persian Gulf's Strait of Hormuz in what the Pentagon called “unsafe and unprofessional” maneuvers by the naval arm of the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates known for 'womanizing,' naked pool parties, biographer says...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-israel-jerusalem-076a9ec7e2bd9c065882c64a4ab820a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Hamas militants fired dozens of rockets into Israel on Monday, including a barrage that set off air raid sirens as far away as Jerusalem, after hundreds of Palestinians were hurt in clashes with Israeli police at a flashpoint religious site in the contested holy city...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distracted Nurse Gives Woman 6 Doses Of Vaccine In Single Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/italy-covid-vaccine-woman-six-doses-distracted-nurse-pfizer-shot-tuscany/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian hospital apologizes for lapse on a busy day, but says the young woman has shown no adverse reaction to the overdose of the Pfizer vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEBOW RETURNS TO NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/jaguars-expected-to-sign-former-qb-turned-te-tim-tebow-to-one-year-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;﻿Tim Tebow﻿ is on his way back to the NFL. The Jaguars are expected to sign the former QB to a one-year deal this week or next to play tight end, Ian Rapoport and Tom Pelissero report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Eminent Domain Is Used for Economic Assassination...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/05/10/when-eminent-domain-is-used-for-economic-assassination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government officials who wield land grabs to pick economic winners and losers now want to use them to kill disfavored businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lutherans elect first trans bishop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/il-state-wire-religion-6c7c25f40661a617d69063d4358dacd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — The Rev. Megan Rohrer was elected bishop of the Evangelical Lutheran Church in America’s Sierra Pacific synod on Saturday (May 8), becoming the first transgender person to serve as bishop in the denomination or in any of the U...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hug with 'care and common sense,' UK PM says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/10/coronavirus-hug-with-care-and-common-sense-boris-johnson-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson confirmed Monday that England will be moving to the next stage of its coronavirus lockdown easing program on May 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Writing Justice Breyer's Obituary...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/volokh/2021/05/10/pre-writing-justice-breyers-obituary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a surreal experience to talk to a reporter who is pre-writing a Supreme Court Justice's obituary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone now 'place where we live', anthropologists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/may/10/smartphone-is-now-the-place-where-we-live-anthropologists-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UCL study has found people around the world feel the same about their devices as they do about their homes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young propelled victory...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article251272304.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sharp increase in Millennial and Generation Z voters was a major factor in President Joe Biden’s 2020 election success, according to a new study from a Democratic analytics firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW 35,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-futures-struggle-for-direction-after-dow-s-p-500-set-records-11620645508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average hit the latest in a string of all-time highs Monday as the broader market saw a mixed performance. The blue-chip gauge was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORSE DOPED:  Medina Spirit tests positive for banned raceday substance...</title>
      <link>https://www.racingpost.com/news/international/kentucky-derby-winner-medina-spirit-tests-positive-for-banned-raceday-substance/488912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.racingpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Reveals Over 200,000 People Involved in Posting Fake Reviews on AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.pcmag.com/news/database-reveals-over-200k-people-involved-in-posting-fake-reviews-on-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pcmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data shows third-party Amazon vendors working with customers to reward fake, positive reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slowing population growth raises questions about USA as land with unlimited horizons...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/a-blinking-light-ahead-slowing-population-growth-raises-questions-about-america-as-a-land-with-unlimited-horizons/ar-BB1gxEif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New population and fertility figures spur debate about political, economic and social impacts — and what, if anything, can or should be done about them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baffert blames 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/bob-baffert-slams-pretty-harsh-response-after-his-kentucky-derby-winning-horse-fails-drug-test-blames-cancel-culture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary horse trainer Bob Baffert has repeatedly stumbled to answer for failed drug tests throughout his career. His latest excuse is "cancel culture."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>73,000 Pack Stadium For Boxing Event In TX...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/05/08/canelo-alvarez-billy-joe-saunders-att-stadium-us-boxing-record-largest-indoor-crowd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a record-breaking evening with 73,126 people in attendance for the boxing match between Mexico’s Canelo Alvarez and Billy Joe Saunders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combined Flu/COVID vax shows promise in animal study...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novavax-combined-influenzacovid-19-vaccine-shows-promise-preclinical-study-2021-05-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Novavax Inc (NVAX.O) said on Monday its combined flu and COVID-19 vaccine produced functional antibodies against influenza and the coronavirus in a preclinical study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA SPACECRAFT HEARS STRANGE 'HUM' OUTSIDE SOLAR SYSTEM...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/space/nasa-voyager-1-space-hum-b1845015.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nasa spacecraft is picking up a strange “hum” outside of our solar system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Civil war brewing': Serving French soldiers send Macron chilling warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9561561/Macron-sent-chilling-warning-soldiers-earlier-letter-calling-military-action.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of serving French soldiers have published a new open letter warning Emmanuel Macron that the 'survival' of France is at stake after the President made 'concessions' to Islamism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baffert blames cancel culture...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/AmericaNewsroom/status/1391765499281817602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Smell Training' Best Way To Recover Lost Sense...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smell-training-after-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOP Impeachment 10' try to navigate Cheney's demise and own futures...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-GOP-Impeachment-10-try-to-navigate-Cheney-s-16165092.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - When 10 Republicans voted to impeach President Donald Trump on Jan. 13, it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ZOOM era has ruined conversation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-the-zoom-era-has-ruined-conversation/ar-BB1gzhy4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interruptions in conversation used to be natural. Try it on a video call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could mean higher gas prices, but too soon to panic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/colonial-pipeline-shutdown-could-mean-higher-gas-prices-but-analysts-say-it-e2-80-99s-too-soon-to-panic/ar-BB1gzuaJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fallout from the massive cyberattack may have regional repercussions in the Southeast if repairs drag on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive turnout, voters of color -- new data fill in details on Biden election win...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/massive-turnout-voters-color-data-100040348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden benefited from high turnout among voters of color and support from college-educated white voters in his 2020 election win, study says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But won't change bets...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/10/a-derby-winners-drug-test-wont-change-the-bets-heres-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So now that the Kentucky Derby winner Medina Spirit has failed a drug test, I can cash my bet on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican villages arm children in desperate bid for attention...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-mexico-police-ddb119a12aaa41cfc4b455426edada7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AYAHUALTEMPA, Mexico (AP) — The children in this mountain village usually spend their days caring for goats or cows and playing with their dogs. But on the rare occasions that the press comes to Ayahualtempa, the kids are lined up and handed guns...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astonishing Collapse of James Franco Career Cemented by Former Pal Seth Rogen...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/05/09/the-astonishing-collapse-of-james-francos-career-cemented-now-by-former-pal-seth-rogen-in-uk-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seth Rogen is done with James Franco. This is BIG news. Franco, who was already on the outs with a lot of people when he made “The Disaster Artist,” still had Rogen in his corner. They&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson investigated over Caribbean vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2021/may/10/boris-johnson-under-investigation-caribbean-holiday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parliamentary standards watchdog says it is looking into a possible breach of MPs’ code of conduct</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration revives anti-bias protections in health care for trans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-care-transgender-sex-discrimination-77f297d88edb699322bf5de45a7ee4ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. will protect gay and transgender people against sex discrimination in health care, the Biden administration announced Monday, reversing a Trump-era policy that sought to narrow the scope of legal rights in sensitive situations involving medical care...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slab City offered quirky isolation, but there's no escaping pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/slab-city-offered-quirky-isolation-but-theres-no-escaping-a-pandemic/ar-BB1gzfaP </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot Users Splurge on $800 Bongs as Stigmas Fade...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/pot-users-splurge-on-800-bongs-as-stigmas-fade-cannabis-weekly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pot Users Splurge on $800 Bongs as Stigmas Fade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attempted lynching of driver in riots near Temple Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/palestinian-youth-injured-in-car-crash-in-old-city-riot-667743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lone police officer arrived at the scene moments after the car swerved off the road and fired warning shots into the air to disperse the mob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Fungus Infection Found in Patients in India...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ninashapiro/2021/05/09/covid-19-infections-complicated-by-deadly-fungus/?sh=3b439cbd62bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 infections can be complicated by a deadly fungus. This devastating disease is sharply on the rise in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency declaration issued in 17 states, DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fuel-pipeline-cyberattack-us-state-of-emergency-dda2e776-f0f0-45cc-ae38-4fea47e014ec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo told CBS there's an "all hands on deck" effort to resume operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake cheers, empty seats: Tokyo gives glimpse of Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fake-cheers-empty-seats-tokyo-084338335.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fake cheers, empty seats and the sound of pounding feet: welcome to the Covid-era Tokyo Olympics, which Japan seems determined to hold at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviews military might as tensions with West soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210509075935-b3h6p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WW2-ANNIVERSARY/RUSSIA-PARADE (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Putin reviews Russian military might as tensions with West soar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Targets Muslim Women in Push to Suppress Births in Xinjiang...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/10/china-targets-muslim-women-in-push-to-suppress-births-in-xinjiang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the government ordered women in her mostly Muslim community to be fitted with contraceptive devices, Qelbinur Sedik pleaded for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP braces for wild week with momentous vote...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/552445-gop-braces-for-wild-week-with-momentous-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republicans return to Washington this week embroiled in a bitter battle over the direction of the party, the face of its leadership and what role former President Trump should play heading into next year’s ele</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Worth More Than All US Currency in Circulation...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/cryptocurrency-worth-more-than-us-currency-circulation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrencies are now worth more than all of the US currency currently in circulation. This is a significant milestone — but could indicate a bubble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Fights for Survival...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/10/as-cuomo-fights-for-survival-he-revives-his-combative-image/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. — Over the past few weeks, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo has crisscrossed New York, promoting the state’s vaccine</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
