<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE: Our Socialist Ideas Are Winning...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-sanders-our-socialist-ideas-are-winning</link>
      <description>‘Our ideas on winning’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANDERS:   'There Will Be Pain'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-bernie-sanders-single-payer-health-care-there-will-be-pain</link>
      <description>‘You got to deal with that pain’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 10% Of People Admit To Checking Phone During Sex...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/06/07/study-10-percent-people-checking-phone-during-sex/</link>
      <description>SureCall's study finds that 10 percent of people check their phone during sexual intercourse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina Peso Plunges To New Record Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-06-08/argentina-peso-plunges-new-record-low</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University prohibits 'harsh text messages'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/post/45647/</link>
      <description>The school also forbids ‘rumors’ and ‘embarrassing pictures.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NANCY? PELOSI FREEZES DURING SIMPLE MATH PROBLEM...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-nancy-pelosi-freezes-during-math-problem-aide-helps-with-answer/</link>
      <description>Maybe now we know why politicians in Washington, D.C. can’t seem to get a handle on the national debt: They struggle with simple math. During her weekly press conference today, House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi froze as she attempted to do a simple math problem in her head. ﻿ Pelosi suffered her usual brain freezes …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump floats pardon for Muhammad Ali...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/08/politics/trump-muhammad-ali/index.html</link>
      <description>President Donald Trump said Friday he is considering posthumously pardoning boxer Muhammad Ali, who was convicted in 1967 after refusing military service in Vietnam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: NYT REPORTERS SAY 'F*CK THE MILITARY,' PROMOTE ANTI-SEMITIC CONSPIRACY THEORIES, TWEET N-WORD...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/07/nyt-reporters-f-the-military-anti-semitic/</link>
      <description>Read what they said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls for Russia to be included in meetings of powers like G-7...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/08/trump-calls-for-russia-to-be-included-in-meetings-of-powers-like-g-7.html</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,000 PALESTINIANS BURN TIRES IN FIERY GAZA BORDER PROTEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/4000-Palestinians-burn-tires-in-fiery-Gaza-border-protest-559498</link>
      <description>Earlier on Friday, Israeli forces along the border with Gaza began preparations for mass riots by tens of thousands of Palestinians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC apologizes for Hindu terror plot after backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/abc-apologises-hindu-terror-plot-quantico-online-backlash-120517319--finance.html</link>
      <description>U.S. television studio ABC has apologised to Indian fans of its crime drama "Quantico" after an episode featuring Indian nationalists trying to frame Pakistan in a terrorist plot sparked online outrage against Bollywood actor Priyanka Chopra, who plays a lead role in the show.  "The episode</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unruly passenger diverts flight after 'yelling death threats'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sbs.com.au/news/unruly-passenger-diverts-flight-after-yelling-death-threats</link>
      <description>A disruptive passenger has forced a flight from Melbourne to Perth to be diverted to Adelaide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney predicts re-election...</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/news/us_politics/2018/06/romney_predicts_trumps_re_election</link>
      <description>PARK CITY, Utah  — He once called Donald Trump "a con man," but Mitt Romney now predicts that Trump would "easily" win his party's presidential nomination in 2020 and "solidly" win a second term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just two months of stress can affect male sperm quality...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/just-two-months-stress-can-12665968</link>
      <description>Researchers from Ben-Gurion University have found that prolonged stress, such as that experienced during military conflict, can impact sperm quality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOURDAIN HANGS SELF IN HOTEL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/08/us/anthony-bourdain-obit/index.html</link>
      <description>Anthony Bourdain, a gifted storyteller and writer who took CNN viewers around the world, has died. He was 61.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi touts Putin ties as US tensions brings them closer...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/xi-touts-putin-ties-us-tensions-brings-them-095441603.html</link>
      <description>President Xi Jinping hailed China's ties with Russia as he treated Vladimir Putin to a state visit on Friday to bring the neighbouring giants closer in the face of US diplomatic and economic challenges.  "No matter what fluctuations there are in the international situation, China and Russia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French opposition, media cry foul over 'fake news' bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-opposition-media-cry-foul-over-fake-news-095043582.html</link>
      <description>French lawmakers accused the government of attempting to legalise censorship during a stormy debate Friday over a bill designed to fight so-called fake news during election campaigns.  President Emmanuel Macron launched a crusade against misinformation after being targeted during his 2017 campaign by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bollywood actress defiant over masturbation scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/bollywood-actress-defiant-over-masturbation-scene-104833420.html</link>
      <description>Bollywood actress Swara Bhasker has hit back at a torrent of online abuse over a masturbation scene in a film dubbed India's answer to "Sex and the City" that is proving a hit worldwide.  "Veere Di Wedding", meaning "Friend's Wedding" in English, has caused a stir</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemala warns of falling ash as volcanic activity picks up...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-guatemala-volcano/guatemala-warns-of-falling-ash-as-volcanic-activity-picks-up-idUSKCN1J322H</link>
      <description>Guatemalan officials warned of falling ash from the Fuego volcano late on Thursday and urged caution with flights as the Central American country recovers from devastating eruptions that have killed at least 109 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican document suggests role for married priests, women...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180608093858-ebieg</link>
      <description>POPE-AMAZON/PRIESTS:Vatican document suggests role for married priests, women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un Impersonator Detained at Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/06/08/kim-jong-un-impersonator-gets-snared-in-singapore-security-net</link>
      <description>Kim Jong Un Impersonator Gets Snared in Singapore Security Net</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby born to trans could become first person without legal mother...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/07/baby-born-transgender-man-could-become-first-person-without/</link>
      <description>A baby could become the first person without a legal mother if a transgender man wins a historic court battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Triple Crown hopeful Justify run at history...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/jun/08/justify-belmont-triple-crown-preview </link>
      <description>The chestnut colt is a heavy favorite to win Saturday’s Belmont Stakes and join the immortal group of horses to sweep America’s three most famous races</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 BATTLES 'AMERICA FIRST'</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5817911/Battered-Trump-G7-leaders-choose-polite-productive.html</link>
      <description>President Donald Trump fired a shot at U.S. allies France and Canada just before the G7 summit of allied industrial powers – blasting them for 'massive tariffs.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria to shut mosques, expel imams in crackdown against Islamist ideology...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5820445/Austrias-right-wing-government-plans-shut-mosques-expel-imams.html </link>
      <description>A hardline Turkish nationalist mosque in Vienna and a group called the Arab Religious Community will be dissolved in 'just the beginning' of a push against Islamist ideology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking satellite photos show entire towns obliterated after Guatemala volcano...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5816065/Shocking-satellite-photos-entire-towns-obliterated-Guatemala-volcano.html</link>
      <description>Shocking satellite photos of before and after the  eruption of Volcan de Fuego in Guatemala show whole towns wiped off the map as hundreds of houses collapsed when falling ash crushed them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE CAR FOR LIFT-OFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/flying-car-startup-backed-google-founder-offers-test-210639148.html</link>
      <description>A flying car project backed by Google co-founder Larry Page was closer to take-off on Wednesday, with a model for test flights by aspiring buyers.  The company was created last year in Google's home town of Mountain View, California, and has been testing a prototype in New Zealand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN WEALTH SURPASSES $100 TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-net-worth-surpasses-100-trillion-1528387386</link>
      <description>The total net worth of U.S. households rose to over $100 trillion for the first time during the first three months of 2018, as rising property prices boosted Americans’ wealth and offset declines in major stock indexes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column and contributes to the PostPartisan blog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA:  Building blocks for life discovered on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/06/07/life-mars-building-blocks-life-discovered-3-billion-year-old-organic-matter/681597002/</link>
      <description>Researchers cannot yet say whether their discovery stems from life or a more mundane geological process.  However, “we’re in a really good position to move forward looking for signs of life,"  said Jennifer Eigenbrode, a NASA biogeochemist and study lead author.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bagpiper cuffed by cops for playing TOO LOUDLY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/2747986/piper-arrested-edinburgh-royal-mile-loud/</link>
      <description>A PIPER was cuffed by cops in front of shocked tourists after playing too loudly. Busker John McDonald was arrested on the Royal Mile during a police crackdown on noisy street performers. Officers …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooters littering city streets shout at people: 'Unlock me or I'll call police!'</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/jun/07/scooters-littering-city-streets-shout-at-people-unlock-me-or-ill-call-the-police</link>
      <description>Built-in alarm sparks anger from US city officials amid concerns over racism and policing: ‘This is a threat to people’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEY-Z TAKE TO THE STAGE AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jun/07/beyonce-jay-z-otr-ii-tour-review-opening-night-cardiff</link>
      <description>On the opening night of their collaborative world tour, the biggest couple in pop are glorious and charismatic – even if the romantic story arc plays down their trauma</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,600 ICE detainees shipped to federal prisons...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-prisons-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-immigration-authorities-sending-1600-detainees-to-federal-prisons-idUSKCN1J32W1</link>
      <description>U.S. authorities are transferring into federal prisons about 1,600 Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) detainees, officials told Reuters on Thursday, in the first large-scale use of federal prisons to hold detainees amid a Trump administration crackdown on people entering the country illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. Seizes NYT Reporter's Email and Phone Records in Leak Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/07/us/politics/times-reporter-phone-records-seized.html</link>
      <description>Federal prosecutors seized the records as part of an investigation into leaks of classified information to the news media by a former Senate aide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Mueller Closing In, Manafort's Allies Abandon Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/07/us/politics/mueller-manafort-witnesses.html</link>
      <description>Allegations that Paul Manafort, President Trump’s former campaign chairman, tried to tamper with witnesses originated with two of his former business associates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive Owner of Triple-Crown Contender Justify:  Soros!</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/07/sports/justify-belmont-george-soros.html</link>
      <description>Mr. Soros’s connection to Justify, not previously reported, has garnered little notice in the sport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In shadow of UBER, taxi driver suicides leave cabbies shaken...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/shadow-uber-s-rise-taxi-driver-suicides-leave-cabbies-shaken-n879281</link>
      <description>"What Uber and Lyft have done is come into the industry and wreck it," a Chicago taxi driver said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paid 'pawternity' leave for new pet parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/06/07/pawternity-leave-for-new-pet-parents-nordic-company-says-yes/</link>
      <description>Pet supply company with 1,500 employees says it’s important that new parents have a chance to bond with their new pet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 BATTLES 'AMERICA FIRST'</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/g7-summit-trump-macron-latest-canada-trudeau-charlevoix-countries-a8388626.html</link>
      <description>World leaders will make clear their opposition to proposed tariffs from Mr Trump, while attempting to avoid a broader international trade war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea summit is signature moment for Trump and his challenge to foreign policy establishment...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/north-korea-summit-is-a-signature-moment-for-trump-and-his-challenge-to-the-foreign-policy-establishment/</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON — During his campaign, Donald Trump lashed U.S. presidents for cutting “stupid” foreign deals, alleging that they gave too much away to allies and adversaries alike, and insisted “the world is laughing at America’s politicians.”
National security and foreign policy experts called him naiv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACRON TURNS ON TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/07/politics/trump-g7-canada/index.html</link>
      <description>President Donald Trump plans to depart from this weekend's Group of 7 summit in Canada several hours early, the White House announced Thursday, punctuating an explosion of acrimony between Trump and his foreign counterparts on the eve of the talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUFFETT: ECONOMY FEELING STRONG...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/07/buffett-says-economy-is-feeling-strong.html</link>
      <description>Warren Buffett and Jamie Dimon say the U.S. economy is in rare form and could continue to prove strong for years to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Urges Europe to Unite in New World Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/06/07/merkel-says-europe-must-step-up-in-world-being-reorganized</link>
      <description>Merkel made a pitch for Europe to play a more assertive role in global affairs in  Trump’s new world order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billion-Dollar Cruise Ship Brings Go-Karts, Laser Tag to High Seas...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-07/go-karts-on-deck-19-laser-tag-coax-cruisers-to-open-wallets</link>
      <description>On the new Norwegian Bliss, cruise passengers can drive go-karts on a two-story racetrack, listen to a Beatles cover band inside a replica of Liverpool’s Cavern Club or play laser tag in a space-themed, outdoor arena.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ends Fleet Street era...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-44391449</link>
      <description>He will give up the editorship of the Daily Mail before turning 70 in November after 26 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>Mike Allen is your early-morning guide to the vital news in business, politics, tech and media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  Advertisers Shy Away From Samantha Bee, Despite Apology...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/samantha-bee-full-frontal-apology-advertising-1202835551/</link>
      <description>Samantha Bee served up plenty of jokes on Wednesday night. Many advertisers weren’t there to help her in her quest. The first broadcast of Bee’s TBS series “Full Frontal” af…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DYLAN BYERS</title>
      <link>https://us11.campaign-archive.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=505046f69e</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins 'hold hands' with friends, call by name...</title>
      <link>https://news.nationalgeographic.com/2018/06/dolphins-animals-courtship-friends/</link>
      <description>Bottlenose dolphins in Australia call each other by name and touch frequently to maintain alliances with other males, a new study says.   </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VATICAN AT BILDERBERG: Top cardinal to join elite meeting...</title>
      <link>https://cruxnow.com/vatican/2018/06/07/vatican-secretary-of-state-attending-elite-bilderberg-meeting/</link>
      <description>Cardinal Pietro Parolin, Vatican Secretary of State, will take part in the Bilderberg Conference, an annual private gathering of global political, business and media leaders, taking place this year in Turin, Italy, June 7–10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>Authentic. Unfiltered. Fearless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE BIG STINK:  Bubble pop? Brownie batter? Vapes' added flavors fuel e-cig debate...</title>
      <link>http://www.tbo.com/news/health/Should-the-government-regulate-vaping-flavors-The-answer-is-far-from-clear-_168858434</link>
      <description>
A heated debate is redrawing alliances in the tobacco control movement as federal officials wrestle with how to regulate the growing e-cigarette market.The players include researchers, smoking-cessat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian neighborhoods  destroyed as lava rolls into sea...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/ny-news-hawaii-volcano-lava-destruction-20180607-story.html</link>
      <description>Volcanic activity in Hawaii has destroyed entire neighborhoods on Big Island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>Get the latest Rolling Stone news with exclusive stories and pictures from Rolling Stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>House GOP leadership will try to win over moderates to prevent them from pushing ahead with their discharge petition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide now 10th leading cause of death in USA...</title>
      <link>http://www.omaha.com/news/nation/suicide-now-the-th-leading-cause-of-death-in-us/article_7b5f1b59-76fa-5fdf-a08e-b14bccc2749c.html</link>
      <description>More than a decade of steadily rising rates have made suicide the nation’s 10th leading cause of death and one of only three causes of death — including Alzheimer’s disease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NY DAILY NEWS] CONFIDENTIAL</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/gossip/confidential</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENEZUELA now world's most dangerous country?</title>
      <link>http://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article212661424.html</link>
      <description>New Gallup study finds Venezuelans perceive their country as the most dangerous on the planet — worse than places like Afghanistan and South Sudan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>LifeZette's mission is contained in its moniker: Life. Explained. Each day the site captures the wonder, the complexity, the frustration and the joys of life in all its variety. This is media built for the way we live--never in one place or focused on one issue to the exclusion of all others. From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain -- and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>HELLO! US, News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turks look to alternative media as news landscape shrinks...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180607-turks-look-alternative-media-news-landscape-shrinks</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EX-BOSSES: Joy Reid threatened colleague, mocked gays...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/06/07/msnbcs-joy-reid-threatened-colleague-mocked-gays-during-her-radio-days-ex-bosses-say.html</link>
      <description>MSNBC star Joy-Ann Reid has physically threatened a senior colleague, mocked a politician on air and often referred to her hateful blog during her short-lived stint as a radio show co-host over a decade ago, former superior colleagues who described her as “evil woman” told Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan filmed fighting digger destroying home...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5817865/Orangutan-defends-forest-grabbing-digger.html</link>
      <description>The animal is hoping to save its trees from loggers believed to be located in the Ketapang Regency on the island of Borneo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dacre Retires From DAILY MAIL; Editor of generation...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5814457/Mails-Editor-new-role.html</link>
      <description>Paul Dacre yesterday announced that he is to step aside as Editor of the Daily Mail after 26 years. Mr Dacre said he will step back from day-to-day editing of the Mail by his 70th birthday in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women who refuse to have babies  --  to save the planet! </title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-5819361/Women-refuse-babies-save-planet.html</link>
      <description>Oonagh Dalgliesh is the first to admit she feels broody. Even so, she has decided she will never experience the joy of discovering she is pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>CBS News is dedicated to the best in journalism under standards it pioneered at the dawn of radio and television and continues to set in today’s digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/news/blogs/the_papers</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>Fox News continues to win in the ratings department, with MSNBC and CNN finishing No. 2 and No. 3 in the relevant dayparts. Chris Cuomo continues to outperform CNN's previous ratings in the 9 p.m. hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG SLAMS TRUMP ANEW...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5304206/donald-trump-discredit-mueller-investigation/</link>
      <description>Rallying to Trump’s battle cry are a growing number of allies </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Medicare for All'  if Dems win House?</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/391214-pelosi-medicare-for-all-should-be-evaluated-if-dems-win-house</link>
      <description>Pelosi said all ideas are "on the table" if Dems win House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/article/declarations.html</link>
      <description>American institutions—and therefore democracy itself—are frailer than we often realize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:   Jodie Foster in Worst Movie of Year!</title>
      <link>http://observer.com/2018/06/total-garbage-hotel-artemis-jodie-foster-worst-movie-of-the-year/</link>
      <description>Amateurish moviemaking aimed at audiences with no taste sinks to an alarming new low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>NYC Guide to Restaurants, Fashion, Nightlife, Shopping, Politics, Movies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE NEWS</title>
      <link>http://news.google.com/nwshp?hl=en&amp;tab=wn&amp;q=</link>
      <description>Comprehensive up-to-date news coverage, aggregated from sources all over the world by Google News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK 'bug' set private info public...</title>
      <link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/06/07/technology/facebook-public-post-error/index.html</link>
      <description>Facebook says an error changed 14 million users' default sharing setting to public for four days in May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>Yonhap produces a wide range of news contents and provides print, broadcast media as well as state and private institutions with real-time news products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROSSFIT Gym Under Fire For Kicking Out Members Who Don't 'Fit In'...</title>
      <link>http://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/06/07/crossfit-gym-utah-members-kicked-out-vision/</link>
      <description>Two women are crying foul after a crossfit gym in Utah kicked them out because they apparently didn't fit the gym's vision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZONFACEBOOKGOOGLETWITTER TEAM WITH SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/06/splc-partner-google-facebook-amazon/</link>
      <description>'An organization that has lost its way'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/columnists/howie_carr</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Pizzeria Worker Mixed Rat Poison In Cheese...</title>
      <link>http://abc11.com/food/employee-accused-of-putting-rat-poison-in-cheese-at-fayetteville-pizza-place/3570247/</link>
      <description>An employee at Primo Pizza off Raeford Road is accused of putting rat poison in shredded cheese that was used on pizzas being prepared in the restaurant, according to Fayetteville police.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
