<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>More UBER layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/14/uber-lays-off-about-350-employees-in-self-driving-eats-and-other-divisions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber has laid off about 350 employees across several teams within the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Residents On Edge After Series Of Unexplained Fires...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/10/13/after-multiple-unexplained-fires-broke-out-in-west-baltimore-community-calls-out-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Eastwood community is saying their neighborhood has been neglected for far too long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hunt for Asia's El Chapo...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/special-report-hunt-asias-el-115908942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is Asia’s most-wanted man. Tse Chi Lop, a Canadian national born in China, is suspected of leading a vast multinational drug trafficking syndicate formed out of an alliance of five of Asia’s triad groups, according to law enforcement officials. The syndicate, law enforcers believe, is funneling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do CA power shutoffs work? Hard to know, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3592cd7314ea41899bbc5d59f71ac729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Millions of Californians spent part of the week in the dark in an unprecedented effort by the state's large electrical utilities to prevent another devastating wildfire. It...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-National Security Council official testifying...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a3d4894a69d4f24814f3fd66e49a2e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Fiona Hill, a former top National Security Council expert on Russia, was testifying to Congress behind closed doors Monday, the latest former Trump administration official to be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nr2X4ty1ZVU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Chief Unleashes on Ronan Farrow in New Staff Memo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nbc-news-chief-noah-oppenheim-unleashes-on-ronan-farrow-in-new-staff-memo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The war between NBC and its former star reporter got even uglier on Monday, with the network dubbing parts of Farrow’s reporting a “smear” or “lie.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff ran 'fight club' for dementia patients at nursing home...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article236192538.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbus statue defaced in Providence...</title>
      <link>https://turnto10.com/news/local/vandals-target-columbus-statue-in-providence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;turnto10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A statue of Christopher Columbus in Providence was vandalized on the holiday honoring him. The statue in Elmwood was found covered in red paint on Monday, which is Columbus Day. A sign stating "Stop Celebrating Genocide" was chained around the pedestal and the word "Genocide" was painted on the base. Providence police took photographs of the damage and collected evidence. The statue, dedicated in 1893, was the target of vandals in 2010 and 2017. Columbus is a polarizing figure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President sets record -- 59 tweets in day!</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/871559/trump-now-averaging-36-tweets-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment has President Trump more hooked on Twitter than ever before. In the week before House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) officially launched an impeachment inquiry into the president, he was still pretty addicted to social media, tweeting an average of 18 times per day. But the start of the inquiry has led Trump to double his tweet time, sending an average of 36 tweets a day, The Washington Post reports. Trump set the single-day tweeting record of his presidency just five days after the impeachment inquiry began, suggesting across 48 tweets and retweets on Sept. 29 that his impeachment would cause a "civil war" and attacking Fox &amp; Friends host Ed Henry 18 times. He then set another record last Friday, hitting "59 total tweets, including 33 in just 20 minutes," The Post writes. That included the announcement that Kevin McAleenan was leaving his spot as acting homeland security secretary. Trump's tweet storm has coincided with another devastating new fact: He's now averaging more false claims per day than ever before. Throughout his presidency, Trump has averaged 14 false claims per day, with a graph from the Post showing the daily total has consistently increased as he approaches his 1,000th day in office. In fact, over the past 65 days, Trump has relayed an average of 22 false claims per day, per the Post. That's largely thanks to Trump's phone call with Ukraine's presidency and all the ways he's tried to cover it up in the weeks since. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg Teases AI 'Brain Chip'...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/10/mark-zuckerberg-ai-brain-chip-elon-musk-neuralink/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“‘Facebook wants to perform brain surgery.’ I don’t want to see the congressional hearings on that one,” Zuckerberg said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside brutal drug cartels who behead rivals with chainsaws...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9819449/mexico-cartels-pregnant-women-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KNIFE-WIELDING gangs and police in full body armour on the beach aren’t things you expect to see on holiday. But it’s a disturbingly common scene in dozens of Brit holiday hotspots in M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCREENED AT DORAL</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/macabre-video-of-fake-trump-shooting-media-and-critics-is-shown-at-his-resort/ar-AAIJ5Bm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMPAIGN ROCKED</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5b4d068063154e74bbfca5cbfa3082c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House says President Donald Trump has yet to watch a graphically violent parody video that depicts a likeness of him shooting and stabbing opponents and members of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Hosts Criticize, Mock President In Ad Meeting...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/14/fox-news-hosts-baier-wallace-maccallum-trump-mock-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report reveals that Fox News hosts criticized and mocked President Donald Trump during a closed door meeting last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Gold Rush...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/a-global-gold-rush-is-imminent_10132019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren flaunts her fitness as candidates' health becomes  issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-10-14/elizabeth-warren-flaunts-fitness-health-democratic-candidates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The age and health of the top Democratic presidential candidates will come under scrutiny in Tuesday's debate, coming after Bernie Sanders' heart attack. Like Sanders and Joe Biden, Elizabeth Warren is in her 70s, but she flaunts her fitness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IRSHMAN' branded Scorsese's 'best film in decades'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-7570493/The-Irishman-wows-critics-call-Martin-Scorseses-best-film-decades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Irishman received rave reviews from critics upon its premiere at the closing gala of the BFI London Film Festival on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of Fake Trump Shooting Media, Critics Shown at His Resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7569619/Horrific-video-meme-Donald-Trump-massacres-fake-news-media-shown-resort.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disturbing display took place at the Trump National Doral Miami last week, which was the site of a three-day conference held by a pro-Trump organization called American Priority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Girl Dies After Falling Off 'Extreme' Ride At Harvest Festival...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/10/13/10year-old-girl-dies-falling-off-ride-deerfield-township-harvest-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey State Police says the 10-year-old girl fell off a ride called "Extreme," which is a Wisdom Super Sizzler amusement park ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In rush to harvest body parts, death investigations upended...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2019-10-13/body-parts-harvesting-hinders-coroner-autopsies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Times found a rising number of death investigations across the country were complicated or upended after transplantable body parts were taken before a coroner’s autopsy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homemade bomb used for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/hong-kong-protests-police-homemade-bomb-mong-kok-11998870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG: Police said that a remote-controlled homemade bomb, similar to those used in "terrorist attacks", was set off for the first time during ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The bluff that kicked off invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-erdogan-turkey-syria-invasion-bluff-fc761d8f-e33b-473b-8ece-d0b8b3a51f26.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump would tell Erdoğan that if he wanted to invade Syria, he would have to own whatever mess ensued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian army moves to confront forces as US withdraws...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a7033640aad04506b2e8aa139d9edabe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AKCAKALE, Turkey (AP) — Syrian government troops moved into a series of towns and villages in northern Syria Monday, setting up a potential clash with Turkish-led forces in the area, as U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to conduct sweeping drills of its nuclear forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3fba5cf04deb44d2a3dc0517b794c1ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia's military will this week undertake a sweeping drill of its strategic nuclear forces. The Defense Ministry said the three-day exercise will begin Tuesday and involve...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US 'medical tourists' seek cheap health care abroad...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-medical-tourists-seek-cheap-health-care-abroad-034811876.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Shale Oil Boom Nearly Over...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-great-shale-oil-boom-060005334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- America’s second shale boom is running out of steam. But don’t panic just yet, a third one may be coming over the horizon.The U.S. Energy Information Administration published its latest short-term energy outlook last week and has cut its forecast of oil production by the end of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blames Kurds?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191014110238-4sp4k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-USA-TRUMP (URGENT):Trump: Kurdish-led forces may intentionally be releasing Islamic State militants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam pulls DREAMWORKS film over South China Sea map...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191014052132-hmcpu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIETNAM-SOUTHCHINASEA/FILM (PIX):Vietnam pulls DreamWorks' 'Abominable' film over South China Sea map</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Video of Fake Trump Shooting Media Shown at His Resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/14/macabre-video-of-fake-trump-shooting-media-and-critics-is-shown-at-his-resort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — A video depicting a macabre scene of a fake President Trump shooting, stabbing and brutally assaulting members of the news media and his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes 'will pull society apart'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/deepfake-videos-will-cause-worldwide-20574174</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are fears fake videos will be used to spread political turmoil and divisions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Socialist Hell: 20 Years of Decay in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/10/13/my-socialist-hell-20-years-of-decay-in-venezuela/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela, my home country, has it all: beautiful and breathtaking landscapes, abundant resources, even unique wonders of nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big changes to grueling Special Forces course draw scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/de165494a09d4e7bb022bcdd7a150f7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMP MACKALL, N.C. (AP) — Deep in the dark North Carolina woods, a small white light flickers in the heavy underbrush. It's after midnight and a soldier is taking a risk by turning on his headlamp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bombs convoy of foreign journalists... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10127621/turkey-bombs-convoy-of-foreign-journalists-and-aid-workers-killing-ten-in-syria-border-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT LEAST 14 people have been killed – including five civilians and a journalist – in a Turkish air raid on a convoy of civilians in Syria today, according to reports. The guarded convoy…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Girl charged with felony for pointing finger at classmates...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article235891762.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Hits Staggering $544M Worldwide In 10 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/joker-box-office-crazy-great-at-55m-addams-family-buries-gemini-man-1247269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Globally, 'Joker' has collected a staggering $544 million. Meanwhile at the specialty box office, 'Parasite' scored the biggest location average in three years with $125,421.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Clinton emphatically states person with beard and penis can identify as woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7568933/Chelsea-Hillary-Clinton-awkward-moment-disagree-trans-self-identification.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalist Decca Aitkenhead said Hillary became 'uneasy' when she asked about trans identification, while Chelsea shot a 'furious stare' at the journalist as her mother answered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House plan to steady ship after hell week...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/white-house-china-trade-war-turkey-sanctions-saudi-arabia-98af7c73-aace-45b0-b28a-ab20a7099004.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has signaled 3 moves that, while modest in substance, throw scraps of reassurance to anxious Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House impeachment roadmap...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/house-democrats-impeachment-roadmap-trump-ukraine-e254769f-2a3d-4e66-8df7-9c3a9409f9c1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are taking the impeachment inquiry in two tightly focused directions: Ukraine and obstruction of justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff Says Secrecy Aimed at Keeping President in Dark...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/schiff-says-secret-testimony-aimed-165106637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff defended holding testimony behind closed doors in the impeachment inquiry he’s heading up against President Donald Trump, likening this phase of the investigation to a “grand jury.”“We want to make sure that we meet the needs of the investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orban Poised to Lose Budapest as Yacht Orgy Dents Dominant Image...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/orban-poised-lose-budapest-yacht-194423503.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Hungarian Prime Minister Viktor Orban’s party lost control of Budapest and four of the country’s biggest cities, in a major rebuke to his rule after a video of one of his allies at an orgy handed a last-minute gift to a galvanized opposition.The unexpectedly strong showing in local elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Trade Handshake Lifts Spirits But Not Sober Outlook...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-china-handshake-lifts-spirits-184205862.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. The pledges China and the U.S. made to keep prospects alive for a comprehensive trade deal did little to alter the deteriorating growth outlooks for both countries because they were sealed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANDERS RIPS WARREN 'THE CAPITALIST'</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bernie-sanders-draws-contrast-elizabeth-warren-capitalist-bones/story?id=66217140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Sen. Elizabeth Warren climbing in polls, Sen. Bernie Sanders highlighted a key difference in their core economic philosophies in an interview on ABC's "This Week."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom of 'blackout babies'?</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/health-and-medicine/article236053063.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wears bulletproof vest!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/justin-trudeau-bulletproof-vest-campaign-security-1.5319953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberal Leader Justin Trudeau took an "unprecedented" step by wearing  a bulletproof vest at a campaign rally in response to a security threat, say two veteran RCMP sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems discuss detaining White House officials who don't testify...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/465551-tlaib-says-democrats-have-discussed-detaining-white-house-officials-who-dont</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau continues campaign after threats to his safety...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trudeau-continues-campaign-threats-safety-195931897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said Sunday he plans to continue campaigning as normal after wearing body armor the night before, a move the CBC reported was due to threats to his security. "This will not change at all how I campaign," Trudeau said, on the sidelines of a campaign event</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters erect 'Lady Liberty' statue on Hong Kong mountain top...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/protesters-erect-lady-liberty-statue-hong-kong-mountain-092458950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro-democracy protesters hauled a four-metre statue known as "Lady Liberty" to the top of a famous Hong Kong mountain early Sunday, announcing the peak would be its "final resting place". The statue depicts a female protester in a gas mask, protective goggles and helmet, an umbrella</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Populists top Poland vote, expand majority on  family values ticket...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/populists-eye-victory-deeply-divided-poland-022137805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland's governing right-wing party topped Sunday's general election, an exit poll showed, expanding its majority thanks to a raft of welfare measures coupled with attacks on LGBT rights and Western values. The Law and Justice party (PiS) scored 43.6 percent of the vote for 239 seats in parliament</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit divorce talks between UK and EU go down to the wire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff28147157854995a358f37a83e821cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson told Cabinet colleagues that it will require a "significant amount of work" to strike a Brexit deal with the European Union, amid signs of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters weary of more investigations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cb9a197eecc3404a9be201d86afa67f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FISHERS, Ind. (AP) — As Democrats' impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump intensifies, Mark Stenske feels like he's seen this movie before, and the storyline is getting old. First,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
