<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DC UGLY:  New Congresswoman Rashida Tlaib Goes off on Trump: We're Going to 'Impeach the Motherf*cker!'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/new-congresswoman-rashida-tlaib-goes-off-on-trump-were-going-to-impeach-the-motherfcker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/_NestorRuiz/status/1081034160888795136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“.@RashidaTlaib saying it louder for the people in the back!! ✊🏾 #116thCongress https://t.co/VeUq0GwI5E”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parade float portraying children in cages draws complaints...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/parade-float-portraying-children-cages-draws-complaints-234544493.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDDLETOWN, Del. (AP) — A parade float portraying children in cages at the U.S. border has drawn criticism from politicians and community activists, who say the event in a Delaware town has gone too far this time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas tech show to celebrate innovation amid mounting concerns... </title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/a/global-tech-show-to-celebrate-innovation-amid-mounting-concerns/4725243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jan. 8-11 Las Vegas trade event offers a glimpse into new products and services designed to make people's lives easier, fun and more productive, though talk of security is expected to grow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronaut sparks panic after accidentally dialling 911 from space...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8116475/astronaut-calls-911-space-nasa-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN astronaut has told how he accidentally rang 911 from space – sending security teams at NASA’s Houston base into a frenzy. André Kuipers missed out a number when making a call through…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Rising obesity killing pets...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/03/fat-dogs-could-die-two-years-six-months-earlier-healthy-pets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pudgy dogs die more than two-and-a-half years earlier than pets of a healthy weight, a study of 20 years of veterinary records has shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's stark warning may be ominous news for China...</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/business/world/109725873/apples-stark-warning-may-be-ominous-news-for-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANALYSIS: China's growth juggernaut has been a driver of the global economy. What happens when it slows - or grinds to a halt?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Teacher had young girl pose in lingerie, planned to sell her in Morocco...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article223863955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amber Michelle Parker, 37, a teacher in Mexia, Texas, is charged with trafficking of persons after she was accused by a family member of planning to sell an underage female relative to men in Morocco for sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The orca and the orca catcher: How a generation of killer whales was taken from Puget Sound...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environment/the-orca-and-the-orca-catcher-how-a-generation-of-killer-whales-was-taken-from-puget-sound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOSTILE WATERS | Namu was Ted Griffin’s greatest prize, a live killer whale, put on display at Seattle’s waterfront. The orca’s journey from wild to captive would spark a worldwide sensation and change everything we knew about "blackfish."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Mulls Jim Webb as Next Defense Secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/03/jim-webb-defense-secretary-1060169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Democratic senator may be the kind of foreign policy iconoclast Trump is looking for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA INFERNO:  At least 7 dead after diesel spill on highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-fiery-crash-gainesville-i75-20190103-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two big rigs and two passenger vehicles collided and spilled diesel fuel across a Florida highway Thursday, sparking a massive fire that killed seven people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF IPHONE ERA?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/03/opinion/apple-revenue-china-innovation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We need the next wave of innovation, and we need it now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia's autonomous train becomes world's largest robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/robot-train-australia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitaltrends.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iron ore mining company Rio Tinto has officially launched its fully automated, heavy-haul, long- distance rail network: A series of mine-to-port trains that can run completely free from human intervention. Here's why it decided to replace human drivers with automated ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicagoland official charged with attempted extortion of BURGER KING owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-alderman-ed-burke-charges-20190103-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ald. Edward Burke, one of Chicago’s most powerful figures and a vestige of the city’s old Democratic machine, has been charged with corruption for allegedly using his political office for personal gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delayed tax refunds. Missed federal paychecks. Shutdown's pain keeps growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/politics-government/article223876930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the partial government shutdown stretches on, employees will miss their first paycheck next week, more agencies will shutter and tax refunds could be pushed back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Releases Thousands More Migrants into USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/03/dhs-releases-over-2k-border-crossing-adults-children-into-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DHS is releasing from custody more than 2,000 border-crossing adults and the children they arrived with over the course of a few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Ryan exits at 12% favorability...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/03/12-percent-paul-ryans-favorability-bottoms-out-as-former-speaker-leaves-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Ryan leaves Congress with one of the lowest favorability ratings a Speaker has ever had, bottoming out at 12 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buzz grows on 'flying cars'... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/buzz-grows-flying-cars-ahead-major-tech-show-020607227.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will flying cars take off at the upcoming Consumer Electronics Show? NFT Inc. co-founders Maki and Guy Kaplinsky, a couple developing a flying vehicle in Israel and California, will have their vision on display at show, with a media session on Sunday. "We believe we have a winning design that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia markets fall again as 2019 off to nightmare start...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/asia-markets-fall-again-tokyo-gets-2019-off-024718656--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was no respite for Asian investors Friday as most regional markets suffered more losses, with Tokyo tanking three percent and technology firms taking another hiding after Apple's shock revenue warning. The new year has proved so far to be anything but happy on trading floors as dealers face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake early warning app now available for LA...</title>
      <link>https://la.curbed.com/2019/1/2/18165972/earthquake-early-warning-app-download-shakealert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;la.curbed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It deploys a warning when shaking is expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Takes Her Out For Ice Cream...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/03/cnn-dana-bash-nancy-pelosi-ice-cream-vaccaros-baltimore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'She likes her chocolate unadulterated'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems pass funding plan without wall, Trump digs in...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f84043fe46ba4cdeb9705f672332908b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On their first day in the majority, House Democrats on Thursday night passed a plan to re-open the government without funding President Donald Trump's promised border wall. The largely party-line votes came after Trump made a surprise appearance at the White House briefing room pledging to keep up the fight for his signature campaign promise. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said Trump and Senate Republicans should "take yes for an answer" and approve the border bill, which was virtually identical to a plan the Senate adopted on a voice vote last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researcher pulls talk on hacking Face ID...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-cyber-conference/cyber-researcher-pulls-public-talk-on-hacking-apples-face-id-idUSKCN1OX1TA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cyber security researcher canceled a hacking conference briefing on how he sai...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro open to US military base in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190104-jair-bolsonaro-says-open-usa-military-base-brazil-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's new President Jair Bolsonaro said on Thursday that he would be open to the possibility of the United States operating a military base on his country's soil, a move that would form a sharp shift in direction for Brazilian foreign policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPGRADE, PLEASE!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/03/heres-tim-cooks-plan-to-get-more-people-to-upgrade-their-iphones.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook laid out his plan for getting revenue back on track by encouraging customers to upgrade their iPhones in an interview with CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$452 BILLION VANISH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/03/apples-losses-since-peak-exceed-the-value-of-496-of-sp-500.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In only three months, Apple has lost $452 billion in market capitalization — and counting, as the tech giant's stock falls further Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bored' firefighter accused of setting homes on fire...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/volunteer-firefighter-allegedly-set-homes-on-fire-because-he-was-bored/4910273/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 19-year-old volunteer firefighter is charged with starting fires at two homes, and police allege that he said he did it because he was bored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: Jurors 'may be impressed' by concert footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.spin.com/2019/01/ed-sheeran-marvin-gaye-lawsuit-update/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit alleging Ed Sheeran's "Thinking Out Loud" infringes on the copyright of Marvin Gaye's "Let's Get It On" is headed to a jury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnamese eatery argues 'discriminatory' to consider 'Pho Keene Great' name offensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.sentinelsource.com/news/local/food-fight-new-keene-restaurant-s-name-flagged-by-city/article_de75a192-c30f-5de4-abb6-390cf905bb12.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sentinelsource.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A soon-to-open restaurant removed its sign this week after city officials alleged its name could be interpreted as offensive and violated a lease agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Sheeran Trial Over 'Let's Get It On' Plagiarism Claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/ed-sheeran-headed-trial-claim-he-copied-lets-get-it-1172992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Sheeran is accused of copying Gaye's 1973 hit "Let's Get It On" in his 2014 song "Thinking Out Loud."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sugar substitutes not healthier than real sugar...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1514691/sugar-substitutes-are-not-healthier-than-real-sugar-says-new-research/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial sweeteners have long pitched to consumers that they represent a healthier alternative to sugar. It's not true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA INFERNO:  At least 6 dead after diesel spill on highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.wesh.com/article/at-least-6-dead-8-injured-in-fiery-crash-on-i-75-near-gainesville/25741060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wesh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least six people are dead and eight others injured after a fiery crash on I-75 near Gainesville in Alachua County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW: Christians 'overrepresented' in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/pew-christians-overrepresented-in-congress-55-percent-protestant-30-percent-catholic-6-percent-jewish</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Congress that was sworn in Thursday afternoon is significantly more religious and Christian than the nation it represents, according to an analysis of religions claimed by House and Senate members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IA Dem Chair Preps Pocahontas 'Joke' for Warren...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/the-run/articles/2019-01-03/elizabeth-warren-heads-to-iowa-for-an-early-2020-bounce-in-democratic-primary-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Swears In Romney, Says It's 'An Honor'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/video/watch-pence-swears-in-romney-says-its-an-honor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No bad blood here...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts warn NETFLIX choose-your-adventure could be ploy to steal thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8108883/black-mirror-bandersnatch-conspiracy-choose-your-own-adventure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANDERSNATCH is one of the most talked-about Netflix episodes ever – and it could be the beginning of a sinister conspiracy to harvest your thoughts. The Black Mirror episode lets viewers choose th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest of 'Yellow Vest' leader sparks outcry in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190103-france-arrest-yellow-vest-leader-drouet-melenchon-police-protest-macron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the leaders of the "Yellow Vest" demonstrations in France was detained by police in Paris, signalling a harder line from the government that sparked a wave of criticism from opponents on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representative reintroduces impeachment articles...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/politics/rep-reintroduces-impeachment-articles-against-president-donald-trump/5010255/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Representative Brad Sherman reintroduced articles of impeachment against President Trump Thursday - the first day of the 116th Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEINSTEIN BACKS BIDEN, SNUBS 'BRAND NEW' KAMALA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-congress-feinstein-20190103-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Dianne Feinstein said she supports former Vice President Joe Biden in the 2020 presidential field, which could make things awkward with fellow Californian and possible 2020 contender Sen. Kamala Harris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Hunting Foreign Buyers for Sovereign Debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/china-is-hunting-for-foreign-buyers-for-its-sovereign-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China Is Hunting for Foreign Buyers for Its Sovereign Debt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany entices illegal migrants to leave with bribes... </title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/germany-entices-illegal-migrants-to-leave-with-bribes-free-rent-for-a-year-at-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 20,000 airport repatriations were scrubbed this year as rejected asylum-seekers vanished before departure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends conservatives for tweets about brussel sprouts, 'drunk' Don Lemon...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/03/newsbusters-daily-wire-conservative-suspended-twitter-brussels-sprouts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Come on, Jack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers leap from UBER as driver has heart attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Passengers-leap-from-car-as-Uber-driver-has-heart-13505898.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Uber driver had a heart attack while driving, forcing two passengers to jump out of the car on a Northern California highway. The Press Democrat reports the 50-year-old male driver was stricken ill Wednesday while driving on the middle lane of Highway 101 in Petaluma. California Highway Patrol Officer Matt Pinheiro says the car drifted off the road onto the shoulder, slowing to about 5 mph when the passengers "ended up exiting the vehicle at a slow roll." Rancho Adobe Fire Protection District battalion chief Mike Weihman says the passengers apparently leapt from the moving vehicle to avoid a potential crash into nearby trees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Mulls Jim Webb as Next Defense Secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/03/us/politics/jim-webb-defense-secretary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Webb’s views align closely with President Trump’s drive to pull American troops from the Middle East and confront China more aggressively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confused Speaker botches speech...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/confused-pelosi-botches-speaker-speech-i-think-i-skipped-a-couple-of-pages-im-not-sure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the conclusion of her first speech to Congress after becoming House Speaker again, Nancy Pelosi realized she “skipped a couple pages” of her remarks. “As we take the oath of office today,” Pelosi said, “we accept responsibility as daunting and demanding as any previous generations of leadership have faced. “Guided by the vision and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man trapped in BURGER KING bathroom sues to regain free meals for life...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article223872735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Portland, Oregon, Burger King offered Curtis Brooner, 50, free burgers for life after he spent an hour trapped in a dirty restroom, but a corporate manager canceled the deal, a lawsuit says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>51-year-old mom accused of abusing her infant triplets...</title>
      <link>https://www.lehighvalleylive.com/bethlehem/2019/01/bethlehem-mom-accused-of-abusing-her-infant-triplets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lehighvalleylive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say the triplets, who were eight weeks old at the time, had broken bones and signs of head trauma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Bibi Must Quit If Indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Netanyahu-must-quit-if-indicted-majority-of-Israelis-say-in-Post-poll-576278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Likudniks don't want Benjamin Netanyahu to go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women navigate toxicity, other barriers in esports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6762c27de8f1434fb5a8e14649d2a50b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Susie Kim thinks the women gamers are out there. As general manager for a championship esports team, she would know. She's not surprised none of them are on her roster. The Entertainment Software Association reported this year that 45 percent of U.S. gamers are female, yet women make up a scant portion of the professional esports player pool. Executives for games like "League of Legends" and "Overwatch" say they are eager to add women to pro rosters, where players can make hundreds of thousands of dollars. Yet LoL's Championship Series hasn't had a female gamer since 2016, and the Overwatch League's inaugural season featured just one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skier saw 'afterlife' after dying for 20 MINUTES in avalanche before coming back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8034586/near-death-experience-ski-accident-austria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRITISH skier who ‘died’ for 20 MINUTES after being trapped in an avalanche revealed today how she “saw a peaceful forest” while experiencing the “afterlife”. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London airports order military-grade anti-drone equipment...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-drones-gatwick/gatwick-and-heathrow-airports-order-military-grade-anti-drone-equipment-the-times-idUSKCN1OX1KX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London's Gatwick and Heathrow airports have ordered military-grade anti-dro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to indict model Bar Refaeli for tax evasion, perjury, money laundering... </title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Police-to-indict-Bar-Refaeli-parents-for-tax-evasion-576237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supermodel and her parents expected to face charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian 'BATWOMAN' Series Moving Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ruby-rose-led-batwoman-pilot-a-go-at-cw-1172794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Nutter, who helmed 'Game of Thrones, 'Arrow' and 'The Flash,' is on board to direct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI IN CONTROL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6554789/Back-Pelosi-poised-reclaim-Speaker-gavel-8-years-minority.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi, grinning broadly and standing out on the House floor in hot pink, was elected Speaker of the House on Thursday. as Democrats returned to power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: EAGLES Fans Ready For Another Magical Run By Backup QB...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/01/02/eagles-may-be-underdogs-again-but-nick-foles-has-fans-feeling-confident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Optimism is high among Eagles fans and with Nick Foles at the helm, it's easy to see why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE BLAMES CHINA</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/apple-entering-dark-chapter-iphone-sales-are-slowing-n954221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is definitely the most defining period for Tim Cook in his career as CEO,” said one analyst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF man arrested in New Year's Eve sex assault of 99-year-old woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/crime/article/Man-charged-with-sexually-assaulting-99-year-old-13504453.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man captured after a New Year's Eve sex assault in San Francisco's Chinatown had attacked a 99-year-old woman in her apartment at the Ping Yuen housing project, officials said Wednesday. The suspect, identified by police as 26-year-old Teandre Howard-Kidd, was charged on Wednesday with sexual assault, residential burglary and elder abuse. He is scheduled for arraignment in San Francisco Superior Court on Thursday. The attack happened around 12:35 p.m. at the storied public housing development on the 800 block of Pacific Avenue known to locals as the Pings, police said. Staff members quickly provided police with surveillance footage of the suspect from one of the many security cameras in the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Vending Machines: PEPSI Testing Delivery Bots...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/food-drink/article223863645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PepsiCo is testing a way to bring snacks directly to college students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feinstein signals support for Biden over Kamala...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/politics/feinstein-signals-2020-support-for-biden-over-harris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Dianne Feinstein said Thursday that it would be difficult not to support former Vice President Joseph R. Biden Jr. if he runs for president in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE shifting billion$ to tax haven Bermuda...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-taxes-netherlands/google-shifted-23-billion-to-tax-haven-bermuda-in-2017-filing-idUSKCN1OX1G9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google moved 19.9 billion euros ($22.7 billion) through a Dutch shell company to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional ghost hunters investigate haunting of US battleship...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article223864065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of nationally known professional ghost hunters intends to spend part of Saturday night aboard the USS North Carolina, to find proof of ghosts that haunt the decommissioned battleship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting depression: Phone apps to monitor teen angst...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/21d8615133864b43bfe071ddfaf55a53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising suicide rates and depression in U.S. teens and young adults have prompted researchers to ask a provocative question: Could the same devices that some people blame for contributing to tech-age angst also be used to detect it? The idea has sparked a race to develop apps that warn of impending mental health crises. Call it smartphone psychiatry or child psychology 2.0. Studies have linked heavy smartphone use with worsening teen mental health. But as teens scroll through Instagram and Snapchat, tap out texts or watch YouTube videos, they also leave digital footprints that might offer clues to their psychological well-being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI IN CONTROL...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pelosi-poised-become-house-speaker-making-history-again-053957706--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi knew this moment would come, even if others had their doubts — or worked to stop her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Bar Refaeli suspected of tax evasion in Israel... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/model-bar-refaeli-suspected-tax-evasion-israel-142109842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's most famous model Bar Refaeli is suspected of tax evasion and will be called into a hearing ahead of her possible indictment, authorities said Thursday. The 33-year-old could be charged pending the hearing, while her parents are also suspected of money laundering, a justice ministry statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX 'MASKED SINGER' STARTS STRONG...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/masked-singer-reveals-huge-premiere-ratings-antonio-brown-fox/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox's new quirky competition "The Masked Singer" revealed itself to 9.2 million viewers on Wednesday night. That is a huge number for Fox</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Army targets millennials in new recruitment drive...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/03/army-targets-snowflakes-binge-gamers-millennials-new-recruitment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Army recruitment campaign seeks to target gamers and millennials stuck in 'boring jobs'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Malley Endorses Beto...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/03/omalley-2020-endorses-orourke-1078587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He promoted O’Rourke as part of a “new generation” of leaders that can unify and heal the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim congresswoman to be sworn in on Thomas Jefferson's Quran...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article223866655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Muslim Congresswoman elect Rashida Tlaib from Detroit Michigan will be sworn in with Thomas Jefferson’s Koran. The Palestinian-American joins Minnesota’s Ilhan Omar as the first female Muslims in the US House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake pastor smuggled drugs into jails using bibles...</title>
      <link>https://www.kwtx.com/cw12tv/content/news/Sheriff-Fake-pastor-carrying-drug-filled-Bible-visited-jail-503847341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kwtx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A search of the Bible he toted revealed Suboxone strips inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC News Veteran Leaves Network, Says Media Have Become 'Prisoners'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/nbc-news-veteran-leaves-network-says-media-have-become-prisoners-of-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"NBC (like the rest of the news media) could no longer keep up with the world," Bill Arkin, a 30 years veteran of NBC says in a memo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg halts FACEBOOK stock sale as value plummets over privacy gaffes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8112733/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-stock-selloff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILLIONAIRE Mark Zuckerberg has halted the sale of his Facebook stock after the company’s value collapsed last year. The controversial 34-year-old has seen his company fall from grace, and fa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American detained in Moscow 'charged with espionage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/03/moscow-spy-charges-ex-marine-arrested-after-usb-drive-pickup-paul-whelan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Whelan had drive with classified list of names when detained, claims news agency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Using AMAZON's Facial Recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/01/fbi-trying-amazons-facial-recognition-software/153888/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The software allows the FBI to go through video surveillance footage much faster than agents can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK PLUNGES 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/03/apple-stock-falls-after-cutting-q1-guidance-on-weak-iphone-sales.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has lost about $450 billion in market value since its peak of about $1.1 trillion last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Took Credit for Stock Records. Deserve Blame for Plunge?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-03/the-president-owned-the-trump-bump-are-we-in-the-trump-slump?srnd=businessweek-v2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pack of teens beats NYC man to steal iPhone...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-assaulted-in-iphone-robbery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four men are wanted by the NYPD for assaulting a man in order to steal his iPhone in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listen Up, This Podcast Will Just Take a Minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/listen-up-this-podcast-will-just-take-a-minute-11546264801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overwhelmed by the choices, some listeners are loading up podcasts that don’t last much longer than a commercial break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two more Puget Sound orcas predicted to die in critically endangered population...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environment/i-am-worried-and-i-am-afraid-two-more-puget-sound-orcas-predicted-to-die-in-critically-endangered-population/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two southern resident killer whales are ailing and are not expected to live, according to the lead demographer of the orca population that frequents Puget Sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy SEAL to Face Court-Martial Over Murder of Young ISIS Fighter...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsandiego.com/news/local/Decorated-US-Navy-SEAL--to-Face-Court-Martial-for-Charges-Including-Premeditated-Murder-in-Death-of-Young-ISIS-Fighter-503810871.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decorated Navy SEAL will face Court-martial for charges, including premeditated murder in the death of a young ISIS fighter in Iraq, NBC 7 has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunar base?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-china-moonlanding-20190102-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Chang'e-4 lunar lander is just part of an ambitious long-term space exploration plan that includes colonizing and commercially exploiting the solar system and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent unrest sweeps India as first women to enter temple forced into hiding...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/kerala-protests-sabarimala-temple-bjp-communist-violence-women-ban-supreme-court-a8709476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp, Amber Heard Legal Documents Shed New Light on Abuse Accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/johnny-depp-amber-heard-legal-documents-shed-new-light-dual-abuse-accounts-1171081 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stars' volatile relationship, and previously unreleased testimony from their 2016 divorce, is expected to be central to Depp's defamation lawsuit against U.K. tabloid The Sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW DIVES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/03/tech-shares-dive-after-hours-after-apple-warning-nasdaq-etf-loses-nearly-2-percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks fell sharply on Thursday after Apple warned first-quarter sales would be less than it previously expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S Clerk Brawls With Man In Spat Over Straw...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/01/02/brawl-mcdonalds-tampa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is under arrest after authorities say he grabbed the shirt of a Florida McDonald's employee and tried to pull her over a counter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns Iran against space launches, ballistic missiles...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190103133455-hiyb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/ (URGENT):U.S. warns Iran against space launches, ballistic missiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National housing crisis brewing?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-national-housing-crisis-is-brewing-What-13505365.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Housing is sputtering. Home sales, home-building and homeownership have gone flat, and the rise in home prices threatens to stall out. Things aren't likely to get better soon, particularly for lower- and middle-income households struggling to make the rent and become homeowners. That is, unless policymakers act. Housing statistics are clear. Sales of new and existing homes have gone sideways over the past year, as has new single- and multifamily home-building. Housing prices are still rising in much of the country, but the pace of growth is throttling back, and some builders are cutting prices to move houses. Homeownership, which collapsed during the housing crash a decade ago, is just off bottom, and foundering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary opposition vows 'year of resistance' to Orban...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190103-hungary-opposition-vows-year-resistance-orban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungary opposition vows 'year of resistance' to Orban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcism, Demonic Possession Now Tools in Culture Wars...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/01/pope-francis-exorcism-demonic-possession-culture-wars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a data-driven science, exorcism is the definition of bullshit, but as a social movement with people behind it, the devil and his works are very real and now apparently need to be confronted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can expect 'different world'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/03/nancy-pelosi-trump-can-expect-different-world-new-congress/2391622002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Pelosi plans to confront Donald Trump on manyÂ fronts, from investigating the deaths of child migrants to protecting Robert Muellerâ€™s probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won't rule out indictment, impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/news/nancy-pelosi-says-she-won-t-rule-out-indictment-impeachment-t146197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As she prepares to resume her role as House speaker, Nancy Pelosi told TODAY she isn't ruling out the idea that Trump could be indicted or impeached while in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Army puts out recruitment call to all snowflakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/calling-all-snowflakes-your-country-needs-you-7g3tv2gqm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The army has a new generation in its sights for its latest recruitment campaign. Instead of hardened gym goers it is targeting gaming addicts and “phone zombies” in the hopes of boosting the number...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal revolt on first day...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Liberal-revolt-threatens-to-derail-House-13503434.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democratic leaders are set to advance sweeping internal rules changes Thursday that would attempt to bring more sunshine to congressional governance and defuse a pair of political powder kegs that wreaked havoc on GOP leaders over the past eight years. But in their first day of power in the new Congress, Democrats must stave off a liberal rebellion after prominent Democrats said they would oppose the entire rules package that has been carefully assembled by Rep. Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., and a top lieutenant. Rep. Ro Khanna of California and Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Women Film Directors See Numbers Shrink...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/women-comprised-just-8-percent-directors-top-2018-films-1172727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new "Celluloid Ceiling" report from San Diego State University finds that while women made incremental gains in other behind-the-scenes roles in 2018, the percentage of directors who were women was down three percent from 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested at Mar-a-Lago; Was there to talk 'trillions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.floridatoday.com/story/news/2019/01/02/palm-beach-police-arrest-mar-lago-trespasser/2469856002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.floridatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man wanted to talk to Trump about his $6.3 trillion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Economic Collapse Has Lessons for America's Socialists...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/venezuela-economic-collapse-has-lessons-for-america-s-socialists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelaâ€™s Lessons forÂ American Socialists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roe v. Wade at stake as 116th Congress convenes?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/roe-wade-stake-116th-congress-convenes/story?id=60033788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress reconvenes for the 116th session Thursday in the wake of political shake-ups that could bring changes to abortion legislation and the look of Roe v. Wade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorean Diplomat in Rome Disappears...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/north-korean-diplomat-in-rome-disappears-11546515512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jo Song Gil, Pyongyang’s interim ambassador to Italy until late last year, has gone into hiding along with his wife, a development that presents embarrassment for Pyongyang as it negotiates nuclear disarmament with the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientology murder mystery as 'church employee' stabbed to death at complex...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8108737/scientology-sydney-church-stabbed-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SCIENTOLOGY employee has been stabbed to death today by a teenager outside the group’s mega church in Australia. A 16-year-old has been arrested after two men were allegedly stabbed in the drivew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Home Prices Fall Under $1 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/manhattan-home-prices-fall-under-1-million-as-sellers-cut-deals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buyers seeking bargains send median to three-year low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Took Credit for Stock Records. Deserve Blame for Plunge?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-president-owned-the-trump-bump-are-we-in-the-trump-slump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Took Credit for Stock Market Records. Does He Deserve Blame for the Plunge?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi breaks with Justice: Trump can be indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nancy-pelosi-speaker-of-the-house-speech-3fc7ccca-ff47-4fe9-bf2f-a3c4d05c30c2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As speaker, she plans to maintain the unyielding posture she's taken with the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI IN CONTROL...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/688ca14bb55642bc825a29bdc3ca1eda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi knew this moment would come, even if others had their doubts — or worked to stop her. Pelosi is poised to be elected Thursday as House speaker, the only woman who has held the office and now one of few elected officials who will be returning to it. The last time a speaker regained the gavel was more than a half-century ago. The California Democrat has spent her political career being underestimated, only to prove the naysayers wrong. In this case, it was by winning back the Democratic majority and amassing the votes for the speaker's job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A real roasting: Coffee startup set to overtake STARBUCKS in China...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/real-roasting-coffee-startup-luckin-set-overtake-starbucks-111401100.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After only a year in business, startup Luckin Coffee said Thursday it will open 2,500 stores this year to dislodge Starbucks and become China's largest coffee chain. The company said it plans to have more than 4,500 stores in China by the end of 2019, taking it past the US coffee giant, which has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naming names: Reckoning underway in Catholic Church...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/naming-names-reckoning-underway-us-catholic-church-104146078.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Over the past four months, Roman Catholic dioceses across the U.S. have released the names of more than 1,000 priests and others accused of sexually abusing children in an unprecedented public reckoning spurred at least in part by a shocking grand jury investigation in Pennsylvania</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'lifts mysterious veil' by landing probe on far side of moon...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190103095508-voxif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-MOON/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-China 'lifts mysterious veil' by landing probe on far side of the moon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's growing anger with Fed chief poses market risks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/423607-trumps-growing-anger-with-fed-chief-poses-market-risks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump would likely find himself in murky legal waters if he attempts to dismiss Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell, but experts say the bigger concern is that any move on that front would ignite a chain of calamities that could derai</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
