<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kamala layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/30/kamala-harris-campaign-layoffs-061112</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never Before Seen Autopsy Photo...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/exclusive/exclusive-never-before-seen-autopsy-photo-of-jeffrey-epsteins-broken-bones-released/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAN FURY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10241849/george-michael-fadi-fawaz-bizarre-twitter-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Michael’s former lover has claimed the singer was HIV positive and “never wrote his own music” in a bizarre Twitter rant today. Former hairdresser Fadi Fawaz, 46, made a nu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Retirement Speeds Up Cognitive Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/if-you-rest-you-rust-study-finds-early-retirement-may-speed-up-cognitive-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study conducted at Binghamton University finds that an early retirement can accelerate the usual rate of cognitive decline among the elderly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police blew up an innocent man's house. Too bad, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-blew-up-an-innocent-mans-house-in-search-of-an-armed-shoplifter-too-bad-court-rules/ar-AAJzs8t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Cuts Rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/30/fed-decision-interest-rates-cut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors expected the U.S. central bank to cut its benchmark interest rate by a quarter point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi 'Davos in desert': Glitz, smiles, hidden name cards...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-davos-desert-glitz-smiles-hidden-name-cards-092911150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street titans smiled and schmoozed at a Saudi investment conference widely shunned last year over a critic's murder, but as wariness lingers some delegates kept their name cards discreetly out of sight. Thousands of policy-makers and executives from over 30 countries packed into Riyadh'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Spy: ISIS Growing in Strength Despite Killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-10-30/isis-remains-potent-deadly-despite-baghdadis-death-top-spy-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Arab Spring unfolding in the Middle East?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-50219821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seething anger on the streets of Arab countries has the air of revolution, says Jeremy Bowen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top diplomat willing to go public...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2019/10/30/politics/bill-taylor-willing-testify-publicly/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top US diplomat in Ukraine, Bill Taylor, is willing to return to Capitol Hill to testify publicly, according to a source familiar with his thinking, making him a potential key early witness for Democrats as they shift their impeachment inquiry into a public phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer worried Trump will force shutdown to impede impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/schumer-worried-trump-will-force-shutdown-to-impede-impeachment-2019-10-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top Democrat in the U.S. Senate said Tuesday he’s worried that President Donald Trump will shut down the federal government in an effort to impede the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady -- To CHARGERS In 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-brady-focused-only-on-the-present-but-expect-him-to-eye-los-angeles-if-he-leaves-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brady hasn't made any indications he's thinking about the future, but here's why some think L.A. is in play</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority of students want PUNISHMENT for 'offensive' Halloween  costumes...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=13923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the numbers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcript gaps...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nyt-vindman-trump-ukraine-memo-edited-claim-09eeefff-44f9-40c8-8ce8-c6b117337854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ellipses in the transcript have long caused worries among Trump officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAYPAL De-Platforms Conservative Street Artist Sabo, Confiscates Funds for Six Months...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/paypal-de-platforms-conservative-street-artist-sabo-holds-his-funds-for-six-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday evening, the conservative street artist Sabo announced that PayPal had de-platformed him and will be holding his money for six months before refunding him. He warned that this might make him homeless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Biden Edge Over Trump Wanes...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/10/30/bidens-edge-over-trump-wanes-polling-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s pitch for the Democratic presidential nomination has rested in no small part on the idea that he’s the most electable candidate -- that he’ll beat President Donald Trump “like a drum” if given the chance. But polling shows that argument is weakening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Denver Record Broken As Temperatures Plunge To Near Zero...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/10/30/denver-weather-record-cold-temperature-broken-plunge-near-zero-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The temperature in Denver officially dropped to 3 degrees above zero early Wednesday morning. It was cold enough to shatter the previous record low for October 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zh-RiVX88Fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This footage was filmed by Nene Angulo while on his way to work near Broadway &amp; 8th avenue in Downtown San Diego in California. In the footage we can see thi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Slapped With Mere $644,000 Fine Over Cambridge Analytica Breach...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/facebook-pays-644000-uk-fine-over-cambridge-analytica-case-doesnt-admit-fault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has agreed to pay the Information Commissioner's Office a £500,000 fine over its Cambridge Analytica data leak, but did not admit any wrongdoing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Lohan's Bizarre Friendship With MBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-lindsay-lohan-and-mbss-bizarre-friendship </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress’ father says his daughter has a “platonic and respectful” friendship with the unpredictable Saudi royal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studio Chief Summit: All 7 Top Film Executives, 1 Room, Nothing Off-Limits...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/hollywood-reporter-executive-roundtable-7-major-studio-chiefs-1250718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, Warner Bros.' Toby Emmerich, Paramount's Jim Gianopulos, Disney's Alan Horn, Universal's Donna Langley, Sony's Tom Rothman, Amazon's Jennifer Salke and Netflix's Scott Stuber gather to debate streaming service ratings, movie star value, China censorship, onscreen violence and the future of a fraught movie business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once one of America's favorite pastimes, greyhound racing eats dust...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/once-one-of-america-s-favorite-pastimes-greyhound-racing-eats/article_76dd15d2-b3f0-5c7f-9909-82063e453893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Rick Bartley once raced the greyhounds he breeds in Kansas all over the country, but the past decade has slowly stripped him of his livelihood. As state laws</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists discover Aztec tunnel world hidden beneath Mexico City...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1197419/archaeology-latest-Aztec-mexico-tribe-history-mexico-city-scientists-underground-tunnel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARCHAEOLOGISTS have discovered a secret Aztec tunnel world nestled below the busy streets of Mexico’s capital city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael's ex claims singer was HIV positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/george-michael-was-hiv-claims-20755151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fadi Fawaz's Twitter account has claimed George Michael was HIV positive in a string of explosive early morning posts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby born in space 'could become real-life Superman...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/10/30/babies-born-in-space-could-become-a-real-life-superman-11003387/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A space society run by a billionaire and a former Lib Dem MP hopes to change society forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackles rise as Chicago teachers strike drags into day 9...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/21204993c556437db1bc91846423ad5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Chicago's mayor on Tuesday accused leaders of the city's powerful teachers union of using its "political agenda" to hold up a contract agreement to end a strike that will keep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulvaney left in dark on al-Baghdadi operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/mulvaney-was-left-dark-al-baghdadi-operation-n1073731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extraordinary move by Trump to leave out his chief of staff suggests that Mulvaney is increasingly sidelined inside the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man seen falling while livestreaming climb up Mt. Fuji on YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-10-30/japan-livestream-fall-mount-fuji</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Shizuoka, one of two prefectures that include Japan's highest mountain, found a body after receiving calls from some viewers of the livestream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosion in Antarctic sea ice levels may cause another ice age?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/explosion-antarctic-sea-ice-ice-age</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upside-down "rivers" of warm ocean water may be one of the causes of Antarctica's ice shelves breaking up, leading to a rise in sea levels. But a new study suggests an increase in sea ice may lead to a much more devastating change in the Earth's climate — another ice age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specter of Nixon impeachment looming over Republican Party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/468068-specter-of-nixon-impeachment-looming-over-republican-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results of the election over four decades ago haunt lawmakers more than ever today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Texas Hit Hard By Shale Slowdown...</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Energy-General/Texas-Hit-Hard-By-Shale-Slowdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As oil prices continue to remain low, Texas banks are turning away independent oil producers looking for loans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSIVE FIRE SIMI VALLEY</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/10/30/brush-fire-erupts-in-simi-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze broke out before 6 a.m. in the area of the 118 Freeway and Madera Road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRUSTRATION RISES WITH ANOTHER ROUND OF BLACKOUTS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/64fdb75d7e434722bd0229e1b458eebc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A new large wildfire broke out Wednesday in Southern California amid gusty winds, forcing the evacuation of the Ronald Regain Presidential Library and nearby homes. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious black splotches creeping over gleaming Jefferson Memorial, monuments...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-10-30/friend-or-foe-washington-vexed-by-uninvited-visitor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mysterious black splotches are creeping over the gleaming Jefferson Memorial and other historic monuments and buildings in Washington. What's causing the unsightly "biofilm"? Theories abound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein body bore telltale signs of homicide, medical examiner claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/forensic-pathologist-jeffrey-epstein-homicide-suicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The forensic pathologist hired by Jeffrey Epstein’s brother to determine his cause of death revealed to "Fox &amp; Friends" in an exclusive interview Wednesday that the autopsy findings are more consistent with homicidal strangulation than suicidal hanging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Exploring 50-Year Bond...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-treasury-department-exploring-50-124518651.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. Treasury Department expressed continued interest in issuing a 50-year bond, for the first time, as part of efforts to expand its investor base as the budget deficit widens to $1 trillion.The department said it’s also considering issuance of a 20-year bond and an inaugural floating-rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OZ: Hundreds of rare koalas feared dead in 'national tragedy' fire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hundreds-rare-koalas-feared-dead-093756516.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of koalas are feared to have burned to death in an out-of-control bushfire on Australia's east coast, wildlife authorities said Wednesday. A bushfire believed to have been sparked by a lightning strike on Saturday some 248 miles north of Sydney has ravaged an area of over 2,000 hectares</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Stabs Woman Over Fear She Would 'Feed Him To Zombies'...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/10/29/deputies-man-stabs-woman-over-fear-she-would-feed-him-to-zombies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Carolina man allegedly stabbed a woman because he feared she would feed him to zombies, according to investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Cut Expected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6f55192f44e4eaca45217228c8b6ca4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve is set to cut its benchmark interest rate Wednesday for a third time this year to help sustain the U.S. economic expansion in the face of widespread trade...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXTREME WARNING: DEVIL WINDS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191030124630-rxtjo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRE/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Dangerous dry winds forecast to sweep into fire-plagued Los Angeles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across the Board, Scores Drop in Math and Reading for U.S. Students...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/education-news/articles/2019-10-30/across-the-board-scores-drop-in-math-and-reading-for-us-students</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests, elections show LatAm tide turning against pro-market agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-latam-politics-reforms/protests-elections-show-latam-tide-turning-against-pro-market-agenda-idUSKBN1X90WO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the streets of Santiago and Quito to the ballot boxes of Buenos Aires, many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong braces for Halloween havoc as protesters target party district...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hongkong-protests/hong-kong-braces-for-halloween-havoc-as-protesters-target-party-district-idUSKBN1X90TF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Hong Kong pro-democracy protesters, many of whom still wear now-ban...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest person dies at age 123...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-woman-said-worlds-oldest-20756117</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanzilya Bisembeyeva was reportedly born in the late-19th century on March 14, 1896</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unknown 'space station' filmed above San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/unknown-space-station-filmed-above-20734601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver was left questioning what he had captured hovering the sky in California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Worst Month in Office Was One Of Pence's Best...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-worst-month-office-one-080000535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- October has been one of President Donald Trump’s worst months in office -- and one of Mike Pence’s best.As a series of damaging revelations in the House impeachment inquiry weighed on Trump, the vice president was thrust into the spotlight twice as the point-man on major policy issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A.'s $1 Billion Trophy Tower Halted as China Pulls Back...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/l-1-billion-trophy-tower-040000137.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s meant to be one of the crown jewels of downtown Los Angeles’ urban renaissance but now it’s in limbo -- plagued by lawsuits from subcontractors, and victim of an ongoing trade dispute between China and the U.S. and a Beijing crackdown on credit and capital flight.Construction has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Russian submarine test fires intercontinental missile for first time...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191030111619-b8m0y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-DEFENCE/SUBMARINE (TV):New Russian submarine test fires intercontinental missile for first time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forces roundup of horses...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191030103214-m26xd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRE/HORSES (PIX, TV):Raging Los Angeles wildfire forces roundup of horses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican lawmakers vote overwhelmingly to end presidential immunity...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191029231904-1vs02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-POLITICS/ (PIX):Mexican lawmakers vote overwhelmingly to end presidential immunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of pets lost...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Hundreds-of-pets-were-lost-in-the-California-14572942.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The submissions pour in by the second.  Tabby cats lost during an evacuation in the Chalk Hill area of Sonoma County. Two friendly goats, Jean Claude and Spanky, who each respond to "boys!" with a whistle at the end. A black and white Border Collie mix that turned up last Wednesday at Sonoma County Animal Services.  The mishmash of animals - lost and found - comprise just a fraction of those displaced from their owners as the Kincade Fire rages in Northern California. The blaze has already spurred unprecedented blackouts and forced more than 200,000 people to flee their homes, sometimes without warning, causing hundreds of cats, dogs, horses and other livestock to be left behind.  Enter Tai Bruce, the 33-year-old co-creator of Pet Rescue and Reunification, a grass roots Facebook effort to compile posts and notices of missing animals all in one place. Bruce and a team of like-minded volunteers work both online and in the field to identify lost pets, track them down and reunite them with their owners - a tireless effort that will continue long after the fire subsides.  Bruce, a former San Francisco Animal Care &amp; Control reserve officer who now lives in Oregon, said she began the initiative with a few other volunteers during the 2015 Valley Fire , located about 100 miles north of San Francisco. They duplicated their efforts for the similarly-destructive 2017 wildfires in Northern California as well as the deadly 2018 Camp Fire. She says the pattern is similar each time: a flurry of Facebook posts and messages from devastated pet owners, desperately in search of their animals with little idea where to look.  Local shelters, clinics and veterinary offices are a good place to start, Bruce said. But oftentimes, pet owners affected by the sudden evacuation orders possess little identifying information for their animals other...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces serious crunch in search for new DHS leader...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/468009-trump-faces-serious-crunch-in-search-for-new-homeland-security-leader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reelection fight most perilous in decades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trumps-2020-reelection-fight-set-most-perilous-decades-012437315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elections are often described as a horse race but when Donald Trump seeks his second term in 12 months, it's going to look more like a monster car demolition derby. One of the most divisive presidents in US history, fighting impeachment in a Congress paralyzed by partisanship, will go before an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I could see demons': Exorcism in Arkansas...</title>
      <link>https://katv.com/news/local/i-could-see-the-demons-an-exorcism-in-arkansas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;katv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amy Stamatis was left paralyzed below the waist after she plunged from the second story of her Searcy home onto a brick patio in November 2006. The circumstances of the incident were unusual. Stamatis had climbed into an open window and was sitting on the sill when she fell. She insists that she did not jump. But for months beforehand, Stamatis had been struggling with &amp;ldquo;dark thoughts. &amp;rdquo; She had heard voices telling her to kill herself and sought treatment from doctors and psychiatrists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Health Among American Men Reveals Death and Despair...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/state-health-among-american-men-040100395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.Signs of declining health for American men abound in the National Center for Health Statistics latest annual report.Life expectancy at birth for males declined to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families crossing skyrockets to record...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/10/29/1-1-million-migrants-crossed-into-u-s-in-fy2019-nearly-half-million-families/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The apprehension of migrants who crossed the border into the U.S. reached 1.1 million during Fiscal Year 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXTREME WARNING: DEVIL WINDS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/getty-fire-e2-80-98extreme-e2-80-99-warning-issued-ahead-of-hurricane-force-winds/ar-AAJyr5v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tick bite led to former senator's death. Here's what is known about virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-tick-bite-led-to-former-senators-death-heres-what-is-known-about-the-virus/ar-AAJwkbJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel tariffs were supposed to save industry. They made things worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/trumps-steel-tariffs-were-supposed-to-save-the-industry-they-made-things-worse/ar-AAJy5Ro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump assumes Obama's mantle as the 'king of debt'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/467825-trump-assumes-obamas-mantle-as-the-king-of-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US national debt at $22 trillion has reached 100 percent of our GDP for the first time in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy upholds sentencing of Navy SEAL for posing with corpse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0af0e8bedab43d892d60bcc7d7fec72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — The U.S. chief of naval operations on Tuesday denied a request for clemency and upheld a military jury's sentence that will reduce the rank of a decorated Navy SEAL convicted of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVIE OF THE YEAR:  Scorsese, De Niro and Pacino on time and 'IRISHMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b4ff3ea3207e41a3bef34393223f3a83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — They come into the room not like the moveable Mount Rushmore that they are but like three old friends, energized by being in each other's company. They are chatting about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration official says US-Mexico border crisis not over...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b923da1cb2254ad59846a033dd670be7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A top U.S. Border Patrol official has a warning: The crisis at the U.S.-Mexico border is not over. Even though crossings have been down over the past few months and news of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRUSTRATION RISES WITH ANOTHER ROUND OF BLACKOUTS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91e853cb78654387becd90e1bf6bb486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN RAFAEL, Calif. (AP) — With no electricity for the fourth straight day Tuesday, chef and caterer Jane Sykes realized she would have to throw out $1,000 worth of food, including trays of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit ballot: UK lawmakers back December 12 election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ff4178638ac407c8dfe5597f81b6c36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britons will be heading out to vote in the dark days of December after the House of Commons on Tuesday backed an early national vote that could break the country's political impasse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House fires back...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7627521/Democrats-publish-resolution-stage-impeachment-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House blasted the Democrats' resolution that outlines the next steps in the impeachment inquiry as 'an illegitimate sham' that lacks 'any due process' for Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Spacey's sex battery case dropped because anonymous accuser died...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7627513/Los-Angeles-prosecutors-reject-Kevin-Spacey-sex-battery-case.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles County District Attorney's office said on Tuesday they were rejecting a sexual battery case against Kevin Spacey because the accuser has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian feminist's transgender talk stirs uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-50214341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests are planned for the talk by the feminist with controversial trans views.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says top replacement also killed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-baghdadis-top-replacement-killed-143811863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Just confirmed that Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi's number one replacement has been terminated by American troops. Most likely would have taken the top spot - Now he is also Dead!" Trump tweeted. Trump did not identify the person or give more detail on how he was killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Economy Might Not Sway 2020 Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/why-the-economy-might-not-sway-2020-voters/ar-AAJvIPK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New procedures unveiled...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-unveil-procedures-for-trumps-impeachment-inquiry-rebutting-gop-attacks/ar-AAJy7it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON! UK set for third election in four years to try to break Brexit gridlock...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/29/brexit-uk-lawmakers-agree-to-hold-december-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British people will vote in the month of December for the first time since 1923.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How millennials are changing funerals
...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20191028-the-high-tech-start-ups-taking-on-frances-funeral-providers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As societies age, death will be a growth business. Now young French entrepreneurs are introducing new services to the traditionally conservative industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans defend key witness from attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/29/republicans-defend-impeachment-witness-vindman-061057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT: House resolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/read-full-text-house-resolution-trump-impeachment-process-n1073481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Intelligence Committee will continue to take the lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Dems alarmed: 'Extremely disturbing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/extremely-disturbing-top-dems-alarmed-over-vindman-s-testimony-trump-n1073371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman, the top Ukraine expert on the National Security Council, was set to testify he was on the July phone call between Trump and Ukraine’s leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY surrenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/sony-surrenders-in-the-streaming-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony to Shut Down PlayStation Vue Live Streaming Service</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanese prime minister quits amid anti-govt protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d17c97c531e4c5eb60215c5bd733858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Lebanon's prime minister resigned Tuesday, bowing to one of the central demands of anti-government demonstrators shortly after baton-wielding Hezbollah supporters rampaged through...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON spends big to remake Seattle's liberal City Council...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/434dc49c048545e682e260b5ad564961</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Brian Sweeney has a long list of complaints about Amazon, from the way it treats warehouse workers to the low taxes it pays and its effort to win concessions from cities to bring in...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
