<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Former MVP QB Cam Newton signs 1-year deal to join PATRIOTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/it-s-official-cam-newton-signs-1-year-deal-to-join-patriots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cam Newton has been without a NFL home since March. That finally changed Sunday night. The 2015 MVP quarterback has agreed to terms on a one-year deal to join coach Bill Belichick and the New England Patriots, NFL Network Insider Ian Rapoport reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers will lose paid sick leave if they travel to states with high infections... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8469051/New-Yorkers-lose-sick-leave-benefits-travel-states-high-COVID-19-infection-rates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers will lose their paid sick leave benefits for voluntarily traveling to states which have a COVID-19 positive test rate of 10 per cent or more under an order made by Gov. Andrew Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From sleepy to senile: Inside  campaign's effort to rebrand Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-campaign-biden-branding-43b2c6a5-3a06-4b20-b18f-38429b0faf28.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's aides say it will be harder to make Biden widely despised than it was with Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil has record week for virus cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-record-week-virus-cases-005920593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil had its worst week yet of the coronavirus pandemic in terms of new cases, registering 259,105 infections in the seven days through Sunday, according to health ministry figures. Brazil, the country with the second-highest number of infections and deaths worldwide after the United States, has struggled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears worse to come...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5a06549049a5471d510ddde7188eeae9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The world surpassed two sobering coronavirus milestones Sunday -- 500,000 confirmed deaths, 10 million confirmed cases -- and hit another high mark for daily new infections as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spies and Commandos Warned Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/spies-and-commandos-warned-months-ago-of-russian-bounties-on-u-s-troops/ar-BB164Uci?li=BBnb4R7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX GOV:  Has taken very dangerous turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mike-pence-in-dallas-as-gov-abbott-says-covid-19-has-taken-very-dangerous-turn-in-texas/ar-BB164Lm2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLY 5% SAY THINGS GOING 'VERY WELL'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/only-5-25-of-americans-in-survey-say-things-are-going-very-well/ar-BB164UX2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB CEO: 'Travel will never, ever go back to the way it was'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/airbnb-travel-coronavirus-3f7ac17c-89d7-4ba6-9b5b-8905e4aa888a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Chesky tells Axios in an interview that global travel may never fully recover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working-class white women turning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/working-class-white-women-turning-164806378.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, Trump held the support of a key group — white women without college degrees. This spring, they've turned against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House denies knowledge...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200628131939-u3umc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AFGHANISTAN/RUSSIA:Trump denies being told about Russian bounties to kill U.S. troops in Afghanistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi takes step toward dropping rebel image from flag...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1d4969cb533fb6ab7fe381fb5855c256</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — Mississippi lawmakers voted Sunday to surrender the Confederate battle emblem from the state flag more than a century after white supremacist legislators adopted the design a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMPAIGN SCRAMBLES TO BOOST REELECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Analysis-Trump-campaign-scrambles-to-boost-15372432.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump and his campaign team are grappling with how to resuscitate his imperiled reelection effort amid a wave of polling that shows him trailing presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden and losing traction even among core constituencies.  Some Trump advisers and allies are privately pushing for sweeping changes to the campaign, including the idea of a major staff shake-up and trying to convince the president to be more disciplined in his message and behavior.  But so far, the campaign has settled only on incremental changes - such as hiring and elevating several operatives who worked on Trump's upset victory in 2016 - and has yet to settle on a clear message for his reelection. Campaign officials and other advisers are also still struggling with how to best focus their attacks on Biden, which so far have been scattershot and have failed to curb his rise among voters.  And then there's Trump himself, who has derailed his team's desired themes on an almost daily basis - deploying racist rhetoric and mounting incendiary attacks on critics amid a surging coronavirus pandemic, an economic crisis and roiling protests over police brutality.  Numerous national polls show Trump losing significant ground with seniors and among white voters, including those with and without four-year college degrees. He has also slipped among white evangelical voters. According to new New York Times/Siena College polls, Trump is at least slightly behind Biden in six states that he won in 2016 and are pivotal to his reelection path - including Michigan, Pennsylvania and Wisconsin, where he trails by double digits.  "You can't win with these numbers. They're atrocious numbers," said Edward Rollins, co-chairman of the pro-Trump super PAC Great America and the former campaign manager for Ronald Reagan's 1984 reelection...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L'OREAL vows to remove 'whitening' from skin products...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1051036/loreal-remove-whitening-word-skin-products/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L’OREAL has today vowed to remove phrases like ‘whitening’ from their skin products in the wake of racism protests. The beauty company announced it had decided to remove the words…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS OUT OF CONTROL:  'Window closing for us to take action'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/28/politics/hhs-alex-azar-coronavirus-rise-in-cases-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Alex Azar warned Sunday that the "window is closing" for the United States to get the coronavirus pandemic under control, as confirmed cases are surging in a majority of the country and some states are dealing with record numbers of hospitalizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TWEET DISASTER</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/06/28/seniors-protesting-the-village-florida-donald-trump-white-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, Donald Trump loves his white supremacists, because he just gave his stamp of approval on a protest where one of his loudest supporters is screaming "white power."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS PULLS ADS FROM SOCIALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/28/starbucks-latest-company-to-pause-ads-across-social-media-platforms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is the latest company said it will pause advertising on "all social media platforms" and promises to have discussions internally and with media partners and civil rights organizations to stop the spread of hate speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign targeting evangelical voters in bid for November surprise...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/biden-campaign-confident-they-can-peel-evangelical-voters-away-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The battle for the soul of our nation deeply resonates with evangelicals,” says John McCarthy, deputy national political director for the Biden Campaign. “They would be open to Joe Biden’s message as well.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WHITE POWER'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7eea48b80f14474b7057967a9654c4f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Sunday tweeted approvingly of a video showing one of his supporters chanting “white power," a racist slogan associated with white supremacists. He later...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Discovery Leads to Parkinson's Disease Cure in Mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/accidental-discovery-leads-to-parkinsons-disease-cure-in-mice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A discovery by researhers in California has led to the development of a treatment that eliminates symptoms of Parkinson’s disease in mice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half million back in lockdown as Beijing fights new cluster...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-puts-half-a-million-people-in-lockdown-as-beijing-fights-new-cluster/ar-BB163Mig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout in college towns could last 'for next decade'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/we-could-be-feeling-this-for-the-next-decade-virus-hits-college-towns/ar-BB163B6P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Promotes Video of Supporter Yelling 'White Power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-promotes-video-of-his-supporters-yelling-white-power-great-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump praised "great people" on Sunday by sharing a video of one of his supporters shouting "white power"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis council members calling to defund police hire private security...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/minneapolis-city-council-members-private-security-detail-death-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Minneapolis City Council members who have received death threats following their calls to defund the police after the death of George Floyd have been assigned private security details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 2 states reporting decline in new cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/28/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two US states are reporting a decline in new coronavirus cases compared to last week -- Connecticut and Rhode Island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Players To Put Social Justice Statements On Backs Of Jerseys...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/nba-players-will-be-allowed-to-put-social-justice-statements-on-the-back-of-their-jerseys-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move will be made with Nike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead, 1 injured at Breonna Taylor protest park in Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/1-dead-1-injured-breonna-taylor-protest-park-kentucky-n1232351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is a tragedy that this area of peaceful protest is now a crime scene," Louisville Mayor Greg Fischer tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Orders US-Based Christian TV Channel Off Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-cancels-evangelical-christian-channel-god-tv-633054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Council for Cable and Satellite Broadcasting threatened to suspend Shelanu TV’s license, pending a review by the council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAY HOME': County Residents Receive Emergency Text Order...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/06/27/texas-residents-emergency-alert-covid-19-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents in one Texas county received an emergency alert about COVID-19, urging them to stay home and avoid gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>114-year-old monk survives coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jun/28/tilahun-woldemichael-ethiopian-orthodox-monk-said-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ethiopian Orthodox monk whose family says he is 114 years old has survived the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern states report record surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/27/southern-states-coronavirus-surge-342267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has also seen a record number of cases nationwide, according to the latest figures released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church of Scientology tried to silence Danny Masterson's alleged rape victims: suit...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/06/27/church-of-scientology-tried-to-silence-danny-mastersons-alleged-rape-victims-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danny Masterson, who made a wisecracking name for himself on “That ’70s Show,” was arrested and charged June 17 on multiple counts of rape against three women. But it’s not just the actor who is on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simmering doubts in 'God &amp; guns' country...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/god-guns-trump-country-simmering-224335706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mohave County, Arizona, which went 73% for Donald Trump in 2016, some residents are starting to question their support for the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breached rules on banned words...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2020/jun/27/twitter-closes-graham-linehan-account-after-trans-comment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Account of Father Ted creator permanently suspended over ‘hateful conduct rules breach’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incest Secret Behind History's Royal Families...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-ugly-incest-secret-behind-historys-royal-families</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new discovery in Ireland is a seamy reminder of one of history’s oldest secrets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How High School Teacher With Mob Ties Allegedly Bribed DEA... </title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-michael-masecchia-a-buffalo-high-school-teacher-with-mob-ties-allegedly-bribed-a-dea-agent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former DEA agent allegedly received a quarter of a million dollars over a decade to protect Michael Masecchia—an unnoticeable high school teacher with ties to the local mob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Testing Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2020/06/27/coronavirus-testing-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months into the pandemic, demand for coronavirus tests is soaring. Texans report problems with almost every facet of the testing process, starting with the glitching websites and unanswered phone lines used to schedule appointments, and extending to long lags before test results come back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian permanently banned from TWITTER after 'transphobic comments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/27/entertainment/graham-linehan-twitter-removal-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graham Linehan, known for his work with "The IT Crowd" and "Father Ted," has been permanently suspended from Twitter, after allegedly making multiple transphobic comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic-Emptied NYC Hotels Could Become Affordable Housing...</title>
      <link>https://bklyner.com/pandemic-emptied-hotels-could-become-affordable-housing-city-officials-suggest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bklyner.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Potentially thousands of vacant hotel rooms are ripe for conversion into permanent residences, deputy mayor, housing groups and hotel owners agree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence cancels political events...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Pence-cancels-some-political-events-because-of-15371360.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) - Vice President Mike Pence called off campaign events in Florida and Arizona this coming week as the states experience a surge in new coronavirus cases.  Pence will still travel to those states, which have set records for new confirmed infections in recent days, the White House confirmed, saying he will meet with governors and their health teams.  Pence said Friday during a briefing by the White House's coronavirus task force that he would be visiting Florida, Texas and Arizona to receive a "ground report" on spiking cases of COVD-19 across the region. The three states' Republican governors have come under criticism for pushing for aggressive reopening after virus-related lockdowns as cases in the states rise.  Pence is traveling to Dallas on Sunday to attend a "Celebrate Freedom Rally" at First Baptist Church Dallas before meeting with Texas Gov. Greg Abbott. But planned political events later in the week have been pushed off.  On Tuesday, Pence was supposed to address a Trump-Pence campaign "Faith in America" event in Tuscon, Arizona, before meeting Gov. Doug Ducey in Yuma. The campaign event has been postponed.  In Florida on Thursday, Pence was to embark on a bus tour, including an appearance in Lake Wales at an event organized by the pro-Trump group America First Policies billed as the "Great American Comeback tour." The group announced that "out of an abundance of caution at this time, we are postponing the Great American Comeback tour stop in Florida. We look forward to rescheduling soon."  The Sarasota County Republican Party confirmed in a note to supporters that Pence's campaign event along the Gulf Coast of the state was also postponed. He was still set to meet with Gov. Ron DeSantis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House denies knowledge...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jun/27/russia-offered-bounties-afghanistan-militants-killing-us-soldiers-report-outrage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fierce response from top Democrats after US intelligence finding was reportedly briefed to Trump in March, but the White House has yet to act</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BATTLE OVER MARY BOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/lawyer-for-robert-trump-says-mary-trumps-tell-all-book-violates-decades-old-nda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Trump’s attorney Charles Harder said Mary Trump signed a confidentiality agreement that prohibits her from writing a book about the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRUNI:  Biden's Best Veep Pick Is Obvious...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/06/27/opinion/sunday/tammy-duckworth-biden-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She, more than anyone, can get under Trump’s skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Russia Secretly Offered Bounties to Kill US Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-secretly-offered-afghan-militants-bounties-to-kill-troops-us-intelligence-says/ar-BB160RXX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White voters on fence?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-god-guns-and-trump-country-simmering-doubts-about-the-president/ar-BB162YvD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED STATES RISK</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/with-trump-leading-the-way-america-s-coronavirus-failures-exposed-by-record-surge-in-new-infections/ar-BB162SAS?li=BBnb4R7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOS ANGELES 'CRITICAL' </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/la-county-faces-critical-moment-as-coronavirus-cases-keep-surging/ar-BB162AQ5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida reports 9,585 new cases, setting ANOTHER daily record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/florida-reports-9585-new-coronavirus-cases-setting-a-daily-record-in-statewide-surge/ar-BB162LNF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bats carry but don't get sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/coronavirus/coronavirus-covid19-bats-immune-inflammation-bucknell-20200627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These nocturnal flying mammals might hold the key to fighting the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:   3 dead after drinking hand sanitizer; 4th permanently blinded...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/27/us/new-mexico-hand-sanitizer-deaths-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An additional three people are in critical condition. "All seven people are believed to have drunk hand sanitizer containing methanol," health officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duckworth!</title>
      <link>https://twnews.us/us-news/tammy-duckworth-is-biden-s-best-running-mate-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twnews.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen to This Op-EdAudio Recording by AudmTo hear more audio stories from publishers like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android.Whatever his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measures to protect  scale up...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/06/26/politics/donald-trump-coronavirus-protocols/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump appears ready to move on from a still-raging coronavirus pandemic -- skipping the first White House task force briefing in months and moving the event out of the White House itself. But the measures meant to protect him from catching the virus have scaled up dramatically.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
