<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Can Science Cure Death?  Sure Looks Like It...</title>
      <link>https://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:w4O9029kuNwJ:https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a36712084/can-science-cure-death-longevity/+&amp;cd=1&amp;hl=en&amp;ct=clnk&amp;gl=us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;webcache.googleusercontent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first unified theory of aging might be the key to humans living forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE:  Learn to switch off...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210718085456-5znvq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-SURGERY/VATICAN (PIX, TV):Learn to switch off, says pope in first appearance at Vatican after hospital stay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan hits RED SOX player with baseball in wild YANKEE scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/07/17/sports/fan-hits-alex-verdugo-with-baseball-crazy-scene-yankee-stadium-game-rain-delay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Red Sox and Yankees played through a downpour, cameras caught the left fielder screaming toward the left-field seats, with the Red Sox departing the field, claiming he was struck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Radio host Larry Elder not on list of CA recall candidates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-health-government-and-politics-elections-california-c5eedc7f144b2e7baa5745b800e67709</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California on Saturday released a list of 41 candidates running in the recall election targeting Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom that was striking for who wasn't on it: conservative radio talk show host Larry Elder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST COVID AT OLYMPIC VILLAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-2020-tokyo-olympics-health-coronavirus-pandemic-8cef15127de660b161807f1a9fd60ecd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Two athletes living in the Olympic Village have tested positive for COVID-19, the first to do so with the Tokyo Games opening on Friday. Organizers confirmed the positive tests on Sunday and both were listed as non-Japanese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMES:  BOOM OR BUST?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jul/17/boom-or-bust-can-troubled-tokyo-olympics-sparkle-once-the-flame-is-lit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most controversial Olympic Games in 40 years are going ahead despite fierce opposition and somehow could still draw us in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police scramble to deal with deadly road rage during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.police1.com/vehicle-incidents/articles/police-scramble-to-deal-with-deadly-road-rage-during-pandemic-IxON1B6pRtbC8yX3/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.police1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2020, 42 people a month on average were shot and killed or wounded in road rage incidents, according to a recent report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media scramble over, books, books, books...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-media-scramble-at-the-heart-of-trump-book-summer/ar-AAMg5ci?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As multiple books about the last president race to the shelves, juicy revelations have journalists chasing advance copies and looking for the best parts. It’s not bad for sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans  turn to 'critical race theory' in push to win back suburbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/article252807478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are betting the issue will not only energize their base, but help bring back some of the swing suburban voters they lost in the last election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop saves stabbing victim's life using potato chip bag and tape...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-officer-saves-stabbing-victims-life-using-potato-chip-bag-and-tape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The officer used the potato chip bag and the tape to fashion a covering for the wound ahead of paramedics’ arrival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  McAfee died broke after blowing $100 million on 'bizarre' houses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9796559/Once-worth-100M-John-McAfee-broke-died-bars-Spain-friend-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon before his death on June 23, McAfee claimed in a tweet that he had no hidden cash and was worth 'nothing' -- though tax evasion charges gave him ample reason to conceal any assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK says it should not be blamed for America failing to meet vaccine goals...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/facebook-says-it-should-not-be-blamed-us-failing-meet-vaccine-goals-2021-07-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook on Saturday defended itself against U.S. President Joe Biden's assertion that the social media platform is "killing people" by allowing misinformation about coronavirus vaccines to proliferate, saying the facts tell a different story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls Out People Closest to Her Who Failed to Show Up While 'Drowning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/britney-spears-calls-out-people-closest-to-her-who-failed-to-show-up-conservatorship-123498406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears on Friday called out the people closest to her who have failed to show support during the pop star’s conservatorship battle, yet have posted about her situation. “There’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Reilly threatens to sue after media reports 'History Tour' with Donald has low ticket sales...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/563548-oreilly-threatens-to-sue-after-media-reports-history-tour-with-trump-has-low</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News host Bill O’Reilly reportedly threatened to sue a Politico reporter over an article revealing that sales for his “History Tour” with former President Trump were low, citing conversations with venue t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Industry a Mess. Everyone Traveling Anyway...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/07/the-travel-industry-is-a-mess-everyone-is-traveling-anyway.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you think it’s hard to find a good flight, wait till you try to book a rental car or a hotel room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA County sheriff will not enforce new mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/not-backed-science-la-county-192256998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new mask mandate in Los Angeles County, set to go into effect at a minute before midnight Saturday and designed to combat the spread of COVID-19, will not be enforced by the county's top lawman or his deputies. The new mandate from the Los Angeles County Department of Public Health requires people to wear masks indoors, even if they are already vaccinated against the disease. But Los Angeles County Sheriff Alex Villanueva said the order is "not backed by science," and that it contradicts guidelines from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, which does not prescribe masks indoors for most vaccinated people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communists holds mass rally in Havana...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cuban-government-holds-mass-rally-180621123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raul Castro was among thousands who attended a government-organized rally in Havana on Saturday to denounce the U.S. trade embargo and reaffirm their support for Cuba's revolution, a week after unprecedented protests rocked the communist-run country. Government supporters gathered on the city's seafront boulevard before dawn to wave Cuban flags and photos of late revolutionary leader Fidel Castro and his brother Raul. The latter retired as Communist Party leader in April but promised to continue fighting for the revolution as a "foot soldier".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French protests call for 'freedom' amid govt vaccine push...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-government-and-politics-france-d25494f4cf4ca6c6d1464188a89ece6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Over 100,000 people protested across France on Saturday against the government’s latest measures to push people to get vaccinated and curb rising infections by the delta variant of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK'S double-jabbed health minister tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/reckless-boris-johnsons-freedumb-day-24558478</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: As England teeters on the edge of 'freedom day', neither average Brits nor frontline heroes think he is making an informed, or correct, choice - and that he is leading the country back in to a dark place</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  McAfee died broke after blowing $100 million on 'bizarre' houses...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/17/john-mcafee-died-broke-after-blowing-100-million-on-bizarre-houses-author/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Writer Mark Eglinton said the antivirus software creator who hanged himself in prison apparently spent many millions on large mansions and compounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike Lee slip-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/17/updating-cannes-prize-winners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apparently, Spike Lee gave away the name of the Palme D’Or winner by accident ahead of time– “Drive My Car,” aka “Titane,” directed by Julia Ducournau. The secon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie where woman has sex with a car takes Palme d'Or ...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/cannes-film-festival-2021-winners-full-list-1234795027/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Refresh for latest…: The 74th Cannes Film Festival is drawing to a close this evening with winners of the main prizes to be announced shortly from the Grand Théâtre Lumière inside the Palais.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANNES FILM FEST WINNERS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cannes-film-festival-2021-winners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannes 2021: The Palme winner is typically revealed at the end of the ceremony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French protests call for 'freedom' amid govt vaccine push...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/french-protests-call-freedom-amid-government-vaccine-push-2021-07-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands marched across France on Saturday to protest against President Emmanuel Macron's plans to force vaccination of health workers and require a COVID-19 free certificate to enter places such as bars, restaurants and cinemas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PFIZER significantly less effective against Delta'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/for-first-time-since-march-855-new-coronavirus-cases-in-israel-674084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PM Bennett: Vaccine ‘significantly less’ effective against the Delta variant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Will NETFLIX Bet On Beyond Subs?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/netflix-earnings-preview-second-quarter-2021-1234983390/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It won’t just be all about subscribers and financials in Netflix’s quarterly earnings report and call on Tuesday, July 20. Wall Street and Hollywood will also be closely watching for management to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling channel GBNEWS hires Farage to host show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-business-government-and-politics-europe-tv-news-82c8f1b0d593cd5dfa1b0f88f5c4f2fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — GB News, a British news channel that launched last month as a right-leaning alternative to the BBC and Sky News, said Saturday it has recruited populist politician Nigel Farage as a presenter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls Out People Closest to Her Who Failed to Show Up While 'Drowning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/britney-spears-calls-out-people-closest-to-her-who-failed-to-show-up-conservatorship-1234984063/#:~:text=The%20pop%20star%20took%20to,you%20even%20had%20to%20ask.%22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears on Friday called out the people closest to her who have failed to show support during the pop star’s conservatorship battle, yet have posted about her situation. “There’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Floats Restoring Diplomatic Relations With NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mexico-floats-restoring-diplomatic-relations-with-north-korea/ar-AAMgpPR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mexico is seeking to reopen diplomatic and commercial relationships with North Korea, Foreign Minister Marcelo Ebrard said. “We have a position of hands-off around the world, we respect all governments, and we want to reopen the relationship with North Korea as well, like any other country,” Ebrard told reporters on the sidelines of a United Nations Security Council meeting in New York. He acknowledged that North Korea had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Highbrow Return of Nicolas Cage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/07/nicolas-cage-pig-movie-review/619466/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor may have retreated from the mainstream, but his latest film is a reminder that he’s always been a magnetic screen presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boredom link to mental illnesses, brain injuries, dysfunctional behaviors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/boredom-s-link-to-mental-illnesses-brain-injuries-and-dysfunctional-behaviors/ar-AAMgjFd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early research often dismissed the psychological state as temporary and inconsequential. But recent work reveals its troubling connections with various disorders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria investigating 'Havana syndrome' among U.S. envoys...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717120140-sn1o3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ENERGYATTACK/AUSTRIA (PIX):Austria investigating reported 'Havana syndrome' cases among U.S. envoys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to unveil new fighter jet at Moscow air show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-europe-russia-moscow-aec52e68fc3b482dfc6a4132a2bafcbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian aircraft makers say they will present a prospective new fighter jet at a Moscow air show that opens next week. The new warplane hidden under tarpaulin was photographed being towed to a parking spot across an airfield in Zhukovsky, outside Moscow, where the MAKS-2021 International Aviation and Space Salon opens Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Great Salt Lake shrinking fast. Fear turning toxic dustbin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/17/us/great-salt-lake-drought-dying/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Great Salt Lake is also known as America's Dead Sea -- owing to a likeness to its much smaller Middle Eastern counterpart -- but scientists worry the moniker could soon take new meaning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christie Brinkley non-negotiable daily habit: Gratitude...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/17/christie-brinkley-at-67-her-non-negotiable-habit-for-energy-and-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supermodel Christie Brinkley says practicing gratitude is the one non-negotiable habit that she does every day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Co-Founder Says Safety Concern Has Him Quitting Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/ethereum-co-founder-says-safety-concern-has-him-quitting-crypto/ar-AAMeULB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Di Iorio, a co-founder of the Ethereum network, says he’s done with the cryptocurrency world, partially because of personal safety concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future JEEPS will be able to drive underwater, CEO says...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/auto/future-jeeps-will-be-able-to-drive-underwater-ceo-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeep CEO Christian Meunier said the brand may one day sell electric vehicles that can be driven entirely underwater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs 'Just Get' Humans In Ways Other Animals Simply Can't...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-just-get-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man’s best friend has actually evolved to understand human gestures and look to humans for help in a way that no other animals do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba president confronts nation in crisis. Among challenges: 'He's no Fidel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuba-e2-80-99s-president-confronts-a-nation-in-crisis-among-his-challenges-e2-80-98he-e2-80-99s-no-fidel-e2-80-99/ar-AAMge05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters and analysts wonder whether Cuba is at a tipping point that will usher in economic reforms — or simply lead to more repression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can USA 'restore' internet to island?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-restore-internet-cuba-013344937.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's suggestion that Washington bring full internet access to Cuba following government restrictions could break new ground on digital rights but face major technical and geopolitical hurdles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand say 'huge focus' on trans trailblazer...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210717-new-zealand-say-huge-focus-on-trans-trailblazer-at-tokyo-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand say 'huge focus' on trans trailblazer at Tokyo Olympics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe picks through rubble from deluge as death toll soars...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210717-europe-picks-through-rubble-from-deluge-as-death-toll-soars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe picks through rubble from deluge as death toll soars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes awaits Palme d'Or winner after vintage year...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210717-cannes-awaits-palme-d-or-winner-after-vintage-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannes awaits Palme d'Or winner after vintage year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France to require negative test within 24 hours for arrivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210717-france-to-require-24-hour-old-covid-test-for-some-unvaccinated-eu-arrivals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France said Saturday it would require people not fully vaccinated and arriving from some European countries to show a negative Covid test taken within the previous 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music banned on Mykonos in new COVID restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717102637-87qks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GREECE-MYKONOS:Music banned on Greece's Mykonos in new COVID-19 restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany cuts short warmup with allegations of racism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-2020-tokyo-olympics-africa-germany-middle-east-03672d7998b1c1772968b8aa33e80fc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAKAYAMA, Japan (AP) — Germany’s Olympic soccer team walked off the field during a preparation match for the Tokyo Games on Saturday in response to alleged racist abuse from an opposing Honduras player toward German defender Jordan Torunarigha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First covid case inside Olympic Village days before Opening Ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/olympics/first-case-of-coronavirus-infection-inside-olympic-village-confirmed-six-days-before-opening-ceremony/ar-AAMfNa4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first positive coronavirus case has been confirmed inside the Olympics Village just six days before the Opening Ceremony, officials confirmed Saturday, amid growing fears about the spread of the virus during the Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Missing, Scores Dead as Raging Floods Strike Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-floods-954655c9382a9b8c12a230bdd8cd5b3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The death toll from disastrous flooding in Western Europe rose above 150 on Saturday as rescue workers toiled to clear up the devastation revealed by receding water and prevent further damage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
