<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Triples in size...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/california/Redding-Wildfire-Shuts-Down-I-5-Prompts-New-Evacuations-492558421.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delta Fire in Shasta County reported Wednesday afternoon tripled in size overnight Thursday from about 5,000 acres to 15,294 acres, the U.S. Forest Service said. The fast-growing fire was burning in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'In God We Trust' sign offended teachers, so school district came up with fix...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/education/fl-pb-schools-sept-5-board-meeting-20180905-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach County teachers who were offended by an “In God We Trust” sign displayed in front offices prompted the school district on Wednesday to come up with a new way to comply with a recently approved state law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denials...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/searing-trump-op-ed-sets-off-wild-guessing-042811615--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pushing back against explosive reports his own administration is conspiring against him, President Donald Trump lashed out against the anonymous senior official who wrote a New York Times opinion piece claiming to be part of a "resistance" working "from within" to thwart his most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn site launches first sex robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/porn-site-launches-cardi-bot-13201916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like a live cam-girl, Cardi-Bot can perform various acts in real-time, including dancing, shaking, and even twerking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to announce charges against NKoreans for SONY hack, Wannacry attack...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/doj-announce-charges-north-koreans-sony-hack-wannacry/story?id=57643239</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is planning to announce charges Thursday against North Korean nationals who U.S. authorities have accused of being behind the massive hack of Sony in 2014 and the Wannacry ransomware attack lack year. Earlier on Thursday, President Donald Trump praised North Korean ruler Kim...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor shortage looms...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/405231-there-arent-enough-doctors-to-go-around</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead, the answer is twofold. The first problem is a fast-changing demographic shift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tells DISNEY greeters he'll blow place up...</title>
      <link>http://newjersey.news12.com/story/39037079/investigators-new-jersey-man-tells-disney-greeters-hell-blow-place-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newjersey.news12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators in Florida say they have arrested a tourist from New Jersey who told greeters at a Disney World resort that al-Qaida sent him to "blow the place up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's fastest SUV hits 200 mph...</title>
      <link>https://www.motoringresearch.com/car-news/world-fastest-suv-lister-lfp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motoringresearch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet the Lister LFP – a 670 horsepower Jaguar F-Pace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT: JOBLESS CLAIMS 49-YEAR LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-jobless-claims-fell-to-a-49-year-low-last-week-1536237250 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing applications for new unemployment benefits fell at the end of August to a nearly five-decade low, as managers face difficulties finding qualified employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Global stock markets swell ranks of super rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/sep/05/booming-global-stock-markets-swell-ranks-of-the-super-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World population of people in ultra-high-net-worth bracket increased by 12% last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholicism has lost more of its faithful than any other religion...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6136581/Modern-exodus-Catholicism-lost-faithful-religion-U-S.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 13 percent of American adults are former Catholics - representing more departures than any other religion has experienced in the U.S., a survey says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli wall rising near border with Lebanon stokes tensions...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/09/06/israeli-wall-rising-near-border-with-lebanon-stokes-tensions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel is building a massive wall along its northern border, saying the barrier is needed to protect civilians from Hezbollah attacks, but the project has raised tensions with Lebanon, which fears the fence will encroach on its territory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denials...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/09/06/donald-trump-seethes-mike-pence-and-others-deny-writing-lodestar-op-ed/1209608002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fallout continues from extraordinary criticism of President Donald Trump in anonymous New York Times op-ed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebel priest takes on church hierarchy over sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/french-rebel-priest-pierre-vignon-lyon-archbishop-philippe-barbarin-sex-abuse/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rev. Pierre Vignon's online petition calling on his boss to resign over alleged cover-up has garnered 100K signatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wired Icelanders seek to keep remote peninsula digital-free...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/news/world/article/Wired-Icelanders-seek-to-keep-remote-peninsula-13208615.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HORNSTRANDIR, Iceland (AP) — The passenger boat arrives at the bottom of Veidileysufjordur, a short inlet with a long name, to drop off backpackers for a multi-day trek. A weather-beaten group that's completed the trip waits to board, eager to get back to a part of Iceland where they can reconnect with the world via Wi-Fi. By boat, that will take about a half-hour. No roads lead to the Nordic country's northernmost peninsula, a rugged glacial horn that reaches for the Arctic Circle. Making a phone call requires walking up a mountain for a cell signal so weak, clouds seem capable of blocking it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist in New York state Senate race remakes herself...</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/article/news/2018/09/06/democratic-socialist-in-new-york-state-senate-race-remakes-herself/23518865/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julia Salazar, 27, seems well-positioned to become the next insurgent to knock off a Democrat incumbent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltic countries want WALMART to remove Soviet-themed shirts...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Lifestyle/wireStory/lithuania-walmart-remove-soviet-themed-shirts-57640571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Baltic countries have lashed out at retail giant Walmart for using the letters USSR and Soviet Union emblems on T-shirts and other products for sale online, and are demanding that the goods be removed. Estonia, Latvia, and Lithuania were forcibly annexed by Moscow in 1940 and remained...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Ford looks back on career with leather and lace...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f346955e20364e1da90b6ca20aa27d79/Tom-Ford-looks-back-on-his-career-with-leather-and-lace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Gigi Hadid took a dramatic twirl on the runway and Cardi B took a seat on Tom Ford's front row as he kicked off New York Fashion Week with a ready-to-wear collecti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned trucks litter California highway as wildfire rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c6df1fe03b91418b881f48a490863c49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. (AP) — An explosive wildfire closed down dozens of miles of a major California freeway only weeks after a nearby blaze that left neighborhoods in ruins and killed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi hangs on...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5388347/nancy-pelosi-democrats-feminism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And she isn’t going anywhere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reptile cafe slithers into people's hearts...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180906-cambodian-reptile-cafe-slithers-peoples-hearts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Falls Off Cliff Again as Cryptocurrency Slump Deepens...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-falls-off-cliff-again-013510098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrencies dropped sharply for the second time in less than 24 hours, sinking toward a nine-month low amid concern that broader adoption of digital assets will take longer than some anticipated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-administration-white-house-leaks-a5a82efa-d6c8-4209-b616-80f1422eb36c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, Trump carried with him a handwritten list of people suspected to be leakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expats Would Rather Live in Bahrain Than USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/09/06/expats-would-rather-live-in-bahrain-than-the-u-s#gs.dvQNx3U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expats Would Rather Live in Bahrain Than the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Passes New York as Home to Most Ultra-Rich...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hong-kong-passes-york-home-025146172.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York has lost its crown as home to the most ultra-rich people, beaten out by the rising tide of extreme wealth in Asia. Hong Kong surpassed the Big Apple as the city with the highest population of people worth at least $30 million, according to a new report. Tokyo came third, while Paris beat out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears rise, diapers vanish: Iran currency crash causes chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/iran-s-rial-at-worst-rate-yet-amid-collapse-of-nuclear-deal/17820609/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's rial fell to a record low on Wednesday as worried residents of Tehran lined up outside beleaguered moneychangers, part of a staggering 140-percent drop in the currency's value since America pulled out of the nuclear deal only four months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY Initiative Makes Big Record Labels Nervous...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/a-new-spotify-initiative-makes-the-big-record-labels-nervous/17822647/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, the path to stardom in the music industry has usually gone through a major record company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Announces First Death Linked to Fukushima Radiation...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/09/05/644933882/japanese-government-acknowledges-first-fukushima-radiation-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people died as a result of the earthquake and tsunami that hit in 2011, but this is the first death that the government says was caused by radiation. He was a Fukushima worker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran tower leaning, sinking -- and now cracking...</title>
      <link>https://abc7news.com/realestate/san-franciscos-millennium-tower-is-leaning-sinking-and-now-cracking/4157161/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SF'S LEANING TOWER: The sinking Millennium Tower in San Francisco has a new problem after a window cracked on the 36th floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubts shadow push for tax cuts 2.0...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/finance/405278-doubts-shadow-gop-push-for-tax-cuts-20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House GOP leaders on Wednesday insisted they plan to hold a floor vote on a second package of tax cuts this month, even as questions arise about whether such a move is politically smart for Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India supreme court legalizes gay sex in landmark ruling...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180906-landmark-india-ruling-ends-gay-sex-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jubilation...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180906091006-vajs3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA-LGBT/ (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-India throws out ban on gay sex, sparking celebrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS FIT 'SENIOR' LABEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-pm-96a6a0a3-7c7d-4a17-9a23-085a497c0080.html?chunk=0#story0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen’s afternoon take on the most important news of the day. Weekday afternoons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookies place odds...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/05/bookies-place-odds-on-anonymous-white-house-official/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence – and “the field” – lead offshore bookmaking picks as the White House mole behind the anonymous bombshell New York Times op-ed blasting President Trump. Pence …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tweet Gives Author Gender Clue?</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/405244-drudge-labels-anonymous-official-in-nyt-op-ed-a-saboteur-in-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative Drudge Report on Wednesday labeled the person identified as a senior Trump administration official who penned an anonymous op-ed blasting President Trump as a "saboteur inside the White House."&amp;nbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST: FRANTIC HUNT FOR LEAKERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/the-sleeper-cells-have-awoken-trump-and-aides-shaken-by-resistance-op-ed/2018/09/05/ecdf423c-b14b-11e8-a20b-5f4f84429666_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘It’s like the horror movies when everyone realizes the call is coming from inside the house,’ one former White House official said about the anonymous New York Times piece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALL PREVIEW:  Trump again threatens shutdown over border wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-shutdown/in-quick-reversal-trump-threatens-shutdown-over-border-wall-idUSKCN1LL1YN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said on Wednesday he would be willing to shut down the U.S. government if Congress does not provide enough funding for border security, reversing a stance he took a day earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua unrest goes on; U.S. warns of regional crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nicaragua-un/u-s-warns-of-regional-crisis-if-nicaragua-unrest-goes-on-idUSKCN1LL33G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States on Wednesday called on Nicaragua to release all detained students and political prisoners, declaring the country's five months of civil unrest a threat to the region's security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest faces rape charge ahead of papal visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180905-latvian-priest-faces-rape-charge-ahead-papal-visit </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Stock plunges during Jack testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/05/twitter-shares-drop-6percent-during-dorseys-senate-testimony.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter shares were down more than 6 percent as CEO Jack Dorsey testified before the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden rips 'phony populism'... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/05/joe-biden-rips-trump-as-he-campaigns-for-democrat-mikie-sherrill-in-midterms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's speech embodies the middle class-focused message he will take around the country as he tries to boost House, Senate and gubernatorial candidates in tight midterm races this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: 'Unelected Cabal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-journalism/2018/09/05/glenn-greenwald-white-house-coward-behind-anonymous-op-ed-part-of-unelected-cabal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalist Glenn Greenwald says the White House "coward," behind the anonymously written New York Times op-ed is part of an "unelected cabal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admits: Algorithms not always impartial...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-45426407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Dorsey denies censoring conservative voices but accepts the company "made mistakes".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India supreme court set to rule on decriminalizing gay sex...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/indias-supreme-court-set-to-rule-on-decriminalising-homosexuality-11490968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Section 377 of the Indian penal code states that gay acts are banned as "carnal intercourse against the order of nature".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA sued for Autopilot crash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f1ac72f186d45cdbfac7dbb04907b11/Utah-driver-sues-Tesla-after-crashing-in-Autopilot-mode</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A Utah driver who slammed her Tesla into a stopped firetruck at a red light earlier this year while using the vehicle's semi-autonomous function has sued the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four UFOs spotted over Trump golf course...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6136563/Four-UFOs-spotted-flying-presidents-Scottish-golf-course.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A golf fan shared a picture of the mysterious objects, seen in the sky above a Scottish flag at Trump's Turnberry club in Ayshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina running out of tools to lift plunging currency...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/finance/405138-argentina-is-running-out-of-tools-to-lift-its-plunging-currency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They may very well soon be forced to reintroduce exchange controls to put an end to the currency’s damaging free fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC, FOXNEWS feud takes personal turn...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/405174-msnbc-fox-feud-takes-new-turn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The feud between Fox News and MSNBC has taken a personal turn, with Fox News host Tucker Carlson accusing “Meet the Press” moderator Chuck Todd of being aware of NBC’s decision to kill a story by Ronan Farrow detailing sexual harassment charges ag</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Players Richer Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-nfls-best-players-are-getting-richer-than-ever-1536163544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The build-up to this NFL season has consisted of routine concerns and drama. But the biggest theme heading into the season, which opens Thursday night, has been the gamut of historic deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Caused Mysterious Leak At Space Station?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/09/05/644820679/who-caused-the-mysterious-leak-at-the-international-space-station </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We don't reject any theories," said Dmitry Rogozin, the head of Russia's space agency. That includes sabotage, though he suspects it was more likely a "technological error."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISLED CONGRESS...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/09/05/facebook-senate-hearing-sheryl-sandberg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook executive Sheryl Sandberg said the company doesn’t operate in countries where it can't hew to democratic values. That’s just not true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roy Moore sues Sacha Baron Cohen for defamation after prank...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/roy-moore-suing-sacha-baron-cohen-95-million-who-is-america-appearance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Alabama Senate candidate Roy Moore is suing Sacha Baron Cohen For $95 million after appearing on his Showtime series 'Who Is America?'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime-afornia:  Thieves stealing artificial lawns!</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2018/09/05/in-crime-afornia-thieves-are-stealing-artificial-lawns-while-citizens-get-kicked-in-the-grass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s probably one thing you wouldn’t expect to see yanked out at a dental office … the lawn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next progressive underdog to shock Dem establishment?</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/article_cbdf42ec-b503-5eba-8c77-f0ad39eaba10.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOVER, Del. (AP) — As outbreaks of antiestablishment activism roil the Democratic Party nationwide, a veteran Delaware political leader who's never been beaten faces a primary election challenge from an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DEMANDS SOURCE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d62a7c631604b1c9211a2188be4bb39/Trump-blasts-critical-op-ed-from-anonymous-senior-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a striking anonymous broadside, a senior Trump administration official wrote an opinion piece in The New York Times on Wednesday claiming to be part of a grou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORD SLEUTHING...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/speculation-who-is-the-anonymous-white-house-official-behind-the-resistance-op-ed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TREASON?'</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/anonymous-official-says-trump-staff-working-against-amoral-221655371.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top members of Donald Trump's administration are so alarmed by his "erratic" and "amoral" behavior they are actively working to undermine him, an anonymous senior official wrote in The New York Times on Wednesday. The US president responded with a one-word tweet asking if the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUCKER CARLSON: Pretty Good Idea Who Wrote Op-Ed...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/carlson-we-have-a-good-idea-who-wrote-the-anonymous-nyt-op-ed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt for leakers...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6136631/West-Wing-Witch-Hunt-Trump-ordering-investigation-whos-leaking-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is ordering a real witch hunt - this one in the corridors of the West Wing in the wake of Bob Woodward's new book 'Fear' and an anonymous op-ed in the New York Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florence, 1st major hurricane of Atlantic season, to approach US East Coast next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/florence-1st-major-hurricane-of-atlantic-season-to-approach-bermuda-and-us-east-coast-next-week/70005975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body Modifications the Future of Fashion?</title>
      <link>https://news.artnet.com/exhibitions/a-human-body-modification-pop-up-museum-1342946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.artnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"A. Human" is celebrity PR guru Simon Huck's new sci-fi-infused pop up museum, imagining body modifications as the next big fashion trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  SABOTEUR INSIDE WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/05/opinion/trump-white-house-anonymous-resistance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I work for the president but like-minded colleagues and I have vowed to thwart parts of his agenda and his worst inclinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Flamboyant legal pimp running for office under investigation for sex assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/news/politics/2018/09/05/legal-pimp-dennis-hof-under-investigation-sexual-assault/1204499002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation was confirmed on Tuesday of the brothel owner who's a Republican candidate for the state Legislature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with 516 body alterations!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/new-guinness-world-records-2019-13198316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are the new entries from next year's Guinness World Records - from the dog with the world's highest jump to the planet's oldest club DJ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would-be burglar jailed after beaten up by tiny zoo monkeys ...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7184542/bloke-jailed-after-being-beaten-up-by-10-inch-squirrel-monkeys-who-left-him-with-a-broken-leg-after-he-tried-to-steal-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DRUNK man is feared to have been beaten up by a pack of tiny monkeys after breaking into a zoo to try to catch one. John Owen Casford snuck through the gates at Wellington Zoo to snatch one of th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,000-year-old bottle filled with mystery liquid discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1013333/bottle-mystery-liquid-jesus-christ-phanagoria-city-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BOTTLE containing a mystery liquid dating back to the time of Jesus Christ has been hailed as a “unique” discovery after being unearthed in Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP 'TREASON?' TWEET...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2018/09/anonymous-official-cites-trump-amorality-in-ny-times-op-ed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior administration official sounded an alarm Wednesday about President Donald Trump’s “amorality” and “impetuous” leadership style in an unsigned opinion piece published in The New York Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela breaks monthly inflation record, opposition says...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuela-breaks-monthly-inflation-record-opposition-says-211937358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation in Venezuela broke the 200 percent barrier for a single month in August, bringing it to 200,000 percent over the last year, the sidelined opposition-controlled parliament said on Wednesday. Only two months ago, inflation over a single month had passed 100 percent for the first time, opposition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller probe troubling reliance on journalists as sources...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/405242-the-mueller-probes-troubling-reliance-on-journalists-as-sources</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is deeply troubling that the FBI and a federal prosecutor with unlimited resources have relied so much on the Fourth Estate’s secondhand reporting to build its Russia case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How big a price will GOOGLE pay for no-show?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article217857925.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Already frustrated with Silicon Valley, senators sharply criticize Google for declining to attend hearing on foreign influence campaigns. Google wanted to send its general counsel, not Alphabet CEO Larry Page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanderg: 'Alternative Facts' to Combat 'Fake News'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/09/05/facebook-coo-sheryl-sandberg-we-use-alternative-facts-to-combat-misinformation-and-fake-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg said her company would use "alternative facts" to combat what she described as "fake news" and "misinformation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Sexually Assaulted Beaver Hit By Car...</title>
      <link>https://www.tri-cityherald.com/news/local/crime/article217791780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tri-cityherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people were arrested by Kennewick police on Labor Day for having methamphetamine, including a man who allegedly was caught having sexual contact with a wild animal in Columbia Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gwyneth Paltrow's GOOP to pay settlement over unscientific claims about vaginal eggs...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/09/05/gwyneth-paltrows-goop-agrees-to-pay-settlement-over-unscientific-health-claims-about-vaginal-eggs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gwyneth Paltrow's lifestyle company Goop has agreed to pay a settlement after it was accused of making unscientific claims regarding three of its products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: NEW YORK TIMES OP-ED 'GUTLESS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-rages-against-gutless-white-house-official-who-penned-ny-times-op-ed-nameless-staffer-is-probably-failing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls for resignation...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/09/05/white-house-calls-for-anonymous-op-ed-writer-to-resign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeowner tired of kids 'trespassing' installs electric fence near bus stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.wric.com/news/local-news/henrico-county/parents-outraged-after-man-installs-electric-fence-near-henrico-county-bus-stop/1417568503</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wric.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students and parents in a Henrico neighborhood learned shocking news at the start of this school year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport security trays carry more germy than toilets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/airport-security-trays-carry-more-germs-than-toilets-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research finds airport security bins are a hotbed for germs that cause illnesses in humans, such as the flu and the common cold</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS FIT 'SENIOR' LABEL</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-pm-96a6a0a3-7c7d-4a17-9a23-085a497c0080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen’s afternoon take on the most important news of the day. Weekday afternoons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy to Woodward: Release your recordings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-lawyer-rudy-giuliani-to-bob-woodward-release-the-tapes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Let’s see what he has, or is he just a phony Washington icon?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt for leakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/05/politics/trump-woodward-book-leakers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump, showing his outrage over Bob Woodward's explosive new book, is ordering a real witch hunt in the West Wing and throughout his administration, asking loyal aides to help determine who cooperated with the book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped by tapes?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-am-20eb0756-a976-4c59-a57a-1144d6082c5e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-handed rookie linebacker to start  Week 1!</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/seahawks/2018/09/05/shaquem-griffin-seattle-seahawks-week-1-start/1205743002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shaquem Griffin, who had a hand amputated at 4 years old due to a congenital birth defect, will start Sunday for the Seahawks against the Broncos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIMMY VS HYPE: NEW FACE OF NFL?</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/sports/sns-tns-bc-fbn-49ers-garoppolo-sportsplus-20180905-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If he performs within an area code of the hype, quarterback Jimmy Garoppolo soon could be the (extremely handsome) face of the NFL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: 'Reveal yourselves, Trump administration resisters' ...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/765667/reveal-yourselves-trump-administration-resisters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shame on the anonymous "resistance" inside the Trump White House. It's time to come out of the shadows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerome Corsi Subpoenaed By Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/mueller-subpoenas-jerome-corsi-birther-ex-alex-jones-associate-n906756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer for the conspiracy theorist says he believes Corsi will be asked about his contacts with former Trump aide Roger Stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves Fate Hangs In Balance As Redstone Lawsuit Talks Start...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/09/cbs-settlement-talks-national-amusements-corporate-fight-lawsuits-les-moonves-1202457668/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Just weeks before the fall TV season starts, the bitter legal battle between CBS and National Amusements over corporate control and a possible merger with Viacom may be coming to an end.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Loomer thrown out...</title>
      <link>https://bigleaguepolitics.com/watch-laura-loomer-confronts-twitter-jack-at-censorship-hearing-gets-thrown-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bigleaguepolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.7 MAG QUAKE SHAKES JAPAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1013544/japan-earthquake-sapporo-hokkaido-earthquake-ring-of-fire-tsunami-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POWERFUL earthquake has rocked the city of Sapporo in northern Japan just hours after large parts of the south of the country were battered by the biggest typhoon to hit in 25 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Wants 5 More Years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8b436c5bef5a4329bc98a9766f4ea68d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. (AP) — Tom Brady is making one thing clear as he prepares for his 19th NFL season: He doesn't plan to stop playing football anytime soon.        In the ep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Vanilla Ice On Board...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/vanilla-ice-emirates-plane-jfk-sick-cdc-new-york-quarantine-492522041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Vanilla Ice was one of the unlucky passengers on board an Emirates flight from Dubai quarantined for hours at John F. Kennedy Airport Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roy Moore sues Sacha Baron Cohen for defamation after prank...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/roy-moore-sues-sacha-baron-cohen-for-defamation-after-prank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roy Moore is suing Sacha Baron Cohen for defamation after falling for one of the British comedian's pranks for his Showtime series, “Who is America?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florence bans eating on sidewalks, doorsteps at meal times...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e5840292f75d48df83ff73cf89061c75</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The tourist magnet of Florence is cracking down on visitors who eat on sidewalks, doorsteps or driveways during lunch or dinner time.        Mayor Dario Nardell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKE Doubles Down; Releases First Kaepernick TV Ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/watch-colin-kaepernick-in-first-just-do-it-commercial-for-nike-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nike has released its first commercial with former San Francisco 49ers quarterback Colin Kaepernick as its new "Just Do It" spokesman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Turns Neighborhood Into Disaster Zone While Installing New Fiber Optic Tech...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/09/04/fiber-upgrade-mess-dixon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Dixon homeowners are demanding AT&amp;T pay for repairs after a contractor damages lawns and sidewalks during fiber optic infrastructure installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerome Corsi Subpoenaed By Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/05/us/politics/jerome-corsi-subpoena-mueller-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Corsi, a conservative commentator and conspiracy theorist, expects to answer questions about his connections to the former Trump adviser Roger J. Stone Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird hexagon on Saturn way bigger than scientists thought...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/weird-hexagon-saturn-way-bigger-scientists-thought-ncna906541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sharp-cornered structure extends a staggering 180 miles above the ringed planet's cloud tops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie ratchets up AMAZON attacks with 'Stop BEZOS Act'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/sanders-ratchets-up-amazon-attacks-with-stop-bezos-act</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bill aims to encourage large corporations to raise wages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to Investigate Whether Socials 'Intentionally Stifling' Free Speech...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/405177-justice-to-convene-meeting-on-whether-social-media-companies-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Jeff Sessions has scheduled a meeting with state attorneys general in September to discuss a “growing concern” that companies may be “intentionally stifling” the free flow of ideas on their platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE:  147 passengers EVACUATED from plane over CHOLERA fear... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/727784/asl-airlines-france-cholera-evacuation-perpignan-oran-algeria-contagious-boeing-737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside MARVEL's first movie starring a female superhero...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2018/09/05/captain-marvel-ew-cover-brie-larson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more on Captain Marvel, pick up the new issue of Entertainment Weekly on stands Friday, or buy it here now. Don’t forget…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOLVO reveals new robo-taxi in race to autonomy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-volvo-cars-autonomous-robotaxi/volvo-reveals-new-robo-taxi-in-race-to-autonomy-idUSKCN1LL18N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volvo Cars presented a fully electric robo-taxi on Wednesday, as the Geely-owned Swedish company races to meet an ambitious target for driverless vehicle sales with its Uber supply deal on hold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio Calls Clown...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2018/09/marco-rubio-calls-alex-jones-a-clown-dont-touch-me-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Democrats are raping InfoWars!” yelled the conspiracy theorist. “Poor Rubio!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones Crashes Hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/live-alex-jones-crashes-facebook-twitter-hearing-in-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jones confronts censorship head-on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC 'WORLD NEWS' MOST-WATCHED; 8.2M VIEWERS...</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/177768336351/world-news-tonight-with-david-muir-is-americas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘World News Tonight’ Wins 29 Weeks in a Row Among Total Viewers ‘World News Tonight’ Is the Only Evening Broadcast to Grow in Total Viewers and Adults 25-54 Season to Date Season to Date ‘World News...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Trade Deficit With China, EU Hits Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/05/us-trade-deficit-jumps-by-the-most-in-3-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. trade deficit increased to a five-month high in July as exports of soybeans and civilian aircraft declined and imports hit a record high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE no-show...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/09/05/senate-intelligence-committee-shaming-google-alphabet-empty-chair.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senators are upset that Alphabet declined to send either Larry Page or Sundar Pichai to Capitol Hill to attend a hearing on foreign interference in the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Mauled To Death By Pit Bull She Rescued 2 Weeks Earlier!</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/09/04/woman-mauled-to-death-by-a-pit-bull-she-rescued-2-weeks-earlier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 64-year-old Maryland woman was mauled to death by a pit bull she recently rescued, police said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  San Fran launching high-tech tracking of homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/san-francisco-system-to-track-homeless-person-2018-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco's ONE System tracks the history and future needs of every homeless man, woman, and child in the city. The platform represents a mounting effort to combat the city's homeless crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE no-show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a51af23a42fb46059a1dfe5c48e7e50a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on congressional hearings on social media issues (all times local):        7:30 p.m.        Sen. Mark Warner of Virginia is blasting Goo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JFK plane passengers 'seriously ill... coughing with fevers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7184226/emirates-plane-quarantined-at-jfk-after-100-people-suddenly-complain-of-feeling-ill-in-mid-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORE than 100 passengers have reportedly been struck down with a mystery illness on an Emirates flight, with reports of coughing and high fevers. Flight 203 from Dubai was heading to New York when …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantined... </title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/100-people-feeling-sick-board-emirates-flight-reports-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rage after 'MEET THE PRESS' Host Says to 'Fight Back'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/car-ramming-attack-on-dallas-fox-affiliate-after-meet-the-press-host-calls-to-fight-back-against-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man rams truck into studios of Fox affiliate KDFW while shouting about 'high treason'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crew taken away in ambulances...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/emergency-crews-respond-to-reports-of-sick-plane-passengers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergency personnel responded to reports of sick passengers aboard an Emirates flight arriving at JFK Airport on Wednesday morning.  Hazardous materials crews were called to the scene just after 9 a.m. after the plane landed safely.  The New York City mayor's office say the plane has been quarantined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEALTH MYSTERY ON THE EMIRATES</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6134833/Emirates-flight-Dubai-quarantined-JFK-passengers-fell-ill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Emirates Airline flight from Dubai to New York City has been quarantined after nearly 100 passengers reported feeling sick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thirty years at VOGUE: Wintour ready to abdicate?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2018/sep/05/30-years-vogue-anna-wintour-changed-way-world-gets-dressed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her years as editor of American Vogue, Wintour has invented soft power dressing and become as famous as her celebrity cover stars. Lionised and satirised, respected and feared – could she now be ready to abdicate?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
