<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>May lead to higher tax bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/heres-how-rising-inflation-may-lead-to-higher-tax-bills.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As inflation surges, the IRS has boosted federal income tax brackets and other provisions for 2022. However, certain fixed provisions may cause higher bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reversed Paralysis in Mice. Humans Could Be Next...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/injectable-gel-reversed-paralysis-mice-165207056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samuel I. Stupp Laboratory/Northwestern UniversityParalysis might one day be as easy to cure as a single injection of a drug, if some promising new results stand up to scrutiny. Scientists at Northwestern University reversed paralysis in mice with spinal cord injuries by injecting them with a self-assembling gel that can repair tissues.We don’t yet know if the findings, published in the journal Science, will translate over to humans. But for the nearly 1.5 million people in the U.S. living with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter arrested on suspicion of murdering mother...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Bay-Area-reporter-suspected-murder-16613055.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bay Area reporter was arrested Monday on suspicion of stabbing his 74-year-old mother...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK TROOPS DEPLOYED...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/british-troops-deployed-poland-belarus-border-migration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The troops will repair or fortify fencing rather than help police the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum computing problem rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/personal-finance/crypto/cryptocurrency-faces-a-quantum-computing-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two cutting-edge technologies that promise to revolutionize entire fields may be on a collision course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbon footprint of COP26 in Glasgow more than DOUBLE that of previous conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.scotsman.com/news/environment/cop26-carbon-footprint-of-cop26-in-glasgow-more-than-double-that-of-cop25-3453546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scotsman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carbon emissions from the Glasgow climate conference are expected to reach more than double the amount pumped into the atmosphere during the last COP, The Scotsman can reveal, with the event on track to be the most polluting summit of its kind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick bald eagles acting strangely in Maryland prompts investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/sick-bald-eagles-found-in-carroll-county-state-wildlife-officials-investigating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five bald eagles were found acting strangely and seemingly sick in northern Maryland, prompting an investigation by state wildlife officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man threatens to kill Republican congressman who voted for infrastructure bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/long-island-man-arrested-for-threatening-congressman-garbarino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long Island man has been arrested for making a death threat against a Republican congressional member who voted for the $1 trillion infrastructure package, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China slams U.S. democracy as 'game of the rich'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/china-criticizes-us-democracy-while-promoting-xis-growing-power.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remarks come as Chinese President Xi Jinping became the third leader to oversee the politically significant approval of a "historical resolution" this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would nation survive a civil war?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/11/would-america-survive-a-civil-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US army could not withstand an insurgency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKLE HAS EYE ON WHITE HOUSE?</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/meghan-markle-wins-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Meghan bestrides the world like a well-coiffed Colossus, the question isn’t whether she could run. It’s whether she’s already started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astroworld Countdown to Catastrophe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/astroworld-festival-deaths-travis-scott-entertainment-houston-music-5628f631f335ea5d182852ba0116d2cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anticipation had been building for hours, but never more than now, as the red numerals on the countdown clock disappeared and the first synthesized notes vibrated. An image of an eagle in a fireball hovered above the stage, a neon red tunnel appeared and eight towers of flames rose to the sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Drake went to strip club after Festival of Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4050746/drake-went-to-a-strip-club-day-after-deadly-astroworld/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAKE went to a strip club with his crew for a private party a day after the deadly Astroworld disaster – which saw nine killed and around 100 injured, The Sun can confirm. In deleted posts s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Committee seeks criminal charges on Meadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jan-6-committee-criminal-charges-mark-meadows-745bc38c-d99f-44e4-8ab8-aed5258bb055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the Jan. 6 committee's third threat of criminal prosecution made in recent weeks against non-cooperative witnesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Breakdown: Dry Cleaners Out Of Hangers, Silverware Shortage For Restaurants, MORE...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/11/supply-chain-impacts-cleaners-hangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supply chain crisis is impacting local businesses that you may not have expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211112143634-x47sh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPA-MIGRANTS/BELARUS-NATO (URGENT):NATO says it remains vigilant over risk of escalation at Belarus borders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER SENTIMENT 10-YEAR LOW</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-consumer-sentiment-drops-10-150000933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for the New Economy Daily newsletter, follow us @economics and subscribe to our podcast.Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesHong Kong's New Museum Tries to Please Art World — and BeijingFarmers Take on ‘Post-Apocalyptic’ Food CrisisGreece’s Popular Islands Are Crowded — With PlasticU.S. consumer sentiment unexpectedly collapsed in early November as Americans grew increasingly concerned about rising prices and the inflation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaverse Is Ultimate Surveillance Tool...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvnxbm/the-metaverse-is-the-ultimate-surveillance-tool</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silicon Valley is rushing to build the next big thing and people should be skeptical of their intent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba braces for unrest as playwright turned activist rallies protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/nov/12/yunior-garcia-playwright-protest-cuba-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Communist party has banned the planned string of pro-democracy marches, saying they are an overthrow attempt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC SHIFTS GOALS AWAY FROM HERD...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/cdc-shifts-pandemic-goals-away-from-reaching-herd-immunity/ar-AAQCZMW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention have set aside herd immunity as a national target for ending the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does COVID change brain? This scientist finding out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/column-one-does-covid-19-120046575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Maura Boldrini is studying the brains of people who died of COVID-19 to better understand how it causes neurological symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANS URGED TO CANCEL PLANS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-angela-merkel-europe-germany-health-07596d4f924ed4937715a3c5bf5252a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's disease control center is calling for people to cancel or avoid large events and to reduce their contacts as the country's coronavirus infection rate hits the latest in a string of new highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norwegian Undersea Surveillance Network Cables Mysteriously Cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43094/norwegian-undersea-surveillance-network-had-its-cables-mysteriously-cut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ocean observatory off the coast of northern Norway can detect submarine traffic and has been offline since April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THREAT OF MILITARY ESCALATION</title>
      <link>https://www.fltimes.com/news/nation/baltic-states-warn-of-possible-military-escalation-at-belarus-border/article_35a9a17f-288f-5213-929a-f33bca6d8ed4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland — The European Union's Baltic member states warned on Thursday of a possible military escalation in the stand-off about migrants trying to reach the European Union from Belarus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU BORDER SHOWDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10195079/Russia-deploys-paratroopers-Belarus-border-region-amid-fears-conflict.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and Belarus said paratroopers from both countries are taking part in unannounced military drills just 20 miles from the Polish border today, to test the 'combat readiness' of their soldiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants Storm US Embassy in Yemen; Seize Hostages, Equipment...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-backed-militants-storm-us-embassy-in-yemen-seize-hostages-and-equipment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department is working to secure the release of several hostages taken by Iran-backed terrorists after they stormed the U.S. embassy facility in Sana'a, Yemen, U.S. officials told the Washington Free Beacon early Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURGE IN MOST-DOSED STATE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/vermont-highest-vaccination-rate-country-cases-surging/story?id=81090116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why COVID-19 cases are surging in Vermont, which is one of the most vaccinated states in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs trained to fly plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/nov/12/experience-i-taught-two-dogs-to-fly-a-plane</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We had only six weeks to turn the dogs into pilots. Shadow got the bit between his teeth and pulled off a figure of eight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French prosecutors investigate female soldier's alleged rape at Elysee Palace...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20211112-french-prosecutors-investigate-female-soldier-s-alleged-rape-at-%C3%A9lys%C3%A9e-palace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have opened an inquiry into an alleged rape of a female soldier by a fellow serviceman at the French presidential palace in Paris last July, a judicial source told AFP on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once-healthy children face symptoms months after infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-kids-long-haul-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study found that COVID affects one in seven children months after they were infected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murkowski announces re-election bid -- setting up fight with The Don...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/alaska-sen-murkowski-announces-2022-re-election-bid-setting-fight-n1283774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In June, Trump endorsed another Republican for the Senate seat, Kelly Tshibaka, a few months after Murkowski voted to convict him over his involvement in Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRACKDOWNS ON UNVAXXED</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/lifestyle/coronavirus/not-vaccinated-prepare-to-pay-as-governments-ready-crackdowns/ar-AAQCQoZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypersonic Sticker Shock: Weapons $106 Million Each...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/hypersonic-sticker-shock-u-s-weapons-may-run-106-million-each</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hypersonic Sticker Shock: U.S. Weapons May Run $106 Million Each</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Algorithms Blamed in Crash That Paralyzed Aspiring Doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/amazon-com-algorithms-blamed-in-crash-that-paralyzed-aspiring-doctor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Sued Over Crashes by Drivers Rushing to Make Deliveries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney: No more 'Black pastors' in court for Arbery case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/al-sharpton-racial-injustice-georgia-brunswick-crime-d79f3ef1a8cc16ce74adc38f9e6ec0ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK, Ga. (AP) — An attorney for one of the white men standing trial in the death of Ahmaud Arbery told the judge Thursday he doesn't want “any more Black pastors” in the courtroom after the Rev.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asian food' joke puts new focus on Rittenhouse judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/not-good-judge-kyle-rittenhouse-021313125.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Bruce Schroeder, who barred the use of 'victims' at the start of the Illinois teen's trial, was again at the center of controversy on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Britney Spears conservatorship end today?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/britney-spears-conservatorship-friday-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hearing will be the first since her father, Jamie Spears, was removed as a co-conservator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris -- 2024 problem for Biden, Dems...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/581248-kamala-harris-a-2024-problem-for-biden-and-the-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the midterms turn out to be a Democratic repudiation, stick a fork in Joe Biden’s presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation spike gives ammunition to Manchin...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/581237-inflation-spike-gives-ammunition-to-manchin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soaring inflation is shaking up negotiations on Capitol Hill over President Biden’s Build Back Better agenda, giving Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) and other centrists more leverage to push for a smaller reconciliation package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>275 Minutes on Hold: Airline Customer Service Still Can't Keep Up...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/12/275-minutes-on-hold-why-airline-customer-service-still-cant-keep-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Southwest Airlines canceled his family’s flight on Oct. 9, Tyler Reece Maness realized that his best option was to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vets Unlikely Lobbyists in Push to Legalize Psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/11/veterans-have-become-unlikely-lobbyists-in-push-to-legalize-psychedelic-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. APPLE VALLEY,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bolsonaro-Trump Connection Threatening Brazil's Elections...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/11/the-bolsonaro-trump-connection-threatening-brazils-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASÍLIA — The conference hall was packed, with a crowd of more than 1,000 cheering attacks on the press, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami mayor says residents will get MiamiCoin proceeds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cryptocurrency-technology-business-miami-7e0ce407441116c46c4c9457442c3cd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Miami's mayor says he plans to distribute the proceeds from the city's cryptocurrency to residents. Mayor Francis Suarez said Thursday during an interview with a cryptocurrency news site that he was planning to convert the millions of dollars in proceeds MiamiCoin has created into a Bitcoin “dividend.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Earthgrazer' flew 'whopping 186 miles' over 2 states -- then vanished, NASA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/an-earthgrazer-flew-a-whopping-186-miles-over-2-states-then-vanished-nasa-says/article_08f5e81b-fdf1-5a22-85f3-fd536e171861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A space object with an intimidating name — “earthgrazer” — zoomed over Georgia and Alabama this week, offering witnesses a glimpse of something rare, NASA says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUROPE FRESH RECKONING</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/covid-19s-epicentre-again-europe-faces-fresh-reckoning-2021-11-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe has become the epicentre of the pandemic again, prompting some governments to consider re-imposing unpopular lockdowns in the run-up to Christmas and stirring debate over whether vaccines alone are enough to tame COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORWAY REINSTATES CURBS</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/norway-to-reinstate-nationwide-measures-as-virus-cases-surge-pm-01636716609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway will reintroduce nationwide measures to stem surging coronavirus cases, including authorising towns to use health passes, the government announced on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy skies, poor air quality: Port congestion worsening LA pollution?</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-11-hazy-poor-air-quality-port.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It hung over the Los Angeles Basin like a curtain—a veil of stagnant air that blotted out the sun and concealed both the San Gabriel Mountains and the skyscrapers of downtown L.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheetahs fast running to extinction as cub trade thrives...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-11-cheetahs-fast-extinction-cub.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiny, weeks-old cheetah cubs suckled from baby bottles and purred weakly, their condition still dangerously precarious after their rescue from the Horn of Africa's illegal wildlife trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESANTIS: If Biden Keeps Sending Illegals, 'I Will Send Them To Delaware'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/11/11/desantis_if_biden_keeps_sending_illegals_to_florida_i_will_send_them_to_delaware_on_a_bus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) on Wednesday commented on the Biden administration sending illegal immigrants from the border to Florida. "The President has said that basically, they want to even pay reparations to people who came illegally, just think about that," DeSantis said. "You as an American, you get higher gas prices, you get higher grocery bills, you get told basically, to just grin and bear it, someone breaks the law, comes illegally, and they're going to cut him a check for hundreds of thousands of dollars. That is just unbelievable. But that's what we're dealing with." "My view would be, why don't we, if they're going to come here, you know, we'll provide buses," he said. "I will send them to Delaware and do that. I mean, if he's not going to support the border being secured, then he should be able to have everyone there. So, we will do whatever we can in that regard. And we are absolutely going to do everything we can."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax mandates spreading. Italy shows what to expect...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/vaccine-mandates-are-spreading-italy-shows-what-to-expect/ar-AAQCy6Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emerging lesson seems to be that a forceful policy can indeed reap a payoff — at least, a modest one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Travis Scott's old neighborhood, residents rethink whether still hero...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-travis-scott-s-old-neighborhood-residents-rethink-whether-he-is-still-the-hero/ar-AAQBpOE </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beneath mystery of Brady greatness is modest secret: Self-discipline...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/beneath-the-mystery-of-tom-brady-e2-80-99s-greatness-is-a-modest-secret-self-discipline/ar-AAQCthU </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Lukashenko threatens to choke off EU gas supply over border dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/12/belarus-threatens-to-choke-off-eu-gas-supply-over-border-dispute.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Belarus has threatened to cut off its transit of gas supply to Europe if the EU imposes sanctions over a migrant crisis at its western border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S CEO faces calls to resign as backlash mounts over insensitive texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/mcdonald-s-ceo-faces-calls-to-resign-as-backlash-mounts-over-insensitive-texts/article_4df777da-4ad7-51bf-a92a-6b6da89f730e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald’s is facing additional pressure over CEO Chris Kempczinski’s text message exchange with Mayor Lori Lightfoot, in which he appeared to blame the deaths of two Chicago children fatally shot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Matter threatens 'riots' and 'bloodshed' on NYC streets...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/11/blm-leader-hawk-newsome-threatens-riots-after-sit-down-with-eric-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Black Lives Matter leader said there will be “bloodshed” after debating police reform with Eric Adams during a sit-down with the Democrat at Brooklyn Borough Hall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Elite Hand Xi Victory, Paving Way for Indefinite Rule...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/xi-jinping-ensures-future-resolution-144755471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Thursday, only two Communist Party leaders have been powerful enough to rewrite China's history. Xi Jinping is now the third.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Expensive Gasoline in America Close to Record Highs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/most-expensive-gasoline-america-close-210705656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- California’s gasoline prices are only two cents away from hitting an all-time high as fuel prices have soared nationwide just two weeks ahead of the Thanksgiving holiday. Most Read from BloombergWhy Hong Kong Is Building Apartments the Size of Parking SpacesFarmers Take on ‘Post-Apocalyptic’ Food CrisisGreece’s Popular Islands Are Crowded — With PlasticDo Prisons Deserve a Second Chance?Retail prices in the state of California were averaging $4.65 per gallon, just two cents shy of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court temporarily blocks Jan. 6 committee from obtaining Trump records...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-district-of-columbia-capitol-siege-bdc8568b074dfefed8d11b883118dc76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal appeals court on Thursday temporarily blocked the release of White House records sought by a U.S. House committee investigating the Jan. 6 insurrection, granting — for now — a request from former President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN SET TO MAKE PUBLIC RETURN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/16707622/queen-will-attend-remembrance-sunday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen WILL attend Remembrance Sunday commemorations – as she returns to official duties after doctors ordered her to take a break. Her Majesty, 95, has been hoping to lead the Royal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costner's 'YELLOWSTONE' Was Most Watched Anything Last Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/11/11/home-hit-kevin-costners-red-state-comfort-food-yellowstone-was-the-most-watched-anything-last-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Nov. blizzard warning issued in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/first-blizzard-warnings-season-issued-powerful-storm-crosses-country-rcna5250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winter alerts were up Thursday morning for 2 million people across the Northern Plains and the Upper Midwest, which included the first blizzard warnings of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China opens first clinic for trans youth...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nbc-out/out-health-and-wellness/china-opens-first-clinic-transgender-youth-rcna5313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking with its usual practices on LGBTQ rights and issues, China launched its first medical clinic to treat transgender children and adolescents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Nov. blizzard warning issued in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/581183-rare-november-blizzard-warning-issued-in-midwest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people living in the Midwestern region of the U.S. received their first blizzard warnings of the season on Thursday, NBC News reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARSTOOL Portnoy fires back over violent sex allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/11/barstool-sports-dave-portnoy-fires-back-over-alleged-abusive-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barstool Sports founder Dave Portnoy went on an online rant, slamming Business Insider for an explosive “slander piece” on his alleged penchant for abusive and violent sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Putin's 'conveyor belt of torture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/europe/leaked-footage-reveals-prisoners-horrific-rape-and-abuse-inside-notorious-russian-jail/news-story/3849c86596b818dc70be82436f3ad7c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disturbing, leaked footage has revealed the systematic torture, sexual abuse and degradation of prisoners inside a brutal Russian jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venture Capitalist Gave Fake Spy $2M For Hoax CIA Missions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/venture-capitalist-gave-fake-spy-2m-for-hoax-cia-missions/ar-AAQBjOq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To the uber-rich venture capitalist Michael Goguen, it was apparently an enticing idea: a supposed former CIA agent named Matthew Marshall wanted to conduct an “off the books” paramilitary operation in Mexico. According to court papers, Marshall planned to lead assault teams on rescue missions and other expeditions. He just needed Goguen’s help to fund his plans. To further bolster his credibility, Marshall allegedly also claimed that he had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court temporarily blocks Jan. 6 committee from obtaining Trump White House records...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/trump-asks-appeals-court-temporarily-block-release-jan-6-records-n1283732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jan. 6 select committee was scheduled to obtain the records on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bracing For Winter Surge...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/11/newsom-california-winter-covid-19-surge-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has begun positioning equipment and locking in contracts with temporary health care workers in preparation for another possible winter surge of coronavirus cases, Gov. Gavin Newsom said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMERS:  'Not Easy to Put Brakes On Here'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/11/ex-treasury-secretary-biden-behind-the-curve-on-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists having sex in dunes ruining Spanish beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/gran-canaria-tourist-sex-dunes-maspalomas-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maspalomas beach is a nature reserve in Gran Canaria, Spain. But tourists having sex on its famous shifting dunes is destroying the environment, says a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Budget Problems About to Get Worse...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/11/inflation-will-make-government-budget-problems-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of interest on the national debt will soon be a huge chunk of change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists Keep Getting Killed in Mexico After Posting on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epxdq7/mexican-journalists-on-facebook-getting-killed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of the eight journalists murdered in Mexico this year posted on Facebook hours before they were killed. Nearly all of them relied on the platform to publicize their stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rents climbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/11/homes/manhattan-rents-rising/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rents in Manhattan rose at the highest rate in more than a decade in October, with increases especially impacting the upper end of the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia pharmacy incorrectly administers doses to 112 kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/11/virginia-pharmacy-incorrectly-administers-covid-vaccine-to-112-kids-officials-pull-remaining-doses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas investigates whether porn available in schools...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/581157-texas-governor-orders-education-officials-to-investigate-whether</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unclaimed soldier: Thousands of veterans die alone every year...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/veterans/2021-11-11/unclaimed-soldier-veterans-vietnam-era-deaths-3583003.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no requirement for local governments — who are responsible for unclaimed bodies — to report them to any national authority, so there is no official count. But tens of thousands of lives in the United States end this way each year, according to a Washington Post investigation. A striking number — thousands every year — served in the military, especially during the Vietnam War.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>110 now suing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/astroworld-lawsuit-110-plaintiffs-travis-scott-drake-live-nation-1234871896/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Antonio lawyer who filed the first lawsuit last weekend over the tragic events at the Astroworld Festival now says he has over 100 clients who are part of the legal action. “I represe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9th Victim Passes...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/bharti-shahani-astroworld-victims-texas-am-student-dies-what-happened-at-festival/11224693/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bharti Shahani had shown no brain activity while she was hospitalized following the Travis Scott concert.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
