<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Year later, treatment better but doctors 'still flying blind'
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/health/2021/03/14/covid-treatments-have-improved-but-more-rigorous-study-trials-needed/4433230001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Care has improved, but in the last 12 months it's been largely trial and error. That's led to missed opportunities to ease suffering, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Strip sees big crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/the-strip/las-vegas-strip-sees-big-crowds-as-capacity-limits-set-to-ease-2303342/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowds flooded the Strip on Saturday, just two days before casino capacity restrictions increase to 50 percent from 35 percent on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems: No cooperation with Republicans who questioned election...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/house-democrats-draw-line-no-bipartisan-cooperation-republicans-who-questioned-n1261015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the Jan. 6 riot, some Democrats say they simply can't work with anyone who voted against certifying the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus tolls similar despite governors' contrasting actions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/public-health-health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-ron-desantis-889df3826d4da96447b329f524c33047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a year after California Gov. Gavin Newsom ordered the nation’s first statewide shutdown because of the coronavirus, masks remain mandated, indoor dining and other activities are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris may face new lockdown as ICUs fill up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-pakistan-islamabad-coronavirus-pandemic-europe-48d675ad33ab33fff3c78fe74e36dfcc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — Officials say the Paris region may be headed toward a new lockdown as new variants of the virus fill up intensive care units and limited vaccine supplies drag down inoculation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump was supposed to be political Godzilla in exile. Instead, he's adrift...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/14/trump-post-presidency-475733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even allies say the president is lacking an apparatus and direction as he sorts out just what he wants to do in his post-presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Markle preparing bid to be America's first woman President?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9359141/Is-Meghan-Markle-preparing-bid-Americas-woman-President.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One senior Labour figure claimed that Meghan Markle, 39, was networking among senior Democrats with a view to building a campaign and fundraising teams for a tilt at the US Presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Hagler dead at 66; Was 'in ICU fighting effects of vaccine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/boxing/article-9359529/Undisputed-middleweight-champion-Marvelous-Marvin-Hagler-passes-away-unexpectedly-aged-66.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boxing was in mourning on Saturday night after the shock early death of one its all-time greats, Marvin Hagler, at just 66. Hagler was floored officially only once in his incredible brutal career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Woody Allen's Close Friendship With Jeffrey Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-woody-allen-close-friendship-090038127.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyOver the past several weeks, audiences have been watching—and endlessly debating—Allen v. Farrow, the eye-opening HBO docuseries examining Dylan Farrow’s allegation that on Aug. 4, 1992, her adoptive father, Woody Allen, took a 7-year-old Dylan up to the attic of their Connecticut country home and molested her.The film, whose fourth and final chapter airs Sunday, March 14, provides testimony from numerous members of the Farrow-Previn clan, including Dylan, her brother Ronan, and their mother Mia; eyewitness accounts from family friends, neighbors, and hired help; interviews with state and city officials in New York and Connecticut; never-before-heard recordings of phone calls between Woody and Mia; and unearthed documents from the New York and Connecticut investigations into Dylan’s welfare. (Allen and Soon-Yi, who declined to participate in the series, released a written statement through Allen’s sister calling it “a hatchet job riddled with falsehoods” and the abuse claim “categorically false.”)Kirby Dick and Amy Ziering, the filmmaking team behind Allen v. Farrow, feel that the Annie Hall filmmaker, whose behavior toward Dylan was deemed “grossly inappropriate” by a judge in the child-custody trial he lost, shouldn’t merely hide behind a prepared statement. “If you had nothing to hide, and you were really being falsely maligned, wouldn’t you want to speak to journalists?” Ziering told The Daily Beast. “What are you afraid of?”‘Allen v. Farrow’ Filmmakers Call Out Woody Allen: ‘What Are You Afraid Of?’ One thing Woody Allen is not afraid of is defending powerful men who have been credibly accused of sexual misconduct. He’s served as one of Roman Polanski’s most vocal defenders, saying the fugitive filmmaker is “a nice person” who’s “paid his dues” for raping a 13-year-old girl and then fleeing the country, and in the immediate wake of the sexual assault allegations against Harvey Weinstein, accused the movie mogul’s victims of conducting “a witch hunt” against him, before walking it back.And then there’s his friendship with Jeffrey Epstein.It’s not clear when Allen and Epstein first crossed paths, though the two were longtime friends and neighbors on Manhattan’s Upper East Side for years. The director and his wife, Soon-Yi Previn, have been photographed a few times leaving the financier’s townhouse—including in September 2013, five years after Epstein pleaded guilty to child prostitution charges, when a Page Six headline declared: “Woody Allen pals around with child-sex creep.”Epstein “was hugging him and talking close to his ear,” and “had his arm on Woody’s shoulder,” one witness told the tabloid, adding that the pals appeared to enjoy a stroll down Madison Avenue before arriving at Epstein’s seven-story mansion.Diplomat Terje Rød-Larsen joined this walk, along with his friend, filmmaker Håkon Gundersen, who told the Norwegian newspaper DN last October: “I heard that Epstein knew Woody Allen and several other famous film producers. With my background, I thought it was very interesting.”When Allen arrived, Epstein allegedly told Gundersen, “Here you will meet someone else who is also very interested in film.” Gundersen said they all visited Central Park for about two hours that day before heading back to Epstein’s home. (Woody Allen and Soon-Yi did not respond to multiple requests for comment for this story.)Woody Allen spotted chumming up with convicted child-sex creep Jeffrey Epstein http://t.co/ziZl1wkhaP— Page Six (@PageSix) September 24, 2013 Around the same time, Epstein hosted another dinner at his New York home, where he introduced Allen to a connection at MIT. Joi Ito, former director of the MIT Media Lab, “met other influential individuals at meetings with Epstein, including Woody Allen, a senior executive at the Hyatt Corporation, and a former prime minister of Israel,” according to a report commissioned by the school on its ties to Epstein.MIT staff even raised the possibility that Epstein would bring Allen to campus during his October 2013 visit. “Ito expressed concern that inviting Epstein and Woody Allen to campus could create a public relations headache for MIT,” the report states. Apparently citing the Page Six story, Ito tried to dissuade Epstein from bringing Allen. “Since you two were just in the news recently, I wonder if that might be bad,” Ito emailed the financier.REVEALED: We Found Billionaire Pedophile Jeffrey Epstein’s Secret CharityYet Allen apparently had no qualms about consorting with a convicted sex offender who served jail time in 2008 and 2009 for soliciting an underage girl, and appeared to stay close to him until his death. In New York, Epstein was registered as a Level 3 offender, meaning he was a threat to public safety and at high risk for committing similar crimes again.The duo also reportedly had another mutual friend: Allen’s former teenage mistress, model Christina Engelhardt, who was 16 when she began dating the director in 1976. Their secret relationship lasted eight years, according to The Hollywood Reporter. Engelhardt tells The Daily Beast that she worked as a personal assistant for Epstein in the early 1980s, back when he was “only a millionaire” and “wasn’t there yet” when it came to sex-trafficking underage girls. She says she told Epstein that she’d dated Allen, but that the two New Yorkers weren’t friendly yet. Christina Engelhardt Amy Graves/Getty “Nothing surprises me with either one of those men,” Engelhardt offers. “I still am shocked that these very talented people choose these sadistic paths that bring them down. There’s nothing good about it.”Working for Epstein eventually became toxic, and Engelhardt decided to flee to Italy to serve as an assistant (and muse) to director Federico Fellini, whom she says was a lovely man. As for her time with Allen and Epstein, Engelhardt says, “I escaped one monster and ran away from the other.”“Woody is a bad guy,” she adds. “And the documentary really helped open my eyes to just how bad.”In December 2010, Allen attended a lavish dinner at Epstein’s residence toasting Britain’s Prince Andrew, who faces abuse accusations himself from Virginia Roberts Giuffre, an alleged victim of Epstein’s. Other celebrity guests at the soiree included TV journalists Katie Couric, Charlie Rose, and George Stephanopoulos, publicist Peggy Siegal, and comedian Chelsea Handler.Back then, Daily Mail columnist Richard Kay reported that “Andrew was in [a] jolly mood... ­especially when other guests, including Hollywood star Woody Allen, asked him for an invite to” the upcoming nuptials of Prince William and Kate Middleton.Handler recently spoke up about the event, which she described as “weird,” claiming she tagged along with Couric and was seated next to Allen and Soon-Yi. “When we got there I was like, what is this gathering?” Handler recently said on Rob Lowe’s podcast. “We had dinner and it was so awkward and so weird. I was like, what are we doing here? And then I asked Woody Allen how he and Soon-Yi met and that was when I left.”“I really was curious!” Handler added. “I had forgotten for a moment… but as it came out of my mouth, I knew that it was too late.” Allen, however, was apparently amused. “And he loved it, and Soon-Yi, I don’t think she heard it…”Epstein reportedly decorated his New York home with photos of himself and famous friends, including Allen, former President Clinton, and Mohammed bin Salman, the crown prince of Saudi Arabia who ordered the assassination of journalist Jamal Khashoggi.Following Epstein’s suicide whilst awaiting trial on charges of sex-trafficking minors, New York Times scribe James B. Stewart detailed visiting Epstein’s Manhattan mansion in August 2018, and spotting the snapshots with Allen and Clinton. “Displaying photos of celebrities who had been caught up in sex scandals of their own also struck me as odd,” Stewart wrote, adding that Epstein called him a week later and invited him to a Saturday dinner with Allen. The reporter declined.“The overriding impression I took away from our roughly 90-minute conversation was that Mr. Epstein knew an astonishing number of rich, famous and powerful people, and had photos to prove it,” Stewart continued. “He also claimed to know a great deal about these people, some of it potentially damaging or embarrassing, including details about their supposed sexual proclivities and recreational drug use.” Ghislaine Maxwell, Jeffrey Epstein, and Michael Bolton Davidoff Studios Photography Allen wasn't Epstein's only Hollywood connection. The financier was friendly with disgraced film mogul Harvey Weinstein, who allegedly tried to attack a woman in Epstein’s orbit. His rolodex included a host of other celebrities including media investor Ron Burkle and actors like Kevin Spacey, Alec Baldwin, Elizabeth Hurley, and Minnie Driver.As The Daily Beast previously reported, Epstein and Allen also had mutual friends in Paris. Former French politician Jack Lang—who’s publicly defended Allen amid Dylan’s child sexual abuse allegations—claimed he met Epstein in 2012 at a party hosted by Princess Camilla of Bourbon Two Sicilies. The socialite threw the party in Allen’s honor.One victim of Epstein even mentioned meeting Allen in a lawsuit she filed against the financier’s estate. The woman, referred to as Priscilla Doe, says she was a 20-year-old dancer in New York when Epstein began abusing her in 2006 until 2012—including when he was on “work release” at the Palm Beach County lockup.“On one occasion, Jeffrey Epstein forced [Priscilla Doe] to serve hors d’oeuvres at Epstein’s private party with Woody Allen,” Doe’s lawsuit states. “This server’s role was forced upon [her] in order to demean her, frighten her, and impress upon her the need for her to conceal the commercial sex trafficking enterprise he was running.”Asked about Doe’s complaint, her lawyer Brad Edwards said, “Woody was a very close friend of Epstein’s. They hung out quite frequently. I cannot comment beyond that.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call me? US-Turkey reset faces hurdles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-turkey-recep-tayyip-erdogan-russia-d122c8e2c8e547fa998698f03b0bcef6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has toned down his anti-Western and anti-US rhetoric in an apparent effort to reset the rocky relationship with his NATO allies, but so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom created 'deepfake' videos to force rivals off daughter's cheerleading squad...</title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/news/2021/03/pa-woman-created-deepfake-videos-to-force-rivals-off-daughters-cheerleading-squad-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman is also accused of telling the teenagers "to kill themselves," according to the Philadelphia Inquirer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli anti-vaxxers submit ethics complaint to ICC...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/coronavirus-israeli-anti-vaxxers-submit-ethics-complaint-to-icj-report-661925</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the suit's claims of severe side effects and deaths allegedly related to the vaccine, only about 0.25% of Israelis who received the vaccine experienced any side effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic redefines 'public' access to govt meetings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/legislature-state-legislature-coronavirus-pandemic-4d6cf5821b44cb0ce70587305d5e1175</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn’t long ago when a “public meeting” of the city council or state legislature meant the general public could show up to watch and, quite often, speak about proposals and perceived...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Markets be damned!': Fed standing firm on inflation fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210314-markets-be-damned-fed-standing-firm-on-inflation-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Markets be damned!': Fed standing firm on inflation fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breonna Taylor marches turn ugly: LAPD runs over 2 protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9360007/Breonna-Taylor-marches-turn-violent-LAPD-patrol-car-runs-two-protesters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters have clashed with cops and members of the public at marches across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel party braces for drubbing in German state polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210314-merkel-party-braces-for-drubbing-in-german-state-polls-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel party braces for drubbing in German state polls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffers stop showing up to work...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/13/cuomo-staffers-have-stopped-showing-up-to-work-sources-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disillusioned staffers are abandoning embattled Gov. Cuomo, sources said. “I hear that most people aren’t even coming into work, and the offices at the Capitol are empty,” said on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police forcibly break up vigil for slain woman...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kidnapping-crime-arrests-london-europe-b25b5340d30221edf6656c6e2e3c8db0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — London’s police department is under scrutiny for the way officers handled some participants at an unofficial vigil Saturday night for a London woman whose death led to murder charges...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of Andrew Cuomo...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-rise-and-fall-of-andrew-cuomo/ar-BB1eyEW5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last spring, when the coronavirus outbreak was surging in New York, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo’s daily briefings became appointment television for many, as he authoritatively ticked through the latest statistics on infections, hospital beds and deaths. Behind the scenes, Mr. Cuomo was often obsessed with another set of numbers: his ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA deployed to help process children in border facilities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fema-deployed-to-help-process-migrant-children-amid-overcrowding-in-border-facilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Migrant children have reported sleeping in overcrowded conditions and having limited access to showers while in Border Patrol custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon leader says family donation to Biden was 'oversight'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-salt-lake-city-mitt-romney-e905c04166cff85343ddd7f744e30bbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A top leader with The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints said Friday political donations made in his name to several Democratic candidates, including President Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tried to quietly reach out to NKorea. It ignored him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/13/politics/north-korea-biden-administration-outreach/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration launched a behind-the-scenes push last month to reach out to North Korea through multiple channels, a senior administration official has told CNN, but thus far Pyongyang has been unresponsive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC SPRINGS BACK TO LIFE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-new-york-new-york-city-birthdays-coronavirus-pandemic-881a5e0b7878d83275015ccd0f0b42b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Pamela Puchalski still remembers how frightening it felt when the coronavirus upended life in her New York City neighborhood last March. With terrifying swiftness came the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil to $100?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/13/crude-to-100-trader-makes-the-case-for-a-spike-in-oil-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising crude oil prices should benefit several key energy stocks, two traders say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Woman Arrested For Refusing To Cover Up Inside TX Bank...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/12/woman-arrested-for-resisting-trespass-after-not-wearing-mask-inside-texas-bank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was arrested at a bank in Galveston on Thursday after she refused to wear a face mask inside the building, police said. The encounter was captured on an officer's body camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of the wild: Great outdoors is great escape in pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-park-city-hiking-utah-coronavirus-pandemic-b05acc8365c0cbb7cc052d8d5ea69b68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those venturing off the beaten path, be advised — it’s a little crowded out there. By nature’s standards, anyway, as the great outdoors has become the great escape. Hiking trails,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
