<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>A Relationship With Jeffrey Epstein That Bill Gates Now 'Regrets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/12/business/jeffrey-epstein-bill-gates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Gates, the Microsoft co-founder, met several times with Mr. Epstein, a sex criminal, a Times investigation found. Mr. Gates now concedes an error in judgment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN CALLS OUT FAKEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/money/elizabeth-warren-runs-fake-facebook-ad-accusing-zuckerberg-of-supporting-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ad was intended to troll Facebook for allowing the Trump campaign to run a blatantly false ad about Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kurds leader tells USA 'you are leaving us to be slaughtered'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/12/politics/syrian-kurds-us-turkey-military-operation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commander of the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Forces told a senior US diplomat, "You are leaving us to be slaughtered," demanding to know whether the US is going to do anything to protect Syrian Kurds as Turkey continues its military operation targeting America's Kurdish allies in Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Columbus: More states jettison day paying homage to the explorer...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-columbusday-debate-20191012-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON Growing up on the Sandia Pueblo Reservation, New Mexico state Rep. Derrick J. Lente learned the same Christopher Columbus stories in school that his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Stands by 'Great Guy' Giuliani as Probe Deepens...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/465528-trump-defends-crime-buster-giuliani-amid-reported-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Saturday defended his personal attorney Rudy Giuliani as the former New York City mayor faces scrutiny from Congress and a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESTRUCTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/oct/12/california-wildfires-los-angeles-suburbs </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people feared dead and numerous buildings destroyed as 100,000 evacuated but utility restores power to many consumers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLASHES WITH COLLEAGUES...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/shepard-smith-stepping-down-from-fox-news </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news anchor was a frequent target of the president’s ire because of his penchant for calling B.S. on his own network’s pro-Trump spin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are these L.A. people sleeping in pods stacked on top of each other?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-12/when-finding-affordable-housing-in-l-a-means-living-in-a-pod-or-a-bunk-bed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No private bedrooms for these L.A. residents. They choose to live in pods or rooms filled with bunk beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS REVIVAL</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7566157/Turkish-military-incursion-Syria-giving-jihadists-chance-regroup.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a televised statement, senior SDF official Redur Xelil said the Syrian Democratic Forces were continuing to cooperate with the US-led coalition against Islamic State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETWORK EXODUS?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/11/media/shepard-smith-leaving-fox-news/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shepard Smith said on his Friday show that after more than two decades at Fox News, he was stepping down as chief news anchor, and leaving the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA WILDFIRES RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/southern-california-wildfires-burning-unchecked-142637647.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gusting winds fueling a fast-moving wildfire in southern California showed no signs of abating Saturday as a blaze that forced the evacuation of some 100,000 people kept burning out of control. A red flag warning of critical fire danger -- strong winds and very low humidity -- has been extended into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW ORLEANS: 1 killed, 18 sent to hospital after crane collapses at HARD ROCK construction site...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/person-killed-18-hospital-crane-collapses-hard-rock/story?id=66232002 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crane collapsed at the Hard Rock Hotel construction site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting NH church... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.unionleader.com/news/crime/shooting-reported-at-pelham-church/article_47642470-9470-5405-9950-d93052742584.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PELHAM - Multiple ambulances have been called to the scene of a reported shooting at New England Pentecostal Ministries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stressed tourist goes on airport rampage after missing flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/stressed-tourist-goes-airport-rampage-20565186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The furious passenger started throwing around computer equipment at Moscow's Sheremetyevo International Airport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Forster, Resurgent Oscar Nominee From 'JACKIE BROWN,' Dies at 78...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/robert-forster-dead-resurgent-oscar-nominee-jackie-brown-was-78-1218184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'Medium Cool' actor also starred for David Lynch in 'Mulholland Drive' and 'Twin Peaks' after Tarantino resuscitated his career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App on Xi ideology allows data access to 100 million user phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Chinese-app-on-Xi-s-ideology-allows-data-access-14516955.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - The Chinese Communist Party appears to have "superuser" access to all the data on more than 100 million cellphones, owing to a back door in a propaganda app that the government has been promoting aggressively this year.  An examination of the code in the app shows it enables authorities to retrieve every message and photo from a user's phone, browse their contacts and internet history, and activate an audio recorder inside the device, according to a U.S.-funded analysis.  "The [Chinese Communist Party] essentially has access to over 100 million users' data," said Sarah Aoun, director of technology at the Open Technology Fund, an initiative funded by the U.S. government under Radio Free Asia. "That's coming from the top of a government that is expanding its surveillance into citizens' day-to-day lives."  The party, led by Xi Jinping, launched the app, called "Study the Great Nation," in January. The name is a pun because the Chinese word for study - "xuexi" - contains the authoritarian leader's family name.  The app contains news articles and videos, many of them about Xi's activities or his ideology, "Xi Jinping Thought." There is even a sense of competition, with users earning points for reading articles and commenting on them, and a leader board showing how users are faring in quizzes.  The app, which can be downloaded on all types of smartphones including Apple and Android, has been called Xi's high-tech equivalent of Mao Zedong's Little Red Book and was launched amid a campaign to bolster the Communist Party's ideological control over the Chinese population.  It quickly became the most downloaded app in China, including in Apple's app store in the country, with state media reporting in April that it had more than 100 million registered users. Google is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychopaths make best doctors?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/psychopaths-make-best-doctors-because-20561310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychopaths' ruthless nature and emotional detachment are perfect attributes for medicine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan hit by simultaneous typhoon and earthquake...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7565683/Japan-braced-Typhoon-Hagibis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 7.3 million people were placed under non-compulsory evacuation orders and more than 30 people were injured after Typhoon Hagibis hit the south coast on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba Urges Citizens to Eat Banana Peels to Improve 'Humor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/10/11/communism-cuba-urges-citizens-to-eat-banana-peels-to-improve-humor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Rebelde, the website of a state-sponsored radio station in Cuba, published an article urging Cubans to eat banana and plantain peels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Will Top Weekend Again, but 'PARASITE' Is Real Box Office Story...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/gemini-man-will-smith-joker-addams-family-jexi-weekend-box-office-1202757855/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;3rd Update, Saturday AM: w/chart Joker’s second weekend is more powerful than imagined, busting past its low $40M projections to what is now looking like $58.7M, which would make it the best …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey Would Like to Help: He Wants End to Trump Presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/james-comey-would-like-to-help/ar-AAIFVsd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The darker side of orgasm: 'Can make people feel emotionally detached or betrayed'... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7563059/The-darker-orgasm-Climaxing-doesnt-mean-enjoyed-sex.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the US and Canada questioned 726 people about their sexual experiences and found there is such a thing as a 'bad orgasm' and there are various reasons people may not enjoy one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less than four months until voting begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e3e8df51cd37499ebe2af97668178cc9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A Democratic presidential race that had been largely static through the summer has tumbled into a chaotic fall, shaped by unpredictable events and the deepening impeachment...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of phone call now imperiling Trump presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ab67c31d9b3c4acdada93a624052ddc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — There were dozens of ears listening to President Donald Trump's 30-minute phone call with the leader of Ukraine that is at the center of a House impeachment inquiry , and as many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Johnson back in spotlight for 1868 impeachment brush...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9c876cd412a443b79be5f0bd9f569031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president traveled the country, fanning racial animus. He viewed the Congress with disdain. He also tried to undo some of the most important achievements of his predecessor, using executive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador clash site has party clowns, recycling, tear gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3163699112084840882bcb603cb7aa2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — As a military helicopter circled overhead, a volunteer clown in a red rubber nose sang a nonsense song to laughing children outside a public theater. Volunteers inside...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell tightlipped as furor grows...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/465368-mcconnell-tightlipped-as-impeachment-furor-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is keeping a low profile amid the growing impeachment battle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq War whistleblower film has Bush and Blair in its sights...</title>
      <link>https://sg.style.yahoo.com/iraq-war-whistleblower-film-bush-blair-sights-100150825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British whistleblower responsible for a dramatic leak in the run-up to the 2003 invasion of Iraq and now the subject of a Hollywood film hopes it will refocus attention on the flawed evidence that led to war. Ex-spy Katharine Gun -- played by British star Keira Knightley in the new movie "Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead, several injured in Brooklyn club shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/12/4-dead-3-seriously-injured-in-brooklyn-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four men were killed and five others injured in a gruesome mass shooting on Utica Avenue in Brooklyn early Saturday, authorities said. The shooting unfolded just before 7 a.m. at what is believed t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amkara steps up assault on Kurds defying sanctions threats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/turkey-steps-assault-syria-kurds-defying-sanctions-threats-130548288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ras al-Ain (Syria) (AFP) - Ankara stepped up its assault on Kurdish-held border towns in northeastern Syria on Saturday, defying mounting threats of international sanctions, even from Washington. Buoyed by a night of steady advances in the countryside, Turkish troops and their Syrian allies entered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orgy on Yacht Testing Orban's Iron Grip on Hungary...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sex-video-scandal-engulfs-orbans-080529072.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A video of one of Prime Minister Viktor Orban’s allies participating in an orgy on a luxury yacht has presented an unexpected gift to Hungary’s opposition on the eve of local elections. Can it make a difference?In neighboring Austria, a damaging tape was able to bring down a government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accounting Tricks Making Earnings Look Stronger Than They Are...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beware-funny-financials-000005786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- However frothy valuations currently seem to be, optimists can always argue they’re justified by strong earnings. In the past four years, S&amp;P 500 operating earnings per share have grown by nearly 40%.Those numbers, however, may be as airy as the asset prices they support. The U.S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American forces come under Turkish artillery fire in Syria...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191011235548-5tqgx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-USA-BLAST (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-U.S. troops in Syria came under fire from Turkish positions -Pentagon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American forces come under Turkish artillery fire in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/us-troops-syria-turkey-1464727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT CELEBRATES</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/oh-thats-a-shame-trump-gleefully-reacts-to-shepard-smiths-fox-news-exit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was no fan of Fox News anchor Shepard Smith. And the news that Smith is leaving the network seemed to make the president's day. Speaking outside the White House en route to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHEP LEAVES FOX</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-shephard-smith-leaving-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News announced late Friday afternoon the anchor is out after 23 years with the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLLEAGUES STUNNED</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/a-little-stunned-and-a-little-heartbroken-watch-foxs-neil-cavutos-shocked-real-time-reaction-to-shepard-smiths-departure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Neil Cavuto opened his broadcast Friday looking positively shocked by the suddenly-announced departure of long time colleague Shepard Smith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA WILDFIRES RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-10/saddleridge-fire-sylmar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast-moving Saddleridge fire in the San Fernando Valley has charred dozens of homes, closed freeways and forced thousands to flee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Said to Be Under Investigation for Ukraine Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/12/giuliani-is-said-to-be-under-investigation-for-ukraine-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — Federal prosecutors in Manhattan are investigating whether President Trump’s personal lawyer Rudolph W. Giuliani broke lobbying laws in his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man becomes first ever to run marathon in under two hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/othersports/article-7565337/Eliud-Kipchoge-begins-attempt-beat-two-hour-marathon-barrier-Vienna.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid jubilant scenes in Vienna on Saturday morning, Eliud Kipchoge became the first runner to finish a marathon in under two hours. He celebrated with his arms outstretched and waved to crowds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man using oxygen tank died within mins of power shutoff...</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/2019/10/11/pollock-pines-family-says-man-died-when-oxygen-tank-lost-power-during-pge-shut-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLLOCK PINES -- The family of 67-year-old Robert Mardis Sr. believes he would still be alive if PG&amp;E didn't shut off their power this week in Pollock Pines. "He had health issues," Mardis' daughter, Marie Aldea, told FOX40. "He had really bad COPD, which didn't help, and he had congestive heart failure and other health issues, but the power going off and him not being able to get to his oxygen is, I believe, is what did it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CRITIC EXITS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6b9f26f305ba4846b35bd8aa165d9959</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Shepard Smith, whose newscast on Fox News Channel seemed increasingly an outlier on a network dominated by supporters of President Donald Trump, abruptly quit after signing off his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Distances Himself from Rudy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/11/politics/donald-trump-rudy-giuliani-ukraine-fallout/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the career ambassador ousted by President Donald Trump was describing to lawmakers Friday the shadow diplomacy carried out by Rudy Giuliani, the President was across town beginning to doubt his attorney's continued ability to defend him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK cryptocurrency coalition falling apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/11/ebay-drops-out-of-facebook-libra-cryptocurrency-one-week-after-paypal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news comes one week after PayPal announced its withdrawal as government regulators continue to scrutinize the plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House accidentally sends talking points to Dems -- again...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/465457-white-house-accidentally-sends-ukraine-talking-points-to-democrats-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House accidentally sent Democrats a list of talking points related to ex-Ukraine Ambassador Marie Yovanovitch’s Friday House deposition, two sources with knowledge of the email told The Hill, the second time in a month the administration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESAME STREET Muppet Reveals Mother Battling Opioids...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/tv-shows/2019/10/11/sesame-street-fans-react-muppet-karli-mother-opioid-addiction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May, Sesame Street introduced a new character, a green Muppet with yellow hair named Karli, and [...]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
