<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside Sex Workers' Addiction Struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-sex-workers-struggles-with-addiction-i-used-to-be-the-last-person-my-family-would-call</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year where we’ve lost so many porn stars to drugs, sex workers open up to Aurora Snow about their personal battles with addiction—and how they overcame it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley nannies phone police for kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Silicon-Valley-Nannies-Are-Phone-Police-for-Kids-13341649.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - Silicon Valley parents are increasingly obsessed with keeping their children away from screens. Even a little screen time can be so deeply addictive, some parents believe, that it's best if a child neither touches nor sees any of these glittering rectangles. These particular parents, after all, deeply understand their allure. But it's very hard for a working adult in the 21st century to live at home without looking at a phone. And so, as with many aspirations and ideals, it's easier to hire someone to do this. Enter the Silicon Valley nanny, who each day returns to the time before screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF spends $300,000 to register noncitizen voters; 49 sign up...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/SF-spends-300-000-to-register-noncitizen-voters-13340917.php?t=1cc71b89e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco's effort to get noncitizen parents to the ballot box is pretty much a bust the first time out, with only 49 signing up to vote in the Nov. 6 election. Back in July, the city began registering noncitizens - including undocumented immigrants - to vote in school board elections. The program is the first-of-its-kind in California and followed passage of a 2016 San Francisco ballot measure opening school elections to noncitizens who are over the age of 18, city residents and have children under age 19. The city spent about $310,000 setting up the new registration system and encouraging people to sign up. But Donald Trump's election quickly put a damper on enthusiasm for the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Races Shift...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/27/politics/cnn-house-key-races-late-october-update/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 10 days until Election Day, Democrats are poised to make significant gains in the US House, propelled by eye-popping fundraising hauls from Democratic challengers and a clear edge on the generic congressional ballot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims identified...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/10/28/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooting-victims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The identities of the victims that were inside the Tree of Life Synagogue Saturday are now being released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enough is enough: Fed-up Americans crave unity amid violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/enough-enough-fed-americans-crave-unity-amid-violence-130716016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — She flipped through television channels and radio stations, scanning from conservative to liberal media, searching for any sign that the polarized nation had finally reached its tipping point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female motortaxi drivers on rise in Bangkok...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fast-lane-female-motortaxi-drivers-rise-bangkok-014703406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hair pulled back tightly as she lounges on her red scooter, Ar is a rare sight among the male-dominated ranks of Bangkok's motortaxi riders plying their trade on the Thai capital's treacherous roads. A veteran of seven years who works in the bustling On Nut district, Ar is among the thousands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipe bomb suspect was spinning records as FBI closed in...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fbi-uncovered-bomb-suspects-id-dna-fingerprint-clues-052108455--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the hours before his arrest, as federal authorities zeroed in and secretly accumulated evidence, Cesar Sayoc was in his element: spinning classic and Top 40 hits in a nightclub where he'd found work as a DJ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilians Head to Polls in Divisive Presidential Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/brazilians-head-to-polls-in-divisive-presidential-election-1540724400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilians began voting Sunday in a divisive presidential race expected to elect combative ex-army captain Jair Bolsonaro, shifting the country’s politics sharply to the right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 minutes of terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-synagogue-suffers-20-minutes-terror-233158762.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunman Robert Bowers only needed 20 minutes to sow terror at the Tree of Life synagogue in the US city of Pittsburgh, where congregants had gathered peacefully for Shabbat services marking a day of rest. Shortly before 10 am (1400 GMT) the 46-year-old Bowers -- who had penned virulent anti-Semitic messages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT CONDEMNS, CALLS FOR ARMED GUARDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-says-pittsburgh-attack-lays-bare-hate-us-181213687--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MURPHYSBORO, Ill. (AP) — President Donald Trump mourned the dead and forcefully condemned anti-Semitism Saturday after a mass shooting at a Pittsburgh synagogue that left 11 dead. But faced with another national tragedy, he did not long turn his focus away from the midterm elections or himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadliest anti-Semitic attack in US history...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apos-multiple-casualties-apos-shooting-150630876.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunman kills 11 at Pittsburgh synagogue He yelled "All Jews must die" Suspect, named Robert Bowers, charged with hate crimes Donald Trump condemns 'evil anti-Semitic attack' Shooting the 'deadliest anti-Semitic attack in recent US history' A gunman shouting "all Jews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NAZI'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/10/report-pittsburgh-shooter-named-on-police-scanner-is-a-nazi-hated-donald-trump-thought-trump-controlled-by-jews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Cabinet exodus likely after midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/28/trump-cabinet-departures-midterms-943375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two years of already-high turnover, the president is expected to push out or accept the resignations of several more department chiefs by January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOODBATH DURING BRIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/active-shooter-reported-near-pittsburgh-synagogue-n925211</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s a very horrific crime scene. It’s one of the worst that I've seen," Pittsburgh Public Safety Director Wendell Hissrich said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RANTED ON SOCIALS BEFORE ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Suspected-synagogue-shooter-appears-to-have-13342102.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Bowers, who authorities said attacked a Pittsburgh synagogue during Saturday morning services, appears to have targeted Jewish people on a social media account rife with anti-refugee, anti-Semitic and white supremacist posts. The postings, which were listed under Bowers' name on the social media site Gab before the account was deactivated Saturday afternoon, could offer the clearest window into the mind-set of the 46-year-old, who police say stormed Tree of Life synagogue shouting anti-Semitic slurs and firing an assault rifle in an attack that left 11 people dead and six wounded, including one in critical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TRUMP HATER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/synagogue-shooter-disliked-trump-posted-i-did-not-vote-for-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunman was an anti-Semite who called Trump a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ALL JEWS MUST DIE'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6323781/Active-shooter-Pittsburgh-synagogue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman has been named by police sources as 46-year-old Robert Bowers.  He was infuriated by the Hebrew Immigrant Aids Society, according to social media profiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA: WE MUST UNITE AGAINST EVIL...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/IvankaTrump/status/1056238987336171520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“America is stronger than the acts of a depraved bigot and anti-semite. All good Americans stand with the Jewish people to oppose acts of terror &amp;amp; share the horror, disgust &amp;amp; outrage over the massacre in Pittsburgh. We must unite against hatred &amp;amp; evil. God bless those affected”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAUGHTER AT SYNAGOGUE; 11 SHOT DEAD</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/10/27/heavy-police-presence-near-synagogue-in-squirrel-hill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven people have been killed and a number of others injured after a shooting at The Tree of Life Synagogue in Squirrel Hill on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAID JEWS COMMITTING GENOCIDE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/017eca5511ec4834b4406ac8c6b5bb13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — The suspect in the mass shooting at a Pittsburgh synagogue told officers that Jews were committing genocide and that he wanted them all to die, according to a charging document made public early Sunday. Robert Gregory Bowers killed eight men and three women inside the Tree of Life Synagogue on Saturday during worship services before a tactical police team tracked him down and shot him, police said in the affidavit, which contained some previously unreported details on the shooting and the police response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLICE DEPLOY TO JEWISH HUBS...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/nypd-deploys-to-jewish-hubs-following-synagogue-shooting/4565353/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is deploying personnel to Jewish centers and houses of worship throughout New York City following an active shooter situation at a Pittsburgh synagogue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSPECT CHARGED...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181027215337-oe0ot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENNSYLVANIA-SHOOTING/ (UPDATE 10, PIX, TV):UPDATE 10-Gunman targeting Jews kills 11 in Pittsburgh synagogue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETANYAHU 'HEARTBROKEN'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20181027172442-k6fsu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENNSYLVANIA-SHOOTING/ISRAEL (URGENT):Israeli prime minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's 'Tropical Trump' poised to win presidency in dramatic swing right...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/brazils-bolsonaro-poised-win-presidency-dramatic-swing-050850896--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilians fed up with corruption and rising crime are expected to elect former army captain turned politician Jair Bolsonaro as their president as voting begins on Sunday in a turbulent swing to the right in the world's fourth largest democracy. Bolsonaro's sudden rise was propelled by rejection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman stabs ex-husband -- takes SELFIE with him as he bleeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/739120/woman-stabs-ex-husband-selfies-bleeding-siberia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan halts after report of abducted child...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/oct/28/migrant-caravan-abducted-child-report-halts-journe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coordinators of a caravan of several thousand Central American migrants moving through southern Mexico urged its members to rest Sunday. At first the migrants vowed to press on anyway but later changed their minds amid reports that a child had been abducted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's first private rocket fails after launch...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/28/chinas-first-private-rocket-fails-after-launch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING — The first attempt by a private Chinese company to send a rocket into space has failed. Beijing-based Landspace said late Saturday that the first and second stage of its ZQ-1 rocket worked…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer cats: The invasive species in your backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cats-invasive-species-in-your-backyard-cbsn-originals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invasive species can be ruthless. Surprisingly, they can also be adorable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost and Angry...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article220730960.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused mail bomber Cesar Sayoc, a pizza deliveryman and strip club floorman living out of his van, never found success at any of the roles he imagined for himself — until he became a Trump warrior and took center stage as perpetrator of a national crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron All In For Beto...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/lebron-james-wears-beto-orourke-for-senate-hat-to-lakers-game-in-san-antonio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'Rourke is running for U.S. Senate in Texas against Ted Cruz, and LeBron has previous praised the candidate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming dementia crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/opinion/article/We-re-not-prepared-for-the-coming-dementia-crisis-13339813.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of us played the lottery this week in hopes becoming an instant billionaire. The chance of winning was less than 1 in 300 million, yet we all believed we could be "the one." We like to believe that good things will come our way and tend to ignore real threats to our health as we age, even though the chances they will happen are high. Retired Supreme Court justice Sandra Day O'Connor recently disclosed that she has now been diagnosed with probable Alzheimer's disease. At 65, she had a 1 in 10 chance of developing dementia. At 85, her odds increased to 1 in 3. Now we acknowledge with great sadness that the 88-year-old's keen mind will fade away and that she, too, will succumb to the disease, just as her husband did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Decries 'Persecution' of Catholic Church Through Accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pope-decries-persecution-of-catholic-church-through-accusations-1540676324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis told a gathering of bishops from around the world that the Catholic Church is being persecuted through accusations—an apparent allusion to clerical sex-abuse scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Troops Deploy 'Overwhelming Force' Against Iceland's Beer Supplies...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/sailors-marines-beer-iceland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL IN LONDON:  4 JAGUARS arrested after brawl over $64,000 bar tab...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/7599437/nfl-team-bar-brawl-arrests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN football stars were involved in a nightclub brawl over a £50,000 bar bill. The four Jacksonville Jaguars players were arrested by cops at 4am. Trouble flared after they were accused of try…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire tycoon feared dead after helicopter crashes outside soccer stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/football/7599458/leicester-city-fc-owners-helicopter-crashes-stadium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEICESTER City owner Vichai Srivaddhanaprabha’s helicopter crashed in a ball of flames in the club’s stadium car park last night. The eight-seater helicopter belonging to 60-year-old ch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Riling Up the Crazies... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/27/opinion/sunday/donald-trump-fear.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only thing we have to fear is Trump himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seinfeld on Cosby, Roseanne and Tense Times in Comedy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/26/arts/television/jerry-seinfeld-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analytical as ever, the comic has strong opinions about disgraced peers like Cosby. He says the audience is always right (even about his #MeToo joke).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland Votes to Overturn Constitutional Ban on Blasphemy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ireland-set-to-overturn-constitutional-ban-on-blasphemy-1540626649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ireland has voted to remove a reference to blasphemy as a punishable offense from the country’s constitution, paving the way for repeal of a law that criminalizes public utterances judged offensive to religious sensibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Silicon Valley is trying to help Dems capture Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Staying-on-the-sidelines-is-no-longer-an-13342348.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Baer faces a tough task on Election Day: She's a first-time Democratic candidate for Congress vying against a veteran Republican in "one of the swingiest swing districts" in southeastern Florida, as she puts it. Like many in her party, Baer says she benefits from a secret weapon - one that is 2,500 miles away from her slice of the Sunshine State. In Silicon Valley, Baer is among a flood of candidates capitalizing on new apps, activist groups and other organizations that spawned after President Donald Trump's 2016 victory with the explicit goal of triggering a Democratic wave this November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba's private sector grows, but restrictions generate millions for other countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article220690245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access to wholesale markets where they can buy raw materials has been one of the principal demands of Cuban entrepreneurs. Without it, Cubans travel overseas to buy products for their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Neither of this week's attacks will affect midterms...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/27/neither-of-this-weeks-attacks-will-affect-the-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whom can we blame? How will it play in November? For the second time in a week, those were the crass calculations running through the minds of the political class. First it was the pipe bombs and n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol stretched thin...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-border-patrol-commissioner-20181026-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a visit to California crossings Friday, Border Patrol Commissioner Kevin McAleenan warned staff are already spread thin, processing and detention space limited</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail bomb suspect's personality changed radically...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mail-bomb-suspect-personality-changed-radically-225705110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Thirteen years ago, mail bomb suspect Cesar Sayoc traveled the country leading a mixed-race troupe of male exotic dancers — he ran scams and had a temper, but a fellow dancer who is African-American said he never expressed racism or homophobia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida mulls letting felons vote again...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-mulls-letting-felons-vote-again-012629413.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yraida Guanipa did time for drug-related offenses and was released more than 10 years ago, but she still is not eligible to vote in the US midterm elections on November 6. Like we are another class of people, an inferior group that cannot speak," said Guanipa, who is 56. Thwarted by the US Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the machines: Automation reshapes job market...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/business/rise-of-the-machines-automation-reshapes-job-market/comment-page-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Melanie Mason, Los Angeles Times FONTANA — Looking at a map of California on a projector screen, Johannes Moenius, an economics professor at the University of Redlands, hovered his mouse over the Inland Empire, which glowed with a splotch of red pixels. The colored dots signified how susceptible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St sours on Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-sours-silicon-valley-140138671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors for years have seemingly adored technology stocks as much as most people love their smartphones. Some of the hardest hit stocks belong to five companies — Facebook, Apple, Amazon, Netflix and Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCTOBER WITCH:  Long-Anticipated Crash Upon Us?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-10-27/long-anticipated-crash-now-upon-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
