<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Police apologize for 'homeless quilt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox10tv.com/news/mobile_county/mpd-apologizes-for-viral-homeless-quilt-social-media-post/article_540e5ef4-2b29-11ea-a54a-2354dbcf7a47.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOBILE, Ala. (WALA) -- A social media post by Mobile police officers featuring a photo and text that some say mock homeless people has resulted in an apology by MPD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NYC Education official arrested for trying to set up sex with underage boy...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/30/top-doe-official-busted-for-allegedly-trying-to-set-up-sex-with-underage-boy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top deputy to city schools Chancellor Richard Carranza was busted in Wisconsin for allegedly trying to arrange sex with an underage boy online, police and sources told The Post. Department of Edu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind turbine knocks over NYC billboard, crushes car...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/30/bronx-wind-turbines-blades-fly-off-smashing-car-and-billboard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blades from a controversial wind turbine in Baychester flew off the massive structure Monday, crashing to the street below, according to officials. No one was injured — but a car was smashed and a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why retiring at 65 could become thing of the past...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/30/why-retiring-at-65-could-become-a-thing-of-the-past.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For lawmakers, raising the retirement age is a controversial issue. However, new research finds that many workers plan to work past 65. Find out what the new default retirement age could become.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer patient accidentally set on fire during surgery... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/30/cancer-patient-accidentally-set-on-fire-during-surgery-in-romania/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cancer patient went up in flames during surgery in Romania — when doctors used an alcohol-based disinfectant, then touched her with an electric scalpel, according to a new report. The unide…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal marijuana sales may spark Midwest interstate tension...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6c671fbaf84255a84a8f4bdcb2d31ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Retailers legally selling marijuana for the past month in Michigan say they have drawn customers from surrounding Midwestern states where the drug remains illegal and, as Illinois...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor hosting Trump pledges safety for undocumented...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/you-dont-have-to-be-a-citizen-pastor-hosting-trump-pledges-safety-for-undocumented/ar-BBYtnM5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says he would consider Republican for running mate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/30/politics/joe-biden-running-mate-republican/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden told voters in New Hampshire on Monday that he would consider choosing a Republican as a running mate, but added, "I can't think of one right now."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Wakes Up From 7 Month Coma After Family Told To 'Pull The Plug'...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/12/30/woman-wakes-up-from-7-month-coma-after-family-told-to-pull-the-plug/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio woman was in a coma for seven months due to a mysterious illness -- but her and her mother's fight for her survival led to a second chance at life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erik Prince referred to Treasury Dept for possible Venezuela sanctions violations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0641c2b37886a08240d0ba64c9319699</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Erik Prince, a major Republican donor and founder of controversial security firm Blackwater, has been referred to the U.S. Treasury Department for possible sanctions violations tied...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parishioner who gunned down killer says he's no hero... </title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/parishioner-gunned-texas-church-shooter-hero/story?id=67982047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two members of West Freeway Church of Christ were killed in the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spooks no longer tailed by 30 foreign govts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7837767/CIA-faces-crisis-intelligence-gathering-digital-footprints.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some governments no longer see the need to physically follow CIA officers to meetings because facial recognition at airports and general surveillance in those countries is so advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shattered': Inside secret battle to save America's undercover spies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/shattered-inside-the-secret-battle-to-save-americas-undercover-spies-in-the-digital-age-100029026.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When hackers began slipping into computer systems at the Office of Personnel Management in the spring of 2014, no one inside that federal agency could have predicted the potential scale and magnitude of the damage. Over the next six months, those hackers — later identified as working for the Chinese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Sanders healthy enough for 'rigors of presidency'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eecb4c98430c1822a1b2d2ee2e3f9e50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders suffered “modest heart muscle damage" during his October heart attack but has since been doing well and should be able to continue campaigning for president “without limitation,"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With births down, USA had slowest growth rate in century...</title>
      <link>https://www.whio.com/news/national/with-births-down-had-slowest-growth-rate-century/g0r9YAR1cR2veFu8qzod7K/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The past year’s population growth rate in the United States was the slowest in a century due t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Pursuit of Florida Latinos, Dems Fight Socialist Tag...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/usa/pursuit-florida-latinos-democrats-fight-socialist-tag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a tiny studio in the sprawling Miami suburb of Doral, a popular Venezuelan-born radio host recently pressed one of Florida's best-known Democrats on a touchy topic: socialism. "Older voters associated you with socialists," host Julio Cesar Camacho told Andrew Gillum, who narrowly lost a bid for governor last year. Gillum blamed Republicans for preying on "sensitivities" of Latinos in Florida, as Camacho translated his complaint into Spanish for listeners. The conversation wasn't just a rehash of another narrow Democratic loss in the battleground state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA devised way to restrict missiles given to allies...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-cyber-missiles/cia-devised-way-to-restrict-missiles-given-to-allies-researcher-says-idUSKBN1YY1BF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Central Intelligence Agency has devised technology to restrict the use ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY:  The four stages of being attacked by Donald Trump... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/James-Comey-The-four-stages-of-being-attacked-by-14939399.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's it like to be personally and publicly attacked by the president of the United States? Like many others in and out of government, I have some experience. I have also watched friends and former colleagues deal with vicious, repeated assaults. The attacks have interfered with their ability to find work after government service, as even employers who see through the lies fear hiring a "controversial" person or being attacked themselves. It can mean reassuring concerned friends and family, who can't imagine themselves the target of presidential wrath, that you're doing just fine. And it also means avoiding much of social media, because every presidential assault unleashes truly disturbed Trump supporters on platforms such as Facebook and Twitter.  So, it's hard on good people, especially those who don't have savings to fall back on. But the truth is that, in many ways, it is not as hard as you might think, especially as it continues endlessly, leaking power, shrinking its source.  At first, the attack is stunning and rocks your world. Waking up to find the president has tweeted that you are guilty of treason or committed assorted other crimes and are a [insert any one of this president's epithets here] is jarring and disorienting. That's the first stage, but it doesn't last.  The second stage is a kind of numbness, where it doesn't seem quite real that the so-called Leader of the Free World is assailing you by tweet and voice. It is still unsettling, but it is harder to recapture the vertigo of the first assault.  But the longer it goes on, the less it means. In the third stage, the impact diminishes, the power of it shrinks. It no longer feels as though the most powerful human on the planet is after you. It feels as though a strange and slightly sad old guy is yelling at you to get off his lawn, echoed by younger but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypersonic Nuclear Missile Stirs Fears of New Arms Race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-hypersonic-nuclear-missile-stirs-134108603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A new hypersonic nuclear missile that Russia says it has deployed is fueling concerns of a new arms race with the U.S. as the clock ticks down on the expiry of the last treaty limiting the strategic arsenals of the two former Cold War foes.Russia’s first regiment of Avangard missiles was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coping with loss of hospital, rural town realizes: We don't need a hospital...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/coping-with-loss-of-hospital-rural-town-realizes-we-dont-need-a-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been about a year since the hospital in Fort Scott, Kan., closed. The lessons for this community about meeting its residents’ health needs could provide insights for the rest of the country.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019's Worst PR Disasters...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/learned-2019-worst-pr-disasters-150035733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- As a public relations professor, I know a few of my fellow professionals can be counted on to do things that keep my students’ jaws dropping in class each week — and, like 2018, this year was no exception. Here are the five decisions that beat out stiff competition to rank as the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 years in, no sign of Trump's replacement for Obamacare...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/968422ef1e16470c967bebc394fee331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As a candidate for the White House, Donald Trump repeatedly promised that he would “immediately” replace President Barack Obama’s health care law with a plan of his own that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, NKorea Rocketing Toward NYE Deadline...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2019-12-26/5-things-to-watch-for-from-north-korea-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDIAN ANGELS OUT IN FORCE; PATROLLING NEIGHBORHOODS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/amp/ncna1108251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're a visual deterrence," said Curtis Sliwa, who founded the unarmed crime prevention group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie warns against religious bigotry hours after Hasidic Jews are stabbed in NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Bernie-Sanders-warns-against-religious-bigotry-14938755.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa - Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., who had relatives killed by Nazis during the Holocaust, responded Sunday to the latest incident of anti-Semitic terror by wearing a kippah and lifting a blowtorch to light a public menorah on the final night of Hanukkah.  And less than 24 hours after an intruder stabbed five Hasidic Jews at a rabbi's home in New York, the Democratic presidential candidate delivered an urgent speech on a frigid evening in Des Moines, decrying recent attacks against Jews and other minorities.  "We're seeing people being stabbed yesterday in New York City because they were Jewish," Sanders said, calling the assault part of an alarming rise in anti-Semitism, both in the United States and globally.  Sanders added, "If there was ever a time in American history where we say no to religious bigotry, this is the time. If there was ever a time when we say no to divisiveness, this is that moment."  The bundled-up crowd, gathered around a menorah at Brenton Skating Plaza, listened intently as the 78-year-old son of a Jewish immigrant spoke and cheered when he called for unity.  The latest attack in New York, which officials said began after 10 p.m. Saturday in the suburb of Monsey, was called an act of "domestic terrorism" by New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, who linked it to the spate of violence against Jewish people.  Sunday's lighting event was scheduled before the Monsey attack- and was planned to be a low-key stop following a day of campaigning in two states. But it became a rare charged moment for Sanders, who often resists departing from his core stump speech.  Sanders - who has long noted that the family of his late father, Eli Sanders, was "wiped out" during the Nazi occupation of Poland during World War II - mentioned his father, who, he said, "came...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEWORK Lays Off 2,400  -- Bosses Get $18 Million Exit Package...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90448185/wework-laid-off-2400-employees-but-its-execs-just-got-a-potential-extra-18-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of layoffs and a cash crunch has not deterred WeWork from generous exit packages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Scientist Who Gene-Edited Babies Is Sent to Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/30/china/gene-scientist-china-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese scientist who helped create the world's first gene-edited babies has been sentenced to three years in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Public School Students Barred From Returning Until They Get Vaccinations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-vaccinations-seattle-public-school-students-required-to-be-vaccinated-after-outbreaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle Public Schools said roughly 2,000 students need to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KIM COY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be887e8a0bd1c3fc4a6f67bdaa65e492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korean leader Kim Jong Un called for his military and diplomats to prepare unspecified “offensive measures” to protect the country’s security and sovereignty, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin weighs future options as he marks 20 years in power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0dc36e0cdf7e6fa3c5e0d735b4c55197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — As Russian President Vladimir Putin marks two decades in power , he boasts about his achievements but remains coy about his political future — a reticence that fuels wild...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Warns USA Its Middle East Dominance Is Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/iran-warns-us-middle-east-dominance-over-naval-drills-russia-china-1479628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messy primary finally meets election year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d4d2857515d8664d24c5419197d9d327</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The presidential politics calendar turned to 2020 nearly a year ago. This week, the actual date catches up. What we’re watching as the preseason closes and election year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Could 'CATS' Lose? $100 Million?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cats-box-office-hairball-how-much-money-could-tom-hoopers-musical-lose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adaptation of Andrew Lloyd Webber's musical will make a quarter of what "La La Land" and "The Greatest Showman" grossed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In strategic Djibouti, a microcosm of China's growing foothold in Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-strategic-Djibouti-a-microcosm-of-China-s-14938761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DJIBOUTI - Above ground in this tiny but strategically located country, signs of China's presence are everywhere.  Chinese entities have financed and built Africa's biggest port, a railway to Ethiopia and the country's first overseas naval base here. Under the sea, they are building a cable that will transmit data across a region that spans from Kenya to Yemen. The cable will connect to an Internet hub housing servers mostly run by China's state-owned telecom companies.  Beijing's extensive investments in Djibouti are a microcosm of how China has rapidly gained a strategic foothold across the continent. Western countries, including Africa's former colonizers, for decades have used hefty aid packages to leverage trade and security deals, but Chinese-financed projects have brought huge infrastructural development in less than a generation.  The construction is fueled mostly by lending from China's state-run banks. Spindles of Chinese-paved roads have unfurled across the continent, along with huge bridges, new airports, dams and power plants as part of Chinese President Xi Jinping's 152-country Belt and Road Initiative.  Overall, Chinese companies have invested twice as much money between 2014 and 2018 in African countries as American companies, spending $72.2 billion, according to an analysis by Ernst &amp; Young.  "The Chinese are thinking far into the long-term in Djibouti and Africa in general," said David Shinn, a former U.S. ambassador to Ethiopia who was also the State Department's desk officer for Djibouti as far back as the late 1960s. "Djibouti is one node in an economic chain that stretches across the northern rim of the Indian Ocean, from ports in Cambodia to Sri Lanka to Pakistan. They have a grand, strategic plan. We don't."  In Djibouti, that strategic plan is all the more evident because of the country's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hecklers derail Biden event...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hecklers-biden-quid-pro-joe-new-hampshire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden was interrupted by hecklers calling him "creepy" and a "pervert" during a campaign event in Milford, NH, Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Worst ever' hoarder house found with 19 dead cats buried under piles of trash...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/worst-ever-hoarder-house-found-21186351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tamara Bender and her husband Jeremy travel with a team of helpers who specialise in cleaning out homes in the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg campaign moves offices into Times Square as staff tops 300...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/476211-bloomberg-campaign-moves-offices-into-times-square-as-staff-grows-above-300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Mike Bloomberg’s campaign is set to move to a new location in Times Square as the campaign swells to more than 300 staffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fun, dynamic, frivolous...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/12/27/whos-up-for-a-roaring-20s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France waits on Macron as pension strike stretches on...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-waits-macron-pension-strike-stretches-142058122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French union leaders upped their calls on Monday for President Emmanuel Macron to give ground on a planned pension overhaul, despite signs that support is flagging for a gruelling transport strike now in its 26th day. Macron will address the nation Tuesday in his annual New Year's Eve address, having</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Obama, Trump Tie as Most Admired Man...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/273125/obama-trump-tie-admired-man-2019.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama and Donald Trump tie as the most admired man this year. Michelle Obama remains the most admired woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Of Americans Had Best Sex Of Their Lives In 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fireworks-nearly-half-of-americans-had-best-sex-of-their-lives-in-2019-survey-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of 2,000 adults asked respondents to recount their sexual experiences in 2019, and found that about half had the best sex of their lives this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight against facial recognition hits wall across West...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/30/facial-recognition-privacy-089881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The result is an impasse that has left tech companies largely in control of where and how to deploy facial recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi arrests hundreds for 'wearing inappropriate clothes', 'indecency'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nst.com.my/world/world/2019/12/551861/saudi-arabia-arrests-hundreds-wearing-inappropriate-clothes-indecency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nst.com.my&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIYADH: Saudi Arabia has arrested more than 200 people for violating “public decency” – including by wearing immodest clothing – and “harassment“, police said, in the first such crackdown since the ultra-conservative kingdom began easing social norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garoppolo Shines...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/bayarea/49ers/where-jimmy-garoppolo-ranks-among-49ers-qb-leaders-after-great-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy Garoppolo joined some 49ers legends with his epic 2019 regular season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Decade of Debt: Big deals, bigger risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-markets-decade-credit/the-decade-of-debt-big-deals-bigger-risk-idUSKBN1YY09Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatever nickname ultimately gets attached to the now-ending Twenty-tens, on Wal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge-Fund Purge Continues With More Closures Than Launches...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/hedge-funds-to-record-more-closures-than-launches-for-fifth-straight-year-1.1367459</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pain kept coming for hedge funds in 2019: if they weren’t being killed off, they were bleeding cash or wringing out dismal returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decade of very poor and super-rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-am-09455429-a788-43d0-8c0f-a6ad3d882e86.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELIN restaurant bible faces ruling in French chef's protest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/michelin-restaurant-bible-faces-ruling-french-chefs-protest-115123105.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French court will rule Tuesday if the authoritative Michelin restaurant guide must hand over its secret reasonings for stripping a chef of his third Michelin star, just a year after the coveted award was won. Marc Veyrat launched the unprecedented lawsuit after his Maison des Bois restaurant in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on 'new way' in Kim Jong Un's New Year speech...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eyes-way-kim-jong-uns-speech-040614958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un has called for "offensive measures" to strengthen security ahead of a New Year speech that could flesh out the nuclear-armed nation’s threat to seek a "new way" forward after the expiration of its year-end deadline for US sanctions relief. Kim’s latest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex toy an electronics show award finalist after controversy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1143b874fe71199db7772f09c38ccdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — A sex toy that can be controlled through a mobile app is a finalist for the Last Gadget Standing award at CES 2020, an electronics show in Las Vegas. The Las Vegas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Political Predictions of 2019...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/12/30/worst-political-predictions-of-2019-089874</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one knows what the future holds, but these pundits and politicians knew even less than the rest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China jails scientist who created world's first 'gene-edited' babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/china-jails-scientist-who-created-21184026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr He Jiankui was charged with illegally practicing medicine in China as he faced a backlash from fellow scientists following his claims that he had changed the genes of twin girls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steep rise in pets needing treatment for anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/steep-rise-pets-needing-treatment-21184637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of insurance claims to treat anxiety, depression and OCD in pets has rocketed, with some owners forking out £1,000 a day for behaviour and hormone treatments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acts of anti-Semitism on rise in New York and elsewhere, rattling communities...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Acts-of-anti-Semitism-are-on-the-rise-in-New-York-14938238.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - Hours after a knife-wielding man barged into a Hannukah party in a New York suburb, stabbing five people, top officials condemned the crime as part of a disturbing trend. New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo called it "domestic terrorism," linking it to the recent spate of violence against Jewish people in New York.  Anti-Semitic attacks are on the rise around the country, leaving Jews and their communities feeling frightened and unsafe. In New York City, anti-Semitic crimes have jumped 21% in the past year. According to the Anti-Defamation League, there were 1,879 incidents of anti-Semitism in the United States in 2018, including more than 1,000 instances of harassment. The 2019 figures are expected to meet or exceed that number.  "This is a national phenomenon that we are seeing, and it's frightening and it's disturbing," Cuomo said at a news conference Sunday. "If anyone thinks that something poisonous is not going on in this country, then they're in denial."  Experts say anti-Semitic violence has been rising for years. In 2018, a gunman stormed the Tree of Life synagogue in Pittsburgh, killing 11 congregants, and wounding six others. It was the deadliest anti-Semitic attack in the history of the United States.  In April, during the observance of Passover, a gunman killed a Jewish worshiper at a Poway, California, house of worship and injured three others.  And a string of attacks in recent weeks has left the Jewish community in the New York area particularly unsettled.  This month, David Anderson and Francine Graham went on a violent rampage at a kosher supermarket in Jersey City, New Jersey, killing three people inside the store. The pair have been linked to the Black Hebrew Israelites, a hate group that traffics in anti-Semitic tropes. Authorities said they also...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Year Flying Saucers Became Legit...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/technology/2019/12/2019-year-in-aliens-ufos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The truth is out there, but it’s fuzzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Trial Tests Incumbents Key to Senate Control...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-trial-tests-incumbents-090000264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Senate’s historic impeachment trial of President Donald Trump will be especially momentous for a small group of vulnerable incumbent senators whose 2020 re-election bids are central to determining control of the chamber.Trump is all but certain to be acquitted on two articles of impeachment</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
