<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>JARED LIVE IN BAHRAIN... </title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/X6n6mdXmi3U?t=54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;youtu.be&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subscribe to our channel: https://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=euronews Watch our LIVE here: https://www.youtube.com/c/euronews/live Find us ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economist: USA may be in recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/06/25/2020-recession-economist-gary-shilling-says-us-may-downturn/1559657001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economist Gary Shilling, who called several recent recessions, says the nation is probably already in a downturn. He cites recently weak job growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM Head Insists App Doesn't Listen to Your Conversations, Look at Messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/members/2019/06/25/instagram-adam-mosseri-app-doesnt-listen-to-conversations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Conde Nast Sells W Magazine...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/conde-nast-sells-w-magazine-sara-moonves-to-replace-longtime-top-editor-stefano-tonchi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN cuts to break after Trump accuser calls rape 'sexy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9369184/cnn-ad-break-trump-accuser-rape-sexy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TV interview with the author accusing Donald Trump of sexual assault had to be abruptly cut short when she bizarrely called rape “sexy”. CNN presenter Anderson Cooper quickly moved to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA WARSHIP DOCKS IN HAVANA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9365741/russia-warns-cuban-missile-crisis-warship-havana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has warned the US its build-up of weapons in Europe risks a repeat of the Cuban missile crisis – as a Moscow warship docked near Havana yesterday. Russian Deputy Foreign Minister Serge…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salvos of insults stoke tensions with Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Salvos-of-insults-stoke-US-tensions-with-Iran-14049350.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Any prospect of easing tensions between the United States and Iran seemed increasingly remote Tuesday as threats and personal insults flew between the two governments.  In language reminiscent of last year's taunts between President Donald Trump and North Korea's Kim Jong Un, Iranian President Hassan Rouhani described the White House as "mentally crippled" and denounced newly sanctions against Iran's supreme leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, as "outrageous and idiotic."  Trump called Rouhani's comments "ignorant" and said Iran does "not understand reality." Any attack on "anything American," tweeted the president - who last week called off a military strike that was to be launched after Iran shot down an unmanned U.S. drone - will bring "overwhelming" U.S. force and "obliteration" of some Iranian assets.  Beneath the din, no new options emerged for avoiding a conflict that both sides say they do not want, and more doors appeared to be closing rather than opening.  Trump has said repeatedly that he wants to talk. But he has indicated that he is prepared to continue squeezing the Iranian economy and leadership until Iran meets the "very simple demands" he has tweeted - "No Nuclear Weapons and No Further Sponsoring of Terror!"  Iran, whose nuclear energy program is under international restrictions, says it sees no reason to talk with an adversary that is crushing the life out of it, and that the United States must first show some respect. It said that "useless sanctioning" of Khamenei and Foreign Minister Mohammad Javad Zarif "means the permanent closure of the doors of diplomacy."  In Washington, even those who fully and vocally support the administration's "maximum pressure" sanctions policy have begun to question whether Trump has a strategy.  Mark Dubowitz, CEO...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK LIVE VIDEO SHOWED COP  DYING ON FLOOR AFTER EXECUTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/06/what-the-hell-google-youtube-still-has-video-up-of-st-louis-police-officer-langsdorf-lying-on-the-floor-dying-after-execution/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>