<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>In Covid-swamped Texas, patients die stranded in rural clinics...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210906-in-covid-swamped-texas-patients-die-stranded-in-rural-clinics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Covid-swamped Texas, patients die stranded in rural clinics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From lockup to landslide: Meet DC's first leader elected from jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210906-from-lockup-to-landslide-meet-dc-s-first-leader-elected-from-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From lockup to landslide: meet DC's first leader elected from jail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former UK PM Blair warns West should prepare for bio-terrorism threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210906104655-bqrp0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SEPT11/BRITAIN-BLAIR (TV):Former UK PM Blair warns West should prepare for bio-terrorism threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ida's death count rises while 600,000 still lack power...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210905202425-6nup6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Ida slammed into Louisiana as a Category 4 hurricane and the latest death toll there rose to at least 13 people on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No cashiers, please: Futuristic supermarket opens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-middle-east-business-2b682282869cb341730d0b34efcb0544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The Middle East on Monday got its first completely automated cashier-less store, as retail giant Carrefour rolled out its vision for the future of the industry in a cavernous Dubai mall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil on Edge as Bolsonaro Tells Base to Take to Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/brazil-tense-as-bolsonaro-calls-out-base-for-independence-day-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil on Edge as Bolsonaro Tells His Base to Take to the Streets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Price Pump Movement Grows Ahead of El Salvador Adoption...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-price-pump-movement-grows-041333104.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A growing movement on social media is calling for people to buy small amounts of Bitcoin in support of El Salvador’s plan to make the token legal tender.Users on platforms including Twitter and Reddit are discussing plans to buy $30 worth of Bitcoin en masse on Sept. 7 to mark El Salvador’s Bitcoin law coming into effect. The potential coordinated price pump echoes previous online campaigns targeting meme stocks like GameStop Corp. El Salvador has begun installing Bitcoin ATMs to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unemployment' cash stops today...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/570948-more-than-7-million-americans-to-lose-jobless-benefits-monday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over seven million people across the U.S. will lose their unemployment benefits beginning on Monday as pandemic safety nets expire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Strange Tale of Smartphone for Conservatives...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/06/the-strange-tale-of-the-freedom-phone-a-smartphone-for-conservatives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a pitch tuned for a politically polarized audience. Erik Finman, a 22-year-old who called himself the world’s youngest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cautionary Tale for the New Roaring Twenties...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/06/a-cautionary-tale-for-the-new-roaring-twenties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE ARE FEW things more glamorous than the belief that we are living through the end of an era —</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Legal Mastermind Behind Victory...</title>
      <link>https://www.texasmonthly.com/news-politics/meet-the-legal-strategist-behind-the-texas-abortion-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texasmonthly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney and former Texas Solicitor General Jonathan F. Mitchell is known for his ability to identify legal loopholes where no one else does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS:   ENDGAME REMAINS UNCERTAIN</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/scientists-path-covid-endgame-remains-232022995.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's basically over already. It will end this October. Or maybe it won't be over till next spring, or late next year, or two or three years down the road. From the most respected epidemiologists to public health experts who have navigated past disease panics, from polemicists to political partisans, there are no definitive answers to the central question in American life: As a Drudge Report headline put it recently, "is it ever going to end?"Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most imp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet ALTOS LABS, Silicon Valley's latest bet on living forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/09/04/1034364/altos-labs-silicon-valleys-jeff-bezos-milner-bet-living-forever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Funders of a deep-pocketed new "rejuvenation" startup are said to include Jeff Bezos and Yuri Milner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Thieves Steal 17 Cars From Dealership!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/09/03/police-search-for-17-cars-stolen-from-brooklyn-park-dealership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local car dealership is hoping for help finding more than a dozen cars that were stolen over the course of two days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Jewish population now numbers 15.2 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/there-are-152-million-jews-in-the-world-jewish-agency-data-678733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the world’s Jews, 6.9 live in Israel, and 8.3 live in the Diaspora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female boxer dies after being knocked out in ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/boxer-jeanette-zacarias-zapata-dies-days-after-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican boxer Jeanette Zacarias Zapata has died after suffering serious injuries in a fight in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian among 3 killed from 'cocaine-laced fentanyl overdose' at LA party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9959319/Comedian-Fuquan-Johnson-three-people-dead-suspected-overdose-party-LA.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other two victims have not been officially identified, while a fourth person who appeared to have also overdosed, believed to be comedian and model Kate Quigley, as per TMZ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE 'Horse Dewormer' Hit-Piece Debunked By Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/rolling-stone-horse-dewormer-hit-piece-debunked-after-hospital-says-no-ivermectin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron's Foreign Gambles Making French Diplomats Uneasy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/macron-s-foreign-gambles-are-making-some-french-diplomats-uneasy/ar-AAO7cGR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s president has fought a quiet battle with his diplomats but was persuaded to start Afghan evacuations earlier than other Western powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why China's bitcoin miners are moving to Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-58414555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing's crackdown on cryptocurrency sends bitcoin entrepreneurs moving to the wild wild west.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Island Man Became 'Forrest Gump of Jihad' -- Then Flipped...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/09/05/forrest-gump-of-jihad-book-excerpt-509587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What Bryant Neal Viñas can teach us about the lessons from Afghanistan the U.S. still hasn’t learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 anchors of safety net ending, affecting millions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-19-safety-net-ending-unemployment-evictions-bca43d873a61a9059c72fe15b88b9a9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Mary Taboniar went 15 months without a paycheck, thanks to the COVID pandemic. A housekeeper at the Hilton Hawaiian Village resort in Honolulu, the single mother of two saw her income completely vanish as the virus devastated the hospitality industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaxx paramilitary group, which discussed violent insurrection, disbanded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-anti-vaxx-paramilitary-group-which-discussed-violent-insurrection-via-telegram-was-disbanded-after-a-newspaper-exposed-it/ar-AAO7ngR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British group 'Veterans 4 Freedom' comprised more than 200 former servicemen and servicewomen and planned to attack vaccine centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady says he contracted after Super Bowl parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32149146/tom-brady-says-contracted-covid-19-shortly-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-parade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady says he was diagnosed with COVID-19 right after the Tampa Bay Buccaneers' Super Bowl parade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan, Harry make audacious bid for meeting with Queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3601938/meghan-harry-queen-summit-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN and Harry have made an audacious bid for a UK meeting with the Queen in the coming weeks. It comes after “olive branch” calls home following the Oprah chat row. Harry and Meghan plan to intr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kabul airport re-opens -- with no radar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kabul-s-airport-re-opens-for-domestic-flights-with-no-radar-as-taliban-battle-resistance-fighters-in-last-holdout/ar-AAO7hjL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news of the domestic flights comes as efforts continue to re-open the airport for international flights, a key step to enable humanitarian aid to enter the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hunting Americans,' says California mom-to-be left behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/taliban-hunting-americans-california-afghanistan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pregnant woman named Nasria, a California native, flew to Afghanistan in June to visit family and get married. As of early September, she remained one of the estimated 100 to 200 Americans left behind in the chaotic withdrawal of U.S. forces, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
