<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE CAFETERIA SHUT AFTER INFECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1184560/white-house-cafeteria-closed-coronavirus-worker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE White House office cafeteria has been closed after a worker contracted coronavirus. Three Trump administration officials confirmed the news to NBC, just hours before the president said that a d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group sues UT-Austin on behalf of white students who say they were unfairly denied admission...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/news/20200722/group-sues-ut-austin-on-behalf-of-white-students-who-say-they--were-unfairly-denied-admission</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A national organization has filed a suit in federal court on behalf of two white members who claim the University of Texas did not give them a fair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 brothers, woman arrested in murder of 3 friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/arrests-massacre-3-friends-fishing-trip-polk-county-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the suspects, Tony "TJ" Wiggins, 26, had previously been charged with 230 felonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Pays Above Face Value For Coins Amid Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/wisconsin-bank-pays-above-face-value-coins-amid-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate poised to defy veto with directive to change base names... </title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/world/americas/300063912/us-senate-poised-to-defy-trumps-veto-with-directive-to-change-military-base-names</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following the Black Lives Matter movement, lawmakers chart collision course with US president who threated to veto any move to change the names of armed forces bases that commermorated Confederate generals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: All Mammals, Including Humans, Share Equal Brain Connectivity...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mri-study-reveals-all-mammals-including-humans-share-equal-brain-connectivity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After examining and comparing brain connectivity across 130 different mammals (including humans), a new study conclude that brain connectivity is equal among all mammals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worries about Trump and bloodbath at polls this fall stokes Republican feuding...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Worries-about-Trump-and-a-bloodbath-at-the-polls-15427337.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Tensions among congressional Republicans fueled by the party's diminishing electoral fortunes broke out into the open this week - as GOP lawmakers sparred over the shape of the next coronavirus aid package, how vigorously to stand behind President Donald Trump and which primaries to wade into that could help determine control of the Senate in November.  In the Senate, GOP senators continued to struggle to find consensus on a massive spending bill aimed at mitigating the pandemic and softening its economic impact - a task complicated by the president's insistence on a payroll tax cut that few in his own party want, intraparty feuding over the cost of the package and disagreements over exactly how the money should be spent.  Across the dome in the House, some of the Trump's closest allies launched a surprising attack against Rep. Liz Cheney, R-Wyo., the highest-ranking Republican woman on Capitol Hill, charging her with disloyalty to the president because she has bucked him on national security issues and embraced public health advice and officials whom Trump has dismissed.  And on Wednesday, allies of Senate Republican leaders formally threw their support behind the establishment choice in a heated GOP primary in Kansas, pitting themselves against a strong supporter of the president who was an early advocate of his immigration policies.  The battles this week were a microcosm of the broader reckoning over the party's future and how strong the populist tenets of Trumpism will hold after the president leaves office. The fractures are emerging now because of worries that the party faces doom at the polls this fall owing to Trump's handling of the pandemic and his resulting falling poll numbers against presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden.  Trump came from nowhere five years ago to effectively...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT INVESTIGATED FOR VIOLATION</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/President-Trump-was-maskless-in-the-lobby-of-his-15426603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The president's maskless appearance at Trump International Hotel this week -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon asks for restraining order...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/22/judge-oregon-request-restrain-federal-agents-378315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state's lawsuit is part of a growing pushback against the Trump administration's use of federal agents against protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted Cardinal Ran 'Sex Cabal' at NJ Beach House...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/crime/2020/07/former-cardinal-mccarrick-accused-of-participating-in-beach-house-sex-ring-lawyers-allege.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victim charges he and others were groomed and manipulated as teenagers when they visited New Jersey beach house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Rare Area 51 pictures show giant hangar vanished...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/rare-area-51-pictures-shows-22399916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New long-range photographs of the top-secret military base deep in the Nevada Desert show a giant hangar previously pictured at the site is nowhere to be seen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 98 Californians infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/1-in-98-californians-infected-with-coronavirus-hospitalizations-at-all-time-high/article_d149c7ff-57b9-5cee-980e-eba2698f25a9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — More than 400,700 Californians — about 1 in 98 state residents — have been infected by the coronavirus. Of those, 7,755 have died as of Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARS IN 4 K:  RED PLANET LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN IT BEFORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8549745/Incredible-images-captured-Mars-remastered-ultra-HD.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British YouTubers ElderFox Documentaries have taken thousands of pictures and converted them into ultra high definition for a 'world first' view of the Red Planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK DOES IT AGAIN: TESLA fourth straight quarter of profits...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/22/tesla-tsla-earnings-q2-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the period ending June 30, 2020, Tesla grappled with the effects of the Covid-19 pandemic and widespread civil rights protests on its employees, customers and U.S. factory operations, especially.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil sets daily record of corona cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/brazil-sets-daily-record-of-new-coronavirus-cases-01595456404?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil recorded a new daily record of coronavirus cases Wednesday with nearly 68,000 infections, a sign COVID-19 is still far from being brought under control in the hard-hit country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANDATORY WHEN LEAVING HOME</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/bowser-masks-mandatory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Face coverings will now be mandatory for any D. C. resident leaving their homes, D. C. Mayor Muriel Bowser announced during a Wednesday press conference. Bowser says this means a mask must be worn when ordering food at a restaurant, waiting for a bus, sitting in a cubicle in an open office space, and walking your dog, just to name a few examples. We know that without a vaccine or a cure for COVID, we have to continue to take precautions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,000 FINE FOR NOT WEARING MASKS IN DC</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/508526-dc-mayor-issues-order-requiring-masks-outside-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., Mayor Muriel Bowser (D) issued an executive order Wednesday requiring residents to wear masks outside of the home as the city battles rising coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating chocolate 'wards off heart disease'...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/chocolate-heart-disease-coronary-artery-disease-231536646.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The indulgence could keep arteries healthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLS ANGELS Accused of Killing Leader of Rival Gang...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/22/hells-angels-accused-of-killing-leader-of-rival-biker-gang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two members of the Hells Angels motorcycle gang and a third man were charged on Wednesday with carrying out the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Narcissists, Psychopaths Less Likely to Wear Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/narcissists-psychopaths-face-mask-requirement-mandate-social-distancing-covid-19-coronavirus-1519732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGERS megadeal bucks conventional economic wisdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Dodgers-working-on-megadeal-for-Mookie-Betts-15426708.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the eve of baseball's regular season opener, amid a global pandemic that makes projecting the sport's economic future difficult if not impossible, the Los Angeles Dodgers nonetheless were believed to be nearing a mammoth contract extension for new right fielder Mookie Betts that would make him among the sport's highest paid players.  Various reports and industry speculation pegged the prospective deal as being in the neighborhood of 10 to 13 years, with a value of between $350 million and $400 million. Boston radio station WEEI first reported the news that an extension was close with Betts, whose résumé includes an MVP award (2018), a World Series title (2018) and the type of production matched or exceeded by only a handful of players over the past few seasons.  Mike Trout's 12-year $426.5 million extension with the Los Angeles Angels remains the largest in the sport's history, and Gerrit Cole, Bryce Harper, Manny Machado and Giancarlo Stanton are also currently on deals worth north of $300 million. Cole's $36 million average annual salary is tops in the game on a per-year basis.  At one time, when the 2020 season hung in the balance due to both the coronavirus and the inability of Major League Baseball and its players' union to strike an economic deal, it appeared Betts would never play a meaningful game in a Dodgers uniform.  Traded to Los Angeles by the Boston Red Sox in exchange for three younger players in February - prior to what would be his final season before reaching free agency - Betts, 27, could have taken his services to the open market this offseason, where he would have been the biggest prize.  But the Dodgers clearly believe Betts is worth handing what would be the largest contract in team history - even at a time when the coronavirus threatens the sport's economics well beyond this summer. Many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans Arrested for Tweeting About Virus, Locked in Rotting Hotels....</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2020/07/22/caruzo-arrested-for-tweeting-and-locked-in-rotting-hotels-how-socialist-venezuela-fights-the-colombian-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has now been four months since the Chinese coronavirus lockdowns began in Venezuela with no apparent end in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holder Concerned Trump Could Use Force to Suppress Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/07/21/holder-we-have-to-be-concerned-about-trump-using-paramilitary-forces-to-suppress-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday's broadcast of MSNBC's "the ReidOut," former Attorney General Eric Holder stated that we should "be concerned" about President Trump using | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA NEARS PEAK LEVEL OF HOSPITALIZATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1286067275200512001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mutation outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/new-covid-19-mutation-helps-outbreaks-spread-quicker-expert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new coronavirus mutation has become the most dominant strain of the virus — and is causing outbreaks to spread more quickly across the world, an expert said. Professor Nick Loman, of the Un…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA surpasses NY in cases...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/california-coronavirus-governor-gavin-newsom-record-number-of-daily-new-cases-1202992176/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Gavin Newsom on Wednesday reported a record 12,807 new coronavirus cases on Monday. He said this total was “the highest in the nation.” The previous record came on July 7 of 11…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAY BALL! Masked men, empty parks, odd sounds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59db961e7181936b80d834fede417167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opening day, at last. A baseball season that was on the brink before it ever began because of the virus outbreak is set to start Thursday night when excitable Max Scherzer and the World...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Love Hormone' May Reverse Alzheimer's Brain Damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/oxytocin-love-hormone-may-reverse-alzheimers-disease-brain-damage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although scientists know many of the underlying symptoms which trigger Alzheimer’s disease, a cure remains elusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEARST Employees Say Mag Boss Led Toxic Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/featured/sns-nyt-hearst-harassment-troy-young-20200722-3i6gyysqbbdzpd3tqlsnefqr54-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades Hearst magazines have advised American women on how they should conduct themselves in the home (Good Housekeeping, Redbook); in society (Harper’s Bazaar, Town &amp; Country); and in the bedroom (Cosmopolitan).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Dropping Oppo on VP Rivals?</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/2020-election/kamala-harris-oppo-dump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris (D., Calif.), whose failed presidential campaign flamed out before any primary votes were cast, is a top contender to be Joe Biden's running mate in 2020. Curiously enough, negative stories about Harris's potential rivals for the VP slot have been popping up of late in mainstream media outlets. Imagine that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGERS Ink Outfielder Mookie Betts To $365M Mega Deal...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/07/22/rumor-mookie-betts-dodgers-close-to-massive-contract-extension/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Red Sox traded Mookie Betts away this past winter, some Red Sox fans held on to some hope that Betts may sign back with Boston as a free agent. Those hopes, small as they may have been, might already be dashed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre Fall of Prominent CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/the-bizarre-fall-of-the-ceo-of-coach-and-kate-spades-parent-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of only five Black chiefs of a Fortune 500 company abruptly resigned after strange allegations — involving a hidden identity as photographer and an extramarital affair — resurfaced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announces 'surge' of federal agents to Chicago, other cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-to-surge-federal-agents-to-chicago-amid-spike-in-violent-crime-move-opposed-by-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump announced on Wednesday that he is deploying 100 federal agents to Chicago to help combat rising crime rates – a move that marks an expansion of the White House’s intervention into local law enforcement as Trump continues to position himself as the “law and order” president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS TIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/trump-biden-locked-in-tight-race-in-texas-poll-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and Joe Biden are in a dead heat in Texas, with a new Quinnipiac University poll showing the presumptive Democratic nominee with a slight edge, 45 percent to 44 percent, within the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas' first drive-thru strip club...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/texas-first-drive-thru-strip-club-has-2-song-limit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s all buns and no burger at this drive-thru. A Texas jiggle joint has found a creative way to attract customers while still letting their ladies strut their stuff during the COVID-19 outbr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs Warn Of Satanic Cult Activity, Animal Sacrifice Near SoCal Lake...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/21/fake-signs-satanic-cult-big-bear-lake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Signs posted around Big Bear Lake warning campers of "satanic cult activity" are fake, city officials confirmed on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON expands robot delivery to more cities...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/amazon-expands-robot-package-delivery-system-to-more-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seen any 6-wheel delivery robots trekking about Snohomish County or Irvine, California? That&amp;rsquo;s Scout, Amazon&amp;rsquo;s fully-electric delivery system designed to distribute packages to customers using autonomous delivery devices. The system was officially launched in January of 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge Kingdom of Judah complex found near US Embassy in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/huge-kingdom-of-judah-government-complex-found-stones-throw-from-us-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the 2,700-year-old finds: 120 inscribed seal impressions on jars at storage facility holding food collected as taxes for kings Hezekiah, Menashe in First Temple times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans mull extending unemployment bonus at $400 through December...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/22/coronavirus-stimulus-republicans-consider-unemployment-insurance-extension.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are considering extending the enhanced unemployment insurance benefit at a reduced level of $400 per month through the rest of the year, sources told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Hospitals Struggling: 'Rooms Look Like War Zones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/texas-coronavirus-hospitals-cases-covid-19-war-zones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While cities like Dallas and Houston are seeing a decrease in positive cases and hospitalizations, virus-related deaths in the state are up 33% over the last 10 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA WHISTLEBLOWER: 'THIS WAS INEVITABLE'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/a-public-health-employee-predicted-floridas-coronavirus-catastrophe-then-she-was-fired-this-is-everything-i-was-trying-to-warn-184810565.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a complaint filed last Thursday, attorneys for Rebekah Jones, who designed a dashboard on coronavirus spread in the state, say she was fired for “refusing to publish misleading health data.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEAMS WITH OBAMA IN NEW PUSH...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/joe-biden-barack-obama-2020-presidential-race-donald-trump-1202991746/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s campaign debuted a new video with Barack Obama, meant as a teaser of a longer conversation between the two on Thursday, as well as to show a contrast with Donald Trump’s pre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Push to remove Confederate statues stalls in rural America...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/805877a5a480f49033ab8c726f5a7531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLINTON, La. (AP) — The statue of the anonymous Confederate soldier has stood in front of the white-columned East Feliciana Parish courthouse for more than a century, leaning on his rifle as he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety in the Bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/07/inside-the-nbas-covid-free-bubble </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC 'When You Leave Home' Mask Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.popville.com/2020/07/new-dc-mayor-order-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popville.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the Mayor's briefing: "Lastly, it's simple: Wear a mask. Save lives. Stop the spread." Full release from the Mayor's Office: "Today, Mayor Bowser issued Mayor's Order 2020-080 to clarify and extend requirements related to wearing masks indoors and outdoors in Washington, DC. Additionally,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Uniformed sailor screams, 'F*** Trump', angrily confronts protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2020/07/21/video-shows-uniformed-sailor-screaming-f-trump-and-angrily-confronting-protesters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her command saw the video and is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEARST Employees Say Mag Boss Led Toxic Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/22/business/media/hearst-harassment-troy-young.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Cosmopolitan staff meetings, workers complain of discrimination and tokenism. Former employees say Hearst Magazines president Troy Young made sexually offensive remarks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Sweden, female priests now outnumber male ones...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200722-in-sweden-female-priests-now-outnumber-male-ones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Sweden, female priests now outnumber male ones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300,000 deaths by year-end?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/22/dr-scott-gottlieb-us-coronavirus-deaths-may-hit-300000-by-year-end.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Right now we have close to 1,000 casualties a day so if we don't change that trajectory, you could do the math," the former FDA commissioner told CNBC on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German state bars students from wearing full-face Muslim veils...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/german-state-bars-students-from-wearing-full-face-muslim-veils/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany’s third-largest state has banned girls from wearing full-face Muslim veils in its schools, according to a report. The move by officials in Baden-Württemberg came amid growing national…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try 'glory holes' for safer sex, B.C. CDC says...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/7204384/coronavirus-glory-holes-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;B.C.'s Centre for Disease Control suggested using a barrier to limit sexual contact during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUBIO:  Is front for 'massive spy operation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/22/marco-rubio-chinese-consulate-houston-front-massiv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Marco Rubio, Florida Republican, on Wednesday said the Chinese consulate in Houston is basically a front for a massive spy operation after the State Department ordered the consulate to close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Sees Ad 'Tsunami' with triple header Saturday!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/fox-sees-tsunami-of-ads-with-baseball-triple-header-saturday/ar-BB173xia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLD NEARS ALL-TIME HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/ever-lower-us-bond-yields-are-driving-gold-e2-80-99s-relentless-rally/ar-BB173rUT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typo gives away man who faked own death...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/da-typo-gives-away-man-who-faked-death-to-avoid-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spelling error and a font inconsistency indicated that a death certificate was fake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Restart: Sneak Peek Shows 'Black Lives Matter' Painted On Courts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/nba-restart-sneak-peek-shows-black-lives-matter-painted-on-bubble-courts-distanced-seats-and-large-screens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The league continues to spread social justice messages as it prepares to resume its season in Orlando</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second wave hits Australia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-pandemic-worse-australia-sees-record-infections-090910225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus death toll in the United States has spiked again with President Donald Trump conceding the pandemic crisis is likely to get worse, as governments across Asia and Europe battled second waves of infections. Australia set a new daily high of 500 cases on Wednesday, likewise Hong Kong broke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Russians fuel private jet demand...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rich-russians-fuel-private-jet-demand-skirt-virus-032913920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For high-flying Russians used to spending summer holidays at Mediterranean resorts or in London penthouses, coronavirus restrictions that closed borders and grounded flights have made international travel a distant dream. Privately-operated flights from Moscow's airports more than doubled between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans in America 30,000 years ago, far earlier than thought... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/humans-america-30-000-years-ago-far-earlier-160114498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tools excavated from a cave in central Mexico are strong evidence that humans were living in North America at least 30,000 years ago, some 15,000 years earlier than previously thought, scientists said Wednesday. Artefacts, including 1,900 stone tools, showed human occupation of the high-altitude Chiquihuite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female leaders doing 'better job', says Lagarde... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/female-leaders-doing-better-job-virus-crisis-says-155427839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Female leaders are doing a better job handling the coronavirus crisis, European Central Bank chief Christine Lagarde said Wednesday, praising them for their honest communication and for showing they cared. Lagarde, who is the ECB's first female president, singled out German Chancellor Angela Merkel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEAMS WITH OBAMA IN NEW PUSH...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-teams-back-obama-election-push-145511405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's getting a big new assist from his old boss Barack Obama this week in the push to defeat President Donald Trump in just over 100 days. A preview of a sleekly produced discussion between the former president and vice president that will air Thursday features Biden questioning Trump'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amber Heard says Johnny Depp threw bottles at her 'like grenades'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amber-heard-says-johnny-depp-threw-bottles-her-152959610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US actress Amber Heard on Wednesday said her ex-husband Johnny Depp threw dozens of bottles at her "like grenades", as she gave evidence for a third day at his London libel action. Heard, 34, said Depp, 57, had lobbed "all the bottles in reach" towards her during an explosive 2015</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELP:  More Than Half Business Closures Permanent...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/yelp-restaurants-temporary-permanent-closures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eateries have been hit the hardest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic-inspired food labeling raises alarms for those with food allergies...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/pandemic-inspired-food-labeling-raises-alarms-for-those-with-food-allergies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration released new “temporary guidance” for manufacturers facing supply chain shortages that allows them to make some ingredient substitutions without changing food label…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation on Verge of Lockdown 2.0...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-verge-lockdown-2-0-143003881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- After two months of what looked like a nascent recovery, the U.S. economy is faltering again. Restaurant reservations, one of the most commonly tracked indicators of local business activity, are stagnating:Americans are also a bit less mobile in July than in June:It’s not hard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insane stock price makes sense in world gone mad!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/teslas-insane-stock-price-makes-110020507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can Tesla and the stock market as a whole continue to defy gravity?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Conservatives are blocking antitrust investigations into Big Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.theamericanconservative.com/articles/the-conservative-inc-to-big-tech-pipeline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanconservative.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist boat at Niagara Falls packed; Canadian vessel next to it are socially distanced...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1180414/niagara-falls-canada-us-tourist-boat-coronavirus-packed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOTOS taken at Niagara Falls on Tuesday shows how differently the US and Canada are handling the coronavirus pandemic. Images from the falls, split between New York and Ontario, shows a US sightse…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autopsies Reveal Unique Pattern Of Cell Death In Hearts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-patient-autopsies-reveal-unique-pattern-cell-death-in-hearts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Damage seen in hearts of COVID-19 patients is not consistent with typical heart muscle inflammation patterns seen with myocarditis, new research shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE KARDASHIANS: Kanye Calls Mother-in-Law 'Kris Jong Un'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/22/kanyes-99th-nervous-breakdown-calls-mother-in-law-kris-jung-un-says-family-tried-to-commit-him-with-5150-hold</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West’s 99th nervous breakdown continues apace. Working up to his album release on Friday (maybe, who knows, maybe he’s imagining it), Kanye has continued his Twitter rant marathon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASK OF THE FUTURE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/21/mit-researchers-designed-reusable-n95-face-mask-for-healthcare-workers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at MIT and Brigham and Women's Hospital have a created a new type of face mask that could be a game-changer for healthcare workers. The new design is reusable, and can easily be sterilized. Plus, in tests, it performed as well as the standard N95 respirators. Take a look at the innovations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Sharks Are Vanishing... </title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/sharks-vanishing-functionally-extinct-in-some-areas-study-finds-crisis-for-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unprecedented global research project uses a simple tool to paint a grim picture of the vital ocean predators' numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA reports over 1,000 daily deaths for first time since May...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-deaths-thousand-may-a10e174a-9cdc-4148-93e1-dfe55c1f03e4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S reported over 63,000 new cases on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gonzalo forms as Atlantic springs back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-gonzalo-forms-in-central-atlantic/780947</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami police officers to form enforcement unit...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/926852/39-miami-police-officers-form-mask-enforcement-unit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you don't wear a mask in Miami, it'll cost you â€” $50 for the first offense, $100 for the second, and $500 every time after that. Miami-Dade County has the state's most COVID-19 infections reported per 100,000 people and the highest death toll, The Miami Herald reports. To try to slow the spread of the coronavirus, people in Miami must wear face masks while in outdoor and indoor public settings, with few exceptions. To ensure people take the ordinance seriously, Mayor Francis Suarez announced on Tuesday that 39 police officers will form a mask enforcement unit, working 'seven days a week.' Anyone who violates the ordinance more than three times will not only get a $500 fine, but will also be arrested. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim calls for compassion during crackup...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/07/22/kim-kardashian-defends-kanye-west-amid-bipolar-twitter-rants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Those who are close with Kanye know his heart and understand his words do not align with his intentions.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era for auto industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-autos-tesla-newera-insight-idUSKCN24N0GB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc's rapid rise to become the world's most valuable carmaker could mark the start of a new era for the global auto industry, defined by a Silicon Valley approach to software that is overtaking old-school manufacturing know-how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Sees Ad 'Tsunami'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/fox-sees-tsunami-of-ads-with-baseball-triple-header-saturday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Sees â€˜Tsunamiâ€™ of Ads with Baseball Triple-Header Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT names Levien CEO as Thompson steps down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-times-names-levien-ceo-thompson-steps-down-134338391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times on Wednesday named Meredith Kopit Levien as its new president and chief executive, succeeding Mark Thompson, who held the job for eight years and led the daily's digital transformation. Kopit Levien, 49, has been chief operating officer since June 2017, a role in which she led</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California surpasses New York state in cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eea842bc48a5b791878ed0c97e539489</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — SACRAMENTO, Calif. — California’s confirmed coronavirus cases have topped 409,000, surpassing New York for most in the nation. John's Hopkins University...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fl0COtEG-TM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCARLET â¤« FEATURING JIMMY PAGE One of three unheard tracks featured on Goats Head Soup 2020, sitting alongside an all-new stereo mix of the original 1973 alb...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arms industry: Gun buys up 95%, ammo 139%; Sales to blacks jump 58%...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/arms-industry-gun-buys-up-95-ammo-139-sales-to-blacks-jump-58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gun industry has never seen anything like 2020, and the explosion in sales driven by the concerns over rising crime, protests, the coronavirus crisis, and the presidential election are expected to continue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Picasso painting found hidden beneath famous artwork...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/12191780/secret-picasso-painting-famous-artwork/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAWINGS by legendary artist Pablo Picasso have been discovered hidden beneath one of his most famous paintings. The sketches of a mug and what could be a newspaper were scribbled on a canvas event…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan says threat of military clash with Beijing on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Taiwan-says-threat-of-military-clash-with-China-15425487.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan - The prospect of a military clash in the Taiwan Strait is rising precariously, the Taiwanese foreign minister warned Wednesday, urging "extreme caution" in the island's dealings with a Chinese leadership in Beijing that he described as both increasingly emboldened and insecure.  The Chinese military has held a growing number of exercises that simulate an invasion of Taiwan, a self-ruled island about 80 miles off China's east coast that considers the United States its main military and diplomatic backer. The pace and scale of China's drills, as well as those of U.S. naval and air forces deployed to the region, have risen in recent months as relations between Beijing and Washington plummet on numerous fronts.  Relations took another sharp turn Wednesday after the State Department said it ordered China to close its consulate in Houston.  Defense Secretary Mark Esper said this week the United States would sell more arms to Taiwan as part of a $10 billion deal approved by Congress. He also said the U.S. military would reposition forces across Asia to prepare for a confrontation with China in flash points including self-ruled Taiwan, which China claims as its territory and has vowed for decades to take by force, if necessary. Inside China, the government has faced growing calls from hawkish military pundits and nationalist commentators to grasp the current strategic window to seize Taiwan, an accomplishment that could rally the Chinese population and burnish leader Xi Jinping's political legacy.  Taiwanese Foreign Minister Joseph Wu said Wednesday he was worried China has conducted an "unprecedented" number of sea and air drills around Taiwan in 2020, with the pace rising to nearly once every day since June. "The threat is on the rise," he said.  Wu speculated that tensions in the Taiwan Strait - one of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED extends face covering requirement to include airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/health-coronavirus-united-arlns/united-airlines-expands-mask-mandate-to-airports-tightens-exemptions-idUSL2N2ET02V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Airlines said on Wednesday it is extending face mask requirements to all of its airport areas across the world starting on July 24 and tightening exemptions to only cover children under the age of two.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEOPLE WHO NEVER TOOK TEST -- BEING TOLD THEY'RE COVID-POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/people-who-never-took-test-being-told-theyre-covid-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How accurate are coronavirus numbers?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gonzalo forms as Atlantic springs back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/new-tropical-depression-forms-as-atlantic-basin-springs-back-to-life/780261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONES jam with Jimmy Page in lost track from 'hallowed era'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200722120540-d42s3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSIC-ROLLING STONES/ (PIX, TV):Rolling Stones jam with Jimmy Page in lost track from 'hallowed era'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden leads by 8 points; Big advantage among undecided voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-poll/biden-leading-trump-by-eight-points-also-has-a-big-advantage-with-undecided-voters-reuters-ipsos-poll-idUSKCN24N1AY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic candidate Joe Biden leads President Donald Trump by 8 percentage points in support among registered voters, and the former vice president appears to have a significant advantage among voters who are undecided, according to a Reuters/Ipsos opinion poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airborne virus probably infectious...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-report-airborne-coronavirus-probably-infectious-090340015.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have known for several months the new coronavirus can become suspended in microdroplets expelled by patients when they speak and breathe, but until now there was no proof that these tiny particles are infectious. A new study by scientists at the University of Nebraska that was uploaded to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurgent 'techlash' overshadows Silicon Valley earnings...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/resurgent-techlash-overshadows-silicon-valley-earnings-041107186.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Tech, its hands full with antitrust probes and complaints growing from activists and politicians, turns its attention to quarterly earnings in the coming days expected to show the growing power of Silicon Valley giants. Amid the coronavirus pandemic, Big Tech has offered a lifeline to consumers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I don't believe it': Huntington Beach symbol of mask resistance as doubters abound...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dont-believe-huntington-beach-symbol-120009131.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As infection rates soar in Orange County, residents of Surf City doubt the severity of the pandemic and call for easing restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Very frightening': Opposition grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edebeb4a7df1c97b10b9ab55a53caa84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — The Trump administration is facing growing pushback — in the courts and on the streets — to sending federal agents to Portland, Oregon, where protests have spiraled into...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: November Election Going to Be Mess...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/07/november-election-going-be-mess/614296/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disaster is avoidable—if lawmakers act now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER TAPPED FOR VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/22/us-government-taps-pfizer-to-produce-millions-of-doses-of-coronavirus-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vaccine candidate is being jointly developed by German biotech firm BioNTech and U.S.-based Pfizer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing delays once again hamper response...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/508432-testing-delays-once-again-hamper-covid-19-response</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surging COVID-19 outbreaks in several states are straining testing capacity across the country as people wait several days or even weeks to get their results back, causing another setback to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raises alarm over takeover of states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/508279-federal-presence-in-portland-raises-alarm-over-takeover-of-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bootstrapping a narrow enforcement authority to protect federal property is alarmingly reminiscent of deploying a federal occupation force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insiders Who Nailed Market Bottom Starting to Sell Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insiders-nailed-market-bottom-starting-100000776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As U.S. stocks climb to their most expensive levels in two decades, the executives in charge of the companies benefiting from the rally are showing signs of anxiety.Corporate insiders, whose buying correctly signaled the bottom in March, are now mostly sellers. Almost 1,000 corporate executives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Science Fiction, Gene Editing Now Looming Reality...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/22/once-science-fiction-gene-editing-is-now-a-looming-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This article is part of a series exploring how the Americans With Disabilities Act has shaped modern life for people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent spread keeps scientists grasping for clues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33ce920720ee71dbabcd8db757b8dfd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the great mysteries of the coronavirus is how quickly it rocketed around the world. It first flared in central China and, within three months, was on every continent but Antarctica,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB players taking visible stance on social justice...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2475947af1645f635024180fb07617cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Major League Baseball hasn't always been at the forefront of the social justice movement in recent years, with leagues like the NBA and NFL usually taking center stage. But in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. tells China to shut Houston consulate in 'unprecedented escalation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-consulate/us-tells-china-to-shut-houston-consulate-in-move-china-calls-unprecedented-escalation-idUSKCN24N0UW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has told the Chinese consulate in Houston to shut down in three days, citing a need to protect American intellectual property and information, amid a sharp deterioration in relations between the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rules rewritten as Hawaii prepares for hurricane amid pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2020/07/22/rules-are-being-rewritten-hawaii-prepares-hurricane-amid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Douglas is the first named storm of the season to come near Hawaii – and the first ever during a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful 7.8 quake rocks Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6e17ff15281994947a180033380ff930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — A powerful 7.8 earthquake struck the Alaska Peninsula late Tuesday, triggering a tsunami warning that sent residents fleeing to higher ground before it was called off...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER bans 7,000 QAnon accounts, limits 150,000 others as part of broad crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/twitter-bans-7-000-qanon-accounts-limits-150-000-others-n1234541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company will classify QAnon as coordinated harmful activity in part because of a rise in harassment targeting high-profile critics of the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell's Testimony About Her Sex Life Could Soon Be Released...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ghislaine-maxwell-e2-80-99s-testimony-about-her-sex-life-could-soon-be-released/ar-BB171M5u?ocid=uxcntrlbingtab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
