<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Shock video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pIGcjlCcv24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A black man (Roderick Walker) was brutalized by police in Clayton County after the driver of the Lyft ride share service was pulled over due to a broken tail...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0M2mOZeiVtA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Follow my Twitter for more f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVIE:  TRANS MAN GIVES BIRTH!</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/09/13/review-in-ground-breaking-french-film-a-good-man-noemie-merlant-is-stunning-as-a-trans-man-who-gives-birth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m the first to tell you I am out of my depth writing about trans anything, gender fluid issues. I’m respectful of all the different aspects, but it’s not an area of expertise. L…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vote-rigging claims fit Russia's plan, former top spy says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-vote-rigging-claims-fit-russia-e2-80-99s-plan-former-top-spy-says/ar-BB18ZAD3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Googling for Gut Symptoms Predicts Hot Spots...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/googling-for-gut-symptoms-predicts-covid-hot-spots-study-finds/ar-BB18Yw1Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRE TORNADO; TEMPS REACH 1,500 DEGREES...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/california/fires/article245692450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WARNING GULF...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/hurricane-warnings-in-effect-for-parts-of-gulf-coast-as-tropical-storm-sally-gathers-strength/811946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALLY EYES NEW ORLEANS...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-09-13-tropical-storm-sally-forecast-hurricane-warning-louisiana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest on what Sally could bring to the Gulf Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel new nationwide lockdown as virus cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af7e03891cdebdc9eb507094401b5146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Sunday announced a new countrywide lockdown will be imposed amid a stubborn surge in coronavirus cases, with schools and parts of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus America, six months in: Disarray, dismay, disconnect...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/706587be1d93d2672087a0ad99459462</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Erin Whitehead has been a committed fan of the crisis-fueled medical drama “Grey’s Anatomy.” She has watched its doctors handle all manner of upheaval inside their put-upon hospital —...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As President played down covid, health experts' alarm grew...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48f77170558376db143da5f0a3f2b3e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Public health officials were already warning Americans about the need to prepare for the coronavirus threat in early February when President Donald Trump called it “deadly stuff”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputy caught punching Black man in Georgia fired...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/404f027814728a12a714e1adf136fb3b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JONESBORO, Ga. (AP) — A sheriff's office in Georgia said Sunday it fired a deputy seen on video repeatedly punching a Black man during a traffic stop. The deputy was being let go for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower's claims on interference fit pattern...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f59968fe06851efc30ccca084c66095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A whistleblower’s allegation that he was pressured to suppress intelligence about Russian election interference is the latest in a series of similar accounts involving former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun-Toting, Millennial Trying to Ride Covid Backlash to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/09/13/lauren-boebert-congress-409983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Boebert pulled off a stunning primary victory after defying government shutdown orders. But could she lose a GOP seat?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State's fire marshal abruptly resigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/pacific-northwest-news/2020/09/oregon-fire-marshal-put-on-leave-amid-historic-wildfires.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oregon State Police on Saturday announced Fire Marshal Jim Walker had been put on paid administrative leave. Then, later in the day, the state police announced its superintendent had accepted a resignation offer from Walker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Multiple Overdoses Connected To Man Handing Out Free Heroin...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/09/11/free-heroin-overdoses-chicago-auburn-gresham/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's an offer some couldn't pass up: free heroin. A bad batch is being passed out on Chicago's South Side, but minutes later people were dropping to the ground, overdosing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandson of Harding, lover wants president's body exhumed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ecb0a2826ce7ea8a818fb9be08c98c0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — The grandson of U.S. President Warren G. Harding and his lover, Nan Britton, went to court in an effort to get the Republican’s remains exhumed from the presidential memorial...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Targeted CIA. They Arrested Him for Child Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-hacker-said-he-had-proof-the-cia-caused-the-anthrax-attacks-they-had-him-arrested-for-child-porn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new doc “Enemies of the State” examines the case of Matt DeHart, an intelligence analyst who was targeted by the authorities after allegedly gaining access to top-secret files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player kicked out of NBA 'bubble' for 'night with female coronavirus testing official'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1463676/houston-rockets-danuel-house-kicked-out-female/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HOUSTON Rockets player will not be allowed to play the rest of the NBA season after breaking the league’s coronavirus safety protocols by having an “unauthorized” guest over to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon prepares for 'mass fatality incident'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/13/us/us-west-fires-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of wildfires tearing through communities across the West have left at least 33 people dead, and authorities fear dozens more are missing and unaccounted for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Illinois cities to vote on merger: 'Reached critical point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/13/cahokia-centreville-alorton-illinois-vote-merger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in Cahokia, Centreville and Alorton will be asked in November to decide whether they want to merge their communities and become one city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another chaotic night in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8727013/More-100-BLM-protesters-shut-George-Washington-Bridge-Manhattan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The George Washington Bridge into Manhattan from New Jersey was blocked on Saturday night by Black Lives Matter protesters, who then marched back into Manhattan to rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLM protesters clash with NYPD after marching onto George Washington Bridge...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/13/blm-protesters-clash-with-nypd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Black Lives Matter protesters were arrested outside of the 34th Precinct in Washington Heights on Saturday night after earlier marching onto the George Washington Bridge and briefly stalling tr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Corporate Rescue vs. America Too Small to Save...</title>
      <link>https://features.propublica.org/cleveland-bailout/the-big-corporate-rescue-and-the-america-thats-too-small-to-save/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;features.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Girish Patel doubts his small, 20-year-old shop will survive the pandemic economy. Thirty stories above, aerospace company TransDigm has sustained eye-popping profits thanks to steep layoffs and raised over a billion with help from the U.S. government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep skepticism for coronavirus response...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/deep-skepticism-trumps-coronavirus-response-endures-poll/story?id=72974847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Americans are skeptical of President Trump's performance on the coronavirus pandemic, a new ABC News/Ipsos poll released Sunday finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK faces 2nd hard lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12656523/prof-trickle-covid-become-cascade-brits-partying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE UK faces a second hard lockdown if partying Brits don’t follow Covid rules, a top academic has warned. Immunologist Peter Openshaw says Covid-19 “isn’t a game” after cas…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive Pentagon program to replace human hackers with AI...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/secretive-pentagon-research-program-looks-to-replace-human-hackers-with-ai/ar-BB18YYiP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem's Great Synagogue closed for High Holy Days for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jerusalems-great-synagogue-to-be-closed-for-high-holy-days-for-first-time-642075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Great Synagogue will be closed for the first time since prayers began there in 1958.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 LA DEPUTIES AMBUSHED</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/l-a-county-sheriffs-deputy-shot-in-compton-agency-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two deputies were shot and left in critical condition Saturday night, the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department released surveillance footage that appears to show the shooting in Comp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS BLOCK HOSPITAL</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/2-lasd-deputies-ambushed-in-compton-shooting/6420532/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department deputies were shot in an ambush at a Metro station in Compton Saturday, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese military calls US biggest threat to world peace...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9c9cf27d653fccbd34baf23f6ed48661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China’s Defense Ministry on Sunday blasted a critical U.S. report on the country’s military ambitions, saying it is the U.S. instead that poses the biggest threat to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/refresh/AL192020_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/215703_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender Satanist anarchist wins Republican nomination for county sheriff...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1463548/transsexual-satanist-anarchist-wins-nomination-new-hampshire-sheriff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARIA DiMezzo, a “transsexual Satanist anarchist,” has nabbed the Republican nomination in the sheriff’s race of a New Hampshire county while running with the campaign slogan “F**k the Police.” DiMe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Trump battle for women who sided with president last time -- and now regret it... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Biden-and-Trump-battle-for-women-who-sided-with-15562688.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From her home in the Philadelphia suburbs, Nin Bell works for an answering service, taking calls from people trying to reach more than 10,000 funeral homes and end-of-life companies. As the coronavirus began to sweep the country earlier this year, the number of calls related to new deaths tripled.  Caller after caller told her about losing a loved one to covid-19, as well as to suicides and drug overdoses. They provided an overwhelmingly painful window into just how badly the country was suffering.  And then Bell would hear President Donald Trump - whom she voted for in 2016, helping him win Pennsylvania - downplay the severity of the pandemic.  "He was telling everybody it wasn't a big deal - but I knew it was a big deal because of my job. I'm like: 'Why am I taking 60 coronavirus deaths in one day, on one shift, when I used to only take 20 death calls a day?'" said Bell, 47, the mother of two teenage boys who lives in Parkside, about 20 miles southwest of Philadelphia."He made a lot of mistakes. He just runs his mouth. . . . He's the president, he can't get away with that, especially when people's lives are in danger."  Bell "definitely, 100 percent" plans to vote for Joe Biden for president - and she has been urging others to do the same.  She's part of a group of White women, especially those who are middle- or working-class, who didn't vote for Hillary Clinton in the last election but are determined to vote for Biden this year.  Those women, who have been targeted by both campaigns, loom large in a presidential race that could, like 2016's, be decided by shifts among a few sets of voters in the highly polarized nation.  Although Clinton won the majority of votes from women in 2016, she lost to Trump among White women. Since then, however, polls have shown Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke plumes unlike anything previously seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/californias-wildfire-smoke-plumes-are-unlike-anything-previously-seen/ar-BB18Y54b?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas turms ghost town where even strippers put up signs saying, 'Sorry, we're clothed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8726053/Las-Vegas-ghost-town-strippers-signs-saying-Sorry-clothed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the shadow of Covid-19, Las Vegas is on its own losing streak. Casinos, hotels and shows which last year generated $60 billion (£48 billion) in tourist revenue are either almost empty or shuttered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WB HIDES 'TENET' BOXOFFICE DATA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/box-office/warner-bros-tenet-box-office-studios-1234767113/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who closely follow box office earnings have noticed a surprising lack of transparency surrounding ticket sales for “Tenet,” the $200 million-budgeted sci-fi epic from director Ch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial resumes after 'unexplained illness'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vaccine-trial-resumes-virus-continues-225916843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clinical trials of one of the most advanced experimental Covid-19 vaccines resumed Saturday after a brief safety pause, as infection numbers continued to march upward in countries across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli protesters keep up pressure on Netanyahu over alleged corruption...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200912182400-pha5g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-PROTESTS (TV, PIX):Israeli protesters keep up pressure on Netanyahu over alleged corruption</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro says Venezuela caught Marine-turned-CIA spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1462920/maduro-venezuela-caught-usa-marine-cia-spy-target-oil-refineries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA’S President says authorities caught a U.S. Marine-turned-CIA spy with ‘special weapons’ meant to target the nation’s oil refineries President Nicolás Maduro said t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's smoke plumes unlike anything previously seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-s-wildfire-smoke-plumes-are-unlike-15562222.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 3.1 million acres have burned in California this year, part of a record fire season that still has four months to go. A suffocating cloud of smoke has veiled the West Coast for days, extending more than a thousand miles above the Pacific. And the extreme fire behavior that's been witnessed this year hasn't just been wild - it's virtually unprecedented in scope and scale.  Fire tornadoes have spun up by the handful in at least three big wildfires in the past three weeks, based on radar data. Giant clouds of ash and smoke have generated lightning. Multiple fires have gone from a few acres to more than 100,000 acres in size in a day, while advancing as many as 25 miles in a single night. And wildfire plumes have soared up to 10 miles high, above the cruise altitude of commercial jets.  Scientists have been scrambling to collect as much data on these wildfires as possible, hoping to unlock the secrets to their extreme behavior and fury. Among them is Neil Lareau, a professor of atmospheric sciences in the department of physics at the University of Nevada at Reno. Lareau closely studies pyrocumulus clouds, towering explosion-like plumes of heat that develop above intense blazes.  He retrieved data from the National Weather Service's network of Doppler radars, which scan the skies every few moments at up to 15 different vertical angles. By stitching these different elevation "slices" together, he was able to produce a three-dimensional model of each smoke plume.  The Creek Fire, which burned nearly 200,000 acres in the Sierra Nevada Mountains, was only 6% contained on Friday. On Sept. 5, a day after it was first ignited, its smoke plume soared to 55,000 feet. That's taller than many of the tornadic thunderstorms that roll across Oklahoma and Kansas each spring.  Such clouds are both indicators of and contributors to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco may soon allow 16-year-olds to vote!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/major-american-city-may-soon-allow-16-year-olds-vote-n1239955</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the proposition passes, San Francisco would become the first large city to give 16- and 17-year-olds the right to vote in local elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Unvetted Vaccine Next?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-pressed-for-plasma-therapy-officials-worry-is-an-unvetted-vaccine-next/ar-BB18Y5jc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Sued for Packing NFL Charters With Young, Blond Crews...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/united-sued-for-packing-nfl-charters-with-young-blond-crews/ar-BB18X2Wi?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France and Spain sets daily infection record...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/france-sets-daily-record-more-22673308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second wave of Covid-19 in France showed no signs of slowing as a record 10,561 new infections were announced, the first time the daily number has topped 10,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LULULEMON, which is worth $40 billion and sells $128 yoga pants, promotes 'resist capitalism' event...</title>
      <link>https://notthebee.com/article/lululemon-which-is-worth-40-billion-and-sells-128-yoga-pants-promotes-resist-capitalism-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;notthebee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROFL 🤣</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WATCH GULF...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/884d6693c5ebb9c9a1b7b440d39d6022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) — Tropical Storm Sally formed Saturday off south Florida, becoming the earliest 18th-named storm on record in an Atlantic hurricane season as it enters the Gulf of Mexico...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY VALLEY  HEARTBREAK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/56216039822719d0760198f4560c0030</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — Wildfire smoke that posed a health hazard to millions choked the West Coast on Saturday as firefighters battled deadly blazes that obliterated some towns and displaced tens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOMADLAND' WINS VENICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/nomadland-wins-golden-lion-award-at-venice-film-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting awards went to Vanessa Kirby and Pierfrancesco Favino at the scaled-down festival</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
