<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Attempted lynching of driver in riots near Temple Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/palestinian-youth-injured-in-car-crash-in-old-city-riot-667743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lone police officer arrived at the scene moments after the car swerved off the road and fired warning shots into the air to disperse the mob.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Fungus Infection Found in Patients in India...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ninashapiro/2021/05/09/covid-19-infections-complicated-by-deadly-fungus/?sh=3b439cbd62bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 infections can be complicated by a deadly fungus. This devastating disease is sharply on the rise in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency declaration issued in 17 states, DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fuel-pipeline-cyberattack-us-state-of-emergency-dda2e776-f0f0-45cc-ae38-4fea47e014ec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo told CBS there's an "all hands on deck" effort to resume operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake cheers, empty seats: Tokyo gives glimpse of Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fake-cheers-empty-seats-tokyo-084338335.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fake cheers, empty seats and the sound of pounding feet: welcome to the Covid-era Tokyo Olympics, which Japan seems determined to hold at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviews military might as tensions with West soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210509075935-b3h6p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WW2-ANNIVERSARY/RUSSIA-PARADE (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Putin reviews Russian military might as tensions with West soar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Targets Muslim Women in Push to Suppress Births in Xinjiang...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/10/china-targets-muslim-women-in-push-to-suppress-births-in-xinjiang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the government ordered women in her mostly Muslim community to be fitted with contraceptive devices, Qelbinur Sedik pleaded for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP braces for wild week with momentous vote...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/552445-gop-braces-for-wild-week-with-momentous-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republicans return to Washington this week embroiled in a bitter battle over the direction of the party, the face of its leadership and what role former President Trump should play heading into next year’s ele</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Worth More Than All US Currency in Circulation...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/cryptocurrency-worth-more-than-us-currency-circulation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cryptocurrencies are now worth more than all of the US currency currently in circulation. This is a significant milestone — but could indicate a bubble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Fights for Survival...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/10/as-cuomo-fights-for-survival-he-revives-his-combative-image/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. — Over the past few weeks, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo has crisscrossed New York, promoting the state’s vaccine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hack Knocks Out Pipeline for Third Day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-fuel-sellers-scramble-alternatives-014304375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Fuel suppliers are growing increasingly nervous about the possibility of gasoline and diesel shortages across the eastern U.S. almost two days after a cyberattack knocked out a massive pipeline.Colonial Pipeline said on Sunday in the U.S. that it was still developing a plan for restarting the nation’s largest fuel pipeline -- a critical source of supply for the New York region -- and would only bring it back when “safe to do so, and in full compliance with the approval of all federal regulations.” Gasoline futures surged by as much as 4.2% in Asian trading on Monday.The attack comes just as the nation’s energy industry is preparing to meet stronger fuel demand from summer travel. Americans are once again commuting to the office, planning major travel for the first time and booking flights. A prolonged disruption along the pipeline system threatens to send average U.S. gasoline prices above $3 a gallon for the first time since October 2014, further stoking fears of inflation as commodity prices rally worldwide.With little to no clarity over when the system will return, traders are seeking vessels to deliver gasoline that would have otherwise been shipped on the Colonial system, according to market participants who asked not to be identified because the information isn’t public. Some tankers are being secured to temporarily store gasoline in the U.S. Gulf in the event of a prolonged shutdown, they said.Colonial halted all operations on its system late Friday after suffering a ransomware attack that affected some of its IT systems.Colonial is just the latest example of critical infrastructure being targeted by ransomware. Hackers are increasingly attempting to infiltrate essential services such as electric grids and hospitals. The escalating threats prompted the White House to respond last month with a plan to increase security at utilities and their suppliers. Pipelines are a specific concern because of the central role they play in the U.S. economy.“It’s an all-hands-on-deck effort right now,” U.S. Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo said of federal government actions as the shutdown drags on. “We are working closely with the company, state and local officials to make sure that they get back up to normal operations as quickly as possible and there aren’t disruptions in supply.”The White House pulled together an inter-agency task force to address the breach, including exploring options for lessening its impact, according to an official. President Joe Biden can invoke an array of emergency powers to ensure supplies keep flowing to big cities and airports along the East Coast.Colonial is a major source of gasoline, diesel and jet fuel to the East Coast from the nation’s refining belt along the Gulf Coast. It has the capacity to send about 2.5 million barrels (105 million gallons) a day from Houston as far as North Carolina, and another 900,000 barrels a day to New York.An ocean-going tanker that had been taking gasoline toward the U.S. Gulf stopped on its voyage and is now stationed east of the Bahamas, data compiled by Bloomberg show. If the halt is prolonged, the fuel islikely to fetch higher premiums in the New York Harbor area.The attack appeared to use a ransomware group called DarkSide, according to Allan Liska, senior threat analyst at cybersecurity firm Recorded Future. The cybersecurity firm FireEye Inc. said its Mandiant incident response division was assisting with the investigation.Extortion FeeRansomware cases involve hackers seeding networks with malicious software that encrypts the data and leaves the machines locked until the victims pay the extortion fee. This would be the biggest attack of its kind on a U.S. fuel pipeline.The national gasoline average stood at $2.96 a gallon Friday, according to auto club AAA. With gasoline inventories ample, the pump price wasn’t expected to tick much higher until Memorial Day at the end of May, which is traditionally viewed as the start of the U.S. summer driving season. If the pipeline doesn’t restart soon it will accelerate the move higher.“I think we’re at strong odds for it by Memorial Day given current trends,” said Patrick De Haan, head of petroleum analysis at Gas Buddy.A key concern at present is meeting product demand in the U.S. Southeast, which is especially dependent on the Colonial system, people familiar with the situation said. Drivers in landlocked and car-dependent Atlanta may be the first to feel the pinch at the pump.“Atlanta will be one of the earlier sore spots, along with eastern Tennessee, and perhaps the Carolinas,” De Haan said.The Northeast can secure gasoline shipments from Europe but it will come at an increasing cost the longer the pipeline stays shut. The fuel’s premium to crude in northwest Europe had jumped by more than 5% in intra-day trading earlier on Monday but was still down week-on-week.“The longer it lasts, the more bullish it will be for refined products on the East Coast,” said Warren Patterson, head of commodities strategy at ING Groep NV. “This will likely also drag European product prices higher, as we see more waterborne cargoes needing to go into the U.S. East Coast to meet the shortfall.”Last year, the U.S. imported about 235k b/d of gasoline from Europe, according to bill of lading and tanker-tracking data compiled by Bloomberg. Stocks of the road fuel in PADD 1 -- the U.S. East coast -- are below the five-year average, at close to 65 million barrels, according to the latest EIA data.Airports on the East Coast, which continue to have some of the steepest drops in air traffic due to the pandemic, have been operating smoothly Sunday, according to the flight-tracking website FlightAware.com.In the meantime, fuel producers including Marathon Petroleum Corp. are weighing alternatives for how to ship their products to the Northeast.One potential route is the Kinder Morgan-operated Plantation Pipeline, even though it only extends as far north Washington D.C. and has a capacity of 720,000 barrels a day, far short of Colonial’s. Kinder said Sunday it’s working with customers to accommodate additional barrels during Colonial’s outage, and that Plantation is deferring where possible any non-essential maintenance that might otherwise reduce flow rates.While all of the major segments of Colonial’s system remain offline, some smaller so-called laterals connecting specific fuel terminals to delivery points are in service, the company said. That laterals gave some traders hope that the full network may be back online within a week.“Hopefully it is a sign that they have made progress either negotiating with those responsible for the attack or have found ways to operate around it, said Debnil Chowdhury, head of Americas refining at IHS Markit. “However to avoid product shortages, all efforts should be made to avoid a 5+ day outage of the main lines.”Inventories offer minimal cover, ClearView Energy Partners said in a research note. Tankers leaving Rotterdam could take up to 14 days to make the trip to the New York Harbor. The Midwest could theoretically send some of its supplies to the East Coast via rail and barge, but the region’s inventories are tighter than in previous years, ClearView said.“The Colonial outage comes at a critical juncture for the recovering U.S. economy: the start of the summer driving season,” ClearView said. “We therefore think lawmakers could begin a ‘blame game’ immediately, and a sustained disruption that leads to a significant pump price spike could increase prospects of domestic policy interventions.”(Adds information on fuel pricing, tanker movements from 10th paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychedelic Revolution Coming. Psychiatry May Never Be Same...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/09/the-psychedelic-revolution-is-coming-psychiatry-may-never-be-the-same/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been a long, strange trip in the four decades since Rick Doblin, a pioneering psychedelics researcher, dropped his first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIRTHDAY HORROR:  7 people dead after shooting in Colorado Springs home...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/crime/colorado-springs-shooting-multiple-victims/73-428e2525-2e0d-4c6e-a716-6badf26bedea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said they found the victims inside a residence early Sunday and that the suspect was believed to be among the dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On policy, Cheney is more of Trump Republican than Stefanik...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/on-policy-liz-cheney-is-more-of-a-trump-republican-than-elise-stefanik</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Republicans want to oust Rep. Liz Cheney from her position as chairwoman of the caucus and replace her with Rep. Elise Stefanik, a younger, much more Trump-friendly Republican. The irony is that Stefanik's voting record doesn’t even line up with the “America First” agenda Trump Republicans…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madrid mayor decries partying Spaniards as  lockdown ends...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/may/09/madrid-mayor-decries-partying-spaniards-as-covid-lockdown-ends</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for restraint as thousands gather to celebrate lifting of nation’s six-month state of emergency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Big Lie' imperils Republicans who don't embrace it...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/michael-pence-donald-trump-election-2020-government-and-politics-0c07947f9fd2b9911b3006f0fc128ffd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Allegiance to a lie has become a test of loyalty to Donald Trump and a means of self-preservation for Republicans...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As pollen torments millions, it might be getting worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/pollen-allergies-coronavirus-philadelphia-trees-grasses-climate-change-asthma-20210508.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trees are popping around Philly, the grasses are awaking, and pollen is likely to get worse. But who's counting?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fat shaming, BMI and alienation: Covid brought new stigma to large-sized people...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fat-shaming-bmi-alienation-covid-120034530.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has brought into stark focus the long battle between the medical establishment and the fat acceptance movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockets fired from Gaza as incendiary balloons hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/incendiary-balloons-light-ashkelon-field-on-fire-667646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two rockets were launched from the Gaza Strip. One rocket fell in an open area and Air Defense Artillery combat soldiers intercepted the second.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mind control' warning as smartphone apps will be used to shape world views...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/mind-control-warning-smartphone-apps-24043891</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Therapists have issued a chilling warning over the potential for "harmless" looking smartphone apps to perform "mind control" and "suddenly shape our world views"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia faces massive new virus surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/asia-india-coronavirus-surge-nepal-c6ceeb37-fbb5-4f8f-9baf-153eb42fd5eb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Southeast Asia region reported over 2.7 million new cases and over 25,000 new deaths."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gangs get more aggressive against law enforcement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ransomware-gangs-hacking-police-cybercrime-pipeline-3a38c27c4fafe0c39461fb71bf91a42a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va., (AP) — Police Chief Will Cunningham came to work four years ago to find that his six-officer department was the victim of a crime. Hackers had taken advantage of a weak password to break in and encrypt the files of the department in Roxana, a small town in Illinois near St...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could lose Derby win!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/medina-spirit-kentucky-derby-positive-drug-test-bob-baffert-f91ccf1fb6a44c3f948a3a2cd2c8c1a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE, Ky. (AP) — Medina Spirit’s victory in the Kentucky Derby is in serious jeopardy because of a failed postrace drug test, one that led Churchill Downs to suspend Hall of Fame trainer Bob Baffert immediately on Sunday in the latest scandal to plague the sport...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PAIN AT PUMP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-342d43005020fbbc2fb279bd593428f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMARILLO, Calif. (AP) — The average U.S. price of regular-grade gasoline jumped 6 cents over the past two weeks, to $3.02 per gallon. Industry analyst Trilby Lundberg of the Lundberg Survey said Sunday that the increase came as the costs of crude oil and ethanol also rose...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 MILLION WATCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/05/09/snl-ratings-elon-musk-hosted-show-lifts-the-numbers-by-1-2-million-viewers-to-4-8-mil-a-healthy-increase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Elon Musk hosted episode of “Saturday Night Live” was a ratings hit. Not explosive, but good enough after a miserable few monnths. The show been mired in low numbers for the last se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police prepare for more Temple Mount violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/palestinian-prayer-goers-walk-to-jerusalem-as-police-close-roads-667608</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions have risen throughout Israel during Ramadan over the potential eviction of Palestinians from homes in Jerusalem's Sheikh Jarrah neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unruly airline passenger behavior spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/unruly-airline-passenger-behavior-spikes-amid-zero-tolerance-policy-faa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines are seeing a spike in bad behavior among people flying despite a zero-tolerance policy, the FAA said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female Fort Bragg soldier charged in another's killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/05/08/one-female-fort-bragg-soldier-charged-in-anothers-killing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sergeant is charged in the death of 22-year-old Spc. Kelia Horton, who police said was found shot outside a Fayetteville home Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRICES RISING EVERYWHERE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/09/investing/stocks-week-ahead/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everywhere you look, there are headlines about higher prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Sniper Boasts of Post-Shooting Sex With Accomplice in New Doc...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/horrific-d-c-sniper-boasts-090258634.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ViceIn I, Sniper, Lee Boyd Malvo speaks at length about the 2002 reign of terror he and partner John Allen Muhammad carried out in the Washington, D.C., area, resulting in ten deaths. Yet despite using audio clips from his phone calls as narration, Vice’s eight-part docuseries (premiering May 10) is most notable for putting its prime emphasis on the pair’s innocent victims, and the countless friends, family members and loved ones left to cope with unthinkable tragedy. To its admirable credit, it’s a true-crime affair that seeks to understand its “monsters” while simultaneously recognizing—and highlighting—the fact that such comprehension doesn’t necessitate empathy, especially when the atrocities in question are as inexcusably heinous as these.Spearheaded by director Ursula Macfarlane, I, Sniper’s calling card is those phone conversations with Malvo from Virginia’s Red Onion State Prison, where he’s currently serving multiple life sentences. In them, the killer recounts, in exacting and chilling detail, both the sniper attacks he perpetrated as a 17-year-old, and the troubled upbringing in Jamaica that led him into the welcoming arms of Muhammad, a Gulf War veteran with a surplus of rage and a desire to unleash it on his homeland. Abandoned by his dad, abused by his mom, and eventually left to fend for himself, Malvo found in Muhammad a father figure who promised to love him as he did his own biological offspring. From the outset, though, theirs was a bond built on exploitation, with Muhammad becoming not only Malvo’s surrogate parent, but also his lover—as well as his mentor, pouring all of his long-simmering hate and resentment into the impressionable, desperate-for-acceptance teen.The Tragic End to Wrestling’s First Great ‘Madman’Muhammad’s gripes were many—he despised the military, white people, and just about every American institutional structure. However, he reserved his greatest enmity for second ex-wife Mildred, who dared to take back her kids after Muhammad had kidnapped them. The loss of his (abducted) brood seems to have been the proverbial match that lit Muhammad’s homicidal spark, and he soon began molding Malvo into his instrument of destruction. Friends and relatives suspected that something was up with their relationship, but no one foresaw what was to come: the cold-blooded murder of Keenya Cook, the niece of Mildred’s friend in Tacoma, Washington, followed by violent robberies, shootings and slayings in Arizona, Louisiana, Alabama, and Georgia. All of those initial acts were merely a test run for Malvo and Muhammad’s grand scheme in Washington, D.C., the epicenter of American power, and thus Muhammad’s venue of choice to strike fear into the heart of the republic by proving that everyone was vulnerable—even children.What transpired was a 22-day nightmare in which 13 individuals (white and Black, young and old, well-off and working-class) were shot, 10 of them fatally, in D.C., Maryland, and Virginia. Because Malvo and Muhammad’s intention was to terrorize in increasingly escalating fashion, each victim was chosen at random at gas stations, on street corners, and in parking lots that afforded the killers ideal vantage points and easy escape routes. They committed these crimes in a customized 1990 blue Chevy Caprice, with Malvo lying in the trunk and firing through the rear keyhole. It was a stealthy plot, and the two benefited from the fact that an early eyewitness said they’d seen a white box truck near the scene—thereby sending police, for the better part of the next three weeks, on a wild goose chase for the wrong vehicle. With no other ballistics-related leads, law enforcement was stymied, which proved to Malvo that Muhammad was right: no one could stop them from exacting their revenge.The question, of course, is revenge against what? I, Sniper connects the dots of Malvo and Muhammad’s troubled pasts and despicable 2002 presents, but no convincing argument is made that Muhammad—the mastermind behind this madness—had suffered losses that weren’t of his own making. Be it his unhinged military tenure, his marital craziness, or his transformation of Malvo into an assassin, Muhammad comes across as a man righteously angry over things that were his own fault. As for Malvo, his cold, clinical recitation of his murderous conduct (and claims of remorse) neuters any sorrow one might feel for his adolescent travails. His present-day compunction is far too little, too late, just as the case he makes for his own victimhood vis-à-vis Muhammad sounds like an accurate and yet insufficient explanation. He knew that gunning down men, women and children was dreadfully wrong, and yet in order to maintain Muhammad’s affection, he actively, and enthusiastically, chose to do it—and even got a thrilling kick from it, as he explains that post-shooting sex with Muhammad was exceptionally exciting.Malvo and Muhammad’s rampage of “retribution and punishment” was unforgivable; as Montgomery County Police Chief Charles A. Moose says, “There’s just no excuse for their behavior. None whatsoever.” To hammer home that point, I, Sniper consistently juxtaposes Malvo’s recollections with prolonged, heartrending interviews with the wives, brothers, aunts and friends of the duo’s victims, as well as some of those who survived their encounters. Those accounts turn out to be vital, providing an up-close-and-personal view of the anguish and trauma that Malvo and Muhammad brought about, and the lingering scars left by this ordeal. They’re the human face of this awful tale, stricken with grief, regret, guilt and fury over senseless crimes that robbed them of loved ones who were simply at the wrong place at the wrong time.Comprised of news reports, crime scene footage, 911 calls, Malvo-penned illustrations, maps and chats with patrolmen, detectives, reporters and doctors, I, Sniper is comprehensive enough to earn the description “definitive.” Yet more than its insight into the mind of its young subject—and, by extension, Muhammad, who was executed in 2009 by lethal injection—what separates it from much of the true-crime pack is its dogged refusal to forget the real, incalculable horror at the center of its story. Malvo is frequently heard but never seen, while the countenances of his and Muhammad’s victims (and those close to them) remain front-and-center throughout. That directorial decision is critical and commendable, allowing the series to pay fitting tribute to the individuals who deserve to be remembered, while keeping its central villain largely faceless, in the dark and out of sight, where he chose to live and kill with his murderous mentor, and where he’ll now remain for the remainder of his days.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Stolen Ahead of Shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colonial-hackers-stole-data-thursday-035900243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The hackers who caused Colonial Pipeline to shut down the biggest U.S. gasoline pipeline on Friday began their blitz against the company a day earlier, stealing a large amount of data before locking computers with ransomware and demanding payment, according to people familiar with the matter.The intruders, who are part of a cybercrime gang called DarkSide, took nearly 100 gigabytes of data out of the Alpharetta, Georgia-based company’s network in just two hours on Thursday, two people involved in Colonial’s investigation said.The move was part of a double-extortion scheme that is one of the group’s hallmarks. Colonial was threatened that the stolen data would be leaked to the internet while the information that was encrypted by the hackers on computers inside the network would remain locked unless it paid a ransom, said the people, who asked not to be identified because the information isn’t public.The company didn’t immediately respond to requests to comment on the investigation. It said earlier that it “proactively took certain systems offline to contain the threat, which has temporarily halted all pipeline operations, and affected some of our IT systems.”Colonial’s decision late Friday to shut down a pipeline that is the main source of gasoline, diesel and jet fuel for the East Coast, without saying when it would reopen, represents a dangerous new escalation in the fight against ransomware, which President Joe Biden’s administration has identified as a priority.It’s not clear how much money the attackers demanded or whether Colonial has paid. Ransomware demands can range from several hundred dollars to millions of dollars in cryptocurrency. Many companies pay, often facilitated by their insurers.AXA SA, one of Europe’s top insurance companies, said this week that it would break with that trend and stop offering policies in France that reimburse customers for payments made to ransomware hackers, which could be the first in the industry, the Associated Press reported.Cyber-attacks have disrupted the operations of other energy assets in the U.S. in recent years. Last year, the Department of Homeland Security revealed that an attack brought down an unnamed natural gas compressor facility for two days. In April 2018, several natural gas pipeline operators had service interruptions because of the hack of a third-party provider whose technology enables electronic communications between the entities.The theft of Colonial’s data, coupled with the detonation of ransomware on the company’s computers, highlights the leverage that hackers often have over their victims in these kinds of cases. The company said FireEye Inc.’s Mandiant digital forensics division is assisting with the investigation.The White House said that Biden was briefed on the incident Saturday morning.A series of major cyber-attacks in recent weeks also underscored the brazenness of the attackers and the challenges of tackling the problem of ransomware.In a matter of days, attacks were revealed against the police department in Washington, D.C. , where the hackers threatened to release information about police informants to criminal gangs; the Illinois Attorney General’s office, which had been warned about weak cybersecurity practices in a recent state audit; and San Diego-based Scripps Health, where medical procedures were canceled and emergency patients diverted to other hospitals.Ransomware Attackers Up Ante as White House Vows Crack Down(Adds reference to recent attacks starting in 11th paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. 5th Fleet seizes weapons shipment from stateless dhow in Arabian Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-5th-fleet-seizes-weapons-shipment-stateless-dhow-arabian-sea-2021-05-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy’s Fifth Fleet said on Saturday that the guided-missile cruiser USS Monterey (CG 61) seized an illicit shipment of weapons from a stateless dhow in international water of the North Arabian Sea on May 6-7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools Open, but Many Families Hesitant to Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/schools-are-open-but-many-families-remain-hesitant-to-return/ar-BB1gwVLI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pauline Rojas’s high school in San Antonio is open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80% Who Refuse Vaccine Say NOTHING Can Change Their Minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/whopping-80-percent-who-refuse-covid-vaccine-say-nothing-can-change-their-minds-but-theres-good-news-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A whopping 80 percent of people who say they won’t get vaccinated also say that there is nothing that can change their minds in a new poll — but there’s some potentially good news in the poll, as well. In a new The Economist/YouGov poll, respondents who said they don’t intend to get the Covid […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden faces struggle to hold Senate, Dem divisions resurface...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-biden-faces-a-struggle-to-hold-the-senate-democrats-e2-80-99-divisions-resurface/ar-BB1gvMd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In crucial Senate races in Pennsylvania, North Carolina and elsewhere, the Democratic coalition that came together to elect Biden is fracturing again — with big implications for his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abbas voices full support for rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.i24news.tv/en/news/israel/diplomacy-defense/1620420142-abbas-voices-full-support-for-palestinians-rioting-in-jerusalem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.i24news.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OF GAS PRICE SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9558509/Fears-gas-price-surge-ransomware-attack-shuts-Americas-key-fuel-pipeline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack on Colonial Pipeline took place Friday, and affected some of its information technology systems. Operations remain shutdown as of early Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Study Mysterious Behavior of Cats Sitting on Squares...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7eexj/scientists-have-studied-the-mysterious-behavior-of-cats-sitting-on-squares</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cats love sitting on any square object, as if drawn by some primordial instinct. A new study shows that the square can even be an optical illusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fire breaks out near Iran nuke power plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/massive-fire-breaks-out-near-irans-bushehr-nuclear-power-plant-report-667581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cause of the fire is still unknown, according to Iranian media reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British royal offers to sell access...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210509-british-royal-offers-to-sell-access-to-putin-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British royal offers to sell access to Putin: report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to 'firmly' defend Russian interests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210509-putin-on-wwii-victory-day-vows-to-firmly-defend-russian-interests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin on WWII Victory Day vows to 'firmly' defend Russian interests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC teacher caught sucking topless man's nipple during ZOOM class...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/08/nyc-teacher-caught-sucking-topless-mans-nipple-during-zoom-class/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teacher Amanda K. Fletcher allegedly performed an “inappropriate sexual act” on a Zoom class at Columbia Secondary School for Math, Science, and Engineering.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
