<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Safety fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/europe-divided-on-astrazeneca-covid-shot-over-safety-fears/ar-BB1evWql</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe’s problems with AstraZeneca Plc’s Covid-19 vaccine deepened, with at least 10 countries suspending use of the shot over safety concerns that Germany and France -- along with the continent’s top health authority -- say are unfounded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Governments Push to Relax Ban on Travel From Rest of World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/eu-governments-push-to-relax-ban-on-travel-from-rest-of-world/ar-BB1ew5yx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of European Union nations that count tourism as a significant industry is pushing for a relaxation of rules on traveling to the bloc from the rest of the world, according to diplomats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio sides with Alabama workers in AMAZON union battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/12/marco-rubio-endorses-amazon-unionization-effort-in-alabama.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an op-ed in USA Today published Friday, Sen. Rubio said he "stands with those at Amazon's Bessemer warehouse."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Faces 'Very Large' EU Advertising Probe, Vestager Says...</title>
      <link>https://tech.hindustantimes.com/tech/news/google-faces-very-large-eu-advertising-probe-vestager-says-71615568750842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tech.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology “is really a high priority for us because what has happened over these last 12 months has changed a lot of habits,” Vestager told an online event Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libertarians Want to Make New Hampshire a Flying Car Mecca...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/libertarians-want-to-make-new-hampshire-a-flying-car-mecca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos invited by Sanders to hearing on income, wealth inequality...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bezos-invited-sanders-hearing-income-160128115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Amazon.com Inc. founder Jeff Bezos, the world’s richest person, has been invited by Senate Budget Committee Chairman Bernie Sanders to appear before his panel for a hearing on income and wealth inequality.Bezos has a net worth of $182.7 billion according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, while many of Amazon’s workers earn so little they receive government subsidies for food and health care, putting the online giant in the company of other big employers like Walmart Inc. and McDonald’s Corp.Amazon didn’t immediately reply to questions about Sanders’s invitation for Bezos to appear before Congress.Sanders plans the hearing for March 17. He also invited an Amazon worker at an Alabama fulfillment center where some employees are trying to form a union.The right of Amazon workers to unionize is getting some Republican support as well. Florida Senator Marco Rubio said in a USA Today opinion column that Amazon has “waged a war against working-class values.”“Uniquely malicious corporate behavior like Amazon’s justifies a more adversarial approach to labor relations,” Rubio said. “It is no fault of Amazon’s workers if they feel the only option available to protect themselves against bad faith is to form a union.”Rubio criticized the Seattle-based company for crushing small businesses and competition and for inadequate working conditions during a year of record profits amid pandemic-related shutdowns. He also took issue with what he described as the company’s left-leaning values imposed on workers and retailers.Stuart Appelbaum, head of the retail worker union behind organizing efforts at the Amazon fulfillment center in Alabama, welcomed Rubio’s support and said the fight to support working people “should not be a partisan issue.”(Updates with request for Amazon comment in the third paragraph and Rubio support for union efforts beginning in the fifth paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  'Historic' snowstorm to pummel Wyoming, Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/historic-snowstorm-to-pummel-wyoming-colorado/914183</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The snowstorm could turn into the biggest on record for one city, and AccuWeather forecasters warn that the heavy rate of snow could shut down travel and lead to power outages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe allergy added to ASTRAZENECA side effects...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-03-severe-allergy-added-astrazeneca-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Severe allergies should be added to the possible side effects of AstraZeneca's coronavirus vaccine after likely links were found to a number of cases in Britain, the EU's drug regulator said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's First Primetime Address Viewership Tops Trump In Early Numbers...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/joe-biden-ratings-covid-primetime-speech-1234713128/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Finding light in the darkness is a very American thing to do,” Joe Biden said last night in his first presidential primetime address. “In fact, it may be the most American thing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican low on reserves to cover deficit, seeking donations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pope-francis-90586d6c79d75d229c207dcddcfe2d9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican warned Friday that it has nearly depleted its financial reserves from past donations to cover budget deficits over recent years, as it urged continued giving from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Peek behind precautions at pandemic GRAMMYS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/los-angeles-music-coronavirus-pandemic-grammy-awards-us-news-1ac46f886b545c78928e152a83c1e7c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — I have covered the Grammy Awards for the Associated Press for 15 years. But this strange year feels like the first time. Built around performances, full of singing and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tussle between US, allies over vaccine supply escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-global-trade-coronavirus-vaccine-coronavirus-pandemic-96e0d1594748dd2c8ccf47d62b8d5fb0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Millions of coronavirus vaccine doses are in cold storage in the U.S. that can’t be injected in the states because they are not yet approved by the Food and Drug Administration,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon goes to war with FOXNEWS over 'feminizing' military...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/mar/11/pentagon-fox-news-host-carlson-go-war-over-feminiz/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of high-ranking military officers are using their official social media accounts to denounce Fox News host Tucker Carlson over recent claims that maternity flight suits for pregnant fliers and new directives that loosen hair regulations to accommodate females in the ranks are “making a mockery” of the U.S. military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronze age burial site in Spain suggests women were among rulers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/11/bronze-age-burial-site-in-spain-suggests-women-were-among-rulers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in Murcia find exquisite objects at women’s graves later used as sites for elite warrior burials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest hotel amenity:  Free test...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/travel/article/The-latest-hotel-amenity-doesn-t-involve-massages-16020968.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a senior manager of member services at Exclusive Resorts, Lambie Swenson assists...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCS Sign Brady To 4-Year Contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-brady-agrees-to-contract-extension-with-bucs-future-hall-of-fame-qb-locked-in-through-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady agrees to contract extension with Bucs: Hall of Fame QB locked in through 2022, per report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROWING CONTROVERSIES FOR TUCKER CARLSON...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tucker-carlson-women-military-sexist-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fox News host said new grooming standards and inclusive military uniforms for women were making a "mockery" of the U.S. military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio sides with Alabama workers in AMAZON union battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rubio-amazon-union-alabama-1776c614-7bef-42eb-8e21-8da65d2f1bed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I stand with [workers] at Amazon’s Bessemer warehouse."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Leaning Towards Big Tech Breakup...</title>
      <link>https://promarket.org/2021/03/09/congress-antitrust-big-tech-break-up-interoperability/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;promarket.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTER: His hands had been all over my body, the small of my back, my waist...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/andrew-cuomo-sexual-harassment-albany-reporter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In my years of reporting on the governor, he frequently put his hands on my body and made inappropriate remarks. The point was to humiliate me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  30 WOMEN</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/03/new-allegations-of-inappropriate-behavior-by-andrew-cuomo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I was thinking, This is the weirdest interaction I’ve ever had in my life … I was like, Don’t touch me.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALLS CLOSING IN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-new-york-andrew-cuomo-bd4c3889049fa84c16da5a065b1ff260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — Multiple members of New York’s congressional delegation called Friday on Gov. Andrew Cuomo to resign in the wake of mounting allegations of sexual harassment and an allegation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much longer can he hold on?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/03/how-much-longer-can-andrew-cuomo-hang-on-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new accusation of sexual misconduct, which has been referred to Albany police, has triggered more calls for his resignation and an impeachment investigation led by his fellow Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE asks for volunteers to deploy to border 'as soon as this weekend' to cope with surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/ICE-asks-for-volunteers-to-deploy-to-border-as-16020687.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement sent an urgent email to senior staff Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga Got Her Dogs Back, but as Criminals Capitalize on Pandemic Pups, Others Aren't So Lucky...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5945294/dog-theft-covid-19-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dog thieves are targeting expensive breeds and puppies that can sell for thousands of dollars online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL VANCE NAIL TRUMP BEFORE EXIT?</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/03/22/can-cyrus-vance-jr-nail-trump </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Adversary Looms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/12/new-adversary-looms-for-trump-as-vance-exits-manhattan-d-a-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyrus R. Vance Jr., the Manhattan district attorney, announced on Friday he would not run for re-election, setting off a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Impossible travel conditions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/12/weather/snow-storm-travel-rockies-central-plains/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Severe weather, historic snowfall and flash flooding are forecast for the next few days in areas of the central United States, from the Rockies to the Mississippi River Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Worried About Pirates...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/03/nasa-james-webb-space-telescope-pirates/618268/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transporting a telescope worth billions of dollars is a risky endeavor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Special Ops Became Solution to Everything...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2021/04/how-special-ops-became-the-solution-to-everything/618080/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s elite forces have solved a lot of national-security problems. But the country’s reliance on them is becoming a problem of its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild True Story Behind GUCCI Assassination Movie...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wild-true-story-behind-lady-095306007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Artists ReleasingLady Gucci: The Story of Patrizia Reggiani, Discovery+’s latest true-crime documentary (premiering March 21), is not a whodunit. In revisiting the March 27, 1995, murder of Maurizio Gucci, the head of the famed Italian fashion brand, director Jovica Nonkovic’s film makes it 100 percent clear that the mastermind behind this assassination was Gucci’s wife Patrizia Reggiani. How so? It interviews Reggiani herself, who candidly admits on camera that she had gone around Milan asking, “Anybody here brave enough to kill my husband?,” and that when cops finally arrived on her doorstep, her reaction was, “I didn’t think they’d catch me.”Reggiani’s participation is the primary draw of the streaming service’s non-fiction feature, whose arrival comes on the heels of Lady Gaga and Adam Driver’s recent announcement that they’re collaborating on the Ridley Scott drama House of Gucci about Reggiani’s story. Certainly, there’s plenty of juice to this tawdry tale, which here is guided by Reggiani, who in the backseat of a luxury sedan traversing the streets of Milan, confesses, “I grew up among beautiful things.” That swanky childhood came courtesy of her mother’s marriage to successful entrepreneur Ferdinando Reggiani, and instilled in her a love of the high life. Her beauty and charm, meanwhile, made her a desirable socialite—“like a mini Liz Taylor,” says one friend—and she subsequently caught the eye of Gucci, who was just the sort of man (handsome, rich, important) she was looking to snag.Exposing the Wild and Tragic Lives of ’90s Teen Stars A 500-person wedding later (in 1972) and they were an international power couple, much to the chagrin of Gucci’s father (who didn’t attend his son’s nuptials). Nonetheless, as Lady Gucci elucidates, Reggiani was well-liked by Gucci’s uncle Aldo, and for a time, their union was a happy one, producing two daughters and leading to a stint living in a fabulous NYC penthouse apartment. Reggiani waxes nostalgic in Nonkovic’s documentary about her lavish jet-setting ’70s existence, replete with waking up at 11 a.m. and being driven around town in a Bentley, and then attending and/or hosting galas where she was the regal center of attention. At this time, she also befriended Giuseppina “Pina” Auriemma, who in a new interview reveals that Reggiani’s personality was deeply shaped by her tumultuous relationship with a self-centered mother who treated her badly (reportedly, she referred to Reggiani as her “bastard”), thus compelling Reggiani to look for loyal love elsewhere.Pina is central to this sordid saga, although Nonkovic takes her time explicating the tangled web that would soon ensnare her various characters. Through interviews with not only Reggiani and Pina but also acquaintances, journalists, criminologists, and investigators, she conveys the glitziness of the environment that Reggiani inhabited, albeit with a hastiness that can be a bit frustrating. Part of the appeal of Lady Gucci is the milieu in which she operated—a day-to-day procession of chauffeured cars, private jets, beautiful models, business tycoons, and celebrity elites that would make Robin Leach salivate. That the show doesn’t spend more time establishing the context of its central crime feels like a minor missed opportunity.Nonetheless, what it does have is Reggiani, sitting in a living room chair speaking to the camera with an unapologetic smugness that’s at once repulsive, humorous, and fascinating. There doesn’t appear to be a shameful bone in the now-72-year-old woman’s body as she describes the shrewd maneuvers that gave her husband control of the family empire, their purchase of a cursed 65-meter sailboat named Creolé, and the 1980s disintegration of their marriage following his literal abandonment of her and their kids for another woman. Reggiani does this with a look of invincibility on her face, and the fact that director Nonkovic routinely punctuates dramatic moments with a zoom into a close-up of the “Black Widow”—her expression oozing cold-blooded haughtiness—only accentuates the proceedings’ comical sensationalism.Things came to a head when Gucci, flailing at the helm of the company, chose to sell his controlling shares to Bahrain-based Investcorp for $170 million, and then asked for a divorce—all while not visiting Reggiani when she was in the hospital for brain-tumor surgery. “You’re a… a deformed growth. You’re a painful appendix,” Reggiani is heard saying to her spouse in a voicemail message, and slurs were only the start of her plot. Faced with losing her social and financial position should Gucci remarry, Reggiani instead opted to do away with him by hiring Pina to find men to carry out a hit. Lady Gucci details this scheme in amusing fashion, having Pina and Reggiani simultaneously give their own versions of events, with the former claiming she had only intended to scam Reggiani out of cash (while never actually having the murder take place), and the latter stating that she was the duped victim of Pina and her crooks. Patrizia Reggiani in Lady Gucci Discovery+ Thanks to a tip that materialized nearly two years after Gucci’s death, chief of police Filippo Ninni (who’s also interviewed at length) eventually unraveled Reggiani and Pina’s conspiracy, via a sting known as “Operation Carlos” that involved an undercover agent posing as a South American hitman. Lady Gucci lets both Reggiani and Pina make their case for their own innocence, although one gets the sense that Reggiani doesn’t really buy what she’s selling. Her egomania is the veritable star of this show, so monumental and unflappable that it wasn’t even dented by her conviction, which earned her 26 years behind bars. “It was great. I wish I was still in San Vittore,” she says about jail, as interviewees report that she received first-class prison treatment that made her stay akin to a spa vacation.Reggiani’s attitude and conduct feel like something out of a florid gangster film, which goes a long way toward explaining why her story continues to resonate—and is primed to be a lavish Hollywood project headlined by one of the world’s biggest music stars. Lady Gucci is far too formally straightforward to become anything close to a global smash. Yet what it lacks in stylistic flair, it makes up for via Reggiani herself. Living proof that the rich and powerful rarely suffer fatal criminal-justice blows (even when they’re found guilty of heinous crimes), she’s a tabloid-ready figure whose defiant lack of remorse makes her a mesmerizingly grotesque monster to behold.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split opposition boosts McAuliffe's comeback bid in Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/12/opposition-mcauliffe-virginia-475454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With multiple women and people of color in the Democratic primary, groups that typically support those candidates are mostly sitting out the race so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China successfully launches Long March 7A rocket after failed first attempt...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2021/03/12/asia/china-long-march-7a-launch-intl-hnk-scli-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China successfully launched its new-generation Long March 7A rocket early Friday morning on its second attempt, sending an experimental satellite into orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vance won't seek reelection; Adds intrigue to probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/12/politics/cyrus-vance-not-running/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York prosecutor leading the most significant criminal probe against Donald Trump and his business announced Friday he is not running for reelection, putting the spotlight on who will be elected to take over the investigation into the former president and his business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of twins being born at 'all-time high', researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2270822-the-number-of-twins-in-the-world-is-the-highest-it-has-ever-been/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rising use of IVF, families having children later in life and medical advances are all contributing to growing numbers of twins being born and surviving – but the rate of twin births may now be at its peak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS creates 'elite new cell of jihadis to carry out attacks on West'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/isis-creates-elite-new-cell-23645245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: ISIS has recruited thousands of fighters in Iraq and Syria in a widespread campaign of fear, and its new leader has remained underground during the terror group's expansion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For some, wearing a mask is liberating!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/For-some-wearing-a-mask-is-liberating-16019292.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year into the pandemic, a lot has changed. And we're reminded of that every time we go...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recording reveals details of Trump call to Georgia's chief elections investigator...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Recording-reveals-details-of-Trump-call-to-16018856.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump encouraged Georgia's chief elections investigator in a December...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vaccine victories build on Trump team's work...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Biden-vaccine-victories-build-on-Trump-team-s-work-16019032.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden beckoned leaders of two of the world's largest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept seeks to build large conspiracy case against Oath Keepers...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/justice-department-seeks-to-build-large-conspiracy-case-against-oath-keepers-for-capitol-riot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department and FBI are seeking to build a large conspiracy indictment against members of the Oath Keepers for their roles in the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer puts gun control on Senate agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/03/11/schumer-puts-gun-control-on-senate-agenda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats announced plans Thursday for a floor vote on legislation to expand background checks for private gun sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama considers 'retiring' from public life...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/michelle-obama-considering-retirement-from-public-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michelle Obama is knitting and thinking about retiring from public life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAJORITY OF NY STATE LAWMAKERS CALL FOR HIM TO STEP ASIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/majority-of-ny-state-lawmakers-now-call-for-cuomo-to-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BREAKING: A majority of New York state legislators are now calling for Gov. Andrew Cuomo to resign amid sexual harassment allegations and a scandal over coronavirus deaths linked to nursing homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-year-old cop has no plans to retire...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/i-love-people-91-year-old-police-officer-still-patrolling-in-arkansas-with-no-plans-to-retire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officer L.C. “Buckshot” Smith was born and raised in his small town of Camden, Arkansas. He works for the local police department, serving a community he’s called home for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA is primed for disaster, but virus took it to another level!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-primed-disaster-covid-19-130023418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southern California is used to bouncing back from earthquakes, wildfires and other disasters, but COVID-19 brought crisis upon crisis — "cascading collective trauma," some scientists called it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Recall Hits Magic 2M Signatures; Special Election Looms...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/newsom-recall-gather-two-million-signatures-reach-goal-1234712417/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late Wednesday night, the group organizing the recall of California Governor Gavin Newsom announced it had collected over 2 million signatures. Orrin Heatlie, Chairman of The California Patriot Coa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE WAS FIRST:  Mysterious virus was just another headline --  until it wasn't...</title>
      <link>https://www.deseret.com/coronavirus/2021/3/10/22320147/coronavirus-covid-pandemic-march-11-recap-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deseret.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been an entire year since March 11 — the day everything changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resignation demands grow as police get Cuomo groping report...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dozens-democrats-demand-andrew-cuomo-resignation-71adbd6f2420a4dc71856428f3663857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo's grip on power appeared increasingly threatened Thursday as a majority of state legislators called for his resignation and police in the state...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly Mayor Predicts Mask Policies Will Be In Place For 'Another Year'...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/philadelphia-mayor-jim-kenney-gun-violence-coronavirus-pandemic-jessica-kartalija/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been a challenging year with the pandemic and rising gun violence, but Kenney says he’s optimistic looking ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minor leagues experimenting with robo umps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mlb-baseball-coronavirus-pandemic-d6b94328a0595eab7a65ddffd3669ea0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Major League Baseball will experiment with several rule changes in the minor leagues this season, including an automated strike zone, restrictions on defensive positioning and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 year after pandemic declared, 1 in 10 Americans fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/11/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactly one year after the World Health Organization declared the novel coronavirus a pandemic and about three months since the first Americans outside of clinical trials got shots, one in 10 people in the US are fully vaccinated against Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police posed as reporter in phone call with hostage taker...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/police-tv-news-maine-31bbb06f0e17559540089319a298d97b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIVERMORE FALLS, Maine (AP) — Maine State Police impersonated a journalist during a deadly standoff with a hostage taker when a TV news reporter received a call from the suspect and handed his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sailors say US sub has been ravaged by bed bugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bedbugs-aboard-a-navy-sub-is-making-life-uncomfortable-crew-says/ar-BB1euCxd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sailors worry that being kept awake by bug bites could lead to a maritime accident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Action Role-Playing Love Triangle Ends in Pipe Bomb Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/live-action-role-playing-love-triangle-ends-in-pipe-bomb-attack/ar-BB1euBZi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A love triangle among competitors in a medieval combat role-playing game inspired a gruesome pipe bomb attack last fall, according to a new federal indictment. Clayton Alexander McCoy, of Ohio, was charged Thursday in federal court with allegedly trying to blow up his romantic rival last October, leaving the man with extensive injuries and serious burns. The allegedly lovelorn bomber was an avid member of the Dagorhir live action role-playing or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGETOWN prof fired for saying black students 'at bottom of her class'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9350921/Georgetown-investigates-professor-saying-black-students-bottom-class.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgetown Law is investigating a video posted to the school's database of professors Sandra Sellers and David Batson in which Sellers claims black students are always bottom of class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEEP unveils $111,000 SUV...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/11/jeep-unveils-long-awaited-grand-wagoneer-suv-topping-111000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Grand Wagoneer SUV will test whether Jeep can expand its product range into the lucrative luxury segment and attract new customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundwork for possible impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/11/nys-assembly-speaker-lays-groundwork-for-possible-cuomo-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speaker of the New York state Assembly on Thursday asked that its Judiciary Committee open an investigation into Gov. Andrew Cuomo — the first step in potentially drafting articles of imp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 'big one' coming, quake alert system launches in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-washington-oregon-japan-earthquakes-85941f7b479f3f0dce8349d27f25613f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — People in Oregon will be better prepared for earthquakes — particularly important in the Pacific Northwest because experts say “the big one" is coming — as an early warning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Defense Secretary: He Started the Riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx83v4/even-trumps-defense-secretary-during-the-capitol-riot-blames-him-for-inciting-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Acting Secretary of Defense Chris Miller told VICE on Showtime he believes Trump’s speech caused the violent mob to attack the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Cuomo allegation referred to police... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/cuomo-allegation-potential-crime-mansion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police Thursday received word from the governor's own office that New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo may have been involved in an incident that could be a crime. The report was made by the New York State Executive Chamber as a matter of protocol in cases involving physical contact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pact with the Press...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/q-and-a/harry-meghan-and-the-pact-between-the-royals-and-the-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British writer and campaigner Anthony Barnett says the royal controversy is evidence of a country in crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer Spills Entire Plot to Murder Investigative Journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/killer-spills-the-entire-plot-to-murder-investigative-journalist/ar-BB1euGgQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maltese man who was hired as a lookout to keep tabs on Panama Papers journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia before she was killed in October 2017, told a court he and her killers argued over whether to assassinate her with a rifle at close range—they ultimately decided was “too noisy”—before settling on a bomb, because it was “cleaner.” Vincent Muscat ‘il-Koħħu,’ who is serving a 15-year-sentence after pleading guilty for his role in Galizia’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why $4-a-Gallon Gas May Be Coming This Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/why-4-a-gallon-gas-may-be-coming-your-way-this-summer/ar-BB1etgvW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON — Even as oil and gasoline prices rise, industry executives are resisting their usual impulse to pump more oil out of the ground, which could keep energy prices moving up as the economy recovers. The oil industry is predictably cyclical: When oil prices climb, producers race to drill — until the world is swimming in petroleum and prices fall. Then, energy companies that overextended themselves tumble into bankruptcy. That...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Gen C, the Covid generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/11/us/covid-generation-gen-c/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have started to use a new term -- Gen C, or Generation Covid -- to describe how the lives of today's children could be shaped by the pandemic far into the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Cuomo Accusation Referred to Albany Police... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/11/nyregion/cuomo-groping-accusation-albany-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The police characterized the alleged groping by the governor of a female aide as something that may rise “to the level of a crime.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distracted Guard, Gate Malfunction Allowed Intruder to Board Aircraft at Andrews...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2021/03/11/distracted-guard-gate-malfunction-allowed-intruder-board-aircraft-joint-base-andrews.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force says a series of missteps at Joint Base Andrews, Maryland, led to a Feb. 4 breach at the installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Navy warships head huge international fleet in show of force against Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/royal-navy-warships-head-huge-23688157</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavily-armed Type 23 frigates HMS Lancaster and Westminster join military forces from nine northern nations in a show of force against countries threatening Europe</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
