<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>First ever A-level where getting HALF answers wrong will get student A...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/08/14/first-ever-level-getting-almost-half-answers-wrong-will-get/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students who got almost half of the answers wrong in their Maths A-level this summer will get a grade A, it has emerged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAT APPLES, DRINK TEA FOR LONGER LIFE...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-live-longer-by-eating-apples-drinking-tea-flavonoids-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that eating foods rich in flavonoids, a compound found in high concentrations in foods like apples and beverages such as tea, lowers one's risk of death, particularly among heavy drinkers and smokers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chip implanted in obese people's brains zaps when think about food...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/chip-implanted-obese-peoples-brains-18932778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A clinical trial will aim to identify the pattern of brain activity that signals the start of a food binge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenspan says no barrier to treasuries falling below 0%...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ex-fed-boss-greenspan-says-there-is-no-barrier-to-treasury-yields-falling-below-zero-2019-08-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is some $15 trillion in government debt that now yields less than zero, and former Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan believes there’s no reason...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vanishing $200 Million Blockbuster...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/vanishing-200-million-blockbuster-1231467 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an increasingly stratified box office landscape dominated by Disney, not a single film this year so far has topped out between $200 million to $300 million domestically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills Suffers Shopping Slump!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/beverly-hills-suffers-shopping-slump-trump-china-trade-war-1231083</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's battle with Beijing and visa policies on Gulf nations are taking a brutal toll on the tony retail zone, with sales down double digits and no relief in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror pics show abused elephant forced to take part in religious festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/abused-elephant-festival-sri-lanka-18930000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PICTURES of an elephant's emaciated body - normally hidden by its colourful costume - have gone viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like horror movie': Camper saves family from savage wolf attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Like-a-horror-movie-Camper-saves-family-of-14303149.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was about half past midnight when Russ Fee woke up to the sound of frantic shouts coming from a campsite next to his in Canada's Banff National Park. From within his tent, he listened, quickly discerning that the voices belonged to a man and a woman. They were screaming for help.  "I threw my shoes on. My wife tossed me a lantern," Fee said in an interview Tuesday with the radio show "Calgary Eyeopener." "I popped out of the tent and just started running toward their tent sort of yelling, 'I'm here! I'm here! What's wrong?'"  Fee, who is from Calgary, told the program that he expected to find "two really scared parents" whose child had wandered off into the woods. Instead, the sight that greeted him was much more distressing.  The family's tent was in shambles, Fee said, and sticking out of its entrance was the rear end of a large wolf.  In what officials with Parks Canada are calling a "very rare incident," a wolf attacked a New Jersey couple and their two children who were visiting the national park in Banff, Alberta, early Friday - a harrowing encounter that may have ended differently if it weren't for Fee's quick thinking, Canadian Broadcasting Corp. reported.  "We are forever grateful to Russ who came to our aid," Elisa Rispoli, whose husband, Matt, was injured in the attack, wrote on Facebook. Describing Fee as a "guardian angel," Elisa added that the Canadian man probably saved her husband's life.  "It could have been so so much worse, and we are just feeling so thankful that we are all still sitting here as a complete family," she wrote.  The Rispolis were asleep in their tent at the park's Rampart Creek Campground when they were jolted awake after midnight by the wolf.  "It was like something out of a horror movie," Elisa wrote in the Facebook post.  Matt...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuser files suit against estate, 'madam'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/jeffrey-epstein-accuser-jennifer-araoz-sues-ghislaine-maxwell-3-other-n1041901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Araoz alleges she was repeatedly sexually assaulted by Jeffrey Epstein at his New York townhouse when she was 14 and 15, including a 2002 rape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS set to seize passport if owe money...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/14/taxpayers-owing-a-lot-of-money-could-have-their-passports-revoked.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may not be able to get a new passport or renew your existing one if you owe the IRS more than $52,000. Worse, your existing one might simply be revoked. Here's what you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish Court Finds Rapper A$AP Rocky Guilty of Assault...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/world/201908141076549028-swedish-court-us-rapper-suspended-sentence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets late last month, President Donald Trump demanded that Sweden should “give [US rapper] A$AP Rocky his freedom”. Stockholm responded by stating that the Swedish judicial system is independent and that “everyone is equal before the law”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA descends on Icelandic lava field to prepare for Mars...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-08-nasa-descends-icelandic-lava-field.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To prepare for the next mission to Mars in 2020, NASA has taken to the lava fields of Iceland to get its new robotic space explorer ready for the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone Scam Targets Man With Bloody Pics; Threatens To Kill Family Unless Pays Cartel...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/13/scam-brooklyn-bloody-pics-cartel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, who hid his face in fear, says last week he got text messages with pictures of blood soaked and mangled people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing god: Temple puts faith in robot priest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/playing-god-japan-temple-puts-faith-robot-priest-043640106.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The android Kannon, based on the Buddhist deity of mercy, preaches sermons at Kodaiji temple in Kyoto, and its human colleagues predict that with artificial intelligence it could one day acquire unlimited wisdom. "This robot will never die, it will just keep updating itself and evolving,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S posts 48% drop in profit...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/macys-posts-48-drop-profit-121501023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company said on Wednesday inventory became a challenge as it also missed the mark with its key women's sportswear private brands and a higher decline in international tourism. "We had a slow start to the quarter and finished below our expectations," Chief Executive Officer Jeff Gennette</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman claims emotional support dog locked in plane restroom...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/woman-sues-american-airlines-claims-emotional-support-dog/story?id=64958059</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The passenger, Avigail Diveroli, said the dog helps her battle severe anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABCNEWS: 36 cases invoking 'Trump' in connection with violence, threats, assaults...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/blame-abc-news-finds-17-cases-invoking-trump/story?id=58912889 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump insists he deserves no blame for divisions in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The No. 1 job in America: Tax manager...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-no-1-job-in-america-with-the-best-career-opportunities-pays-112000-a-year-and-its-not-in-tech-2019-08-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This analysis is based on median salary, overall job satisfaction and the number of job openings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant who contracted measles dies amid rise in outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Israeli-flight-attendant-who-contracted-measles-14301329.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli flight attendant died after contracting measles and falling into a coma, Israeli media reported Tuesday, the latest incident amid growing measles outbreaks worldwide.  More cases of the virus were reported in the first half 2019 than in any other year since 2006, the World Health Organization announced Monday. Compared to this time last year, there have already been nearly three times more reported cases of measles. While many of the measles outbreaks occurred in places with low vaccination rates, the WHO said, others are occurred in nations that have high rates, resulting from "lack of access to quality healthcare or vaccination services, conflict and displacement, misinformation about vaccines, or low awareness about the need to vaccinate."  "The United States has reported its highest measles case count in 25 years," the WHO said in the announcement.  The woman, a mother of three, is just the third death from measles in Israel in the past 15 years, according to the Times of Israel. In 2018 an 18-month-old child and an 82-year-old woman also died from the virus.  In a statement to the Jewish Press, the airline, El Al, said that "the company is bowing its head over the death of a member of El Al's aircrew. The company will continue to act on the matter in accordance with the health ministry's guidelines. Once the case became known, the company acted to vaccinate the company's aircrews. The company shares the deep grief of the family and will continue to accompany the family."  The Washington Post reported on April 17 that the 43-year-old flight attendant had flown in late March on an El Al flight from New York's John F. Kennedy International Airport to Israel and was later admitted to the hospital after developing encephalitis, a complication of the illness in which the brain swells.  In early April, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watching sports good for you: Cardio workout similar to 90-min walk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7355817/Watching-football-good-you.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of Leeds analysed 25 fans of the city's football team over three games. They found the supporters' heart rates increased by around 64 per cent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Demotes top DC editor over tweets...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/jonathan-weisman-demoted-nyt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times on Tuesday demoted deputy Washington editor Jonathan Weisman following a series of questionable tweets about people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study reveals emotional journey of digital detox while travelling...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-08-reveals-emotional-journey-digital-detox.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research reveals the emotional journey that tourists go on when they disconnect from technology and social media while travelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 2020 Rust Belt Pitch Threatened by Manufacturing Recession...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-2020-rust-belt-pitch-080000058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. President Donald Trump has been boasting about creating manufacturing jobs in states key to his re-election, but an emerging recession in the sector threatens to reverse that trend and imperil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Brink of Blackouts, Texas Makes Case for Power Plant Boom...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/brink-blackouts-texas-makes-case-052950761.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It may be time to start building power plants in Texas again.The state’s generators made a killing this week as unrelenting heat sent electricity prices skyrocketing to unprecedented levels, briefly blowing past a $9,000 a megawatt-hour price ceiling. That put producers more than two-thirds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body odor? Bacteria-embedded bodysuit may help...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190814090751-fs65x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CLOTHING/SKIN II (PIX, TV):Body odour? Bacteria-embedded bodysuit may help</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY: Video captures brutal attack on comedian Andy Dick...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/video-captures-brutal-attack-comedian-andy-dick-new-orleans-police-n1042086 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video appears to show the moment an unidentified man viciously sucker-punched the 53-year-old actor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guards were 'asleep and faked log entries'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7354679/Corrections-officers-prison-Jeffrey-Epstein-held-falsified-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corrections officers at a New York prison where Jeffrey Epstein was being held had 'fallen asleep and falsified reports' to show that they checked on him when they hadn't before his apparent suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How stocks performed under each president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2019/business/stock-market-by-president/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump often cites the stock market as a scorecard of his policies. Here’s how the S&amp;P 500 performed under each president from Reagan to Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Say Can't Afford Vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/americans-say-they-can-t-afford-a-vacation-1.1301199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 40% of Americans have opted out of a getaway over the past year specifically because of the cost, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Meat Next Sin Tax?</title>
      <link>https://www.accountingtoday.com/articles/is-red-meat-more-expensive-could-be-next-sin-tax-after-sugar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accountingtoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meat could be a target for higher taxes given criticism of the industry’s role in climate change, deforestation and animal cruelty, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING: Yield curve nearly inverted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/13/us-bonds-yield-curve-at-flattest-level-since-2007-amid-risk-off-sentiment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The yield on the 10-year Treasury note threatens to break below that of the 2-year while the 30-year bond rate neared an all-time low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA bans some APPLE laptops from flights over fire risk...</title>
      <link>https://au.finance.yahoo.com/news/faa-bans-recalled-apple-laptops-230926613.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. airline safety regulators banned select MacBook Pro laptops on flights after Apple Inc. recently said that some units had batteries that posed a fire risk.In a statement, the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration said it was “aware of the recalled batteries that are used in some Apple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge overseeing key Jeffrey Epstein case dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/25/judge-jeffrey-epstein-case-dies-1292394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan-based U.S. District Court Judge Robert Sweet passed away Sunday at age 96.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waning of American Power? </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/13/world/asia/trump-asia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration has taken a hands-off approach to conflicts — from Kashmir to Hong Kong to the rivalry between Japan and South Korea — as Asian officials escalate the battles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backs down again, delays new tariffs on China...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/trump-backs-down-again-delays-many-new-tariffs-on-china-until-december/ar-AAFKH9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Scrambles As Rogue Drone Captures Epstein Raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/fbi-scrambles-as-rogue-drone-captures-epstein-raid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agents cover windows with blankets, cardboard upon noticing peeping drone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women accuse opera legend Domingo of sexual harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2d51d690d004992b8cfba3bad827ae9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Placido Domingo, one of the most celebrated and powerful men in opera, has tried to pressure women into sexual relationships by dangling jobs and then sometimes punishing the women...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMING BATTLE BEGINS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/89ed1bbe8bc442319d16cd615db8a5c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The newly combined ViacomCBS will invest in more movies and TV shows and try to sell more advertising as it seeks to become a bigger player in the growing business of streaming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDSTONE MOST POWERFUL WOMAN IN MEDIA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/after-years-of-battle-shari-redstone-runs-an-empire-of-her-own/ar-AAFKMz4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Sues CNN's Don Lemon for Alleged Assault at Bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/man-sues-cnns-don-lemon-for-alleged-assault-at-sag-harbor-bar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is suing Don Lemon, claiming the CNN host attacked him at a Hamptons bar last summer. The suit, obtained by Mediaite, was filed Sunday and seeks unspecified damages for "emotional pain and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC Chief Says Willing to Break Up Companies Amid Big Tech Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-13/ftc-chief-says-willing-to-break-up-companies-amid-big-tech-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA Made GOOGLE Give Up Info on Everyone in Area in Hunt for Antifa...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/manhattan-da-cy-vance-made-google-give-up-info-on-everyone-in-area-in-hunt-for-antifa-after-proud-boys-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;…and investigators ended up targeting the wrong people, at least in part from that information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple Married 68 Years Has Worn Matching Outfits Every Day...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/12/secret-to-happy-marriage-couple-matches-outfits-for-seven-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s one thing to match on your wedding day but it’s another to match for 68 years. That’s what Francis and Rosemary Klontz have been doing for seven decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LYFT's 'Woke' Image Collides With Flurry of Sex Assault Suits...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-13/lyft-s-woke-image-collides-with-flurry-of-sex-assault-lawsuits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Referred to HIMSELF as 'Fredo'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/13/chris-cuomo-once-referred-to-himself-as-fredo-in-radio-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN anchor Chris Cuomo, who was captured on a viral video getting into a profanity-laced exchange with a person who called him “Fredo,” once referred to himself as the hapless “Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery: Old TVs placed on porches of 50 homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/local/henrico/mystery-in-henrico-old-tvs-were-placed-on-front-porches/article_53bef019-a18e-593a-a5de-81c03a870826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 50 television sets were mysteriously left on the front porches of homes throughout the Hampshire neighborhood in western Henrico County, surprising residents who found them Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau calls for gun control as violence spikes in Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-guns-idUSKCN1V31U9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said on Tuesday that a recent spate of gu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim women 'sterilized' in Chinese 're-education' camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/asia/chinas-sickening-acts-on-female-prisoners-at-reeducation-camps/news-story/34d531c19a5bb060881a76ac8b478609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is forcibly sterilising women held in its vast network of “re-education” camps which house political and religious prisoners, survivors have claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller alum landing cushy jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mueller-alumni-landing-cushy-jobs-at-law-firms-universities-even-a-book-deal-after-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top investigators who worked alongside former Special Counsel Robert Mueller have certainly landed on their feet since the shuttering of the two-year Russia probe, securing big jobs at prominent law firms and universities -- and even a book deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Better than LeBron:' Meet basketball's next teen phenom...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/13/emoni-bates-is-basketballs-next-teenage-phenom-better-than-lebron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some teenage phenoms, such as LeBron James, live up to the insane hype assigned to them, while others end up like Freddy Adu. The world will be watching to see how 15-year-old hoopster Emoni Bates …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Paid Contractors to Transcribe Users' Audio Chats...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-paid-hundreds-contractors-transcribe-190743545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Facebook Inc. has been paying hundreds of outside contractors to transcribe clips of audio from users of its services, according to people with knowledge of the work.The work has rattled the contract employees, who are not told where the audio was recorded or how it was obtained -- only</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Orthorexia' vying for classification as mental disorder...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/orthorexia-vying-for-a-place-in-the-dsm-as-more-people-become-obsessed-with-clean-eating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether it’s a ‘real’ mental disease or an imaginary one, the behaviours and consequences are certainly real, according to a new study’s author</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway producer arrested on child porn charges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1cac49f35090418e9c6f060db4f39154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A Broadway producer whose first big-budget show was derailed by a con man's false financial promises has been arrested on child porn charges. The producer, Ben Sprecher, was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating Apps Expose Precise Locations Of 10 Millions Users...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/four-major-dating-apps-expose-precise-locations-of-10-million-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Updated: In some countries, such lax security can be of real risk to a user’s personal safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKYNEWS LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=siyW0GOBtbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch Sky News live. Today's top stories: MPs say hands-free mobile phones should be banned while driving, more than 200 people who say their babies were aff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN STANDS BY ANCHOR...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/celebrities/2019/08/13/cnn-stands-anchor-chris-cuomo-after-nsfw-fredo-video/1994358001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Cuomo was capturedÂ during a heated exchange with a man who called him "Fredo," which Cuomo says is a racist slur comparable toÂ the N-word.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave American flag, sing national anthem...</title>
      <link>https://www.theweek.in/news/world/2019/08/13/hong-kong-protesters-wave-american-flag-sing-national-anthem.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theweek.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese media have accused the United States of supporting the riots in Hong Kong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Allahu Akbar'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9710046/sydney-stabbing-cbd-attack-news-latest-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEROES have fought off a knife-wielding attacker with a chair before pinning him to the ground with a milk crate after he allegedly stabbed a woman and ran through the streets of Sydney with a huge…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OVER LITTLE BLACK BOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9709564/jeffrey-epstein-british-contacts-mick-jagger-tony-blair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein listed 301 British associates in a “little black book” of society figures uncovered by the FBI, it was revealed last night. Among the contacts were celebrities such as M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's raining plastic: Microscopic fibers fall from sky in Rocky Mountains...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/aug/12/raining-plastic-colorado-usgs-microplastics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discovery raises new questions about the amount of plastic waste permeating the air, water, and soil virtually everywhere on Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Executive Editor Dean Baquet Admits Racism Headline Was 'F*cking Mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-york-times-editor-dean-baquet-trump-unity-headline-was-a-fcking-mess</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a lengthy town-hall meeting on Monday, the paper’s top brass addressed a bevy of recent controversies centering around the Times’ coverage of Trump, race, and politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campus Men Were Punished Over #MeToo Allegations. Now They're Suing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/campus-men-were-punished-over-metoo-allegations-now-theyre-suing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused men everywhere are suing over due process. “If you’re found responsible for sexual misconduct at a university in America, your future is arguably over,” said one attorney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Extreme Larks': Life of Person Who Wakes Up Really, Really Early...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/08/how-know-if-youre-morning-person/595990/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Extreme larks” get up naturally when some people have hardly gone to bed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man sent woman 10,000 texts in 12 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/parkland/fl-ne-parkland-man-accused-20190813-5osyicfftzaklmi4clp5ggcjza-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Parkland man, Nicholas C. Nelson, 48, is accused of sending a woman more than 10,000 text messages in less than a two-week period in April. Some were sexually explicit and some were threatening, according to a Broward County arrest affidavit. Nelson is being held without bond because of a case in Palm Beach County that court officials said involved a different victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Areas With More Fast Food Restaurants Report More Heart Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/areas-with-more-fast-food-restaurants-report-more-heart-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study out of Australia shows a connection between the number of fast food restaurants in a town or city and the number of people who suffer from heart attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOREST ANIMAL POPULATIONS PLUMMET BY HALF SINCE 1970...</title>
      <link>https://www.scotsman.com/news/people/forest-animal-populations-have-plummeted-by-half-since-1970-report-warns-1-4982614</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scotsman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Populations of animals that live in the world's forests have declined by more than half in the past 50 years, a study warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3022668/riot-police-protesters-clash-unprecedented-violence-hong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters surrounded man in terminal building, accusing him of being an undercover security officer from mainland China. There was then more trouble outside the building as protesters turned on police who were there initially to help ambulance take man to hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP NEUTRAL</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/08/trump-china-hong-kong-protests-1452624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president regularly thrashes China over trade policy but has been mostly silent on the growing pro-democracy protests in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor handed out almost 10,000 painkiller prescriptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article233944487.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSVIACOM merge to form $30 billion media company...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/cbs-viacom-merge-form-30-billion-media-company-n1041306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With streaming video now the leading story, the two companies are fusing their war chests to better compete for viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guard Was Substitute...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/in-short-staffed-jail-epstein-was-left-alone-for-hours-guard-was-substitute/ar-AAFHzBc?sf18867990=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMES B. STEWART:  The Day Jeffrey Epstein Told Me He Had Dirt on Powerful People...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/the-day-jeffrey-epstein-told-me-he-had-dirt-on-powerful-people/ar-AAFI7k5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO GOES CRAZY!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/cnns-chris-cuomo-filmed-threatening-heckler-who-called-him-fredo-ill-fcking-ruin-your-sht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video going viral on Twitter tonight shows CNN's Chris Cuomo getting pretty heated with someone who called him "Fredo."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial recognition mistook 1 in 5 California lawmakers for criminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-12/facial-recognition-software-mistook-1-in-5-california-lawmakers-for-criminals-says-aclu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 20% of legislators were erroneously matched to a person arrested when the ACLU used face-scanning software to screen their pictures against a criminal database.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino defends depicting Bruce Lee as 'arrogant a**hole'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/bruce-lee-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-quentin-tarantino-daughter-shannon-lee-brad-pitt-mike-moh-a9055196.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director Paul Haggis, Rape Accuser Fight Over Morning-After Texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/paul-haggis-rape-accuser-fight-her-morning-text-messages-1230923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In communications with a friend, Haleigh Breest writes about "getting a ride home" from Haggis and discusses in graphic terms the physical impact of the encounter: “He was so rough and aggressive never ever again!!!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global censorship minefield for NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-netflix-navigates-increased-scrutiny-international-territories-1229760 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the streamer expands rapidly worldwide, it finds itself embroiled in regional controversies — for example, there were calls in Jordan to ban a show in which a female actor kisses two different boys — while navigating a minefield of local sensibilities and regulatory and political challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bystanders use chairs, milk crate to trap man on stabbing rampage in Sydney...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Significantly-brave-bystanders-use-chairs-and-a-14300265.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blood-spattered man climbed atop a Mercedes-Benz at a stoplight in downtown Sydney and held a knife in the air. He'd already stabbed one woman at a nearby hotel, police later said, and tried to attack others in the busy commercial district on Tuesday.  That's when a bystander, armed only with a wooden chair, jumped into action. Others quickly helped. Soon, the civilians subdued the attacker, pinning him to the pavement with chairs and a milk crate until police arrived.  "They were significantly brave people," New South Wales Police Superintendent Gavin Wood told reporters at the crime scene. "To approach a person with a mind set of obviously what this person did, with clear evidence of a stabbing previously, these people are heroes."  Police have identified the attacker as Mert Ney, 21, the Sydney Morning Herald reported. Authorities told the newspaper they do not consider the attack to be terrorism-related, but they are investigating. Ney had a history of mental health issues, the Morning Herald reported.  "Information was found on him that would suggest he had some ideologies related to terrorism . . . but he has no apparent links to other terrorist organisations," NSW Police Commissioner Mick Fuller told the Morning Herald. "It is not currently classed as a terrorist incident. . . . As investigation continues, we will reassess that."  Ney is now in police custody. The woman stabbed in a hotel is expected to survive, police said, but investigators later found another woman dead in a nearby apartment. They're working to determine if that death is related to the stabbing attack.  It's not yet clear what set off the attack, which Wood called "unprovoked," noting that the attacker "stabbed an innocent woman for no specific reason."  Police first got a call around 2 p.m....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE FOR FREEDOM!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/james-carafano-what-hong-kong-unrest-tells-us-about-chinas-plans-for-the-rest-of-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Hong Kong, China is acting like a global bully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY: Andy Dick sucker-punched after performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox8live.com/2019/08/13/andy-dick-attacked-after-french-quarter-show-representative-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox8live.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A representative for Andy Dick says the controversial comedian was sucker punched, knocked unconscious and put in the ICU after a performance in the French Quarter early Saturday (Aug. 10).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUMANOID HEADED TO SPACE STATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7352321/Russias-space-agency-releases-eerie-footage-human-like-android-Fedor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;icknamed Fedor, the anthropomorphous machine - which is remarkably agile - was seen undergoing a battery of stress-tests at the Baikonur Cosmodrome in Kazakhstan, last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUT OF CONTROL:  Federal Spending Sets New Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/3727014000000-federal-spending-sets-record-through-july-treasury-runs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Alex Wong) (CNSNews.com) - The federal government spent a record $3,727,014,000,000 in the first ten months of fiscal 2019 (October through July), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement released today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/asia/live-news/hong-kong-protests-airport-chaos-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos has erupted at Hong Kong's airport as police officers clash with protesters. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAPCHAT TRIES AGAIN: Announces $380 sunglasses with 3D cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/13/snapchat-spectacles-3-price-release-3d-cameras.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snapchat Spectacles 3 have a stainless steel design and cameras that shoot in 3D and let users add augmented reality effects to videos and photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession fears rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/13/investors-flock-into-bonds-as-recession-fears-rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the most bullish outlook on fixed income since November 2008, as lower yields mean higher prices and capital appreciation for bondholders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrieking heard from cell...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-death-shrieking-heard-jail-cell-morning-he-died-metropolitan-correctional-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress is the latest to start investigating his apparent suicide over the weekend​, with new reports raising questions about the federal jail where he was being held</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military forces mass at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hong-kong-protest-airport-flights-cancelled-china-defense-forces-mass-at-border-today-2019-08-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese security forces mass at border of semi-autonomous city in ominous display of power as Beijing calls protests an "existential threat"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students sign petition to ban 'offensive' white man in crosswalk signs...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=13566</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'll totally sign that"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Posted On 4Chan Before Announced...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/janelytvynenko/fdny-investigating-jeffrey-epstein-4chan-post</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 38 minutes before news outlets first reported Jeffrey Epstein's death in prison, a 4chan user published a detailed post about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans apply for jobs at food plant raided by ICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/08/13/americans-apply-jobs-koch-foods-after-ice-raid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 150 locals sought jobs at Koch Foods' chicken processing plants in Mississippi, following the August 7 removal of illegal migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-fat diet 'stops brain signalling when full'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/world/high-fat-diet-stops-brain-from-signalling-when-you-are-full-943490.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breakingnews.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study suggests a previously unknown gut-brain connection that helps explain how extra servings lead to weight gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  VERIZON sells early social-media darling TUMBLR for 'well below' $20 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/verizon-tumblr-wordpress-automattic-e6645edd-bc73-45c2-9380-9fe8ca34291f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yahoo acquired the company in 2013 for $1.1 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer Fatally Shoots Self In 8th NYPD Suicide This Year...</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/officer-fatally-shoots-self-8th-nypd-suicide-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 35-year-old police officer took his own life early Tuesday morning, marking the eighth NYPD suicide this year and the sixth since June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/akcay_nuri/status/1161304509068578817</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Hong Kong havaalanında polis ve göstericiler arasında çok sert çatışmalar yaşanıyor. -Polisler göstericilerden bildiğiniz dayak yiyor. https://t.co/NWWIz1av0R”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hanged himself with prison bedsheet'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/12/jeffrey-epstein-hanged-himself-with-prison-bedsheet-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convicted pedophile apparently, who was 6 feet tall, killed himself by kneeling toward the floor and strangling himself with the makeshift noose, a law enforcement source said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American household debt nears $14 trillion... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/11/bankruptcy-filings-rising-across-the-country-and-it-could-get-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bankruptcies are back — flashing warnings that more Americans are knee-deep in debt in big cities like New York. While total bankruptcy petitions nationwide by consumers and businesses are still we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chlamydia vaccine shows promise in early tests...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chlamydia-vaccine-shows-promise-early-tests-223135618.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first chlamydia vaccine encouragingly triggered an immune response in women during preliminary clinical trials and was found to be safe, researchers said Tuesday. Further trials, starting later this year, will show whether the vaccine actually protects against the sexually transmitted disease (STD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Working on Pill for Loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/all-the-lonely-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some, the idea is just another sign of the creeping medicalization of everyday human woes: Is it really the best we can do to fix the loneliness ‘epidemic’?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Loomer Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN! RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://granite3.com/advertise/drudge-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;granite3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deficit Widens 27%...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-budget-deficit-already-exceeds-180000048.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. fiscal deficit has already exceeded the full-year figure for last year, as spending growth outpaces revenue.The gap grew to $866.8 billion in the first 10 months of the fiscal year, up 27% from the same period a year earlier, the Treasury Department said in its monthly budget</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive-in sex booths proposed for historic Berlin airport...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/08/12/europe/berlin-tempelhof-sex-work-sex-booth-intl-scli-grm/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berlin's former Tempelhof airport has witnessed some major events in its time -- a Nazi airfield during World War II, it was the site of the Berlin airlift during the Cold War, and most recently an emergency shelter for refugees fleeing Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of Argentina Default Loom Large as Traders Dump Everything...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-set-sell-off-argentina-030759812.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Suddenly, fears of a full-blown financial crisis in Argentina have once again come rushing to the fore.In the wake of President Mauricio Macri’s stunning rout in primary elections over the weekend, investors dumped its stocks, bonds and currency en masse in a selloff that left much of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes undermine fragile truce over Jerusalem holy site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/04c82bdb58e24c348a88694637e71a7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — It wasn't inevitable that the overlap of Jewish and Muslim holidays would lead to clashes at a Jerusalem site deeply revered by both faiths. But when rumors circulated that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIOT POLICE STORM HKG</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/riot-police-storm-hong-kong-airport-day-cancellations/story?id=64941993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong International Airport has canceled all remaining flight departures for the second straight day due to protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Showbiz, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news, politics, culture, technology, health, and more, through its articles, podcasts, videos, and flagship magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://www.pravdareport.com/world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pravdareport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer presses President Donald Trump on money to address gun violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times opinion columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mediaite is the top U.S. website covering the intersection of media and politics with original reporting and bi-partisan commentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRAP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>http://www.jewishworldreview.com/0219/shapiro_archives.php3#.XG2A5KJKhhE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jewishworldreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELLO! brings you the latest celebrity &amp; royal news from the UK &amp; around the world, magazine exclusives, fashion, beauty, lifestyle news, celeb babies, weddings, pregnancies and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighter dies after working 24 hours in a row...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/fdny-lieutenant-dies-after-24-hour-shift</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say a New York City fire lieutenant died of a heart attack after going home from a 24-hour tour of duty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC is the world leader in business news and real-time financial market coverage. Find fast, actionable information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch CBSN the live news stream from CBS News and get the latest, breaking news headlines of the day for national news and world news today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Morning America was the week's most-watched morning show, and delivered its largest total audience in six weeks. NBC's Today marked its 189th consecutive week at No. 1 among adults 25-54.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking the biggest stories in celebrity and entertainment news. Get exclusive access to the latest stories, photos, and video as only TMZ can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and analysis from the U.S. and around the world at WSJ.com. Politics, Economics, Markets, Life &amp; Arts, and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Magazine energizes people around shared interests, igniting important conversations on the news, politics, style, and culture that drive the world forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters pose challenge to Chinese communist rule...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190813150804-788jt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-PROTESTS/ (WRAPUP 2, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 2-Clashes at Hong Kong airport; U.N. urges restraint over protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Farm $1,300,000 In Red...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/the-average-u-s-farm-is-1300000-in-debt-and-now-the-worst-farming-crisis-in-modern-history-is-upon-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We haven't seen anything like this since the Great Depression of the 1930s.  Leading up to this year, farm incomes had been trending lower for most of the past decade, and meanwhile farm debt levels have been absolutely exploding.  So U.S. farmers were desperate for a really good year, but instead 2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston news, sports, politics, opinion, entertainment, weather and obituaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
