<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Can Navy fight and win war?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/578216-can-the-us-navy-fight-and-win-a-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worrying question is whether the U.S. Navy is fit and prepared for a conflict with an adversary that is at least as well equipped and armed as it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Challenges Biden Again With Broad Cybersurveillance Operation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/25/russia-challenges-biden-again-with-broad-cybersurveillance-operation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEA ISLAND, Ga. — Russia’s premier intelligence agency has launched another campaign to pierce thousands of U.S. government, corporate and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case aginst Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2021/10/25/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-whistleblower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC has been asked to probe whether Mark Zuckerberg's ironclad management style, described in newly released documents and by insiders, led to disastrous outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIS CLOSE: McAuliffe, Youngkin tied in gov race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578241-mcauliffe-youngkin-dead-even-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin are locked in a tied race nearly one week out from Virginia's gubernatorial election, according to a poll released on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538: Biden approval rating dips to new low...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/biden-approval-rating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest polls on President Joe Biden’s approval ratings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Thai Temple Where Tattoos Come to Life...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/25/inside-the-thai-temple-where-tattoos-come-to-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sky was streaked with purple when I boarded the early-morning train from Bangkok to the Nakhon Chai Si District</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FACEBOOK Papers: Docs reveal internal fury and dissent over site's policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/facebook-whistleblower-documents-detail-deep-look-facebook-rcna3580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook whistleblower documents reveal internal dissent over the company's policies and frustrations with its efforts to address its problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tired of waiting for asylum in southern Mexico, thousands of migrants march north...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/tired-of-waiting-for-asylum-in-southern-mexico-thousands-of-migrants-march-north/ar-AAPUcDU </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden meeting with pope carries resonance as disputes divide U.S. Catholics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-e2-80-99s-meeting-with-the-pope-carries-resonance-as-disputes-divide-us-catholics/ar-AAPTpbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second Catholic president, like the leader of the Catholic church, is striving to move conservative institutions in a more liberal direction after rising to leadership late in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spent most of his covid business loan on one item: $57,789 POKEMON card...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-man-spent-most-of-his-covid-19-business-loan-on-16560641.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Department news releases document a litany of luxury items allegedly bought with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How party mom courted kids with SNAPCHAT, TIFFANY jewelry, Tahoe trip, drunken parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2021/10/24/how-los-gatos-party-mom-courted-their-kids-with-snapchat-tiffany-jewelry-tahoe-trip-drunken-parties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They thought she was the adult in the room. But they soon discovered how a Los Gatos boy’s mother was manipulating their kids through texts and Snapchat that would also be her undoing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West braces for Turkey's possible expulsion of 10 envoys...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/world/west-braces-turkeys-possible-expulsion-10-envoys-2266766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA: Turkey's relations with Western allies edged towards their deepest crisis of President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's 19-year rule on Monday (Oct 25) as world capitals braced for Ankara's possible expulsion of ambassadors from the US and nine other countries. The lira touched new historic lows ahead of a C</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria threatens lockdown for unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/578137-austrian-chancellor-considering-implementing-lockdown-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian Chancellor Alexander Schallenberg says he is considering imposing a lockdown on people who are not vaccinated against the coronavirus if case numbers continue rising, the Associated Press reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Dems plan billionaires' unrealized gains tax to help fund spending bill...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/24/dems-plan-billionaires-unrealized-gains-tax-to-help-fund-2t-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s spending package continues to stall as senior Democrats are hoping to finalize a proposal on a new annual tax on billionaires’ unrealized capital gains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Mexican Dealmaker in Shanghai Behind Trump's SPAC Deal...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meet-mexican-dealmaker-shanghai-behind-140550584.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A Mexican dealmaker in China was one of the key architects behind former President Donald Trump’s deal with a special purpose acquisition company. Most Read from BloombergCities' Answer to Sprawl? Go Wild.Hamburg Is at the Heart of Germany’s Growing Dilemma Over ChinaWhy Americans and Britons Are Rushing to Buy Idyllic Homes in ItalyOne of California’s Wealthiest Counties Could Run Out of Water Next SummerThe Top Money Maker at Deutsche Bank Reaps Billions From SingaporeShanghai-b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In France, Trump-like TV pundit rocks presidential campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-france-paris-europe-migration-a681f51a334fe7e2ccc680d2b52ab4b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A survivor of the terrible journey to Auschwitz remembered how the youngest wailed. There were 99 children squeezed among 751 adults gasping for air, crazed by thirst and hunger, aboard convoy No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin was practicing pointing revolver at camera...</title>
      <link>/https://nypost.com/2021/10/25/alec-baldwin-was-practicing-pointing-revolver-at-camera-during-fatal-prop-gun-mishap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Norah O'Donnell in danger of losing top spot at 'CBS EVENING NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/24/norah-odonnell-in-danger-of-losing-anchor-spot-at-cbs-evening-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norah O’Donnell is in danger of losing the top spot at “CBS Evening News,” as cost-slashing execs at the broadcasting giant quietly search for her replacement amid sagging ratings, The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAND PAUL: CRYPTO COULD REPLACE DOLLAR AS WORLD'S RESERVE CURRENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/preview-axios-on-hbo-rand-paul-a9267a71-e3cb-4edb-b83d-d685e63d0cce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catch the full interview on Sunday at 6 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mag 3.9 quake rattles SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/magnitude-3-9-earthquake-rattles-socal-strikes-near-maywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 3.9 magnitude earthquake shook parts of Southern California early Sunday. The quake was centered near the Los Angeles County community of Maywood. Check back for updates on this developing story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELTICS support for Enes Kanter after Beijing criticisms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/celtics-support-enes-kanter-amid-his-stance-for-tibet-and-against-chinese-government/ar-AAPQEUW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran center on Wednesday posted a video on his social media platforms in which he blasted the Chinese government for its policies regarding Tibet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan hurtling toward collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/24/asia/afghanistan-collapse-sweden-pakistan-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghanistan will shortly collapse into chaos unless the international community acts rapidly, Swedish and Pakistani ministers warned on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tahoe braces for 100 mph winds, 3 feet of snow...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/atmospheric-river-Tahoe-Sierra-California-2021-16558088.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snow levels in the Tahoe Basin could drop as low as 6,000 feet on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgruntled employee sentenced to 6 months for releasing rats in workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-disgruntled-employee-has-been-sentenced-to-6-months-in-prison-for-releasing-rats-at-his-workplace/ar-AAPTDB9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John O'Neill, a 61-year-old man from Cork, in Ireland, released two live rats in a council building after an alleged dispute with his manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci under fire after 'dogs were locked in cages to be eaten ALIVE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3920949/fauci-puppy-experiments-beagles-locked-in-cage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DR Anthony Fauci is under fire for allegedly funding experiments where beagle puppies were locked in cages with hungry sandflies that would eat them alive. The non-profit organization White Coat Wa…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
