<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>11 Iranians arrested in Arizona after jumping U.S.-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/3/iranians-arrested-border-parol-jumping-us-border-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents arrested 11 Iranians Monday after they snuck across the border into Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST MASS VAX SITE OPENS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/federal-government-opening-first-mass-covid-19-vaccination-sites-california-n1256611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort is a change in course from the Trump administration, which left vaccine administration largely to the states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry took private jet to 'environmental' award...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/john-kerry-private-jet-iceland-climate-award </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARLER CEO Ousted by Mercer...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/media/parler-ceo-john-matze-says-hes-been-terminated-by-board-i-did-not-participate-in-this-decision</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parler has terminated CEO John Matze, according to a memo Matze sent to staffers that has been obtained by Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors can't find Kyle Rittenhouse, seek arrest warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.wisn.com/article/prosecutors-kyle-rittenhouse-violated-conditions-of-release/35410096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wisn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge allowed Rittenhouse, now 18, of Antioch, Illinois, to be released in November on $2 million cash bail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tries to board flight from Florida with 22 pounds of meth...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/03/man-tries-to-board-flight-from-florida-with-22-pounds-of-meth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger at Orlando International Airport in Florida was arrested for trying to board his flight with 22 pounds of crystal meth, authorities said. A TSA agent stopped Eli Brown at a gate around …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to Vote on Punishment...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/03/democrats-marjorie-taylor-greene-committee-posts-465546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steny Hoyer announced that the House will vote Thursday on a measure to punish Greene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Outraged' NYTIMES Staffers Demand Reporter Apologize for Slur...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/ny-times-staffers-send-outraged-221537209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orjan F. Ellingvag/GettyNew York Times staffers on Wednesday sent a letter to the paper’s top bosses criticizing their handling of complaints that star journalist Donald McNeil Jr. used racist language while on a Times-sponsored student trip.As The Daily Beast reported last week, McNeil, a veteran Times reporter who has emerged as one of the paper’s most high-profile reporters, was accused of making racist remarks while serving as a representative on a 2019 educational trip to Peru alongside high-school students. After the trip, multiple students left reviews alleging the reporter used the “n-word” while on the trip. Three other participants also alleged that he made racist comments and used stereotypes about Black teenagers.In the Wednesday afternoon letter, signed by more than 150 staffers and addressed to executive editor Dean Baquet along with other top members of the Times masthead, employees expressed feeling “deeply disturbed” by the paper’s handling of the allegations, which thus far included a statement declaring McNeil had been “disciplined.”Furthermore, the signees called upon newspaper brass to conduct further investigation of the complaints against McNeil; an apology from McNeil to the students and their parents, tour staffers, and his fellow Times colleagues.“We, his colleagues, feel disrespected by his actions,” the letter said. “The company has a responsibility to take that experience seriously.”Star NY Times Reporter Accused of Using ‘N-Word,’ Making Other Racist CommentsIn a note to staff following last week’s article, Baquet said that upon hearing the complaints, he was outraged and initially intended to fire McNeil. But while the top editor acknowledged that the award-winning science reporter had made offensive comments, he said that an investigation by the paper found the reporter did not act in a hateful manner.“I authorized an investigation and concluded his remarks were offensive and that he showed extremely poor judgment, but it did not appear to me that his intentions were hateful or malicious,” Baquet wrote.But the company’s conclusion about McNeil’s intent was “irrelevant,” the irate staffers wrote in the letter, adding that the paper’s own harassment training “makes clear that what matters is how an act makes the victims feel; Mr. McNeil’s victims weren’t shy about decrying his conduct on the trip.”Signees called on the paper to study how racial biases affect pitches, editing, and sourcing, and reiterated a commitment to the paper’s existing non-discrimination and anti-harassment policies.The letter also called on the Times to reinvestigate the 2019 trip as well as “any newly surfacedcomplaints,” noting that in the days since The Daily Beast’s article, current and former staffers have also said that McNeil had shown “bias against people of color in his work and in interactions with colleagues over a period of years.”“Our community is outraged and in pain,” the signees wrote. “Despite The Times’s seeming commitment to diversity and inclusion, we have given a prominent platform—a critical beat covering a pandemic disproportionately affecting people of color—to someone who chose to use language that is offensive and unacceptable by any newsroom’s standards. He did so while acting as a representative for The Times, in front of high school students.”Inside the NY Times Probes Threatening a Star Reporter’s CareerThe letter on Wednesday came as Times brass have attempted to grapple with internal outrage over McNeil’s alleged comments.Baquet and Carolyn Ryan, the assistant managing editor, held a meeting on Friday with Times journalists—including prominent Black reporters such as Nikole Hannah-Jones—to try and explain their handling of McNeil’s behavior. While some attendees expressed displeasure at the paper’s handling of the complaints against McNeil, others said Baquet appeared to be taking staff concerns seriously.“I do honestly think Dean has taken this to heart and he has taken this very seriously and I really appreciate it,” reporter John Eligon, who covers race for the Times and was at the meeting, told The Daily Beast. “My message to management was can we find a better way when things happen that we can be more transparent.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Officials Baffled...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9219379/Why-coronavirus-cases-falling-fast-New-infections-drop-44-three-weeks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday, a total of 110,679 new coronavirus cases were reported with a 7-day rolling average of 135,904, a 44% decline from the average three weeks earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear bangs on door during DJ livestream...</title>
      <link>https://www.citizen-times.com/story/news/local/2021/02/01/asheville-realter-and-dj-jody-flemming-gets-black-bear-visit-during-livestream-session/4328528001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.citizen-times.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asheville resident Jody Flemming obliviously receives a visit from a black bear while he livestreams a techno DJ session in a video now seen around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKER DECISION LOOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/02/jeff-zucker-is-close-to-riding-the-ratings-wave</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After pushing back against pandemic-related cuts and outlasting Trump, Zucker enjoys broad newsroom support at a network that “has never been defined by its leader like it is right now,” says one employee. “It’s like Roger Ailes without the sexual abuse and hush money.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Wallen apologizes as backlash grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/03/entertainment/morgan-wallen-racial-slur/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Morgan Wallen is apologizing after a video surfaced in which he reportedly used a racial slur and profanities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA mulls using RICO against Capitol rioters...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-capitol-rico-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-mulls-using-law-designed-to-prosecute-mafia-against-capitol-rioters-idUSKBN2A32W2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Justice Department is considering whether to charge members of far-right groups involved in the deadly Jan. 6 storming of the Capitol under a federal law usually used against organized crime, according to two law enforcement sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Putin Resorts to Jailing Journalists for Retweeting Jokes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/desperate-putin-resorts-to-jailing-journalists-for-retweeting-jokes/ar-BB1dmGVT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW—Vladimir Putin took a dark new turn towards authoritarianism on Wednesday when his regime began to imprison journalists who dared to report on the growing opposition protests. A Moscow court ordered the jailing of one of the country’s leading independent journalists, Sergey Smirnov, editor-in-chief of Mediazona. His supposed crime? Retweeting a joke on Twitter. The post included the date of an upcoming rally in support of Alexei Navalny,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  No threat amid rise of white supremacy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-race-and-ethnicity-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-football-3862d432823887c5e4655c58963fb97c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — There is no specific threat of an attack connected to the Super Bowl and related events despite concerns about the rise of white supremacist extremism, law enforcement officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Shine joins NEWSNATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9220249/Former-Fox-News-exec-White-House-Chief-Comms-Bill-Shine-joins-NewsNation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shine was hired by NewsNation - the new, unbiased, 24-hour news service by WGN - in June 2020, before its official launch. He will help oversee talk shows across the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue Pooch -- Rescues Owner Suffering Stroke!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/03/rescue-dog-saves-owners-life-after-he-suffers-stroke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the Ramapo-Bergen Animal Refuge, Sadie, a 6-year-old rescued German Shepherd, rescued her owner Brian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazi Rapper Known As 'Far-Right Weird Al' Arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvxbz3/neo-nazi-rapper-known-as-a-far-right-weird-al-arrested</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weapons and Third Reich memorabilia were found when police raided the home of the 36-year-old, who has a neo-Nazi fanbase in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 4 Americans say they'll never get shot...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/03/1-in-4-americans-say-they-would-never-get-covid-vaccine-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in four Americans said they would never get the coronavirus vaccine, a new national poll reveals. Republicans were the biggest COVID-19 vaccine resisters, with 42 percent saying they will &amp;#822…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulgar emails to Nunes' wife triggered criminal investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/california/article248839774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Devin Nunes’ wife received vulgar emails at the public school where she works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Screen Time Causing Vision Problems During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/vision-related-issues-covid-screen-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors say they are seeing an uptick of vision issues related to computer use, including dry eyes and eye strain which can lead to headaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest who boasted about Capitol exorcism faces expulsion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9216209/Catholic-priest-Capitol-protest-captured-video-saying-performed-exorcism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rev David Fulton, a pastor at two churches in Nebraska, was among the thousands of Trump supporters who protested at the US Capitol in Washington, DC, on January 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 30 Pit Bulls, 5 Pythons, 4 Children Removed -- From Mobile Home...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/02/02/washington-township-animal-cruelty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty American terrier pit bulls, four children and several other animals, some dead, were removed from a mobile home in Lawrence County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran sues own school district to force in-person classes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/san-francisco-lawsuits-coronavirus-pandemic-dennis-herrera-california-9fa9cf285326935ce79b86c3c4c56774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — The city of San Francisco took a dramatic step Wednesday in its effort to get children back into public school classrooms, suing its own school district to try to force open...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium: Imam deported, mosque may close after anti-LGBTQ activities...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/belgium-imam-deported-mosque-may-close-after-anti-lgbtq-activities-657707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70 roosters seized in LA cockfighting investigation...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/70-roosters-seized-several-people-detained-during-illegal-cockfighting-investigation-in-llano-lasd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of roosters were confiscated during an investigation into illegal cockfighting in Llano, the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department said Wednesday. The Los Angeles County Sheriff&amp;#821…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Schools can reopen without teacher shots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seoul-south-korea-coronavirus-pandemic-africa-south-africa-bceee1a70b42731ae9e65aa288a2c320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Director of the CDC says schools can safely reopen even if teachers are not vaccinated for the coronavirus. As some teachers’ unions balk at resuming in-person instruction...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Bars BUCS From Shooting Cannons Out Of Iconic Pirate Ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/super-bowl-2021-nfl-says-buccaneers-cant-fire-cannons-from-famed-pirate-ship-following-touchdowns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is trying to keep this neutral field as neutral as possible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAME OVER? REDDIT trader behind surge 'loses $13 MILLION in day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2263010/gamestop-reddit-rally-roaring-kitty-keith-gill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE REDDIT trader who sparked the GameStop frenzy says he has lost $13MILLION in a single day after share prices plummeted this week. Keith Gill — otherwise known as as DeepF—ing Value on Reddit an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racial slur costs chart-topping country star spot on radio...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/nation-world/national/article248972905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I used an unacceptable and inappropriate racial slur that I wish I could take back,” Wallen said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom approval plummeting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/poll-newsom-approval-plummeting-third-134650084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a third of the state's registered voters said they would vote to oust Newsom from office if the recall qualified for the ballot, though 45% said they would oppose such a move, a Berkeley IGS poll found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA causing arm side effects in some...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2262521/moderna-vaccine-causing-covid-arm-rash-side-effects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MODERNA’S vaccine is causing a rash on some people’s arms after injection. The side effect, dubbed “Covid arm”, appears around a week after receiving a dose and affects very few patients, doctors s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASH OF THE TITANS:   Who is richest tech CEO as Bezos steps away from AMZN...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2262604/who-is-the-richest-tech-ceo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON founder Jeff Bezos is stepping down as CEO of the company that once made him the richest man in the world. As Bezos aims to focus “time and energy” on new ventures away from Amaz…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Weather Has Greater Impact On Spread Than Distancing...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/weather-impact-covid-19-spread/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say the lack of climate data included in epidemiological models has left a glaring hole in the plans to defend against COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 2 million seek appointments in Chicago  -- during first hour!</title>
      <link>https://www.radio.com/wbbm780/news/local/cook-county-covid-website-sees-1-9m-hits-in-first-hour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook County has another mass-vaccination site opening Wednesday morning at Triton College in River Grove - the second of four such sites – and to say interest is high would be an understatement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Sues NETFLIX Over Work Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/actor-sues-netflix-over-covid-19-work-conditions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face of NYC prevention tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-health-commissioner-tests-positive-for-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's health commissioner announced Wednesday that he has been infected with the virus himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentary shows how influencers fake their way to fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/02/hbo-fake-famous-how-instagram-influencers-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO's 'Fake Famous' features an experiment where three Instagram users try to boost their social media followings using tricks sometimes employed by top influencers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locations Being Kept Secret...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/02/02/sacramento-vaccines-secret-locations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The location of some vaccination sites are not being made public until someone makes an appointment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates' Sentences Shortened If They Get Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/03/massachusetts-prison-inmates-coronavirus-vaccine-good-time-sentences/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inmates in the Massachusetts Department of Correction can get a week taken off their prison sentence by getting the coronavirus vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation Shows CHIEFS Winning Super Bowl 37-27...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/02/03/madden-nfl-21-simulation-chiefs-super-bowl-lv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madden is picking the Chiefs to repeat as champions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES, HOSPITALIZATIONS CONTINUE FALL...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EtQmLA4VgAEmtA9?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Scottish lawmakers want to pursue The Don with 'unexplained wealth' probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/scottish-lawmakers-want-to-pursue-trump-with-e2-80-98unexplained-wealth-e2-80-99-probe-over-his-purchase-of-golf-courses/ar-BB1dm3LR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If ordered by a court, the Trump Organization would be required to reveal how it financed the purchases of the Turnberry and Aberdeen golf resorts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashian thief recounts Paris heist in tell-all book...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210203-kardashian-thief-recounts-paris-heist-in-tell-all-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kardashian thief recounts Paris heist in tell-all book</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Penn fires back at criticism over jab site: 'Betrayal of all'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sean-penn-fires-back-criticism-130008456.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two anonymous comments disparaged the actor's vaccination effort at Dodger Stadium. Penn fired back in an email: "And to whoever authored these, understand that in every cell of my body is a vitriol for the way your actions reflect so harmfully upon your brothers and sisters in arms."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird New Era of Cosmic Travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/02/spacex-elon-musk-jared-isaacman/617910/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s SpaceX just started launching NASA astronauts last spring, and it’s already moving on to private citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaders reach deal to fully transfer power to Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/03/senate-reaches-deal-on-organizing-resolution-chuck-schumer-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans technically controlled Senate committees for two weeks after Democrats took a majority in the chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNUBS, SURPRISES...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globes-snubs-nominations-bridgerton-zendaya-tom-hanks-spike-lee-surprises-1234685955/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the tumultuous year that’s just ended, you may feel hard pressed to be surprised by anything at this point, but the Golden Globes this morning aimed to prove that notion incorrect Offering pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX DOMINATES GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/golden-globe-nominations-2021-0e5be6d70f02b936b0a5025bb026e761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — After a year where the pandemic nearly emptied movie theaters, Netflix dominated nominations to the 78ths Golden Globe Awards on Wednesday, with David Fincher's “Mank" leading film...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empire State Building, related properties now powered solely by wind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-empire-state-building-and-its-related-buildings-are-now-powered-by-wind/ar-BB1dlK2q?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire State Building and its 13 related properties are buying wind power, making it the nation's largest real estate portfolio to go green.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNUBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/02/03/live-golden-globes-updates-big-snub-for-one-night-in-miami-minari-comedy-actress-nominees-no-one-knows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Golden Globes are always full of surprises. Today they snubbed Spike Lee and “Da 5 Bloods” and star Delroy Lindo. They totally ignored Regina King’s “One Night in Miami&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/2021-golden-globes-nominations-list-nominees-1234686095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations for the 78th annual Golden Globe Awards are being revealed this morning beginning at at 5:35 a.m. PT/8:35 a.m. ET as the Hollywood Foreign Press Association sets its noms for the best f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B9N_NgEQ5PE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live as Sarah Jessica Parker and Taraji P. Henson reveal this year's nominees for the 78th Golden Globe Awards on the TODAY Show and E! News. Full nomi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toddler to release debut album recorded in womb...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/feb/03/us-toddler-to-release-debut-album-recorded-in-the-womb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luca Yupanqui was recorded by her parents using ‘biosonic MIDI technology’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lin Wood spent months claiming fraud cost Trump election. Now Georgia investigating whether he voted illegally...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/l-lin-wood-spent-months-falsely-claiming-voter-fraud-cost-trump-the-election-now-georgia-is-investigating-whether-he-voted-illegally/ar-BB1dlM2z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative attorney L. Lin Wood faces an investigation in Georgia over whether he illegally voted in the Nov. 3 elections after buying a home in South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog Keeps Guard Over Owner's Body For 2 Days After Dying on Hike...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/02/02/david-deshon-missing-foresthill-dog-doesnt-leave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Deshon was found dead two days after he was reported missing near his Foresthill home last week - but his dog wouldn’t leave his side, family says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinfection NOT Rare?</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/02/covid-reinfection-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's some bad news and perhaps some good news for people who've been previously infected with the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna? Harry Potter? Churchill? Tom Brady May Be Beyond Compare...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/03/madonna-harry-potter-churchill-tom-brady-may-be-beyond-compare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arc of Tom Brady’s career — his rise to Super Bowl mainstay as quarterback of the New England Patriots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys Dealt Another Blow as Feds Crack Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/proud-boys-dealt-another-blow-as-feds-crack-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Proud Boys’ former lawyer says he’s taking the name back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shockingly Realistic Porn Movie Has SUNDANCE Talking...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pleasure-is-the-shockingly-realistic-porn-movie-that-has-sundance-talking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swedish filmmaker Ninja Thyberg opens up to Marlow Stern about “Pleasure,” her feature directorial debut centered on a young woman navigating the adult industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Truthers' New Freakout: Being Forced to Eat Bugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/covid-truthers-new-freakout-is-over-supposedly-being-forced-to-eat-bugs </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERY state will see below freezing temps next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/02/weather/polar-vortex-forecast-freezing-cold/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coldest air of the season will be diving south, not leaving anyone out. Every single state in the lower 48 US will be below freezing Monday morning. This includes 86% of the country and 235 million people, and this one system alone is responsible for much of that. Check how cold your low will be Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA to oversee investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/02/tech/spacex-starship-sn-9-test-launch-faa-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration said it will oversee an investigation into a crash landing of a SpaceX prototype rocket on Tuesday. The announcement comes after the FAA forced SpaceX to delay the launch as it investigated a previous explosion of a similar rocket prototype.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Barts shuts down...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/02/st-barts-is-shutting-down-due-to-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jetsetters should bid “adieu” to upcoming St. Barts vacations. The Caribbean island popular with celebrities will bar most visitors beginning Wednesday to comply with coronavirus protoc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark to develop digital passport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-health-denmark-coronavirus-pandemic-europe-8ffacf05453c6f259d5e2cea033ae5ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Denmark's government said Wednesday it is joining forces with businesses to develop a digital passport that would show whether people have been vaccinated against the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa's famed strip clubs brace for unusual Super Bowl...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-super-bowl-health-football-coronavirus-pandemic-27ba9985cfc3aaa4c5ba5eae7f8a2d93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — Elizabeth Reed dances at Scores Gentleman's Club, a strip club near the stadium hosting the Super Bowl, and says wearing masks while working is like “doing cardio” with her nose...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B-1 Bombers Deploying To Norway For First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39053/b-1-bombers-are-deploying-to-norway-for-the-first-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deployment is part of the Air Force's new focus on the Arctic and will position the bombers near Russia's sprawling Naval bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For billionaire Jared Isaacman, cosmic tourism era begins...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-02-billionaire-jared-isaacman-space-tourism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jared Isaacman is not a professional astronaut, but by the end of the year the young billionaire will have shot around the Earth multiple times at the helm of a space mission made up entirely of tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets face, hands in rare surgery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-new-york-coronavirus-pandemic-face-transplants-1e11f620bd84c817e99b00bdf874625a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Almost six months after a rare face and hands transplant, Joe DiMeo is relearning how to smile, blink, pinch and squeeze. The 22-year-old New Jersey resident had the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political storms swirl...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/gavin-newsom-california-coronavirus-pandemic-kevin-faulconer-9d2032fd2aff2d48f4350fc5b861be6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — In the year since California saw its first coronavirus case, Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom has gone from a governor in command to one lurching from one political crisis to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned with low reimbursement, doctors stop testing...</title>
      <link>https://newyorknewstimes.com/burned-with-a-low-reimbursement-some-doctors-stop-testing-covid/103087/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyorknewstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Robin Lullaby was excited to start offering coronavirus tests at a pediatric clinic in Denver last fall.The test for kids Often lacking, And her new machine was able to return results within minutes. She soon discovered an unexpected obstacle. It’s a major health insurance company that paid her for less than the cost of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO team visits Wuhan lab, meets 'Bat Woman'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210203100527-9j9ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-CHINA (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-WHO team probing COVID-19 visits Wuhan lab, meets 'Bat Woman'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen Summons Regulators to Discuss Market Volatility...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yellen-summons-regulators-discuss-financial-021235999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen has summoned U.S. financial regulators to discuss recent volatility in financial markets, in her first public effort to address the tumult involving GameStop Corp. shares and broker-dealer Robinhood Markets Inc.Yellen called a meeting with the Securities and Exchange Commission, the Federal Reserve Board, the Federal Reserve Bank of New York and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, the Treasury said in a statement late Tuesday. The Biden administration and regulators have faced pressure in recent days to respond to the market frenzy.“Secretary Yellen believes the integrity of markets is important and has asked for a discussion of recent volatility in financial markets and whether recent activities are consistent with investor protection and fair and efficient markets,” the department said.Yellen’s predecessors, including Steven Mnuchin, also organized meetings of financial agencies during times of tumult. They aren’t necessarily a signal that any policy moves are imminent. The SEC already said Friday it’s seeking to identify potential misconduct and will scrutinize brokerages’ decisions to halt buying that triggered a retail-investor revolt.GameStop, a video-game retailer, was one of a handful of companies whose shares began soaring in late January, driven by an army of retail investors active on the online forums hosted by Reddit. Some investors openly called on others to bid up the shares of certain names in order to trigger losses for hedge funds that had bet their prices would fall.GameStop shares went from $19.95 to a peak of $347.51 on Jan. 27 in just 10 trading days, and with no meaningful change in the company’s profit outlook. It has since swung wildly and fell 60% to close at $90 on Tuesday, suggesting the frenzy may be easing.The episode has raised questions about whether broader risks for the financial system are brewing. As Treasury secretary, Yellen is chair of the Financial Stability Oversight Council, which was set up in the wake of the global financial crisis to monitor systemic risks. This week’s meeting about GameStop is not a formal FSOC session, but more of an ad hoc gathering of top financial regulators.The SEC’s acting chair, Allison Herren Lee, said Monday that the agency is keeping a close eye on stocks that have surged to extraordinary heights during the recent bouts of wild trading but has seen no evidence that the broader market is under threat.“We haven’t seen anything to indicate anything that suggests it would bring down the market,” Lee told NPR in an interview.The wild trading has left politicians in both parties grasping for responses to the new phenomenon of retail investors banding together on social media.On Monday, the House Financial Services Committee announced that it would hold a hearing on Feb. 18 regarding “recent market volatility” involving GameStop and other companies.Yellen has requested an ethics waiver to hold the meeting, a Treasury spokeswoman said, confirming a Reuters report.Yellen received more than $700,000 in speaking fees from Citadel, the financial empire run by billionaire Ken Griffin. Griffin runs a hedge fund and controls Citadel Securities, a giant market making firm that executes trades for Robinhood’s customers.Read more: The Citadel Link: What Ken Griffin Has to Do With GameStopRichard Berner, professor at New York University’s Stern School of Business and the former director of the Treasury’s Office of Financial Research, said it’s important that the SEC and other regulators are monitoring markets for any signs of fraud or manipulation.“Both are potentially financial stability issues,” he said. “Were they to escalate and persist, these events might erode investor trust. Trust in markets and market integrity is absolutely critical for markets to function and for people to engage in them.”The market turbulence comes at a particularly awkward time in Washington, where the Biden administration is still taking wing. Many of the president’s cabinet choices and picks for other crucial jobs await Senate confirmation -- including Gary Gensler, his nominee as SEC chairman.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Down Side to Life in Supertall Tower: Leaks, Creaks, Breaks...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/03/the-down-side-to-life-in-a-supertall-tower-leaks-creaks-breaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nearly 1,400-foot tower at 432 Park Avenue, briefly the tallest residential building in the world, was the pinnacle of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas becoming worthless?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/finance/news/gasoline-is-becoming-worthless-210636353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors are beginning to value internal-combustion technology at 0 or less, which is forcing the faster adoption of electrics at GM, Ford and other automakers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
