<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Officer Complains About Dead General, Comms Meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-officer-complains-dead-general-113255353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irina Rybakova/Press service of the Ukrainian ground forces/ReutersThe Ukrainian defence ministry has a released audio from a call which it claims captured two Russian officers lamenting the death of a top general and the collapse of its secure communications network in Ukraine.In the call—which has been verified by Bellingcat, the fact-checking group known for exposing Kremlin misinformation—two purported Russian FSB officers are heard discussing the death of a general killed in fighting near K</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Truth Social Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2022/03/donald-trump-truth-social-failure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Truth Social has been a complete disaster and the ex-president seems to know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan Migrants Coming Home as Maduro Embraces Capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/maduro-s-switch-from-socialism-is-helping-bring-venezuelan-migrants-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan Migrants Are Coming Home as Maduro Embraces Capitalism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your toilet paper roll is slimming down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/08/business/toilet-paper-roll-shrinking-inflation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slimmed down toilet paper, fewer cookies in a bag, less conditioner in squeeze tubes. The changes are subtle and might evade less discerning shoppers. But retail industry experts say we could see more consumer products start shrinking in size or quantity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators look to lock down Moscow gold reserves...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-senators-look-to-lock-down-russias-gold-reserves-04c6c7bb-cc32-4e72-981e-fa972c31a1a4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal is to include the legislation in the omnibus spending bill lawmakers hope to pass by Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How Did This Many Deaths Become Normal?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2022/03/covid-us-death-rate/626972/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is nearing 1 million recorded COVID-19 deaths without the social reckoning that such a tragedy should provoke. Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldiers 'Desert Posts' After Heavy Losses...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4845314/russian-general-killed-ukraine-vladimir-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE OF Vladimir Putin’s top generals has been killed in fighting outside of Ukraine’s second city Kharkiv, in another major blow for the Russian president. Vitaly Gerasimov is the secon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposes nationalizing foreign-owned factories that shut...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/ukraine-crisis-russia-sanctions/russia-proposes-nationalising-foreign-owned-factories-that-shut-operations-idUSKBN2L51BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior member of Russia's ruling party has proposed nationalising foreign-owned factories that shut down operations in the country over what the Kremlin calls a special military operation in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Spies See Grim Global Outlook With Russia, China Top Foes...</title>
      <link>https://www.moneyweb.co.za/news/international/us-spies-see-grim-global-outlook-with-russia-china-top-foes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moneyweb.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the annual threat assessment by the Office of the Director of National Intelligence.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shoppers Scramble for Staples as Food Fallout From War Spreads Around World...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6155752/ukraine-war-food-prices-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shockwaves in global crop markets from Russia’s invasion of Ukraine are spreading to store shelves around the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN New Boss Signals for Truce With FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cnns-new-boss-signals-for-truce-with-fox-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this week’s Source Material, we reveal massive changes coming to CNN, the way Twitter quietly changed its rules during wartime, and the drama at ABC News and G/O Media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eternal Youth On Horizon? Cell Therapy Reverses Signs Of Aging...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/reverses-signs-of-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breakthrough may be able to extend life and help people gain the ability to become more resistant to stress, injury, and disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Drug Factory' Implants Cure Certain Cancers -- In 6 Days!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drug-factory-implants-cure-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team tested this potentially groundbreaking treatment in mice, but they add that clinical trials in human cancer patients could start by fall 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>459-Foot Mystery in Tuscan Port: Is It Oligarch Superyacht?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/08/a-459-foot-mystery-in-a-tuscan-port-is-it-a-russians-superyacht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Germany’s North Sea ports to the French Riviera, open season has been declared on superyachts. Across Europe, authorities are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States move to roll back firearm permits, over police objections...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/597227-states-move-to-roll-back-firearm-permits-over-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Russia Military Stumbles, Adversaries Take Note...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/07/as-russias-military-stumbles-its-adversaries-take-note/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONSTANTA, Romania — When it comes to war, generals say that “mass matters.” But nearly two weeks into President Vladimir</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seemingly stuck convoy hides mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/seemingly-stuck-russian-convoy-hides-mysteries/ar-AAUKVUU </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden sends Harris to Poland and Romania...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-sends-harris-to-poland-and-romania-amid-global-crisis/ar-AAUM95K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DWTS' alum escaped. Wracked by survivor's guilt, he says he's returning to Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-dancing-with-the-stars-alum-escaped-ukraine-wracked-by-survivor-s-guilt-he-says-he-s-returning-to-europe/ar-AAUMhQm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHELL CUTS TIES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/08/energy/shell-russia-oil-ban/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is finding it ever harder to sell its oil and gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltic states fear Putin has in sights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/baltic-states-in-europe-fear-putin-has-them-in-his-sights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions are rising in Europe's ex-Soviet Baltic nations that Putin might not stop at invading Ukraine, and could have his sights set on them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB, other sex sites face ban in France...</title>
      <link>https://thestreetjournal.org/pornhub-four-other-sex-sites-face-ban-in-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thestreetjournal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pornhub and four other sites hosting sexually explicit content face a possible ban in France after the country’s media regulator said Tuesday it had filed a legal complaint against them. The sites were told in late 2021 that they needed to bring in a system that prevented children from viewing their videos. Under a new […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST DRAMA: Spielberg, others grumbling about OSCARS changes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/steven-spielberg-isnt-only-director-000347723.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood's big dogs are barking about changes to the Oscars, including best-picture nominees Steven Spielberg, Jane Campion and Denis Villeneuve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Now it's no mercy,' Ukrainian soldiers vow, as showdown nears...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/now-no-mercy-ukrainian-soldiers-223041610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian troops in Irpin, on the outskirts of Kyiv, dig in as a long column of Russian tanks advances toward them. They vow to fight to the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilian suffering intensifies as new Russian-Ukrainian talks fail to yield breakthrough...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/ap/international/civilian-suffering-intensifies-as-new-russian-ukrainian-talks-fail-to-yield-breakthrough/article_20312ff0-a248-5db9-9cec-dc27e6caab24.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine — A dozen days into a devastating war and a burgeoning refugee crisis, Russian forces on Monday launched withering new attacks on civilian areas and strategic centers in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Weighs Russian Oil Ban as Gas Prices Surge and Ukraine War Grows...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/07/u-s-weighs-russian-oil-ban-as-gas-prices-surge-and-ukraine-war-grows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden came under increasing pressure on Monday to ban Russian oil imports into the United States, forcing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former California Gov. Jerry Brown living off grid in retirement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-climate-biden-science-b7f4d8399218bdc4330305a913d56bb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILLIAMS, Calif. (AP) — Former California Gov. Jerry Brown is living off the grid in retirement, but he's still deeply connected on two issues that captivated him while in office and now are center stage globally: climate change and the threat of nuclear war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge set to question juror who convicted Ghislaine Maxwell...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-entertainment-crime-jeffrey-epstein-alison-j-nathan-1e73604530ea5e4013545163f3970766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A U.S. judge was set Tuesday to question one of the jurors who convicted the British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell of helping the millionaire Jeffrey Epstein sexually abuse teenage girls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS HITS RECORD</title>
      <link>https://www.gasbuddy.com/newsroom/pressrelease/1104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gasbuddy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous record of $4.10 per gallon set in 2008 has fallen as gas prices continue to rise BOSTON (March 7, 2022) -- The national average price of gas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA WARNS $300 OIL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/russia-warns-of-300-oil-if-ban-goes-ahead-threatens-to-cut-off-european-gas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has been considering whether to impose a ban on Russia's oil and gas exports as a way of punishing Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher gas prices will cost you $2,000 a year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/gas-prices-household-impact-2000-a-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Already slammed with the highest inflation in 40 years, some consumers say they'll cut back amid rising gas prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXODUS: 2 million flee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-united-nations-evacuations-62fa232dcb9d6260fef0e9c7f5386f9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LVIV, Ukraine (AP) — Evacuations of people fleeing embattled Ukrainian cities along safe corridors began Tuesday, while U.N. officials said the exodus of refugees from Russia's invasion reached 2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheat Closes at Record High as War Paralyzes Ukraine Grain Flows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wheat-climbs-nearer-record-ukraine-010300415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chicago wheat settled at the highest price on record as Russia’s intensifying war in Ukraine cuts off supplies from one of the world’s leading breadbaskets. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Russian Official Threatens Europe Gas PipelineChina Warns U.S. Against Forming Pacific NATO and Backing TaiwanStakes Rise as Putin Says His War in Ukraine Will ContinueUkraine Update: U.S. May Go Alone on Russia Oil Ban; Crude SoarsHypersonic-Missile Failures Risk U.S. Chase of China, Ru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Construction spotted at NKorea nuke site for first time since '18...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/construction-spotted-n-korea-nuclear-223956639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commercial satellite imagery shows construction at North Korea's nuclear testing site for the first time since it was closed in 2018, U.S.-based analysts said on Tuesday, amid fears the country could resume testing major weapons. Images captured by satellite on Friday showed very early signs of activity at the new site, including construction of a new building, repair of another building, and what is possibly some lumber and sawdust, specialists at the California-based James Martin Center for Nonproliferation Studies (CNS) said in a report. "The construction and repair work indicate that North Korea has made some decision about the status of the test site," the report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychologist suggests taking out frustration by building fire bombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kyiv-psychologist-suggests-angry-ukrainians-take-out-their-frustration-by-building-fire-bombs/ar-AAUKBp7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple victims shot outside Iowa High School... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/crime-and-courts/2022/03/07/des-moines-police-responding-to-report-of-multiple-people-shot-outside-des-moines-east-high-school/9416980002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Des Moines police say multiple people were injured in a shooting outside Des Moines East High School.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr hits back at The Don's 'childish' letter: 'Throws tantrum and attacks'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bill-barr-fires-back-trumps-182117069.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's par for the course," Barr said of Trump. "When he's told something he doesn't want to hear, he immediately throws a tantrum."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'20th hijacker' from Guantanamo sent home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-cuba-prisons-mental-health-d33e83ec3effdc35167d635ea0f0b78f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A Saudi prisoner at the Guantanamo Bay detention center who was suspected of trying to join the 9/11 hijackers has been sent back to his home country for treatment for mental illness, the Department of Defense said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas cop now accused of 3 casino heists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-crime-arrests-las-vegas-b992a874e704ea06a5e6f64cb5e41ae1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — A Las Vegas police officer who was arrested Feb. 27 for attempting to rob a casino on The Strip has been charged in federal court in connection with two other casino robberies. The federal criminal complaint filed Friday accuses Caleb Rogers, 33, of arming himself in all three heists dating to November with the same .357-caliber service revolver that belonged to the Las Vegas Metro Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man drives truck through Russian embassy gates in Ireland...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishtimes.com/news/crime-and-law/russian-embassy-appreciates-help-of-irish-authorities-after-truck-driven-through-gates-1.4820488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I’ve done my bit, lads,’ says Leitrim businessman Desmond Wisley</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. far from normal with deaths 10 times higher than seasonal respiratory viruses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/07/us-far-from-normal-with-covid-deaths-10-times-higher-than-flu-rsv-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid is still causing an "intolerable" level of death that is far higher than the toll of common seasonal viruses, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Sticks With Putin for 'Essential' Energy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/germany-putin-oil-gas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Olaf Scholz brushes off pressure from Ukraine and the US to stop pouring money into the Kremlin’s war coffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials engage with Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article259151443.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s opposition was caught off guard and angered as details emerged of a meeting between Biden and Maduro officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL suspends star for betting on games...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33446869/nfl-suspends-atlanta-falcons-wr-calvin-ridley-least-2022-season-betting-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has suspended wide receiver Calvin Ridley for at least the 2022 season for betting on NFL games during the 2021 season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge Cocaine Lab Found Inside World Heritage Site...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3n8zy/bolivia-world-heritage-site-cocaine-lab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The authorities have found drug labs in the Noel Kempff Mercado National Park before, and many more could still be operating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In S Korea, 'Squid Game Election' campaign gets ugly...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/03/07/1084874629/in-south-korea-the-squid-game-election-campaign-gets-ugly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negative campaigns are aggravating South Korea's already severe political divide as presidential elections approach on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside private company surveilling immigrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/07/us-immigration-surveillance-ice-bi-isap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BI claims it provides immigrant tracking and ‘quality’ case management. A Guardian investigation paints a very different picture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fremont, CA Tops List Of 'Happiest Cities'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/money-americas-happiest-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WalletHub study of the country's 182 largest cities finds Fremont, California tops the list as the happiest place in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning the propaganda war...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2022/03/03/how-ukraine-is-winning-the-propaganda-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside boots on the ground, this war is a battle for the world's hearts and minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Love child' closes socials after wave of extreme trolling...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10586395/Putins-love-child-18-closes-social-media-wave-extreme-trolling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Putin ordered the invasion, Luiza Rozova, a student in St Petersburg, had been deluged with hostile posts from people angry at the Russian president's brutal actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Churchill? Zelensky praised as war communicator...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-volodymyr-zelenskyy-entertainment-media-social-media-896ac1afc240fdf349c0d4c96d5e2afc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To a watching world, his message is this, in both his words and his resolute, sometimes haggard appearance: He stands as a mirror to the suffering and spirit of his people. It appears to be getting through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL becomes first state to recommend AGAINST vaccinating children...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10586973/Florida-recommend-against-COVID-vaccines-healthy-kids.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Surgeon General Dr. Joseph Ladapo said Monday that the state will formally recommend against COVID-19 vaccinations for 'healthy; children, the first state to do such a move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S, COCA-COLA boycott calls grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-60649214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Food and drink giants have been criticised on social media for failing to speak out on Ukraine's invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly discovered brain cells may be memory filing system...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2022/03/07/newly-discovered-brain-cells-may-be-memory-filing-system-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in a federally funded BRAIN Initiative consortium monitored electrical activity in patients' brains to find new groups of neurons involved in the creation of memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nearly 100%' of pre-staged combat power now moved in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-07-22/h_2382a0569210f658ffb89bd569d5f7e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine and Russia will hold a third round of talks Monday, according to negotiators as from on the ground in Ukraine as Ukrainian civilians are trapped in the cities of Mariupol, Volnovakha and Kyiv after evacuation efforts failed. Follow here for live news updates from on the ground in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial rock art may depict extinct giants of ice age...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/07/americas/rock-art-colombia-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  AMAZON continues using Chinese suppliers linked to forced labor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/amazon-suppliers-linked-forced-labor-china-watchdog-group-says-rcna16452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company’s supplier list includes firms accused of using Uyghur laborers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PLANS TRIP TO SAUDI ARABIA</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-saudi-trip-oil-b7a91070-8045-4155-9120-a35d59fd7603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hat-in-hand trip would illustrate the gravity of the global energy crisis driven by Russia's invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Nears All-Time High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-inflation-set-heat-further-173411886.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's invasion of Ukraine has dashed any hope U.S. consumers might have had for relief from sky-rocketing costs, with prices at the gas pump in the last week surging by the most in nearly 17 years and prices for other goods like food ready to march higher as well. Even before the invasion, the latest U.S. monthly inflation report, due on Thursday, was set to show prices rising at their fastest in 40 years. The data, which is for February, will likely show only a preliminary impact from the surge in U.S. oil prices, which hit $130 a barrel on Monday, but the spike is seen driving overall inflation higher in the months to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETS: Oil $200 a Barrel This Month...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oil-traders-betting-prices-may-051731959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Traders piled into options that oil could surge even further after rising to the highest since 2008, with some even placing low-cost bets that futures surpass $200 before the end of March.Most Read from BloombergStakes Rise as Putin Says His War in Ukraine Will ContinueUkraine Update: U.S. May Go Alone on Russia Oil Ban; Crude SoarsPutin’s Ruble Workaround Still Leaves Bond Payments in DoubtUkraine Update: U.K. Premier Says More Pressure Needed on PutinOil Jumps Near $123 as Chanc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Silence on Florida 'Don't Say Gay'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/diseny-dont-say-gay-bill-florida-bob-chapek-lgbtq-ron-desantis-1234972655/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing rising outcry, Disney CEO Bob Chapek has decided to play a political and cultural version of a church mouse when it comes to Florida’s new ‘Don’t Say Gay’ bill. With the openly discrimatory …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Kyiv's Middle-Class Suburbs, People Are Trapped and Desperate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-kyiv-e2-80-99s-middle-class-suburbs-desperate-people-are-trapped/ar-AAUJlKf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny radio station broadcasting propaganda in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-tiny-radio-station-broadcasting-russian-propaganda-in-d-c/ar-AAUJktB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad Has Already Lost the Digital War....</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2022/03/putin-lost-cyber-and-information-war-abroad-will-he-lose-home/362794/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its diplomatic efforts in tatters, its agencies beset by cyber vigilantes, the Russian government is still choking off the information that fuels its homegrown protest movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Can Shrink Brain as Much as Decade of Aging, Study Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2644036?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even a mild case of COVID-19 can damage the brain and addle thinking, scientists found in a study that highlights the illness’s alarming impact on mental function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists identify new gene differences in severe patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-identify-gene-differences-severe-160624182.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have pinpointed 16 new genetic variants in people who developed severe COVID-19 in a large study published on Monday that could help researchers develop treatments for very sick patients. The results suggest that people with severe COVID have genes that predispose them to one of two problems: failure to limit the ability of the virus to make copies of itself, or excessive inflammation and blood clotting. "It is potentially possible in future that we will be able to make predictions about patients based on their genome at the point of presenting (for) critical care," said Kenneth Baillie, consultant in critical care medicine at the University of Edinburgh and one of the study authors, told reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may act alone to ban Russian oil imports...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-prepared-move-alone-banning-155638109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is willing to move ahead with a ban on Russian oil imports into the United States without the participation of allies in Europe, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters, after Russia's invasion of Ukraine. President Joe Biden is expected to hold a video conference call with the leaders of France, Germany and the United Kingdom on Monday as his administration continues to seek their support for a ban on the imports. Germany is accelerating its plans to expand its use of alternative energy sources but cannot halt imports of Russian energy overnight, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Maps shows Putin's secret mansion worth $1 BILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/vladimir-putins-alleged-secret-palace-26404333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President of Russia Vladimir Putin is alleged to have a £1 billion mansion on the Black Sea. He denies the claims and the Kremlin insists it is merely a business venture by wealthy Russians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns of 'global collapse' over West sending weapons to Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-russia-chilling-warning-sending-26405640</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier today Vladimir Putin demanded Ukraine must distance itself from NATO, lay down its arms and recognise Russia's claims to Crimea, and to acknowledge that Donetsk and Lugansk are independent states before war can end</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold crosses $2,000; Nears Historic Highs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/07/gold-markets-palladium-russia-ukraine-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold prices briefly scale the $2,000 level for the first time in 1-1/2 years as investors rushed to safety in the wake of an escalating Russia-Ukraine crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron keeps an open line to Putin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-business-europe-moscow-912c39b11b42be00c88aff8740c9aae8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICE, France (AP) — While most of the world is shunning President Vladimir Putin over Russia's invasion of Ukraine , one of the few leaders keeping an open line of communication is French President Emmanuel Macron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll surpasses 6 million for pandemic now in 3rd year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-health-lifestyle-9cd511bc84955131ba00846716e02647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — The official global death toll from COVID-19 eclipsed 6 million on Monday — underscoring that the pandemic, now entering its third year, is far from over. The milestone, recorded by Johns Hopkins University, is the latest tragic reminder of the unrelenting nature of the pandemic even as people are shedding masks, travel is resuming and businesses are reopening around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ackman says WWIII already started...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/07/russia-ukraine-bill-ackman-says-world-war-iii-likely-already-started.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire hedge fund managerÂ BillÂ Ackman has warned that World War III has "likely started already" amid Russia's ongoing attack on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX man could become first Capitol rioter convicted by jury as trial ends...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/07/first-capitol-rioter-faces-possible-convictions-from-jury</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department of Justice lawyers make closing arguments against Guy Reffitt, first of 750 people charged with joining riot to face trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How far-right militia groups found foothold in deep-blue California...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/How-far-right-militia-groups-found-a-foothold-in-16983102.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. - The far right is rising in the ranchland of Northern California, using...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Russia Hacks U.S. Satellite, Then What?</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2022/03/if-russia-hacks-us-satellite-then-what/362761/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian official warned that impacting their satellites would be considered a declaration of war, but the U.S. stance is more circumspect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Signals Opposition to Cutting 'Essential' Russian Energy...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/germany-signals-opposition-to-cutting-essential-russian-energy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
