<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Florida bans childlike sex dolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandoweekly.com/Blogs/archives/2019/05/24/florida-gov-ron-desantis-signs-bill-outlawing-child-sex-dolls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandoweekly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On&amp;nbsp;Thursday Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law legislation that bans the sale or possession of child-like sex dolls after it unanimously passed the Florida Legislature....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'American Soil' Increasingly Foreign Owned...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/05/27/723501793/american-soil-is-increasingly-foreign-owned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of acres of U.S. farmland held by foreign-owned investors has doubled in the past two decades, raising alarm bells in farming communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 LEECHES found in carry-on...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article230885464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have day off? Try doing nothing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/memorial-day-how-to-make-use-of-your-day-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We need to be OK with accepting the day for what it is — which is a day off," says New York Times Smarter Living editor Tim Herrera</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As ER wait times grow, more patients leave against medical advice...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/as-er-wait-times-grow-more-patients-leave-against-medical-advice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowded emergency rooms are likely to blame. In 2017, the median ER wait time for patients before admission as inpatients to California hospitals was 336 minutes — or more than 5½ hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF EU</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6152801851684d879999dbcdc62c1e0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — France's pro-EU president and the leader of Italy's euroskeptic, far-right movement jockeyed for the role of chief powerbroker on the continent Monday after elections to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY HORROR:  1-year-old killed, 6 family members hospitalized in golf cart mishap...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/1-year-old-north-carolina-boy-killed-in-golf-cart-accident/5318951/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The North Carolina Highway Patrol says a 1-year-old boy was killed when the golf cart he and family members were riding in hit a pothole and overturned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan bus stop stabbing wounds dozens... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20190528_12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www3.nhk.or.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese police say 16 people, including schoolchildren, have been injured in a stabbing in Kawasaki City near Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The value of $1 in every state...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/05/25/us-dollar-how-much-its-worth-value-in-every-state/39501091/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The value of a dollar ranges by more than 30 cents across the US, depending on the state. In Mississippi, $1 is worth $1.16; in Hawaii, only 84 cents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 die -- in 10 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7075541/American-climber-dies-descent-summit-Mount-Everest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher John Kulish, 62, scaled the 8,850 metre (29,035 feet) peak from the normal Southeast Ridge route in the morning but died suddenly at South Col after descending from the summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 42 inmates strangled to death in clashes...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-brazil-violence-prisons/at-least-42-inmates-strangled-to-death-in-amazon-prison-gang-clashes-idUKKCN1SX1X1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 42 prisoners in Brazil were found strangled to death on Monday in four ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger dies on flight after ingesting 246 cocaine packets...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/man-dies-cocaine-flight-mexico-japan-aeromexico-colombia-a8931831.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump attack on Biden echoes left-wing criticism...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/05/27/donald-trump-joe-biden-crime-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump attacked 2020 Democratic presidential front-runner Joe Biden on Twitter Monday with a critique that liberal outlets have been using for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laptop full of most dangerous malware auctions for $1.2M...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/05/27/persistence-of-chaos-malware-laptop-auction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meant as a work of art, this laptop contains six dangerous viruses and sold for $1.2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented photo of first known albino giant panda...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/camera-trap-snaps-photo-of-first-known-albino-giant-pan-1835050847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using a motion-activated camera, scientists at Wolong National Nature Reserve in southwest China have snapped a blurry but unprecedented photograph of the world’s first known albino giant panda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33 shot, 5 killed so far as Chicago 'floods zone' for holiday weekend...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/crime/2019/5/26/18639572/11-wounded-in-shootings-may-24-may-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were killed and three more wounded Sunday in a shooting on the Near West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran, 95, graduates decades after leaving high school for World War II...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/hillsborough-county/world-war-ii-vet-95-gets-high-school-diploma-more-than-70-years-later/2027358262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Perricone walked across the stage to fetch his diploma Saturday, more than 70 years after leaving school to join the war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True crime with gory footage hottest TV trend in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-Brazil-true-crime-is-the-hottest-TV-trend-13898873.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO - A gunman bursts into a family's home as they gather for dinner. The father throws a chair at him and is shot. The father falls to the floor. He lifts his head weakly and is shot a final time.  Car chases, lifeless bodies, pools of blood. It's not an action movie - it's just another Brazilian morning show.  As the country battles a historic crime wave that has claimed tens of thousands of lives, the staples that once dominated morning television here - celebrity news, cooking advice, feel-good stories - have been replaced with increasingly gory footage of real violence. And Brazilians cannot get enough of it.  In January, "Primeiro Impacto," a show that focuses exclusively on true-crime footage, became the second-most-popular morning program on network television.  The gunshots that are fired around the country at night are replayed on television screens the next morning, accompanied by an action-movie soundtrack. The camera zooms in on body bags. Suspects are circled in red.  In a nation suffering a record spike in killing, the fear is palpable - but so is the anger.  "There's no talking to these thugs," says the show's host, known as Marcão do Povo, or Mark of the People. "They deserve a bullet to the back. That's what thugs deserve."  The surge in violence - a record 64,000 people were killed in 2017, many of them in the gang war over the drug trade - has made Brazil one of the most dangerous countries in the world and left Brazilians clamoring for the tough-on-crime approach they see on television.  Politicians are responding. Promises of harsher sentences for criminals and protections for police officers who kill on the job helped catapult the previously obscure right-wing congressman Jair Bolsonaro into Brazil's presidency last November.  "I'm going to stuff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey experiments offer clues on origin of language...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190527-monkey-experiments-offer-clues-origin-language</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monkey experiments offer clues on origin of language</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuck and Sandberg will defy Canadian subpoena, risking contempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/27/tech/zuckerberg-contempt-canada/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's Mark Zuckerberg and Sheryl Sandberg will not attend a hearing in Ottawa later this week, despite receiving summonses from the Canadian parliament, Facebook confirmed on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman says he's taken photo with dead enemy...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/politics/story/2019-05-25/hunters-father-and-son-hold-town-hall-to-discuss-border-then-and-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congressman from Alpine and his father discussed border security and other issues in front of a friendly audience in Ramona Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX approves safe gun storage campaign over NRA objection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b118f256955e439d8157743177765c0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Lawmakers in gun-loving Texas have quietly gone around the National Rifle Association by slipping language into a massive spending bill that would fund a $1 million public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Miracle baby': Woman pregnant after fallopian tubes removed...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/business/health-care/article230397424.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF hits Syrian targets...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Israeli-drone-brought-down-over-the-Golan-by-Syrian-anti-aircraft-missile-590824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The missile didn't hit the Israeli aircraft, which was conducting a routine flight over northern Israel, and fell within Syrian territory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump intervenes...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-tweet-israel-netanyahu-466590aa-322a-4ed1-b52b-bbb6146d7a29.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's move is unprecedented for being so public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball icon Bill Buckner dead at 69...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/26832836/bill-buckner-dies-69-battling-dementia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Buckner, who played 22 years in the majors and won a batting title, died at the age of 69 after battling Lewy body dementia, his family said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortages plague Cuba as economic woes sharpen...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-economy/shortages-plague-cuba-as-u-s-sanctions-sharpen-economic-woes-idUSKCN1SX1P1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel Hidalgo and his wife left home around 7:30 a.m. to reach a supermarket ac...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aspiring PhD student sues university after rejection for 'lost sex drive'...
...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7075059/Aspiring-student-7-11-worker-sues-3million-lost-SEX-DRIVE.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kuldeep Singh Mann paid James Cook University (JCU) in Townsville, north-eastern Queensland, $20,000 to study the prestigious research degree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot trend in smartphones? Not buying new one...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/27/the-hot-trend-in-smartphones-not-buying-a-new-one.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smartphone users in Singapore, the U.K. and China told CNBC's "Beyond The Valley" that foldable smartphones are "very strange," "super bulky," and expensive compared to the range of devices already available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franklin Graham calls Christians to ask God to embolden Trump against foes...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article230871584.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to win job back!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d9ab9b916a5145cb9b7f0046732427ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIENNA (AP) — Austrian Chancellor Sebastian Kurz was ousted by parliament in a no-confidence vote Monday, paving the way for a new election. The young leader, riding high in popular support,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain is back: Sanchez's Socialists return to top table...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-election-spain/spain-is-back-sanchezs-socialists-return-to-eu-top-table-idUSKCN1SX1EA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buoyed by two electoral victories in a month, Spain's Socialist leader Pedr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video sting crisis rolls on...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-austria-politics/austrian-lawmakers-sack-kurz-as-video-sting-crisis-rolls-on-idUSKCN1SX0S3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian conservative Chancellor Sebastian Kurz suffered the biggest setback of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasite in paradise: Rat lungworm disease confirmed in Hawaii visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/27/health/rat-lungworm-hawaii-cdc-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rat lungworm disease has sickened three more visitors to the state of Hawaii recently, bringing the total number of cases to 10 for 2018 and five so far this year, the state's Department of Health said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada emerges as wild card...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/445489-nevada-emerges-as-wild-card-in-2020-democratic-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nevada is lining up to be the wild card in the Democratic presidential primary after being largely been ignored by candidates so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Health Organization deems 'gaming disorder' official illness...</title>
      <link>ttps://www.cnet.com/news/world-health-organization-deems-gaming-disorder-an-official-illness/#ftag=COS-05-10aaa0j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Droid writes in languages --- it's never seen before...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/robot-writing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After training to hand-write Japanese characters, the robot could then copy words in Hindi, Greek, and English just by looking at examples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON.COM Announces $5 Million Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.subscriptioninsider.com/news/salon-announces-5-million-deal-to-sell-itself-to-new-buyer-6517-1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.subscriptioninsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salon is selling its assets for $5 million after steadily losing money since going on public in 1999. Get the details at Subscription Insider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete pushes for massive fundraising haul...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/26/pete-buttigieg-fundraising-2020-1345001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South Bend mayor's campaign is pushing bundlers to help keep his momentum going with a big second-quarter fundraising total.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is latest spate of twisters new normal in Missouri and Kansas?</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/article230790399.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'whizz-kid' politician to deposed leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190527-austrias-sebastian-kurz-whizz-kid-politician-deposed-leader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria's Sebastian Kurz: from 'whizz-kid' politician to deposed leader</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Organizes Striking Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/26/sanders-campaign-using-voter-data-email-lists-to-help-organize-striking-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-VT) is increasingly using his campaign’s mailing lists and voter data to rally striking workers across the nation. | Politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This Is Just the Beginning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2019/05/27/farage-declares-history-made-brexit-party-takes-lead-eu-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nigel Farage has led the Brexit Party to victory while the establishment parties suffered historic losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 forecast modelers predict Trump will win in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-2020-presidential-election-forecast-models-b9a95aca-7f25-4c6a-af91-720b7828afa5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jobs and incumbency resonate with voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memorial Day Weekend Heat Wave Sets All-Time May Records in Southeast...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/holiday/memorial-day/news/2019-05-17-memorial-day-weekend-heat-wave-could-smash-may-records-in-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memorial Day is the unofficial kickoff to summer. You'll get no argument in the Southeast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK takes heat...</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/2019/05/27/facebook-still-cant-control-the-far-right-political-propaganda-monster-it-built/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;venturebeat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The week leading up to the European Union Parliamentary elections reinforced the image of Facebook as a company unable to control its platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High stakes for enclave as Europe's biggest casino goes bust...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/high-stakes-enclave-europes-biggest-casino-goes-bust-035531527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campione d'Italia (Italy) (AFP) - Campione d'Italia, a tiny Italian enclave on the shores of Switzerland's Lake Lugano, is fighting for its survival after its main source of income -- a giant casino -- went bankrupt. "Rien ne va plus" -- the French version of "no more bets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton appears in Memorial Day parade... </title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020-vision-clintons-appear-in-ny-memorial-day-parade-as-bill-looks-pale-frail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For not being a political candidate, Hillary Clinton sure is keeping up a campaign-like schedule. Bill and Hillary are once again marching in the New Castle-Chappaqua, New York Memorial Day parade, according to Twitter users in attendance. Tradition continues in Chappaqua at Memorial Day Parade on beautiful day. pic.twitter.com/kbnbChh0Ni — David Weissmann (@djweissmann) May 27, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever private border wall built in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/27/first-ever-private-border-wall-built-new-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A private group announced Monday that it has constructed a half-mile wall along a section of the U.S.-Mexico border in New Mexico, in what it said was a first in the border debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria's Kurz Ousted After Nationalists Turn on Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/27/austrian-far-right-party-likely-to-back-motion-to-oust-chancellor-eu-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motion in parliament, backed by MPs from Social Democrats and far-right Freedom Party, follows video-sting scandal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/05/exclusive-video-we-build-the-wall-completes-first-half-mile-of-us-border-wall-in-4-days-from-private-donations/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope cries racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/pope-francis-sounds-racism-alarm-as-eu-nationalists-win-big</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AFP) - Pope Francis warned on Monday (May 27) against a rise of intolerance and racism as far-right nationalists and eurosceptic parties made historic gains in European elections.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortest-serving chancellor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/austrian-chancellor-set-no-confidence-showdown-044037009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria's Chancellor Sebastian Kurz on Monday lost a no-confidence vote in parliament, removing him and his cabinet from office over a corruption scandal that brought has down his coalition government. "An application (by the opposition Social Democrats) has been accepted, so he has lost the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standoff...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/israeli-political-standoff-risks-provoking-election-rerun-134505307.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli coalition negotiations remained deadlocked Monday as Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and a right-wing party leader engaged in a standoff that could provoke new elections only months after April 9 polls. Netanyahu has until Wednesday night to form a coalition government, but ex-defence minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian official floors journalist who asks about alleged corruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/pro-vladimir-putin-official-floors-16208984</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burly bureaucrat Sergei Zaitsev, 52, was furious over questions asked by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL: Villagers kill Ebola health worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190527-villagers-kill-ebola-health-worker-eastern-dr-congo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Villagers kill Ebola health worker in eastern DR Congo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUSTRIA: 'Shocking' defacements of outdoor Holocaust art...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190527-shocking-defacements-outdoor-holocaust-art-austrian-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Shocking' defacements of outdoor Holocaust art: Austrian president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT co-founder: Glorifying extreme work schedules 'toxic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/reddit-co-founder-alexis-ohanian-on-glorifying-being-overworked.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexis Ohanian, the co-founder of Reddit and managing partner at the venture capital firm Initialized Capital, says bragging about working insane hours can be dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China state TV uses 'DAILY SHOW' clip as Anti-American propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f75250e73fbe490fa7cc76cfec559adc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China has deployed an unlikely voice in its trade war with the U.S.: Trevor Noah of Comedy Central's The Daily Show. A brief clip from the comedian's "If You Don't Know, Now...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel coalition in crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190527-merkels-coalition-crisis-talks-after-eu-vote-debacle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel's coalition in crisis talks after EU vote debacle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper prints cut-out skullcap to fight anti-Semitism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190527-german-paper-prints-cut-out-kippa-fight-anti-semitism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German paper prints cut-out kippa to fight anti-Semitism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy stunned as Salvini wins majority; 'New Europe is born'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1132447/european-elections-latest-news-matteo-salvini-league-lega-italy-democratic-party-brexit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MATTEO SALVINI's Lega Nord (League) Party has claimed a convincing European Parliament victory, in a shock result in Italy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive policing could see innocent citizens framed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/777862/uk-police-predictive-policing-minority-report-liberty-crime-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria's Kurz Faces Ouster After Nationalists Turn on Him...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/austria-kurz-faces-ouster-nationalists-074214749.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Freedom Party decided to back the no-confidence vote against Kurz and his cabinet that will be decided in parliament about 5 p.m. in Vienna. The motion was brought by Austria’s Social Democrats, the biggest opposition group. It means the country will likely be ruled by a caretaker government ahead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Farage become UK PM?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/05/27/nigel-farage-become-prime-minister-brexit-party-9695684/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farage has warned Tories the Brexit Party will 'stun everybody' in a general election if the UK fails to leave the EU on October 31.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO recognizes 'burn-out' as medical condition...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/world-health-organisation-recognises-burn-out-as-medical-condition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AFP) - The World Health Organisation has for the first time recognised "burn-out" in its International Classification of Diseases (ICD), which is widely used as a benchmark for diagnosis and health insurers.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTINENT AT CROSSROADS</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6152801851684d879999dbcdc62c1e0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — European Union leaders and party officials plotted strategy Monday after European Parliament elections ended the domination of the main center-right and center-left parties and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems claim victory as president gets battered in court...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/445498-democrats-claim-victory-as-trump-gets-battered-in-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump took a beating in federal court this week, losing a pair of lawsuits aimed at hindering House Democrats' investigations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of Trump tweets on decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/the-impact-of-trump-tweets-is-on-the-decline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s tweets have less of an impact now than they did two years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Screaming and panicking' as log ride boat ejects family at California park...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article230858699.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONALISTS GAIN</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-election/nationalists-surge-in-eu-parliament-vote-but-pro-eu-parties-remain-dominant-idUSKCN1SX0P7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro-European parties kept a firm grip on the EU parliament on Monday as liberal ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In vastly white Iowa, black Dems poised to play 2020 role...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8a57aa8ecd0244eb8de9d37eae89d814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — In Iowa, one of the whitest states in the nation, more than 100 black Democrats who expect to attend the 2020 caucuses crammed into a tiny community center in the capital...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army TWITTER question highlights toll of America's wars...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-army-twitter-highlights-toll-americas-wars-025724107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days ahead of an annual holiday when Americans remember those who died while serving in the armed forces, the US Army's Twitter account asked people how their time in the military affected them and received an outpouring of grief. "OEF, OIF ptsd with chronic pain," one Twitter user wrote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK 'gives global platform to illegal dogfighting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/26/facebook-gives-global-platform-to-illegal-dogfights </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Global rivers awash with 'dangerous levels' of antibiotics...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/may/27/worlds-rivers-awash-with-dangerous-levels-of-antibiotics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Largest global study finds the drugs in two-thirds of test sites in 72 countries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy plan outlines how war-games harm marine animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/navy-plans-testing-of-futuristic-technology-sonar-harm-to-mammals-in-pacific-northwest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy intends to continue testing and training operations in the Pacific Northwest, including sonar, Growler jets and rail guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME Columnist Trump 'Quote' Goes Viral -- Then Admits Made Up...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/05/26/ian-bremmer-fake-trump-quote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time columnist Ian Bremmer on Sunday tweeted a quote from Donald Trump about North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un that quickly went viral — but it wasn't real.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
