<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Impeachment now inevitable?</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/10/impeachment-now-inevitable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russiagate consumed the first three years of Trump's presidency. "Ukrainegate" and impeachment give promise of dominating the fourth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  BIDEN WORKED WITH WHISTLEBLOWER</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/joe-biden-worked-with-whistleblower-when-he-was-vice-president-officials-reveal  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2020 Democratic candidate with whom the CIA whistleblower had a "professional" tie is Joe Biden, according to intelligence officers and former White House officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO IS PAYING RUDY?</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/We-have-no-idea-who-is-paying-Rudy-Giuliani-14506916.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani is not the secretary of state. In fact, he has no official position in President Donald Trump's Cabinet or administration. Yet he is traveling the world holding himself out as a U.S. government operative, engaging in some unknown amount of "unofficial" diplomacy and insisting his work is not only officially sanctioned by the president but also assisted by the State Department. The president's "private lawyer" is not charging Trump for his services, but he and his law firm are known to have dozens of clients - including foreign entities - who are paying for whatever services they think Giuliani can provide for them.  That is a very convenient setup for Giuliani - but it leaves the public in the dark about the wealthy special interests who might be subsidizing his gratis work for Trump - or for whom he might actually be working while invoking Trump's name and that of the State Department. Because Giuliani is not officially a federal employee, he can sidestep ethics obligations that would require transparency behind the foreign or domestic interests who are paying him.  Giuliani appears to have spearheaded Trump's efforts to convince the Ukrainian president to open an investigation into Trump's political rivals. Text messages released by Congress also show he was steering U.S. policy in Ukraine in a direction that alarmed career State Department officials, who thought it harmed U.S. interests there. Giuliani himself has boasted that he effectively had official imprimatur for what might appear to have been freelance diplomacy with Kiev: Appearing on CBS's "Face the Nation" on Sept. 29, Giuliani said about his outreach to Ukraine: "I did not do this on my own. I did it at the request of the State Department, and I have all of the text messages to prove it."  Despite playing such an important role in U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National security officials raised alarms about Ukraine policy before and after Trump call... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Several-national-security-officials-raised-alarms-14510135.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - At least four national security officials were so alarmed by the Trump administration's attempts to pressure Ukraine for political purposes that they raised concerns with a White House lawyer both before and immediately after President Donald Trump's July 25 call with that country's president, according to U.S. officials and other people familiar with the matter.  The nature and timing of the previously undisclosed discussions with National Security Council legal adviser John Eisenberg indicate that officials were delivering warnings through official White House channels earlier than previously understood - including before the call that precipitated a whistleblower complaint and the impeachment inquiry of the president.  At the time, the officials were unnerved by the removal in May of the U.S. ambassador to Ukraine; subsequent efforts by Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani to promote Ukraine-related conspiracies; as well as signals in meetings at the White House that Trump wanted the new government in Kiev to deliver material that might be politically damaging to Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden.  Those concerns soared in the call's aftermath, officials said. Within minutes, senior officials including national security adviser John Bolton were being pinged by subordinates about problems with what the president had said to his Ukrainian counterpart, Volodymyr Zelensky. Bolton and others scrambled to obtain a rough transcript that was already being "locked down" on a highly classified computer network.  "When people were listening to this in real time there were significant concerns about what was going on - alarm bells were kind of ringing," said one person familiar with the sequence of events inside the White House, who, like others, spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss a sensitive matter....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rick Perry subpoenaed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/10/democrats-subpoena-rick-perry-for-documents-in-impeachment-inquiry-000280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Clinton For Congress?!</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-nita-lowey-reelection-2020-20191010-cpu4x77l2vbgdb2oxpihxrpd3i-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westchester Democrats want the Clinton machine back in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Study Tracks 'Attentiveness' of Viewers via In-Home Data Collection...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/carols-second-act-has-attentive-viewing-new-series-1246901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS comedy's audience had its eyes on the screen more than any other series premiere, according to a company that tracks viewing habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'POSE' Star Billy Porter to Play Fairy Godmother in 'CINDERELLA' Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/billy-porter-talks-join-sonys-cinderella-1244953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Emmy winner and 'Pose' star will join Camila Cabello, who is tackling the titular princess role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders' heart attack puts his campaign in uncharted territory...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sanders-heart-attack-puts-campaign-080000425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders has so far muscled past questions about his age by keeping a grueling campaign schedule, bouncing between ice cream socials, private meetings, rallies or town halls in a single day -- with aides decades his junior struggling to keep up.But the 78-year-old’s heart attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi confronts decision on vote... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pelosi-confronts-decision-impeachment-vote-080000147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump is pushing House Speaker Nancy Pelosi to hold a formal vote on impeachment, a move that would change the politics of the probe more than its legal standing.Trump this week escalated his fight against the Democratic-led investigation of his dealings with Ukraine with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charged with federal campaign finance violations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9125e9ccd894965bbf2860100366779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Two Florida businessmen tied to President Donald Trump's lawyer and the Ukraine impeachment investigation were charged Thursday with federal campaign finance...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Low IQ Linked To Greater Risk Of Suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/low-iq-associated-with-greater-risk-of-suicide-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have found a connection between low IQ scores in adolescence and a greater risk of suicide or attempted suicide during adulthood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire's comments about 'getting into a girl's pants' spark backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fisher-investments-ken-fisher-billionaires-sexist-comments-spark-outrage-getting-into-a-girls-pants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is why we haven't had our #MeToo moment," said one female wealth manager who heard Ken Fisher's remarks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTAGE OUTRAGE: PG&amp;E Egged By Frustrated Resident...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/10/10/pge-office-in-oroville-gets-egged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PG&amp;E is taking a lot of heat as frustration mounts over the Public Safety Power Shutoffs that have hit a good swath of Northern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  How the NBA censored me on American soil...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/10/how-the-nba-censored-me-on-american-soil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve been an NBA fanatic as long as I can remember. Growing up, I rooted for the Minnesota Timberwolves. I was there for the ups — who can forget that almost magical 2004 season? — and all of the d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities Banning New Fast-Food Drive-Throughs...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2019/10/10/765789694/why-u-s-cities-are-banning-new-fast-food-drive-throughs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of the bans aim to curb emissions and protect pedestrians. The bans are also sometimes touted as a way to help fight obesity, but past studies suggest they don't have that effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for Chelsea?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/10/nita-lowey-congresswoman-people-think-chelsea-clinton-groomed-replace-retire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Democratic Rep. Nita Lowey announced she will not seek reelection in 2020 in a district where Chelsea Clinton is reportedly considering a run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos' Master Plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/11/what-jeff-bezos-wants/598363/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What the Amazon founder and CEO wants for his empire and himself, and what that means for the rest of us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  PARTISAN DIVIDE TURNS UGLY</title>
      <link>https://www.people-press.org/2019/10/10/partisan-antipathy-more-intense-more-personal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.people-press.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Division and animosity between the two political parties in the U.S. has deepened. Most partisans view the other side as ‘closed-minded’; Republicans see Democrats as ‘unpatriotic.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first cloned cow Kaga dies at 21 -- outliving twin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-first-cloned-cow-kaga-20554342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaga and Noto were the born in Japan using the same tech as Dolly the Sheep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA player$ warned to avoid China talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/10/sports-agents-warn-players-to-avoid-china-talk-as-nba-walks-fine-line.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The backlash could hit closer to home for players, many of whom spend part of their summers in China promoting lucrative deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT CAFE BURGLARIZED; CATS SAT AND WATCHED...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/article235986393.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter shut down for asking about censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/10/10/watch-cnn-reporter-shut-down-for-asking-nba-stars-about-china-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CNN reporter was cut off by an NBA staffer while asking James Harden and Russell Westbrook about the free speech furor surrounding China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk plane passenger vomits on woman's hair...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10105088/drunk-plane-passenger-vomit-flight-usa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DRUNK plane passenger was escorted off the aircraft after throwing up on a woman’s head, forcing cabin crew to clean her up in the sink. The ordeal prompted cabin crew to make passengers de…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NBC Roiled by Ronan Farrow Book Accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nbc-execs-andy-lack-and-noah-oppenheim-back-on-hot-seat-over-farrow-allegations-on-weinstein-lauer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I honestly want to throw up,” one NBC employee told The Daily Beast amid new disturbing claims about the network’s dealings with Harvey Weinstein and Matt Lauer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NERVOUS NATION: 1 In 5 Americans Believe They Have Anxiety Disorder...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/nervous-nation-1-in-5-americans-believe-they-have-an-undiagnosed-anxiety-disorder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shocking one in five respondents say they feel anxious so often that they actually believe they are dealing with an undiagnosed anxiety disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' CRASH AND BURN; UNDER 3 MILLION VIEWERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/10/09/tuesday-tv-ratings-empire-drops-again-as-fans-turn-away-tune-out-plus-ncis-dips-below-12-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Empire” is not going out in style. The once hot-as-a-pistol show dropped again to its lowest ratings ever. Tuesday’s night audience was down to 2,793,000 from 2,941,000 in week 2…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obesity Weighing on Education, Productivity and Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.moneyweb.co.za/news-fast-news/obesity-is-weighing-on-education-productivity-and-the-economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moneyweb.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adults who are overweight are less productive and more likely to be absent from work, study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I hate going back to the U.S.':  69-year-old left Utah for Portugal, where you can live well on $2,000 month...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-hate-going-back-to-the-us-this-69-year-old-left-utah-for-portugal-where-you-can-live-well-on-2000-a-month-2019-10-09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pros and cons of living in Portugal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Farms that supply WHOLE FOODS subject workers to oppressive condiitons...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/farms-that-supply-whole-foods-subject-workers-to-oppressive-conditions-international-report-finds-2019-10-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The charity claims that laborers that supply Whole Foods reported working up to 14 hours a day in “oppressive heat with few rest breaks,” and often with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Adviser Claims CHINA Handed Him Intelligence on Hunter Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-pillsbury-trump-adviser-claims-china-handed-him-intelligence-on-hunter-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Pillsbury is an informal White House adviser who Trump once called “probably the leading authority on China.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Best Nude Beach in World...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/balmins-best-nude-beach-in-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beach itself is beautiful, but what makes it remarkable are the demographics it attracts and the liberating sensation unique to this place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How America Lost Dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/10/work-its-whats-for-dinner/599770/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne and George Conway's tawdry love triangle with all of us...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Kellyanne-and-George-Conway-s-tawdry-love-14504402.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm beginning to wonder whether George and Kellyanne Conway have enlisted us all into a private fetish - a relationship-spicing exercise defined by mutual debasement and public shame. We now know too much about the marriage between two prominent Republicans. Not the nitty-gritty of who snores and who loads the dishwasher wrong, but the vast cosmic business, like who has apparently lost all semblance of respect for who's lifelong wedded partner.  George Conway, according to the succinct bio accompanying the essays he publishes in national media sharply criticizing the Trump administration, is "a lawyer in New York." Which is true, but this description is like calling George W. Bush "a painter with an exhibit at the Kennedy Center." Also true, weirdly, but that's not why anybody's buying tickets.  George Conway is known for is being a vehement Never Trumper, but what he's really known for is being the husband of Kellyanne Conway. Who is herself a senior counselor to President Donald Trump.  George has become the toast of the resistance. Not because of what he says; scores of learned experts have spent the past three years furiously penning similar arguments. He has become the toast of the resistance mostly because we know who his wife is. He's riding her coattails while on an apparent mission that would, ultimately, put her out of a job. Which makes the whole thing more ... diabolical? More squalid? More delicious?  "There is a cancer in the presidency," George wrote in April; in June he described one of Trump's briefs as "spectacularly anti-constitutional." He seemed to peak in July, calling his wife's boss "racist," as well as "boorish, dim-witted, inarticulate, incoherent, narcissistic and insensitive." Then, last week he hit a new apex with a massive 12,000 word piece in the Atlantic, whose scathing contents, while...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS PRICES HIT $6 IN LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-prices-exceed-5-a-gallon-at-some-los-angeles-area-stations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As gas prices reached its highest level in the state of California since 2015, some Los Angeles area gas stations are charging more than $5 a gallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: 'PARASITE' must-see movie of year...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/870601/parasite-mustsee-movie-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bong Joon Hoâ€™s latest is hilarious, devastating, and a serious Oscar contender</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Suicides: Top Cop Says Department Dealing With Mental Health Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/10/09/nypd-commissioner-james-oneill-on-officer-suicides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYPD Commissioner James O'Neill sat down with CBS2's Jessica Moore for one of his first interviews about officer suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Giuliani Associates Arrested...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/2-florida-men-tied-guiliani-142138820.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Florida businessmen tied to President Donald Trump's personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani have been arrested on campaign finance violations resulting from a $325,000 donation to a political action committee supporting Trump's reelection. Lev Parnas and Igor Fruman were arrested on a four-count</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 2:  Mass blackouts in CA due to fire danger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/014e1056b9ad4ef092ec4a7a1195dfad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SONOMA, Calif. (AP) — More than 1.5 million people in Northern California were in the dark Thursday, most for a second day, after the state's largest utility cut off electricity to more customers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: 8-year-old scales border wall replica -- in minute!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-8-year-old-scales-border-wall-replica-in-one-minute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump told reporters in San Diego last month that the government tested wall prototypes with “20 mountain climbers” who concluded the design going up along the U.S.-Mexico border “was the one that was hardest to climb.” Trump said the climbers invited to participate were “very good” – “some of them were champions” – …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athlete glues self to  top of jet in 'climate' protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10104063/extinction-rebellion-london-city-airport-today-shut-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Extinction Rebellion protester glued himself to the top of a British Airways plane at London City Airport today. The man, identified by Extinction Rebellion as former Paralympic cyclist James Br…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RAGES: Polls 'Suck', Napolitano 'Terrible', Shep Smith, 'Fired' Donna Brazile...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-loses-it-on-fox-news-polls-suck-napolitano-is-terrible-shep-smith-fired-donna-brazile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump slammed Fox News on Thursday for the network's new poll showing most of the country's registered voters want him impeached and removed from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Pope say Jesus isn't God?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/michael-w-chapman/scalfari-pope-francis-told-me-jesus-incarnate-was-man-not-all-god</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis and his long-time  friend and interviewer Eugenio Scalfari. (Radio Spada)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 stashing cash at home in fear of recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/10/almost-1-in-5-americans-hide-cash-in-their-homes-fearing-a-recession.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on their fears of a potential recession, 17% of Americans have stashing cash at home, according to a new poll from MetLife</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E Truck Struck By Bullet Driving On Highway...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/10/09/pge-truck-window-struck-bullet-colusa-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the CHP, the marked PG&amp;E truck was driving south on I-5, south of Lenahan Road when the passenger-side window shattered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Uses Propaganda in TV Graphic...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/espn-uses-chinese-propaganda-in-tv-graphic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN on Wednesday evening showed a graphic recognizing China's erroneous claim to own the South China Sea, despite the Permanent Court of Arbitration ruling against China in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: High School Teacher Pummeled By Student While Trying To Prevent Fight...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/10/09/watch-teacher-pummeled-student-after-he-tried-prevent-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teacher who was trying to prevent two high school students from fighting landed in the hospital Monday, school officials in Atlanta said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert who called '08 crisis says repeat of December meltdown inevitable...</title>
      <link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/expert-who-called-the-2008-crisis-says-repeat-of-december-meltdown-is-inevitable-2019-10-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A repeat of that rout that wiped nearly 20% off the S&amp;P 500 last December may be unavoidable, warns our call of the day from former GLG global macro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Pope say Jesus isn't God?</title>
      <link>https://www.thetablet.co.uk/news/12111/scalfari-claims-pope-does-not-believe-jesus-the-man-was-divine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetablet.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian journalist Eugenio Scalfari has caused a new uproar by writing in Italy&amp;rsquo;s respected&amp;nbsp;La Repubblica newspaper that Pope Francis does not believe 'Jesus of Nazareth' was God.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIVERSITY BANS WHITE STUDENTS FROM ATTENDING ANTI-RACISM MEETING...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/university-bans-white-students-from-attending-an-anti-racism-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh, the irony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives call for 'expeditious' probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Conservatives-call-for-expeditious-impeachment-14506081.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - More than a dozen prominent conservative lawyers, including George Conway, offered their legal reasoning for an "expeditious" impeachment probe into President Donald Trump, creating a document they hope will be read by Republicans who continue to stand by the president.  The 16 attorneys, many of whom worked in Republican administrations, wrote in a joint statement to be released Thursday morning that Trump's now infamous call with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky, the text messages between diplomats and Trump's public call for China to investigate a political opponent are "undisputed" events that amount to Trump violating his oath of office.  "We have not just a political candidate open to receiving foreign assistance to better his chances at winning an election, but a current president openly and privately calling on foreign governments to actively interfere in the most sacred of U.S. democratic processes, our elections," they wrote.  Conway, husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway and outspoken Trump critic, helped form a coalition of like-minded conservatives a year ago who wanted to call out what they deemed illegal and unconstitutional behavior by the president. The signatories are members of that group, Checks and Balances.  Paul Rosenzweig, who served as President George W. Bush's deputy assistant secretary for policy at the Department on Homeland Security, said he personally would have gone further than the group's comments, which are stern, but measured in tone.  "It strikes me that no reasonable attorney can doubt that there was a quid pro quo here," said Rosenzweig, referring to Trump's holding back military aid to Ukraine while requesting the country investigate a political foe.  "I would vote for impeachment, and I would vote for conviction and removal in the Senate as well,"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Special Forces member: 'I am ashamed for first time in career'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/turkey-syria-invasion-special-forces-soldier-kurds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Special Forces soldier serving alongside the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF) in Syria told Fox News' Jennifer Griffin on Wednesday they were witnessing Turkish atrocities on the frontlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young people quitting jobs in droves...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/young-people-quitting-jobs-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It should come as no surprise that younger generations are paving the way for the de-stigmatization of mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice Roberts would be 'umpire' in Senate trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/10/10/impeachment-chief-justice-roberts-donald-trump-umpire/3920262002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Roberts was arguing a case before the Supreme Court during the Senate's last impeachment trial. He could be presiding over the next one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAK OUT? Turkey shelled prison holding ISIS fighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-syria-security-turkey-prison/turkey-shelled-prison-holding-is-foreign-fighters-kurdish-led-administration-idUSKBN1WP15C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Syrian Kurdish-led authorities accused Turkey of shelling a prison holding I...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan threatens to send 3.6 million refugees to Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-syria-security-turkey-europe/turkeys-erdogan-threatens-to-send-syrian-refugees-to-europe-idUSKBN1WP1ED</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Tayyip Erdogan said on Thursday Ankara will send the 3.6 million Syria...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea threatens to resume nuke, long-range missile tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/75aaddf43e064d44b667bf09da627201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea threatened again Thursday to resume nuclear and long-range missile tests, accusing the U.S. of having instigated some members of the U.N. Security Council to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uganda plans bill imposing death penalty for gay sex...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191010103819-wbt6x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bill was nullified five years ago on a technicality and the government says it plans to resurrect it within weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to host first post-impeachment inquiry rally in Dem stronghold...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191010093342-xhyld</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/TRUMP (PIX):Trump to host first post-impeachment inquiry rally in Democratic stronghold</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The minivan-driving fiscal conservative who could beat Canada's Trudeau...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191009195604-xpz4x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANADA-ELECTION/SCHEER (PIX):The minivan-driving fiscal conservative who could beat Canada's Trudeau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCKETS NIKE merchandise disappears from stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-basketball-nba-nike/houston-rockets-nike-merchandise-disappears-from-china-stores-idUSKBN1WP109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Houston Rockets sneakers and other merchandise were pulled from several Nike sto...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG&amp;E pleads for employee safety; Vehicle hit by gunfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/PG-E-pleads-for-employee-safety-amid-outage-14505820.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials at Pacific Gas and Electric Co. on Wednesday called for the public to let employees do their jobs safely amid frustrations with a widespread California power shutdown, after authorities reported that a bullet was fired at one of the energy provider's vehicles.  The plea came the same day that police say a threatening letter was reported at a PG&amp;E facility, as the utility switched off electricity to hundreds of thousands of people. The planned outage - the biggest in the state's history, announced as a measure to reduce wildfire risk - comes as PG&amp;E faces massive liabilities for starting a blaze that killed 85 people and destroyed the town of Paradise last year.  "We realize and understand the impact and the hardship as the result of this decision that we've made," Sumeet Singh, vice president of PG&amp;E's Community Wildfire Safety Program, said at a news conference. But employees and contractors "have families that live in your communities, they have friends that are members of your communities," Singh added. "So let's just ensure their safety as well as they are doing this work in the interest of your safety."  Power companies worried about California's devastating wildfires are increasingly turning to planned shutdowns. PG&amp;E says this latest, unusually disruptive measure, which could last several days, was prompted by the dry winds like those that helped fuel disastrous fires before. The outages have upset customers, closed schools and workplaces and raised fears that people who rely on electricity for medical needs could be caught unprepared.  Some have questioned this week's shutdown, which PG&amp;E expects to affect 800,000 people, as excessive. About 650,000 customers were expected to lack power Wednesday evening, according to the company.  "This cannot be something that can be acceptable nor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey says ground forces advancing in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8500277b239b4acab805e5e2bdb43938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEYLANPINAR, Turkey (AP) — Turkish ground forces pressed their advance against Kurdish fighters in northern Syria on Thursday, Turkey's Defense Ministry said, launching airstrikes and unleashing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Bastion Georgia Suddenly in Play for Dems in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gop-bastion-georgia-suddenly-play-080000622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Republicans have had a hammerlock on Georgia for a generation. It could slip away — if Democrats decide to make it a fight.The state is a must-win for President Donald Trump. Republicans are defending two U.S. Senate seats that may swing control of the chamber. Democrats remain underdogs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Watching at Home? Cam Footage Reviewed by Humans...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-workers-may-watching-cloud-090003511.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In a promotional video, Amazon.com Inc. says its Cloud Cam home security camera provides “everything you need to monitor your home, day or night.” In fact, the artificially intelligent device requires help from a squad of invisible employees.Dozens of Amazon workers based in India and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS LACK UNDER PRESSURE...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/10/09/nbc-news-chief-andy-lack-preyed-on-female-employees-for-sex-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News chief Andrew Lack — once accused of mishandling sexual harassment complaints at the Peacock Network — preyed on female underlings and pursued sexual relationships with them, according to o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador protesters march; Clashes break out in Quito...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fc922b2c8baa4cf9a22f6b9481b3e7a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — Thousands of protesters staged anti-government rallies Wednesday, seeking to intensify pressure on Ecuador's president after a week of unrest sparked by fuel price...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska Supreme Court hears youth 'climate change' lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ca969f3562494dcea5f60242fcd55f21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — An Alaska law promoting fossil fuel development infringes on the constitutional rights of young residents to a healthy environment, a lawyer told Alaska Supreme Court...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House aides try disappearing act amid impeachment talk...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/63a2cabb2a54492591165fe0fcc20214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — They've skipped the high-profile Sunday TV shows and avoided driveway chat sessions with reporters. Few who are typically eager to defend the president have appeared at all on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW NORMAL?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/oct/08/california-pge-power-shutdown-wildfire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With nearly 800,000 customers affected in the largest shutdown this year, the utility is hoping to avoid a devastating fire season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's decision tests bounds of Republican support...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-syria-decision-tests-the-bounds-of-republican-support-as-he-demands-solidarity-on-impeachment/ar-AAIxy7x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.kqed.org/science/1948809/searchable-map-of-bay-area-power-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kqed.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find out if you're in an area slated for a PG&amp;amp;E power outage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto on Brink of Elimination from Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/10/09/end-road-beto-orourke-failed-meet-polling-threshold-november-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O'Rourke has not met the polling threshold for the MSNBC/Washington Post debate in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican Considers Recognition of 'Ecological Sins'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2019/10/09/vatican-synod-amazon-proposes-recognition-ecological-sins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican synod on the Amazon region has proposed adding “sins against the environment” to lists of traditionally recognized sins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic 'all-out blizzard' to bury, punish central USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/historic-allout-blizzard-to-bury-huge-swath-of-central-us-unleash-punishing-cold-blast/598076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Stripper to Superstar: Cardi B Set To Be Queen Of All Media...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/cardi-b-rhythm-flow-review-nancy-drew-treadstone-hip-hop-songs-that-shook-america-show-to-watch-this-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just like a great hip hop tune, there’s a lot in the mix this week for the show you have to watch. We’ve got a small screen offshoot of a big screen franchise, a new iteration of a certain teen sle…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence aiming to release records of his own... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e48c28cf0625430fa829431df3872ead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAUKEE, Iowa (AP) — Vice President Mike Pence said Wednesday he is working with the White House counsel's office to release transcripts of his own calls with Ukranian President Volodymyr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will put medical emergency planning to test...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/health-and-medicine/article235940257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KURDS BETRAYED...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/They-fought-alongside-the-US-for-five-years-to-be-bombed-by-US-NATO-ally-604103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like thieves in the night US forces withdrew from their positions, without explanation, processes, discussions, or leaving behind people to monitor the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Physically Rips Down NBA Ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/watch-triggered-chicoms-physically-rip-down-nba-ads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communists proceed with anti-NBA censorship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX SHOCK:  51% WANT TRUMP REMOVED</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-poll-record-support-for-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just over half of voters want President Trump impeached and removed from office, according to a Fox News Poll released Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  TAKE YOUR PROBE AND SHOVE IT!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d0c86f98067b46ccaebb059f5881c22d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The combative White House letter vowing to defy the "illegitimate" impeachment inquiry has actually put President Donald Trump on a more certain path to charges. His refusal to...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
