<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Covid wars launch DeSantis into GOP 'top tier'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/16/covid-ron-desantis-2024-469071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida governor’s clashes with the media and reluctance to embrace coronavirus restrictions are fueling conservative chatter about a 2024 presidential bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mariachis' 'Hand of God' touches patient on ventilator...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mariachis-hand-god-touches-covid-012220387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wife of an ailing Anaheim locksmith hires a band to lift his spirits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Soothing, Digital Rooms of YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/16/the-soothing-digital-rooms-of-youtube/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picture this: You’re in the Hogwarts library. Rain falls outside, a fire crackles across the room, and somewhere offscreen, quills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Debt Prisons...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/16/the-new-debt-prisons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While controversial calls to “defund the police” have grabbed headlines, we urgently need to examine how we fund the police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While rest of country freezes, Florida's sunny beaches overflow with crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/while-the-rest-of-the-country-freezes-floridas-sunny-beaches-overflow-with-crowds/ar-BB1dIfJV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — As a massive, historic winter storm swept across the U.S. on Monday, unloading dangerous snowfall, freezing rain and piercing wind chills, South Florida’s scorching beaches served as a hot destination for hundreds of tourists and the usual crowd of locals who enjoyed the long holiday weekend by the water, despite the coronavirus pandemic. Wearing little to no masks and barely keeping ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep's family DISOWNS him:  Relatives call him 'disappointment to God' and member of 'devil's army'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9264005/Kinzinger-releases-letter-family-saying-joined-devils-army-backing-Trumps-impeachment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Adam Kinzinger told the New York Times he received the pejorative note just two days after he called for Trump to be removed from office following the Capitol riots on January 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Mardi Gras canceled, New Orleans residents are making their homes into floats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mardi-gras-is-canceled-so-residents-are-making-their-homes-into-floats-e2-80-98new-orleans-doesn-e2-80-99t-know-how-to-do-anything-halfway-e2-80-99/ar-BB1dGVFd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It started on Twitter: "Turn your house into a float and throw all the beads from your attic at your neighbors walking by. #mardigras2021.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media video leads police to suspect in Chihuahua's death...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/social-media-video-leads-riverside-police-to-suspect-in-chihuahuas-death/ar-BB1dHq7m?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Riverside Police Department said a call about a video of a small Chihuahua with a large laceration on its neck led to an arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians accuse Israel of blocking vaccines to Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210215-palestinians-accuse-israel-of-blocking-vaccines-to-gaza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians accuse Israel of blocking vaccines to Gaza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed in freak accident at car wash...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/customer-killed-by-suv-at-queens-car-wash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 54-year-old woman was killed in a freak accident at a Queens car wash on Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donor gave millions for 'voter fraud' investigation. Now he wants his money back...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2021/02/15/a-republican-donor-gave-25-million-for-a-voter-fraud-investigation-he-wants-his-money-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s campaign and the Republican Party collected $255 million in two months, saying the money would support legal challenges to an election marred by fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway moves mountains to bring skiing to the people...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/norway-moves-mountains-bring-skiing-015228337.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norwegians, the saying goes, are born with skis on their feet. But with a lack of snow and the pandemic this year leaving many in despair, authorities are bringing snow and ski trails to downtown Oslo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woke teachers want Shakespeare cut from curriculum...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/15/woke-teachers-want-shakespeare-cut-curriculum-abou/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crown teachers once put on Shakespeare now lies uneasy upon his head as the English playwright comes under assault from teachers who fault his un-woke attitudes regarding race, sexuality, gender and class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the Anti-Influencer Influencer...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dpaja/rise-of-the-anti-influencer-influencer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTubers are taking on their own notoriously underregulated industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New skin patch promises comprehensive health monitoring...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/02/15/New-skin-patch-promises-comprehensive-health-monitoring/9271613404438/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have developed a thin, flexible skin patch, worn on the neck, that can provide all-in-one health monitoring capabilities, including the wearer's heart rate, blood pressure and glucose levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROOF OF VACCINE FOR RESTAURANTS?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14045626/brits-covid-vaccine-passport-pub-or-restaurant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITS may have to show a vaccine passport to go to a pub or restaurant Dominic Raab suggested today. Proposals to introduce documents to let immunised Brits lead a normal life are “under considerat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys tortured in sick YOUTUBE snuff films...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14032495/youtube-baby-monkeys-torture-animal-cruelty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BABY monkeys are being tortured, exploited and even killed in a wave of sick cruelty YouTube videos. Animal rights activists have slammed the social media giant for continuing to host the disturbin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror Movie Targets Ugliness of Influencer Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/shook-is-a-horror-movie-targeting-the-ugliness-of-social-media-influencer-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new horror film ‘Shook,’ premiering on Shudder, attempts to expose the empty narcissism of influencers. But it mostly plays itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St regulators signal tougher approach to industry after GAMESTOP frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Wall-Street-regulators-signal-tougher-approach-to-15950501.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is sending a clear signal to Wall Street that the industry's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Warns LeBron About Flopping After Dramatic Dive...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nba/lakers/news/la-lakers-lebron-james-kyle-kuzma-warned-for-flopping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lakers receive first warning for violating anti-flopping rule this season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Lifeforms Found in Hostile Darkness Beneath Antarctica...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/mystery-lifeforms-have-been-found-living-in-the-dark-beneath-antarctica-s-ice-shelves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The waters below Antarctica are amongst the most inhospitable environments on our planet - or so we thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Portugal, noise ban lifts hopes for peace at last...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-portugal-noise/in-portugal-noise-ban-lifts-remote-workers-hopes-for-peace-at-last-idUSKBN2AF0JW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The construction site outside Brazilian journalist Giuliana Miranda's suburban Lisbon apartment didn't bother her much - until remote working kicked in and the drilling noise drowned out her interviewees on Zoom. Soon, she moved house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRISON OR SCHOOL? Classroom Armed with 28 Plexiglass Shields...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/myrtle-beach/horry-county-schools-plexiglass-installation/video_e55d0a0c-57fd-11eb-b5cd-f33758e05e47.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video that Teresa Holmes, a Horry County Schools teacher, took of her Forestbrook Elementary School classroom ahead of the return of hybrid instruction on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China topples USA as EU's top trade partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/china-topples-us-as-eus-top-trade-partner-over-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new data come as Brussels is trying to intensify its economic ties with Beijing by concluding an EU-China investment pact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems buzz about breakout stars of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/15/democrats-breakout-stars-trump-impeachment-469021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House members who prosecuted the case against Trump are being eyed for higher office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancel Uncle Sam?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2021/presidents-day-2021-opinion-is-it-time-to-re-think-uncle-sam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America is reckoning with representation and icons of yore. Is it time to reassess our national mascot?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man leaves $5M for dog in will...</title>
      <link>https://www.newschannel5.com/news/8-year-old-border-collie-named-lulu-inherits-5-million-in-owners-will</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newschannel5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a story of a truly pampered pet, Lulu, an 8-year-old border collie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi calls for '9/11-type' commission on Capitol attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/pelosi-calls-9-11-type-commission-capitol-attack-n1257954</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic leader also said Congress needs to pony up more money for security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Accuses NY Lawmakers of 'Extortion' Over Calls to Investigate Nursing Home Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/cuomo-accuses-ny-lawmakers-of-extortion-over-calls-to-investigate-nursing-home-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Cuomo blasted state lawmakers who have threatened to rescind his emergency powers and investigate his administration’s coverup of nursing home data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue FAA Employee Offered to 'Commit Treason' For China...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/rogue-faa-employee-offered-to-commit-treason-for-china/ar-BB1dHLTX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) employee offered to commit “treason and espionage” in exchange for $27.7 million and a promise of asylum in Germany, France, or China, according to a plea agreement filed Feb. 10 in Washington, D.C. federal court. In a statement of offense attached to the plea, Brian J. Booth, who was assigned to the FAA’s Enforcement Division, admitted to disclosing U.S. secrets last year when he sent letters to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency founded because of 9/11 shifts to face threat of domestic terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-agency-founded-because-of-911-shifts-to-face-the-threat-of-domestic-terrorism/ar-BB1dG54W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising extremism at home has forced a reassessment of priorities at the Department of Homeland Security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones Seen Capturing 30% of Express Delivery Market by 2040...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/drones-seen-capturing-30-25-of-express-delivery-market-by-2040/ar-BB1dFI5w?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Electric aircraft such as drones could account for 30% of same-day package deliveries by 2040 as network scale dramatically brings down costs, according to L.E.K. Consulting. The exact market share for vertical takeoff-and-landing aircraft will depend on how transport operators configure their networks and the comparable cost of transporting goods through road-based methods, L.E.K. said in a report Monday. Drones aren’t likely...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE AFTER TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/gop-finds-it-hard-to-quit-trump-forcing-a-post-trial-reckoning/ar-BB1dFxvS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s impeachment trial exposed the political dilemma for Republicans struggling to move past the former president, as a majority of GOP senators show they are unwilling to publicly defy him without knowing how tight a grip he still has on the party’s base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne, George Cameos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/e2-80-98american-idol-e2-80-99-premiere-features-claudia-conway-audition-with-cameos-from-her-parents-kellyanne-and-george/ar-BB1dH0bo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claudia Conway’s “American Idol” audition means that another ABC reality competition will have ties to the former Trump White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Workers Flee to $70,000-a-Month Resorts While Awaiting Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/remote-workers-flee-to-2470000-a-month-resorts-while-awaiting-vaccines/ar-BB1dH4o7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% of new serious cases are under 60 years old in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/covid-19-40-percent-of-new-serious-cases-are-under-60-heres-why-658917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Health Ministry data, almost 75% of people diagnosed over the weekend were under 40 years old, while only around 7% over 60.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother's search for missing son leads to dark world of marijuana dispensary...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/a-mother-s-search-for-missing-son-leads-to-dark-world-of-a-marijuana-dispensary/article_c911eb67-5bbb-534e-89e2-588276a7c668.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Juan Carlos Hernández went to work one afternoon and never came home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper holes up in Spain university to avoid jail for tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210215-rapper-holes-up-in-spain-university-to-avoid-jail-for-tweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper holes up in Spain university to avoid jail for tweets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAGUAR To Turn All Electric By 2025...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaeltaylor/2021/02/15/jaguar-to-turn-all-electric-by-2025-land-rover-evs-start-in-2024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaguar will pivot away from its heritage to become a full electric car brand within five years, while its Land Rover stablemate will have six EVs by 2025, the British company announced this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA readies for 'seven minutes of terror' with Mars landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1397923/mars-rover-landing-nasa-perseverance-seven-minutes-terror-nasa-news-evg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA'S Mars rover Perseverance will attempt to land on the Red Planet this week and pull off a daring manoeuvre NASA's engineers have dubbed the "seven minutes of terror".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NFL star Vincent Jackson found dead in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/30907010/ex-nfl-wr-vincent-jackson-found-dead-florida-age-38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NFL wide receiver Vincent Jackson was found dead Monday at the age of 38, the Hillsborough County (Florida) Sheriff's Office said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injured migrants say Border Patrol sent them back to Mexico after they fell off wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/immigration/2021/02/14/injured-migrants-say-border-patrol-sent-them-back-to-mexico-after-they-fell-off-trumps-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALOMAS, Mexico – To escape the lingering, devastating effects of two hurricanes and the reach of organized crime, Pedro Gomez fled Guatemala in January...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk claims he is 'alien' in bizarre  exchange...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/elon-musk-claims-alien-bizarre-23491683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla and SpaceX owner became the world's richest person last month. His response came when asked about how he runs so many massive companies simultaneously</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers tell Kamala Harris' niece to stop using aunt to build brand...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9260427/Kamala-Harris-niece-Meena-36-using-VPs-flog-merch-clothing-line.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meena Harris's Phenomenal line is still listed on non-profit retail website Social Goods next to a quote from Harris, including a $59 sweatshirt with the word 'Ambitious' emblazoned across it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first robot ARTIST set to exhibit series of self-portraits...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9259195/Worlds-robot-ARTIST-set-exhibit-series-self-portraits.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ai-Da's work will be displayed at the Design Museum in London between May and June - if lockdown rules allow. She is named after 19th-century mathematician Ada Lovelace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAIL:  So much for privacy!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-9262851/Prince-Harry-Meghan-Markle-primetime-TV-interview-Oprah.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS revealed on Monday morning that it will air the 90-minute special 'Oprah with Meghan and Harry' on March 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the dark underbelly of CHIPPENDALES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-9251957/The-dark-underbelly-Chippendales-Historian-lays-bare-sordid-origins-male-revue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Your Fantasy explores the origins of Chippendales, which was founded by Indian immigrant Somen 'Steve' Banerjee and Bruce Nahin in 1979.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctic sponges discovered under ice shelf perplex scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/15/world/antarctic-ice-shelf-sponge-discovery-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The accidental discovery of strange life forms on a boulder beneath the ice shelves of the Antarctic has confounded scientists. Animals like these aren't expected to live so far from sunlight and any obvious source of food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SILENCE OF LAMBS' at 30: Masterpiece still gripping Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/14/silence-of-the-lambs-celebrates-30th-anniversary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Silence of the Lambs" was a low-budget sleeper hit that gained widespread critical acclaim and box office success. The film has had a lasting impact on Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From medieval times to current crisis, plagues often accelerate extremist movements...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/From-medieval-times-to-our-current-crisis-15951550.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Crigler used to feed his YouTube following a politics-free diet of chatter about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADE: She Was Used...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/columns/claudia-conway-american-idol-2-1234905949/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claudia Conway faces challenges that evoke real and powerful sympathy, and not just because of her tender age. First, this 16-year-old emerged onto the national stage as someone seemingly desiring …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honolulu mayor extends restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/538869-honolulu-mayor-extends-coronavirus-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honolulu Mayor Rick Blangiardi has extended coronavirus restrictions until the middle of March despite reports of new cases remaining low in the state the past two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NESTLE announces vegan Kit Kat bar...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/538893-nestle-announces-vegan-kit-kat-bar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nestle will soon launch a vegan Kit Kat bar, expected to be the first chocolate bar from a major candy brand to be 100 percent vegan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONTECITO:  Meghan to give tell-all Oprah interview...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/royals/oprah-announces-first-interview-meghan-markle-prince-harry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oprah Winfrey was a guest at Meghan and Prince Harry's royal wedding and now lives near them in California</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Starting from scratch': Harris contradicts Fauci on White House plan...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/15/starting-from-scratch-harris-contradicts-fauci-on-white-house-covid-vaccine-plan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;​Vice President Kamala Harris ​is claiming in a new interview that the Biden administration is “starting from scratch” to develop a ​national ​vaccine distribution plan because former P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians want answers about National Guard's lengthy DC deployment...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/15/politicians-want-answers-about-national-guards-lengthy-dc-deployment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — More Republicans are demanding House Speaker Nancy Pelosi brief lawmakers on why thousands of National Guard troops are being kept in Washington, DC, until the middle of March. R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex offender charged after 'deep-fried' body parts found...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/15/pa-sex-offender-charged-after-deep-fried-body-parts-found/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Philadelphia man has been busted after body parts were found in a U-Haul and dumpster — including deep-fried hands and feet, according to a report. Taray Herring, 47,  was arraigned Saturday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems hire ex-gang member to top campaign post...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/14/house-dems-hire-ex-gang-member-to-top-campaign-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Democrats’ campaign arm has hired an ex-gangster-turned-high-profile criminal justice advocate for a top leadership position, The Post has learned. The Democratic Congressional Camp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study finds 7 new 'worrying' corona variants in USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/study-finds-7-worrying-coronavirus-130100654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America seems to be incubating a number of its own unique coronavirus variants, new research suggests. A study posted Sunday that hasn't yet been peer reviewed identified seven new "lineages" of the virus, The New York Times reports. While the lineages evolved independently of one another, they seem to display the same genetic mutation. The change is seen in a gene that influences how the virus finds its way into a host's cell, suggesting it could make these variants more contagious — though this hasn't been confirmed. "I think there's a clear signature of an evolutionary benefit," said Jeremy Kamil, a virologist at Louisiana State University Health Sciences Center and a co-author of the new study. The new variants have been spotted across the country, but it's hard to tell just how prevalent they are or where they began because the U.S. performs genome sequencing on just a tiny fraction of coronavirus test results. And while viruses evolve all the time, the risk is that a new variant could be more contagious or more deadly. This is exactly what happened with the B.1.1.7 strain — nicknamed the "U.K. variant" — that's now spreading rapidly in the U.S. It is estimated to be up to 45 percent more transmissible, and up to 70 percent more deadly. Experts warn this new variant could be dominant in the U.S. by March. Still, the U.S. is making progress against the virus, at least for now. The country is administering 1.66 million vaccine doses a day, and the seven-day rolling average of new infections dropped below 100,000 Friday for the first time in three months, leading governors across the country to ease pandemic restrictions — like mask mandates and limits on gatherings. But health experts are nervous. Angela Rasmussen, a virologist at Georgetown University, told the Times that letting our guard down now would be "courting disaster." More stories from theweek.comRepublicans are suddenly very in favor of a third political party, according to Gallup7 scathingly funny cartoons about Republicans' impeachment cowardiceCentral U.S. is 'the most unusually cold region on the planet' right now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron, Le Pen in battle for support of right...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/macron-le-pen-battle-support-125729914.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron is seeking to gain ground on far-right leader Marine Le Pen ahead of a possible duel in 2022 elections by seizing votes on the right, with a tough-talking interior minister and a bill cracking down on radical Islamists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyalty remains fault line for Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/loyalty-trump-remains-fault-line-142600990.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven Republicans voted to convict Trump, several more condemned him, but the party, overall remains loyal to the former president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom polishes image as recall drive escalates...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gov-gavin-newsom-polishes-image-140000290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A string of outdoor events implies that Newsom and his advisors believe he needs to polish up his image as an effective and caring political figure, given the negative tone of the recent recall polls. | OPINION</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to launch leisure 'Green Pass'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210215173744-3w3rq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL (PIX):Israel to ease more COVID curbs, launch leisure 'Green Pass' on Feb. 21</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Discovers 'Unusual' Shard on Far Side Of Moon...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/china-discovers-unusual-shard-moon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Yutu 2 Rover discovered an unusual elongated rock on the surface of the moon — and they suspect it might be a shard from a meteor impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand Gets Reality Check as Auckland Locked Down...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zealand-gets-pandemic-reality-check-213652442.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- New Zealand’s summer of unrestricted movement and social interaction has been brought to an abrupt halt by three new community cases of Covid-19.After an emergency cabinet meeting on Sunday, Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern placed largest city Auckland into a snap, three-day lockdown and reimposed social distancing requirements for the rest of the country while authorities race to find the source of the new infections. Genomic sequencing shows them to be the more virulent U.K. strain of the virus, the Ministry of Health said on Monday.“This result reinforces the decision to take swift and robust action around the latest cases to detect and stamp out the possibility of any further transmission,” the ministry said.It’s a pandemic reality check for the South Pacific nation, which hasn’t had to impose any restrictions since August last year when a community outbreak pushed Auckland into a three-week lockdown. The fresh limitations on activity could dent the country’s strong economic rebound and will be a further setback for the establishment of a free-travel zone with Australia, which is also grappling with a new outbreak in Victoria.Australia and New Zealand have both had their international borders closed since the outset of the pandemic and require returning residents to isolate in quarantine hotels.Auckland’s move to Alert Level 3 means people are asked to stay at home and work remotely if possible. Schools, daycare centers, shops and public venues are largely closed, and gatherings are restricted to 10 people. The rest of New Zealand has been raised to Alert Level 2, requiring social distancing, but schools and businesses remain open. Gatherings are restricted to 100 people.The restrictions will impact on sporting events, including the next round of the America’s Cup sailing regatta scheduled for Wednesday, and prevent Aucklanders from traveling outside the region.The new cases are a family from South Auckland -- a mother, father and daughter. In addition to visiting local shops, two of the people traveled to the North Island city of New Plymouth last weekend, where they visited a number of tourist attractions.There were no additional community cases reported Monday. Health officials said they have identified 10 close contacts of the infected household, six of whom have returned negative tests with four results pending.It is not yet clear how the family contracted the virus but the woman works for LSG Sky Chefs, an airline catering company, where she handles laundry.Ardern said several scenarios are being investigated. One is that the virus came from a transit passenger, while another is that it came from international aircrew, who in some cases have their uniforms cleaned at the facility where the infected woman works, she told Radio New Zealand Monday. But the most likely scenario is human-to-human transmission, Ardern said.The new restrictions are initially in place until midnight on Wednesday but will be reviewed daily.(Adds latest health update in ninth paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In and Around Guadalajara, Homes Like Sanctuaries...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/15/in-and-around-guadalajara-homes-like-sanctuaries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEEN FROM ITS suburban street in Guadalajara, the capital of Jalisco state in western central Mexico, Casa Padilla looks less</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Rome Has Urgent Warning for Us...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/15/ancient-rome-has-an-urgent-warning-for-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was a child of privilege turned demagogue, a man who blurred the boundaries of politics and spectacle and seemed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech's Unlikely Next Battleground: N Dakota...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/14/big-techs-unlikely-next-battleground-north-dakota/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, a lobbyist approached Kyle Davison, a North Dakota state senator, with an unusual proposal: a law to stop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Suspends Correspondent For Violating Company Covid Policy...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/matt-gutman-abc-news-covid-19-1234694009/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: ABC News chief national correspondent Matt Gutman has been suspended for violating a company policy on Covid-19 safety. A spokesperson for the network declined to comment, as did Gutman.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Australian media company strikes GOOGLE news pay deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-australia-media-journalism-sundar-pichai-9aa2105cf512177b276bdf6ae9e045a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Seven West Media has become the largest Australian news media business to strike a deal with Google to pay for journalism in a partnership announced Monday before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The superspreaders behind top conspiracy theories...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/conspiracy-theories-iran-only-on-ap-media-misinformation-bfca6d5b236a29d61c4dd38702495ffe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus spread across the globe, so too did speculation about its origins. Perhaps the virus escaped from a lab. Maybe it was engineered as a bioweapon. Legitimate questions about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus may never go away but could change into mild annoyance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/common-cold-india-coronavirus-pandemic-latin-america-infectious-diseases-9ff4108bb925762655b6f6e23ffcf500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — What if COVID-19 never goes away? Experts say it's likely that some version of the disease will linger for years. But what it will look like in the future is less...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
