<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210213142042-9fl09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Strong quake hits off Japan coast, triggering blackouts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House prosecutors to call Republican lawmaker to testify at Trump trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9257009/Mitch-McConnell-wil-vote-ACQUIT-Donald-Trump-sign-ex-president-escape-conviction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell has told colleagues he will vote to acquit Donald Trump on the charge of incitement of insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECHNO MUSIC LEAST EFFECTIVE AT REDUCING ANXIETY?</title>
      <link>https://mixmag.net/read/techno-anxiety-music-genre-euphoria-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mixmag.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has found that techno is the least relaxing form of music – anyone who's spent the weekend at Movement or Berghain might disagree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will money laundering laws end art world's culture of secrecy?</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/money-laundering-laws-end-art-020347054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a Botticelli painting went under the hammer last month at Sotheby's in New York for $92 million, it was assumed the buyer was a Russian oligarch since the bidding was done by an adviser to wealthy Russians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SENATE TO HAVE WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2021/02/13/trump-impeachment-trial-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impeachment charge against Trump alleges that he “willfully made statements that encouraged — and foreseeably resulted in — imminent lawless action at the Capitol.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details about Trump conduct revealed in McCarthy call...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/13/trump-impeachment-trial-day-5-468985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If no witnesses are called, the trial on Saturday will move to closing arguments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign nationals getting vaccines in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-foreign-nationals-are-getting-coronavirus-vaccines-in-the-united-states/ar-BB1dEqPa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Difficult issues of immigration and health policy are playing out in border states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence 'could let humans to talk to animals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/artificial-intelligence-could-humans-talk-23454476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So much effort has gone into teaching systems such as Siri and Alexa to understand us that using AI to decode animal communication could be a logical next step.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decline of Proud Boys: What does future hold?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/decline-proud-boys-does-future-100010463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the Trump era, the group enjoyed presidential support and recruited thousands – but their role in the Capitol attack has led to new charges A member of the Proud Boys in Sacramento, California, on 7 November 2020. Photograph: David Odisho/EPA During the the Trump era, the far-right Proud Boys rode high, enjoying presidential support, recruiting thousands of men, and, as the self-nominated nemesis of leftist Antifa activists, participating in a string of violent street altercations around the country. But now since Trump’s election loss and the aftermath of the 6 January attack on the Capitol in Washington DC, a series of blows dealt by law enforcement, elected officials and their own leaders have shaken the extremist fraternity that the Southern Poverty Law Center describes as a hate group. The cumulative impact has experts wondering about the Proud Boys’ long-term future. Since their foundation in 2016 by the far-right Canadian media personality and entrepreneur Gavin McInnes, the all-male group – who wear uniform clothing, enforce bizarre initiation rituals, eschew masturbation, and reward violence with higher degrees of membership – have been an outsized presence on the landscape of pro-Trump extremism, and successful in promoting themselves as the most militant part of his coalition. But their role in the Capitol insurrection especially has brought far less welcome attention. Law enforcement agencies have connected at least 10 Capitol arrestees with the Proud Boys in criminal complaints and affadavits. Those charged include leaders like the Florida combat veteran and conspiracy theorist Joe Biggs and Washington state’s Ethan Nordean, whose prominence rose in the group after he was caught on film attacking an antifascist during a 2018 riot in downtown Portland, Oregon. Proud Boys members Enrique Tarrio, left, and Joe Biggs, in Washington DC on 12 December 2020. Photograph: Jim Urquhart/Reuters Biggs – a former employee of Alex Jones’s conspiracy-minded Infowars network – was central in organizing incursions into the city of Portland in 2019 and 2020, each of which drew Fred Perry-clad militants from around the country to confront antifascists and city authorities. He is now charged with impeding Congress, unauthorized entry to the Capitol, and disorderly conduct. However, the affidavit supporting the charges also alleges Biggs was involved in extensive radio communications with other Proud Boys on the day. The allegations of coordination between members of the group may hint at more charges to come. Alex Newhouse, a researcher at the Center on Terrorism, Extremism, and Counterterrorism at the Middlebury Institute, said in a telephone conversation that it was likely that “more conspiracy charges being levied on some of these people in the future”. Shannon Reid, an assistant professor in criminology at the University of North Carolina, said the strategy in these cases resembles the one prosecutors often use in pursuit of criminal enterprises, where the aim is to “pick up as many people as humanly possible and to hope that they just plead out”. The cases against Biggs and Nordean turn what had been the Proud Boys’ greatest weapon – social media – against them as authorities have detailed their alleged misdeeds using material that they and others posted online. For example, a grand jury indictment of a Texan, Nicholas Decarlo, and the founder of the group’s Hawaiian chapter, Nicholas Ochs, alleges that they together inscribed “Murder the media” on the front door of the Capitol before stealing a Capitol police officer’s handcuffs. In an affidavit, an FBI special agent says that they determined that Ochs had been in the building from his own Twitter account. Meanwhile, Dominic Pezzola and William Pepe allegedly conspired with each other in a sequence of events which included Pezzola assaulting a Capitol police officer, stealing his riot shield, and then using it to smash in one of the Capitol’s windows. The evidence cited in affidavits includes Pezzola’s account on the shuttered conservative-friendly social media service, Parler, and videos posted online by other rioters. The FBI says that another arrestee, Bryan Betancur, was wearing a Proud Boys cap at the rally. They also say that Betancur is a “self-professed white supremacist” who discussed carrying out school shootings and expressed support for Charlottesville killer, James Fields. He was placed inside the Capitol building by signals from his court-ordered ankle monitoring device, a parole condition related to an earlier offense. Newhouse said that voluminous social media evidence suggests that “this was carefully planned and extensively communicated in the moment”. The connection between Proud Boys and other extremist organizations – previously noted on several occasions by US law enforcement – has now led to the first instance of the group being outlawed. Last Wednesday, the Canadian parliament formally declared the Proud Boys a terrorist group, citing their “misogynistic, Islamophobic, antisemitic, anti-immigrant and/or white supremacist” ideology and their association with “white supremacist groups”. The designation opens the way for any crimes committed by Proud Boys to be prosecuted as terrorist acts. It also means that any fundraising, travel, recruitment and training for the group can be prosecuted, and members can be added to no-fly lists or denied entry to Canada. Meanwhile, parliamentarians in Australia are pushing their government to follow suit, after McInnes was denied entry to the country on character grounds in 2018. Gavin McInnes speaks on stage with Proud Boys in New York City on 20 January 2018. Photograph: Andrew Kelly/Reuters In the US, while criminal acts can be prosecuted as domestic terrorism, it has not been possible to designate domestic groups as terrorist, and, at least in theory, the first amendment prevents authorities from surveilling domestic groups on the basis of their political beliefs, even if those beliefs encompass an advocacy of violence. Increasingly over the life of the Trump administration, however, Democratic politicians advocated for just such an approach to rightwing extremists. Now, the first bill aimed at addressing rightwing extremism as domestic terrorism has been introduced to Congress by the Illinois Democrat Brad Schneider and has attracted bipartisan sponsorship. If passed it would set up dedicated domestic terrorism units within the Department of Justice, the Department of Homeland Security and the FBI. It would also require those departments to report to Congress twice a year on domestic terrorism incidents and hate crimes, and their progress in dealing with such cases. In a telephone conversation, Schneider said that while he had first proposed a version of the bill in 2017, before he had become aware of the group, the Proud Boys were “certainly a troubling group, in their rhetoric and their actions”. “We have seen what they’ve done in various places, whether it was in Washington last year or it with the insurrection in the capital last month,”Schneider added, calling the latter event an attack “not just members of Congress, but the foundation of our government, our constitution, and our republic”. Other events have compounded the effects of the additional scrutiny. During the Trump presidency, police in cities from California to Kalamazoo were regularly accused of having a soft touch when it came to the Proud Boys and their far-right allies, and these claims have been borne out in nationwide studies. But since the election, local agencies around the country have appeared more ready to respond with force when the group’s street protests become violent. Police have used batons, gas and other “non-lethal” weapons on Proud Boys in Salem, Oregon, and Washington DC during December and January. Some Proud Boys have remarked on the apparent sea change: in a podcast released on 4 January, Nordean, the Washington state arrestee, said that “the police are starting to become a problem,” even though “we’ve had their back for years”. On 2 February, those comments were quoted in the criminal complaint detailing Nordean’s alleged participation in the riot. Just before the riot, Enrique Tarrio, the chair of the Proud Boys, was arrested on charges related to the vandalism of a black church and illegal weapons. Then, last week, it was revealed that he had been a “prolific” police informant. Since the revelation that he had been a police informant, Proud Boyschapters in Nevada, Missouri and Alabama have publicly announced theirdeparture from the main organization on the messaging platform,Telegram. On the same platform, the also-departed Oklahoma Proud Boyshave exchanged barbs with Tarrio and other leaders. Proud Boys during a Trump rally in Washington DC on 12 December 2020. Photograph: The Washington Post/Getty Images Tarrio took over leadership of the group after McInnes ostentatiously resigned as a member following Guardian reporting that revealed that federal authorities considered them an extremist group. Notwithstanding his earlier public disavowals, in 2020 McInnes attended and spoke at the group’s annual WestFest event in Las Vegas in 2020, and has persisted in advocating for the group in the online outlets available to him, including his Telegram and Parler accounts. Though the Proud Boys may be reeling now, Newhouse warns that opposing a Democratic president gives them a similar opportunity to previous waves of rightwing militancy, like the militia movement in the Clinton years, and its revival as the so-called Patriot Movement during Obama’a time in office. “I don’t think they’re going anywhere,” he said. “The more extreme fringe actors are going to gain influence,” with some Proud Boys drifting into adjacent extremist groups in the Boogaloo movement or neo-Nazism. “De-radicalization is one of the hardest problems,”Newhouse said, “harder even than preventing acts of terrorism.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Nightmare -- Even for Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/florida-is-a-covid-nightmare-even-for-vaccinated-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a state defined by pandemic recklessness, getting a shot is no silver bullet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rogue Paparazzo Who Made Life Living Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/adnan-ghalib-the-rogue-paparazzo-who-made-britney-spears-life-a-living-hell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-paparazzo who dated Britney Spears at the height of the tabloid frenzy (and was allegedly shopping a sex tape) won’t take responsibility for his own role in the chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fall of John Weaver, LINCOLN PROJECT co-founder whose career shrouded in mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/The-fall-of-John-Weaver-a-Lincoln-Project-15948531.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The puzzle that is John Weaver comes in fragmented pieces: He's described as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen 'could win French presidential election'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210213122938-mcy50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-LEMAIRE/LEPEN: Far-right leader Le Pen could win French 2022 presidential election-Le Maire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender identity bill divides Spain feminists, left-wing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-spain-gender-identity-1d53f28df5988032e538c37f80928633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Victòria Martínez continues to sign official documents with the name that she, her partner and their two daughters ditched four years ago. Barring any surprises, she expects the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Hit by 7.1-Mag Quake Off Fukushima... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-shaking-felt-huge-71-23494867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Japan Meteorological Agency said an earthquake hit off the coast of Fukushima but a tsunami warning has not been issued despite the quake's 7.1 preliminary magnitude</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEARJET Fall From Luxe to Loser Reflects Rising Bar for Swank...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/learjet-s-fall-from-luxe-to-loser-reflects-rising-bar-for-swank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learjet’s Fall From Luxe to Loser Reflects Rising Bar for Swank</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us6000dher/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-day-5-2021-02-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate is convening for a rare Saturday session.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate poised to vote on holding Trump accountable for siege...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/b245b52fd7d4a079ae199c954baba452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senators are poised to vote on whether Donald Trump will be held accountable for inciting the horrific attack at the Capitol after a speedy impeachment trial that laid bare the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Close watch on tight-lipped McConnell's stand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-impeachments-trump-impeachment-mitch-mcconnell-0a14d2e41e376331580b98a992f7d856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Seldom has Mitch McConnell signaled so little about such a consequential vote. Many expect the Senate's top Republican will back acquitting former President Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Who the f*** do you think you are talking to?'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9255877/Trump-refused-call-mob-new-details-McCarthy-call-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New details from a call between then President Trump and House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy show a president who was unwilling to call off the MAGA mob during the January 6 insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero tried to save trapped drivers as cars crashed in deadly I-35 pileup in Fort Worth...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article249193010.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan Chaney said he helped pull a woman from her wrecked car, but watched as another person died in front of him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist sues after he was allegedly injured while under hypnosis at Las Vegas show...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/local-las-vegas/las-vegas-hypnotist-sued-after-tourist-claims-he-was-injured-during-show-2278347/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arizona tourist has filed a lawsuit that claims he was injured while under hypnosis at the Marc Savard Comedy Hypnosis Show in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer Issues Veiled Threat :  No One 'Anxious to Have Primary Challenge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-lawyer-bruce-castor-says-the-quiet-part-out-loud-in-his-argument-to-senators-no-one-here-is-anxious-to-have-a-primary-challenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's impeachment lawyer Bruce Castor pointed out that no Senators are "anxious to have a primary challenge" while defending the former president's case -- saying the quiet part out loud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imploding Trump Plaza 'poetic justice.' Atlantic City torn about legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/trump-plaza-implosion-atlantic-city-casino-20210212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The struggling resort town offers up an exclamation point to the end of Trump presidency. For those who worked there, the dramatic end is bittersweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeps low profile and avoids reporters at Oval Office meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9255771/Cuomo-looks-sheepish-Oval-Republicans-Democrats-join-calls-resign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Cuomo on Friday was in the Oval Office for a meeting with other governors about a COVID relief package, but no questions were taken, amid mounting calls for him to be prosecuted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refused for months to release data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cuomo-admin-nursing-home-data-requests-1911c49d8f6cd30970f6c2eaf06c6209</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo's top aide told Democratic lawmakers that the administration took months to release data revealing how many people living at nursing homes died of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman repeatedly stabbed her sister with EpiPen...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/epipen-attack-arrest-275698</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 12--A Florida Woman who repeatedly stabbed her sister with an EpiPen told cops that she was “allergic to drunks” and was simply trying to sober up the victim, according to a police report. I</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts for last-minute witnesses over Trump-McCarthy call...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-impeachment-trial-witnesses-senate-democrat-chris-van-hollen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats may be opening up to the idea of extending former President Donald Trump's historic second impeachment trial and calling witnesses as new details emerge of events surrounding the siege of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President refused to call off the rioters?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/12/politics/trump-mccarthy-shouting-match-details/index.html?bt_ee=9Oa9pLBkTfrCvTfRoM5%2FdK0piCC3RJjpCsSVXMwozM4%3D&amp;bt_ts=1613186299898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an expletive-laced phone call with House Republican leader Kevin McCarthy while the Capitol was under attack, then-President Donald Trump said the rioters cared more about the election results than McCarthy did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspended for week...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tj-ducklo-suspended-threaten-reporter-9bf6b2cf1c8a092194652ce014923c8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — White House deputy press secretary T.J. Ducklo has been suspended for a week without pay after he reportedly issued a sexist and profane threat to a journalist seeking to cover...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police emphasize clampdown on crowds as Mardi Gras nears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/louisiana-coronavirus-pandemic-new-orleans-mardi-gras-fda74cf29143fe31c8b999d6358d69ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowds are usually welcome and even encouraged in tourist-dependent New Orleans in the days leading up to Mardi Gras but as the final weekend of the 2021 season began Friday, police warned that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican senators face big decision...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-alaska-susan-collins-lisa-murkowski-1fefa4b5d70394b9667b4dcec0038db9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Most every Senate juror has said they will listen to the evidence in Donald Trump’s historic second impeachment trial, but most minds were likely made up before the trial began....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines push White House to reject testing for US flights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-pete-buttigieg-bd9661efc8614bca3e64b91f96f05b6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Leaders of several major U.S. airlines met online Friday with White House officials to press their case against requiring coronavirus tests for passengers on domestic flights,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France wades into South China Sea with nuke attack sub...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210212-france-wades-into-the-south-china-sea-with-a-nuclear-attack-submarine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French nuclear attack submarine SNA Emeraude recently conducted a patrol in the South China Sea, Defence Minister Florence Parly announced this week, sparking questions over the timing and tensio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: CDC's New 'Reopening' Guidance Will Keep Schools Closed in Fall...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/12/cdcs-new-reopening-guidance-will-keep-schools-closed-in-the-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is what you get when you mix "science" with "stakeholders."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who runs CNN next? It's complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/who-runs-cnn-next-it-s-complicated-n1257732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as CNN’s parent company AT&amp;T tries to position itself for a new era, the list of people who are seen as capable of running a major television news organization is short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orgasms work as well as drugs for curing migraines...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14035479/sex-orgasm-cure-headache-say-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ORGASM works just as well as drugs for curing a migraine, says a brain expert. The bed-gripping new research means having a headache is no longer an excuse for avoiding sex. In fact, it is even …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel vows lockdown will not last day longer than needed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211173905-8y3if</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY-MERKEL (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-Merkel promises lockdown will not last a day longer than necessary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor quits after posing as female immigrant on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-chemistry-immigration-9b071aa2db8f8d32e012fb6395bd2a7a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white, male University of New Hampshire chemistry professor has resigned after being accused of posing as a female immigrant of color on Twitter to make racist and sexist comments. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sasse bets political future on opposing Don...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-censures-omaha-ben-sasse-a9af5767d6c7e1b6cc8912a60aeda8af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — When Ben Sasse heard that GOP activists in Nebraska were primed to censure him for insufficiently supporting Donald Trump, the Republican senator didn't try to talk them out it....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confuse STEELERS QB With GA Official...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/02/12/bruce-castor-confuses-steelers-qb-ben-roethlisberger-with-georgia-secretary-of-state-brad-raffensperger-during-trump-impeachment-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media is once again poking fun at Bruce Castor's defense of former President Donald Trump during the impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveils epic troll...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9254633/Donald-Trumps-lawyers-start-defense-presidents-speech-wasnt-incitement-riot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden said he's watching to see if his Republican 'friends' in the Senate 'stand up' to Donald Trump as he and Jill visit her Valentine's Day message on White House lawn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team rests...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-impeachment-trial-02-12-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump's defense team will begin their arguments today against conviction. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say there was no insurrection...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/12/trump-impeachment-trial-live-updates-video-day-4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's legal team is set to defend the former president on Day 4 of the impeachment trial in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goes beyond call; Grand jury subpoenas coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9254147/Georgia-prosecutor-says-probe-goes-Donald-Trumps-votes-call-Raffensperger.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia prosecutor Fani Willis said her investigation goes beyond President Donald Trump's infamous phone call to Georgia Secretary of State Brad Raffensperger asking him to 'find' votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Convict' banner flies over Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/538642-convict-trump-banner-flies-over-mar-a-lago-during-senate-impeachment-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calls for former President Trump to be convicted in his second impeachment trial came in the form of a sky banner flying over his Mar-a-Lago residence on Friday as his attorneys mount their defense in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with threats to politicians, media personalities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-media-social-media-manhattan-courts-bcd082b27978c56e250832ee4c385d48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A New York man faces charges alleging that he threatened past and present political figures and media personalities on social media, authorities announced Friday. Rickey...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-year-old spends $10,000 on WSJ ads to complain about slow AT&amp;T internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvu.com/news/90-year-old-man-spends-10000-on-2-ads-in-wsj-to-tell-att-ceo-about-his-slow-internet-service</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 90-year-old California man took out two ads in the Wall Street Journal, which set him back over $10,000, to let AT&amp;T’s CEO know about his abysmal internet service speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Strong evidence in-person schooling can be done safely...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-teaching-michael-pence-coronavirus-pandemic-4265da944bb3b6c863db6ca6a03caa58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s top public health agency on Friday provided a roadmap for reopening schools in the middle of a pandemic, emphasizing mask wearing and social distancing and saying vaccination of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Investigating...</title>
      <link>https://yashar.substack.com/p/scoop-fbi-investigating-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;yashar.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is investigating allegations against longtime GOP political consultant and Lincoln Project co-founder John Weaver, according to two sources who said they were contacted by FBI agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovered being reinfected with new strains...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/12/recovered-covid-patients-have-been-reinfected-with-new-virus-strains-who-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary reports from South Africa show people who have recovered from Covid-19 have been reinfected with a new, more contagious variant of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence's 'nuclear football' almost nabbed...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/966485/mike-pences-nuclear-football-also-apparently-risk-during-capitol-siege</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New security camera footage unveiled Wednesday at former President Donald Trump's impeachment trial showed just how close the mob ransacking the Capitol on Jan. 6 came to nabbing former Vice President Mike Pence and his family. When U.S. Strategic Command saw the footage, CNN reported late Thursday, they realized how close the mob came to Pence's 'nuclear football,' the backup nuclear launch system a military aide carries near the vice president at all times in case the president is incapacitated. The military officer, apparently seen fleeing down back stairs with Pence and his family, never lost control of the backup 'football,' and Trump was safe in the White House during the entire period Pence was being hunted down, a defense official told CNN. That means the Pentagon would not have needed to deactivate Pence's nuclear launch system, even if they had been aware it was in danger. And if the insurrectionists had managed to grab the 'football,' they would not have been able to bypass the security systems, the official added. That's not the point, Kingston Reif of the Arms Control Association told CNN. 'The risk associated with the insurrectionists getting their hands on Pence's football wasn't that they could have initiated an unauthorized launch. But had they stolen the football and acquired its contents, which include pre-planned nuclear strike options, they could have shared the contents with the world,' creating 'a security breach of almost incomprehensible proportions.' The people who broke into the Capitol were clearly not opposed to taking home trophies. Florida Man, Helpfully, Includes Closeup Of Barcode On Damaged U.S. Senate Property In His Facebook Post About Storming The U.S. Capitol pic.twitter.com/d5cSXVkkEA — Ryan J. Reilly (@ryanjreilly) February 11, 2021 Thankfully, we never have to know what they would have done had they found Pence, or his nuclear strike machine. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$76 million deal with French publishers leaves many outlets infuriated...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-france-copyright-exclusive/exclusive-googles-76-million-deal-with-french-publishers-leaves-many-outlets-infuriated-idUSKBN2AC27N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet Inc's Google has agreed to pay $76 million over three years to a group of French news publishers to end a more than year-long copyright spat, documents seen by Reuters show, a deal one news publishers' lobby deemed unfair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COKE tries first paper bottle...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56023723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The test is first step towards all-paper bottle that can withstand pressure from fizzy drinks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/journalists-decry-tj-ducklo-after-bombshell-report-in-which-the-biden-wh-adopts-trump-tactics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists are condemning the reported actions of White House official TJ Ducklo after a stunning Vanity Fair report reveals his abusive behavior towards Politico's Tara Palmeri.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspended for week... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/biden-aide-tj-ducklo-suspended-by-white-house-over-report-he-threatened-politicos-tara-palmeri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;T.J. Ducklo, deputy press secretary to President Joe Biden, was suspended for one week without pay, the White House told Mediaite Friday. The suspension comes after Vanity Fair reported he threatened a Politico writer working on a story about his relationship with Axios correspondent Alexi McCammond. The full statement read: T.J. Ducklo has apologized to […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play vid montage of Dems 'inciting violence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2322181/trump-impeachment-trial-team-dems-violence-day-four/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s impeachment team slammed the “witch hunt” trial and played videos of Democrats objecting to the 2016 presidential win at the start of their case presentation. Micha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States eye flurry of new taxes on Internet giants...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/States-eye-flurry-of-new-taxes-on-Amazon-15945322.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State lawmakers around the country are exploring a range of new taxes targeting Amazon,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE APOLOGIZES TO BRITNEY SPEARS, JANET JACKSON...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/music/news/justin-timberlake-apologizes-britney-spears-janet-jackson-i-failed-1234907138/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of accusations of sexism and misogyny against Justin Timberlake regarding his treatment of former girlfriend Britney Spears, and the “wardrobe malfunction” with Janet Jackso…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oath Keeper wanted to load boat with weapons for Potomac?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/538621-oath-keeper-wanted-to-load-boat-with-weapons-for-potomac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of the right-wing paramilitary group the Oath Keepers in the days leading up to the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON sues NY AG to preempt covid lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210212152756-kmr55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON.COM-COMPLAINT/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Amazon sues New York attorney general to preempt COVID-19 lawsuit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEX PRESIDENT HAILS BORDER WALL FREEZE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210212132945-xh1h0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-BORDER/:Mexican president hails Biden's border wall freeze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Touts Vaccine Rollout Despite Troops' Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-02-11/pentagon-acknowledges-concerns-of-widespread-vaccine-refusal-among-troops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Department is touting its vaccine administration rate as concerns mount that troops are declining to take the voluntary inoculation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raging bears turn on rescuers moments after being released...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2321518/six-bears-attack-crowds-released-cages-wild/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REPORTERS and police sprint for safety as a group of caged bears go on the attack moments after being released into the wild. The chaotic scene was captured in these dramatic pictures of a wildlife…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Gov't Employees Outfitted With Contact-Tracing Wearables...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/02/treasury-bureau-outfit-onsite-employees-contact-tracing-wearables/172023/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal is to proactively prevent COVID-19 outbreaks within its facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT:  LA church to host indoor conference of 3,000 attendees, despite public health order...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-02-12/l-a-church-to-host-indoor-conference-of-3-000-attendees-despite-public-health-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grace Community Church plans to host its annual Shepherds' Conference in Los Angeles in March despite public health officials saying conferences are prohibited under the county's COVID-19 health order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two officers who helped fight MAGA mob died of suicide. Many more are hurting...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/nation-world/capitol-attack-police-suicides-jeffrey-smith-howard-liebengood-20210212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The families of Officers Jeffrey Smith and Howard Liebengood want their deaths recognized as "in the line of duty."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAKER:  If Convicting Is Out of Reach, Managers Seek Verdict From Public and History...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/nation-world/ct-aud-nw-nyt-trump-impeachment-verdict-analysis-20210212-6mgbi75tmbddlkwtfkwayp62mq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Trump is not convicted, the managers want to ensure that he remains so politically radioactive that he cannot be the same force he once was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defenders take impeachment stage to make his case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trump-impeachment-trial-update-2-12-2021-f831653160706c49987c9d33228ccbbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — After a prosecution case rooted in emotive, violent images from the Capitol siege, Donald Trump's impeachment trial shifts on Friday to defense lawyers prepared to make a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald returns to spotlight in trial -- but not on his terms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-impeachment-trial-spotlight-3b7a3a90c48861e701b07a69dbd97757</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — His rallying cry to supporters has been dissected. His videos, press conferences and calls to Fox News have played on loop. His Twitter account is once again dominating news...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TO LET 25,000 IN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-25000-asylum-seekers-782c8495f29d9d73f2ffc80d5b2a2aef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — The Biden administration on Friday announced plans for tens of thousands of asylum-seekers waiting in Mexico for their next immigration court hearings to be allowed into the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
