<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tom Ford entices fashion crowd into an old subway station...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/tom-ford-entices-fashion-crowd-031912148.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Ford enticed the fashion crowd into an abandoned subway station downtown by serving up dumplings before a precarious three-story walk to the rails, and, yes, heels were involved. Miley Cyrus, sitting front row Monday in a floppy black hat, could easily pull off any of his bra tops in metallic green</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STANDING O  FOR 'JOKER' IN TORONTO...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/09/09/toronto-cheers-for-joaquin-phoenix-astonishing-performance-as-the-joker-in-violent-comic-book-opera</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin Phoenix received cheers and a standing ovation tonight in Toronto for his starring performance as the “Joker.” Todd Phillips’ origin story of Batman’s villain is sup…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 deficit surpasses $1 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/460603-deficit-surpasses-1-trillion-cbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal deficit surpassed $1 trillion in the first 11 months of fiscal 2019, the Congressional Budget Office (CBO) said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is dengue so widespread this year? </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dengue-why-widespread-031859064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed "breakbone fever", dengue is one of the world's leading mosquito-borne illnesses and infects tens of millions across the globe annually. Explosive outbreaks have ravaged Southeast Asia this year, infecting hundreds of thousands, killing hundreds, and crippling health care systems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 countries cited for extreme media censorship...</title>
      <link>https://cpj.org/reports/2019/09/10-most-censored-eritrea-north-korea-turkmenistan-journalist.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cpj.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apps may tell FACEBOOK last time users had sex..</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/apps-may-tell-facebook-about-last-time-users-had-sex-study-2098310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your best friend may not know when you last had sex, but it's possible that Facebook does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No One Shows for Impeachment Event in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/09/09/lleftists-d-c-impeach-donald-trump-protests-a-bust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one showed up for protests promoted online for Washington, DC, and other cities to push for the impeachment of President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant NKorea launches two more projectiles after 'advanced missile' warning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-korea-says-willing-resume-152041803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea launched two projectiles toward the sea on Tuesday, South Korea's military said, hours after the North offered to resume nuclear diplomacy with the United States but warned its dealings with Washington may end without new U.S. proposals. The launches and demand for new proposals were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's First Gay Credit Union Gets Green Light...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/america-first-gay-credit-union-170720269.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Do lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people need a bank of their own? Superbia Credit Union is about to find out.Michigan on Monday approved a charter for the new financial institution designed for LGBT customers, clearing the way for online service to begin early in 2020.Superbia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLO Poised to Land First Oscar Nomination for Stripper Performance?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/jennifer-lopez-is-poised-land-her-first-oscar-nom-hustlers-1238125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For her work in Lorene Scafaria's dramedy about New York strippers who team up to con male patrons in order to survive the Great Recession, J-Lo has received some of the best notices of her acting career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Accuses Rivals of Plotting to 'Steal' Israeli Election... </title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/09/netanyahu-accuses-rivals-of-plotting-to-steal-israeli-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - JERUSALEM — Fighting for his political life, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu of Israel on Monday accused opponents of trying to “steal” next week’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Liberals haunted by social media tactics they use against the right...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/460595-liberals-haunted-by-social-media-tactics-they-use-against-the-right</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The people who have made an industry out of destroying ordinary people’s lives over old social media posts and out-of-context comments are very upset that it’s happening to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary challenges show potential cracks in Trump's GOP...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/460585-primary-challenges-show-potential-cracks-in-trumps-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s campaign is moving to block three Republicans challenging him in next year’s primary election, cognizant of the potential threat those challengers represent to Trump’s hold on his vaunted Republican base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD CONTINUES:  Highest August border arrests in more than decade...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190909221852-3iuee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/ (UPDATE 6, PIX):UPDATE 6-U.S. credits Mexico, Central America for sharp drop in border arrests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds probe 8-year-old boy's YOUTUBE channel...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9896654/ryan-toysreview-youtube-channel-probe-ryan-kaji/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POPULAR YouTube channel hosted by an eight-year-old boy is being probed over claims it is “deceiving” kids into buying toys. Schoolboy Ryan Kaji and his parents make £17.3 million ($22 million) a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant NKorea launches two more projectiles after 'advanced missile' warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-north-korea-launches-two-19916742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea fired two projectiles on Tuesday morning from South Pyongan province toward the east, a report citing South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff states</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE FACES 50 PROBES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/09/texas-attorney-general-leads-google-antitrust-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news follows the announcement of a joint state Facebook probe led by the attorney general of New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moody's downgrades FORD to 'junk' status on weak outlook...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/moodys-downgrades-ford-junk-status-weak-outlook-210253793.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moody's downgraded Ford's credit rating to speculative or "junk" status on Monday, citing the company's weak financial outlook as it embarks on an ambitious restructuring. Characterizing the auto giant's current overhaul as "unprecedentedly large and challenging,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST DRAMA:  Weinstein Attacks Paltrow...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/09/gwyneth-paltrow-harvey-weinstein-sexual-harassment-she-said-book-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-new-york-times-1202729541/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the day that Harvey Weinstein’s postponed trial for rape was supposed to have started in New York City, the much accused producer’s team today tried to damn Gwyneth Paltrow in the court of publi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even for Trump, it's been busy stretch of media attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec9e76c9ac9c4c1e985a364f402882e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Even for a president who has made attacks on the media routine, the past few days have seemed turbo-charged. Within five days, President Donald Trump has tweeted a video of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 TEST IN NORTH CAROLINA!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/743fe7db77c543c498e33df29f6c53ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVELOCK, N.C. (AP) — President Donald Trump's rally in North Carolina on Monday will serve as a measure of his clout in trying to elect a Republican to the House in a closely watched special...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK's Johnson to close Parliament as his Brexit plans stall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/600609137bf34bcba826085b085bfcbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British lawmakers demanded Monday that Prime Minister Boris Johnson's government release officials' private correspondence about plans for Brexit, as the government prepared to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany considers 'shadow budget' to circumvent national debt rules...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190909134128-csy5m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-BUDGET/ (UPDATE 1, EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Germany considers 'shadow budget' to circumvent national debt rules - sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Are America's 3 Biggest Metros Shrinking?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/09/americas-three-biggest-metros-shrinking/597544/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a post-recession boomlet, the New York, Los Angeles, and Chicago areas are all seeing their population decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher federal gas taxes? Businesses pushing idea...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article234762262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NKorean-Israeli Shadow War...</title>
      <link>https://www.tabletmag.com/jewish-news-and-politics/290884/north-korean-israeli-shadow-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tabletmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Getting Menstrual Cycle Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/these-menstrual-tracking-apps-reportedly-shared-sensitive-data-with-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the apps shared things like contraception use and other personal info, according to a UK advocacy group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Police Believe Suspicious Van In Baltimore Used To Steal Gas...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/09/09/suspicious-vehicle-baltimore-maryland-police-fire-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After evacuating part of downtown Baltimore and an hours-long investigation, police now believe the suspicious van leaking gas in a parking garage near the Inner Harbor was being used to steal diesel fuel, and was not as hazardous as initially believed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA's Secret Quest For Mind Control...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/09/09/758989641/the-cias-secret-quest-for-mind-control-torture-lsd-and-a-poisoner-in-chief</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalist Stephen Kinzer reveals how CIA chemist Sidney Gottlieb worked in the 1950s and early '60s to develop mind control drugs and deadly toxins that could be used against enemies of the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health systems sue patients, seize paychecks, put liens on homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/uva-has-ruined-us-health-system-sues-thousands-of-patients-seizing-paychecks-and-putting-liens-on-homes/ar-AAH27ni</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Commerce Secretary Threatened Firings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/commerce-chief-threatened-firings-at-noaa-after-trumps-hurricane-tweets-sources-say/ar-AAH2AlS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Todd Palin files for divorce from Sarah Palin...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/anchorage/2019/09/09/todd-palin-files-for-divorce-from-former-alaska-governor-sarah-palin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The filing cites “incompatibility of temperament” and asks for joint custody of the couple’s only child under 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parliament Speaker Bercow Quits...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9893756/remainer-speaker-john-bercow-quits-after-tories-plot-to-oust-him-over-brexit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANGRY Tory Brexiteers have slammed ‘biased’ John Bercow as “nauseating” after the Speaker broke down in tears as he announced he was quitting. Remainer Bercow – known for his eccentric …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 dead in Netherlands shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2019/09/09/several-people-killed-in-shooting-in-dutch-city-of-dordrecht-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have not released any other information about the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student faces 2 years behind bars for trying to hack Trump's taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberscoop.com/trump-tax-returns-hack-student-guilty-plea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cyberscoop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Philadelphia man has pleaded guilty in connection with a scheme to trick a U.S. government website into serving up the president’s tax returns. Andrew Harris, a student who attended Haverford College, admitted in court last week that he used a school computer and the Free Application for Student Aid website to try to access Donald Trump’s financial records. By opening a FAFSA account in the name of a Trump family member and using Trump’s Social Security number, Harris and another student apparently thought the FAFSA page would populate with Trump’s tax data. The attempt failed when the pair found a username and password for Trump already existed. Harris, 24, pleaded guilty on Sept. 5 to two misdemeanor counts of computer fraud. He faces two years in federal prison and a $200,000 fine. Another man, 22-year-old Justin Hiemstra of Minnesota, pleaded guilty last month. FAFSA is run by the Department of Education, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative Network OANN Files $10M Defamation Suit Against Maddow, MSNBC...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/lawsuit/conservative-network-files-10-million-defamation-lawsuit-against-rachel-maddow-and-msnbc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIANTS Fan Arrested For Mass Shooting Threat at GILLETTE...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/09/gillette-stadium-threat-arrest-foxboro-new-england-patriots-tobias-gray-antonio-brown-new-york-giants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York Giants fan was so angry about the New England Patriots signing Antonio Brown he issued a threat to Gillette Stadium on Facebook, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says 'willing' to resume US nuke talks in Sept...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190909161016-di24s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-USA/ (UPDATE 2, TV):UPDATE 2-North Korea says it is willing to resume nuclear talks with U.S. in late September</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwear blunder stalls trial of Chinese Mar-a-Lago trespasser...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/underwear-blunder-stalls-trial-chinese-woman-accused-trespassing-mar-lago-n1051506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yujing Zhang is acting as her own attorney during the federal trial on accusations she lied to a Secret Service agent and trespassed at President Donald Trump's Palm Beach club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Real US debt levels could be shocking 2,000% of GDP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/09/real-us-debt-levels-could-be-a-shocking-2000percent-of-gdp-report-suggests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putting all that together paints a daunting picture but one that requires nuance to understand. Paramount is realizing that not all of the debt obligations are set in stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLYBURN: Not Too Sure Bill of Rights Would Pass Today...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/09/08/dem-rep-clyburn-not-too-sure-the-bill-of-rights-would-pass-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday on MSNBC, House Majority Whip James Clyburn (D-SC) wondered if the Bill of Rights would pass in today's "climate." |</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test for president... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/743fe7db77c543c498e33df29f6c53ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's rally in North Carolina will serve as a measure of his clout in trying to elect a Republican to the House in a closely watched special election that's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stampede at Lil Wayne Concert Causes Injuries, Thefts...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/lil-wayne-crowd-stampede-injuries-new-orleans-1203328503/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several fans were injured during a crowd stampede at Lil Wayne’s outdoor Lil WeezyAna Fest in New Orleans on Saturday night. According to the city’s Times Picayune, “large segments of an audi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech backlash kicks into gear with antitrust moves...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/big-tech-backlash-kicks-gear-antitrust-moves-155146813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top legal officials from dozens of US states were set to unveil a probe of Google over allegations of "anticompetitive behavior," days after a separate coalition announced a similar investigation of social networking giant Facebook. A coalition led by Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton scheduled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance state fears as cops hand out free AMAZON RING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9886618/police-amazon-free-camera-doorbells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON’S video doorbell company is working with police forces to hand out thousands of its devices, it has been reported. The move to distribute the £89 Ring devices has, however, raised Big Brothe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  TV's War on Trump Leaves Little Time for Dem Candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/rich-noyes/2019/09/09/campaign-2020-tvs-war-against-trump-leaves-little-time-dems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From June 1 through August 31, the networks devoted 838 minutes of airtime — nearly 14 hours — to coverage of President Trump personally, and the spin of his coverage during these three months was 90% negative. Meanwhile, the 21 Democratic candidates shared 187 minutes of evening news airtime this summer, less than one-fourth of that of Trump alone, with spin that was friendlier than their coverage of the President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London woman stabbed to death in street just minutes before man shot dead yards away...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/chalk-farm-murder-woman-stabbed-19911691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim, who was in her 20s and described as a "wonderful young lady", was knifed in the chest outside a tower block in Chalk Farm, north London, at around 11pm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ageless Brady Begins Hunt For 7th Super Bowl...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/08/brady-patriots-blow-out-steelers-week-1-victory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defending champs kicked off their season with a Super celebration, and they followed it up with a victory over the Steelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NWS chief backs forecasters who contradicted Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e7a4480d33ce4040b59bd48d4b832c05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTSVILLE, Ala. (AP) — The head of the National Weather Service issued a strong public defense Monday of forecasters who contradicted President Donald Trump's claim that Hurricane Dorian posed a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falwell Aides Break Silence: LIBERTY officials describe culture of fear, self-dealing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/09/09/jerry-falwell-liberty-university-loans-227914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen current and former Liberty University officials describe a culture of fear and self-dealing at the largest Christian college in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leprosy in LA?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7442947/Homeless-people-risk-LEPROSY.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Marc Siegel, of New York University's Langone Health, fears it is just a 'matter of time' before the bacterial disease strikes. He pointed to Los Angeles County as being particularly at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA extracted top spy from inside Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/09/politics/russia-us-spy-extracted/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a previously undisclosed secret mission in 2017, the United States successfully extracted from Russia one of its highest-level covert sources inside the Russian government, multiple Trump administration officials with direct knowledge told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM YANG CROWD-SURFS</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/863618/andrew-yang-crowdsurfed-2020-town-hall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang is doing what Beto O'Rourke could only dream of. The 2020 Democrat and entrepreneur was spotted performing what might be a presidential campaign first on Saturday: crowd surfing across a wave of supporters at the AAPI Democratic Presidential Forum in California. And if the sight of Yang's ride wasn't triumphant enough, the fact that two other presidential candidates were at the forum makes it even sweeter. Havenâ€™t crowdsurfed in a while #YangGang @GPSofficial pic.twitter.com/3ynxj8m21v â€” Andrew Yang (@AndrewYang) September 8, 2019 Yang joined Rep. Tulsi Gabbard (D-Hawaii) and billionaire Tom Steyer at the event, which is put on by an Asian American and Pacific Islander-focused super PAC. Yang is currently beating those two contenders in polls and number of legs off the ground, and is polling around the same 3 percent as fellow ex-punk O'Rourke. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor would like everyone to stop being so cynical...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/863541/tom-hanks-like-everyone-stop-being-cynical</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the reasons why Tom Hanks decided to play Fred Rogers in the new movie A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood is because he was drawn to the beloved television host's innate kindness. "Cynicism has become the default position for so much of daily structure and daily intercourse," Hanks told reporters at the Toronto Film Festival on Sunday. "Why? Because it's easy, and there's good money to be made. Cynicism is a great product to sell, and it's the perfect beginning of any examination of anything. And part of that is conspiracy theories and what have you." When Rogers started Mister Rogers' Neighborhood in the late 1960s, children were receiving negative messages on other programs, Hanks said. "Why would you put something that is cynical in front of a 2- or 3-year-old kid?" he asked. "That you are not cool because you don't have this toy? That it's funny to see someone being bopped on the head?" That's a poor way to treat the audience, and Rogers did the exact opposite. "We are allowed, I think, to feel good," Hanks said. "There's a place for cynicism, but why begin with it right off the bat?" Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief scientist investigating NOAA backing of Trump over experts on Dorian...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/460493-chief-scientist-will-investigate-noaas-backing-of-trump-over-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acting chief scientist of the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Association (NOAA) is investigating whether the agency's response to President Trump’s claims about Hurricane Dorian constituted a violation of policies and ethics,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of evacuees booted off Florida-bound ferry...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/09/hundreds-of-evacuees-from-bahamas-booted-off-florida-bound-ferry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Bahamians attempting to flee the Hurricane Dorian-ravaged island were booted off a ferry bound for the US if they did not have a visa to enter, a report said. Brian Entin, an investigat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ERA: Last Peep Show in Vegas Closes Down...</title>
      <link>https://lasvegassun.com/news/2019/sep/09/showgirl-video-closure-era-peep-shows-las-vegas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lasvegassun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showgirl Video, which included an adult bookstore, operated on Las Vegas Boulevard for nearly four decades and eventually became the area’s lone peep show ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Ken Griffin Adds $99 Million Florida Beach House to Property Empire...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ken-griffin-adds-99-million-133427306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Ken Griffin’s splurge on luxury real estate properties shows no signs of abating.The hedge fund titan spent $99.1 million for a beachfront house adjacent to his existing Palm Beach estate, according to the Palm Beach Post, citing sources with knowledge of the transaction and a deed filing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Child-Rape Holocaust Movie Causing Walkouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-painted-bird-the-child-rape-holocaust-movie-thats-causing-festival-walkouts </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Václav Marhoul’s “The Painted Bird” is causing disgusted viewers to walk out at festivals—including TIFF. Is it really that shocking?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady, PATRIOTS will be unstoppable -- if Antonio Brown doesn't stop them...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27567237/brady-patriots-unstoppable-antonio-brown-stop-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the explosive WR adopts the Patriot Way, New England will have enough firepower to evoke memories of its 2007 juggernaut that started 18-0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant calf born with human face!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mutant-calf-born-human-face-19912138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The malformed animal's face resembled a grumpy human</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts: 2 new cases of deadly mosquito virus...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/cases-eee-include-year-girl-woman/story?id=65451615 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two new cases of EEE have been detected in Massachusetts. The mosquito-transmitted illness is rare but can be deadly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Halperin 'Threatened' MSNBC Chief for Nixing Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mark-halperin-threatened-msnbc-chief-phil-griffin-for-nixing-his-comeback </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources said the disgraced political reporter became hostile in a phone chat with his ex-boss after reports emerged that MSNBC brass axed plans for Halperin to return to punditry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi set to go nuclear...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-energy-wec-saudi-nuclearpower/saudi-arabia-wants-to-enrich-uranium-for-nuclear-power-minister-idUSKCN1VU168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia wants to enrich uranium in the future to fuel its planned nuclear p...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah downs Israeli drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Hezbollah-downs-Israeli-drone-in-ongoing-tension-14424127.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - Hezbollah announced Monday it had downed an Israeli drone in southern Lebanon, part of a string of clashes between Israel and Iranian-banked groups throughout the region.  The Israeli army also said early Monday that Iran's elite Quds Force oversaw the firing of several rockets from Syria toward Israel, none of which managed to reach their target.  The rocket attacks follow reports from Syrian opposition activists that several Iranians and allied militias were killed by airstrikes in eastern Syria near the Iraqi border. It was not immediately clear who had carried out these strikes, although Israel has launched a significant number of attacks on Iranian targets in Syria throughout the country's civil war.  In recent weeks, Israel has struck targets in Syria, Iraq and Lebanon to stop Iran from distributing sophisticated weapons within striking distance of its borders.  Although limited, Hezbollah's downing of a drone - seen as a possible retaliation for an earlier strike that the militant group blamed on Israel and which Jerusalem has yet to deny - and the rockets fired from Syria could be the latest salvos in the simmering tensions between Israel and Iran, Hezbollah's chief sponsor.  In a statement, Hezbollah said that its operatives shot down the Israeli drone outside the village of Ramyeh, across the border from northern Israel and that "it is now in their hands."  The Israeli Army confirmed in a statement that the drone had been shot down "on a routine mission in northern Israel" as it "fell into Lebanese territory." Lt. Col. Jonathan Conricus, a spokesman for the Israeli Army, declined to comment on the specific nature of the drone's activities in Lebanon or if Israel had been involved in the strikes on Syrian territory.  "There is no risk of breach of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE NEST camera ALWAYS scanning faces...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/google-nest-hub-max-a-new-face-tracking-camera-for-your-home-weve-got-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nest Hub Max always watches for a familiar face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Financial Stress Making 2 In 5 Young Americans Sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/money-matters-financial-stress-literally-making-2-in-5-americans-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a survey of 1,000 Americans aged 25-45, financial worries and stress due to health care concerns are quite literally making people sick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino Shows Art Cinemas Can Live Happily Ever After...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/quentin-tarantino-shows-art-cinemas-can-live-happily-ever-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino Shows Art Cinemas Can Live Happily Ever After</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITISH AIRWAYS grounds nearly all flights as pilots strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/baaba9bbb7934b6f9da725c1b79825cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Airways said Monday it has canceled almost all its flights for 48 hours, affecting as many as 195,000 travelers, due to a strike by pilots over pay. The U.K.'s flagship...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Dressed As Elmo Accused Of Groping Girl In Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/09/09/times-square-elmo-charged-with-forcible-touching/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 54-year-old man from New Jersey was arrested Saturday and charged with forcible touching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi fights for political life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-fights-political-life-week-israel-votes-105832717.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the September 17 vote looming, Netanyahu and his right-wing Likud have drawn outrage from opposition parties with a push for last-minute legislation that would allow party officials to bring cameras to polling stations. The bill would allow election supervisors from political parties to bring cameras</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Booming Texas May Usher in Dem Win in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/booming-texas-economy-may-usher-080000440.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. For Republicans, the Texas Miracle may become a victim of its own success.The booming economy that helped the Lone Star State weather the 2008 recession has also sparked a migration there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Another TESLA Driver Caught Asleep At Wheel On Highway...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/08/video-driver-apparently-asleep-auto-pilot-mass-pike-self-driving-tesla/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver is hunched over and seemingly fast asleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's giant telescope picks up mysterious signals from deep space...</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/2019-09/09/c_138377523.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next target in 'climate-change' debate: Gas stove...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190909111047-te8j6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of cities are considering legislation to limit the use of natural gas, amid evidence that it leaks of unburned gas may harm the climate more than carbon dioxide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin party loses third of seats in election bloodbath...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9891426/vladimir-putin-party-loses-third-of-seats-moscow-election/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s United Russia party has sensationally lost a THIRD of its seats in Moscow in a local election bloodbath. Sunday’s poll was one of the most closely watched regional elections in yea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Stadium Seats Empty as 100th Season Kicks Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/09/08/weak-1-seats-still-empty-for-several-teams-as-nfls-100th-season-kicks-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week starts the NFL's 100th season, but some teams seem to still be finding a awful lot of empty seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession Already Grips Corners of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/a-manufacturing-recession-could-cost-trump-a-second-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Manufacturing Recession Could Cost Trump a Second Term</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli PM former protege could now bring his downfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/937e390293d24c4e80cd5fa535a8f543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Avigdor Lieberman entered Israeli politics as a loyal protégé of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. Now, the maverick politician could be the one to topple his former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans face must-win race in NCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/460449-gop-faces-must-win-race-in-north-carolina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are scrambling to avoid what would be a devastating loss in the special House election in North Carolina’s 9th District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein accuser sent affectionate e-mails after alleged sex attack...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/09/08/weinstein-accuser-sent-affectionate-e-mails-after-alleged-sex-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandra Canosa, who is suing Weinstein in Manhattan federal court, wrote him the 2010 missive along with, “Miss you too. Love to you and the girls” in early 2011 — less than two weeks after she c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 STATES CANCEL PRIMARIES</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/republicans-in-three-states-cancel-primaries-and-caucuses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP delegates in Nevada, Kansas and South Carolina will be committed to President Trump</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
