<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Clashes break out in Jerusalem after Palestinian who stabbed Israeli killed by police...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/clashes-break-out-in-jerusalem-after-palestinian-who-allegedly-stabbed-israeli-is-killed-by-police/ar-AARsFd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli flight forced to reduce altitude due to spy plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/israeli-flight-to-russia-forced-to-reduce-altitude-due-to-spy-plane-687816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Putin set video call...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-83e399de3cd43eee751553aafb543052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Presidents Joe Biden and Vladimir Putin will speak in a video call Tuesday, the Kremlin said, as tensions between the United States and Russia escalate over a Russian troop buildup on the Ukrainian border  that's seen as a sign of a potential invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More omicron detected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-new-york-new-york-city-kathy-hochul-5129e53128a7a249d36790402220aecc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York announced three more cases of the omicron variant of the coronavirus Saturday, bringing the number of state cases linked to the new variant to eight. “The omicron variant is here, and as anticipated we are seeing the beginning of community spread," state Health Commissioner Mary Bassett said in a news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension Erupts as Top Diplomats Face Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-russia-tension-on-ukraine-erupts-as-top-diplomats-face-off-1.1691101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken and Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov had a testy exchange over Ukraine at a dinner with dozens of their colleagues this week, according to people familiar with the discussions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio Cancels New Year's Eve Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/rio-de-janeiro-cancels-new-year-s-eve-party-on-omicron-fears-1.1691095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) --</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC nurse charged for making fake vax cards...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/584343-south-carolina-nurse-charged-for-allegedly-making-fake-vaccine-cards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal grand jury on Friday indicted a South Carolina nurse on two counts of producing fake vaccine cards, the U.S. Attorney's Office in South Carolina announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Psychedelics Next Big Treatment for Depression?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/psychedelics-next-big-treatment-depression-050022986.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/GettyIn 2019, the FDA made a groundbreaking decision to approve a form of ketamine as a clinical treatment for patients suffering from treatment-resistant depression, a condition which is estimated to affect nearly three million Americans. The drug, called Spravato, is the first psychedelic drug to be approved for the treatment of mental illness. This approval, along with large-scale clinical trials of LSD, MDMA, and psilocybin (the active co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Economic Collapse, Afghanistan Gripped by Starvation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/04/facing-economic-collapse-afghanistan-is-gripped-by-starvation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAH WALI KOT, Afghanistan — One by one, women poured into the mud brick clinic, the frames of famished children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Removes Top Comedians From Service In Royalty Payments Dispute...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/spotify-removes-top-comedians-from-service-royalty-payments-dispute-1234884794/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Mulaney, Jim Gaffigan, Tiffany Haddish and Kevin Hart are among the big name comedians whose work has been removed from streaming service Spotify in a fight over royalty payments. The Wall St.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 33-year-old lives on $88 a day in S Africa after moving from NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/04/how-this-33-year-old-lives-in-south-africa-on-88-a-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanisha Colon-Bibb says “nothing has really changed” about her routine in South Africa despite the emergence of a new coronavirus variant there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Plunges in Another Sign of Global Market Nerves...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-plunges-over-20-another-063422558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin plunged along with other cryptocurrencies on Saturday, in another indication of the risk aversion sweeping across financial markets.Most Read from BloombergThe Hot New Trend For Hedge Funds Is—Finally—Female Founders‘Ghost Signs’ Haunt London’s Reviving NeighborhoodsAutomating the War on Noise PollutionReliving the New York Subway Map DebateThe largest digital token fell as low as $42,296 before paring some of the tumble. It was trading at about $48,300 as of 10:31 a.m. in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flee as Indonesia volcano erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/04/asia/indonesia-mount-semeru-eruption-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mount Semeru, a volcano on Indonesia's East Java Province, erupted on Saturday, spewing a column of smoke and ash while displacing thousands from the area, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France First Female President Could Be Right-Wing Pecresse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/france-s-republicans-pick-pecresse-as-presidential-candidate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s Republicans Pick Pecresse as Presidential Candidate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthodox priest shouts 'Pope, you are heretic' at Francis in Athens...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211204145529-cfa0h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-GREECE/ARCHBISHOP-PROTESTER (PIX, TV):Orthodox priest shouts 'Pope, you are a heretic' at Francis in Athens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugstores squeezed by jab demand, staff shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-science-business-health-b02158b1530871161f3c78d0ca915b67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rush of vaccine-seeking customers and staff shortages are squeezing drugstores around the U.S., leading to frazzled workers and temporary pharmacy closures. Drugstores are normally busy this time of year with flu shots and other vaccines, but now pharmacists are doling out a growing number of COVID-19 shots and giving coronavirus tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern-day slavery uncovered in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/this-has-been-happening-for-a-long-time-modern-day-slavery-uncovered-in-south-georgia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — A yearslong human trafficking operation trapped migrant workers in “modern-day slavery” on South Georgia farms, according to a federal indictment unsealed last week. Victims include over one hundred laborers smuggled from Mexico and Central America into “brutal” and “inhumane” working cond...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIOLENT CRIME SHAKES LA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/brutal-brazen-crimes-shake-la-leaving-city-at-a-crossroads/ar-AARsCHd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearing Repeat of Jan. 6, Congress Eyes Changes to Electoral Count Law...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/04/fearing-a-repeat-of-jan-6-congress-eyes-changes-to-electoral-count-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Members of the select congressional committee investigating the Jan. 6 attack at the Capitol are pressing to overhaul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denzel Washington, Man on Fire...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/04/denzel-washington-man-on-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Denzel Washington and Frances McDormand began rehearsing to play the Macbeths, he asked her how she thought the couple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Households with married couple and children falls to record low...</title>
      <link>https://www.nny360.com/news/number-of-u-s-households-with-married-couple-and-children-falls-to-record-low/article_3dc0544b-cfcf-50ee-a83d-ad09927e38cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nny360.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The number of U.S. homes with a married couple and kids fell to a record low, according to new government data, as the pandemic further delayed weddings and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine defense keeps 'spotlight' on Epstein, other powerful men...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/ghislaine-maxwells-defense-keeps-spotlight-epstein-powerful-men-rcna7516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell is the one accused of sex trafficking, but during the first five days of testimony in a New York City courtroom her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala staff exodus reignites questions about her leadership -- and future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-kamala-harris-staff-exodus-reignites-questions-about-her-leadership-style-e2-80-94-and-her-future-ambitions/ar-AARshLP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shares genetic code with common cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/omicron-possibly-more-infectious-because-it-shares-genetic-code-with-common-cold-coronavirus-study-says/ar-AARscA9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO CRASHES; BITCOIN DOWN 17%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/04/cryptocurrencies-bitcoin-and-ether-prices-drop-sharply.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a 24-hour period spanning Friday morning to Saturday morning, bitcoin's price went from about $57,000 to $47,000, losing $10,000, or more than 17%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal experts on Baldwin risky interview: 'No-upside situation'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/legal-experts-alec-baldwins-risky-004841420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baldwin's decision to speak on national television during an active criminal investigation into the 'Rust' shooting was highly risky, legal experts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amish Hold Key To Healthier Heart? Gene Linked To Lower Disease Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gene-heart-disease-amish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, study authors say fewer than one person in 10,000 has this particular gene -- B4GALT1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blizzard warnings in effect for Hawaii as potent storm wallops islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/blizzard-warning-hawaii-flood-watch-kona-low/1056085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vigorous storm system known as a Kona low is expected to bring a widespread flood threat to the drought-stricken islands, while also blasting the highest elevations of the Big Island with snow and winds up to 100 mph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Half of young adults believe democracy in trouble, failing...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/52-of-young-adults-surveyed-believe-us-democracy-in-trouble-or-failing-harvard-poll-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many young Americans have a gloomy outlook on the state of democracy, but they’ve also indicated what a successful one would look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pals yank dead friend out of his coffin to take him on one last motorcycle ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/pals-yank-dead-friend-out-25612444</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - GRAPHIC CONTENT: Erick Cedeno’s pals claim to have received permission from his parents to exhume his coffin take him out on "one last" motorcycle ride and say goodbye "as they should"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job growth disappoints in Nov despite high hopes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/03/jobs-report-november-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls were expected to increase by 573,000 in November, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICANS 'NUMB' TO COVID...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/americans-seem-to-have-become-numb-to-delta-omicron-is-coming-but-older-variant-is-still-driving-infections-203546167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. public health officials are facing a new challenge: warning Americans about Omicron, the new strain of the coronavirus, while reminding them that the Delta variant is showing clear signs of resurgence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Save Notre Dame Cathedral from 'Cultural Vandalism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/12/saving-notre-dame-cathedral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notre Dame’s new renovation plans symbolize Leftist cultural vandalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah,</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-public-health-utah-3b5b95121bd8aa757a7fd78b43133b53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Utah has confirmed its first COVID-19 case of the omicron variant in a patient who traveled to South Africa, state health officials announced Friday. The positive case was discovered in an older adult who lives in the southwestern part of the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia: Drunkest Country in World...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkpp9z/australia-is-the-drunkest-country-in-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People from Australia are getting wasted at a much higher frequency than the rest of the world, according to a global drug survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flash mob' robberies roiling retailers, traumatizing workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Flash-mob-robberies-roiling-U-S-retailers-16671485.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say they hit critical mass in late November when stores were piled high with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly,</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/12/03/covid19-omicron-variant-reported-philadelphia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials say a male resident in his 30's from Northwest Philadelphia has tested positive for the omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare blizzard warning in Hawaii; Up to 12 inches of snow expected...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/03/rare-blizzard-heavy-snow-warnings-issued-in-hawaii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare blizzard warning has been issued for the Big Island of Hawaii, with a large amount of snow anticipated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore,</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/12/03/maryland-has-three-confirmed-cases-of-the-omicron-variant-hogan-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Larry Hogan on Friday announced three Marylanders have the new Omicron variant of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eastman takes the Fifth...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/03/eastman-takes-the-fifth-with-jan-6-committee-523712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney, who helped former President Donald Trump contest the 2020 election, asserted his right against self-incrimination in a Dec. 1 letter to the Capitol riot panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could seaweed save humanity?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/could-seaweed-save-humanity-from-covid-19-687775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA cops arrest 14 suspects in connection with 11 smash-and-grabs -- but release ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10271809/LA-cops-arrest-14-suspects-11-smash-grab-robberies-freed-zero-bail-policy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Police Chief Michel Moore announced the arrests of 14 suspects in connection with 11 recent flash mob-style retail heists, but said all of the accused bailed out or met no-bail criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive test prompts National Guard chief to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/12/03/national-guard-bureau-chief-isolating-after-testing-positive-for-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hokanson has held post since August 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of car windows smashed, burglaries while fans at SAINTS game...</title>
      <link>https://www.wwltv.com/article/news/crime/video-shows-car-windows-smashed-apparent-burglaries-while-fans-at-saints-game/289-53ee0e35-1301-441b-a512-2ebb14b42a7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wwltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of fans said they returned to their cars after the game to find the windows broken and their cars vandalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Curbs UFO Transparency...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-12-02/new-pentagon-office-criticized-as-effort-to-control-ufo-investigations-end-transparency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Defense Department group will now oversee U.S. government-wide investigations into UFOs – with little hope for transparency or oversight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 23,500 airmen, guardians say no...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/12/03/over-23500-airmen-and-guardians-say-no-to-covid-vaccines-as-final-deadline-passes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 14,000 Air Force Reserve and Air National Guard members were unvaccinated as of Friday, a day after the deadline for receiving the shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Great Pacific Garbage Patch, scientists find surprise: Coastal life...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/environment/great-pacific-garbage-patch-scientists-find-surprise-coastal-life-rcna7292</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coastal marine species carried out to sea on debris are not only surviving, they’re colonizing the high seas and making new communities on the floating plastic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Parents Of Michigan School Shooter Charged With Manslaughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/oxford-school-shooting-ethan-crumbley-parents-charging-decision-watch-today-2021-12-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James and Jennifer Crumbley have each been charged with four counts of involuntary manslaughter, prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMICRON SPREADING TWICE AS FAST AS DELTA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2021/12/03/world/omicron-variant-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new research indicates that the variant can spread more easily than Delta, which was previously the most contagious version of the virus. Omicron has been found in at least six states, mostly among travelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS FOREVER? Oregon considers permanent mandate...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/coronavirus/1007727/will-a-new-indoor-mask-mandate-in-oregon-actually-be-permanent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle sees wettest fall on record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-environment-and-nature-seattle-weather-bellingham-ef26f2e09054e55e38cce0415a76daeb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Seattle, a city known for soggy weather, has seen its wettest fall on record. The National Weather Service says 19.04 inches (48.4 centimeters) of rain fell between Sept. 1 and Nov.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
