<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CNN Lemon and guests mock Trump supporters as uneducated and illiterate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/cnns-don-lemon-and-guests-mock-trump-supporters-as-uneducated-and-illiterate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN's Don Lemon and two guests on his show are facing backlash after they mocked President Trump's supporters and depicted them as uneducated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg surpasses Buttigieg in national poll...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/480236-bloomberg-hits-double-digits-in-new-national-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential hopeful Michael Bloomberg hit double digits in a new Morning Consult poll on Tuesday, marking the latest sign of his campaign's growing support since launching in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pictures show helicopter in ball of fire...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/28/pictures-show-kobe-bryants-helicopter-in-ball-of-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The images show Bryant’s helicopter exploding in a ball of flames after slamming into a Los Angeles hillside, killing the NBA superstar, his 13-year-old daughter and seven others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg rise sets off alarms on left...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/28/bloomberg-progressives-leftists-2020-dnc-106712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearful he's avoiding scrutiny, progressives are pressing the DNC to change its debate rules so Bloomberg would be forced to confront his rivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas House special election to gauge suburban mood... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/first-vote-2020-ends-tuesday-texas-n1124266</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in a state house district in the Houston suburbs are set to deliver the first electoral decision of the year — and both parties are watching closely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR TRAFFIC IN FREE-FALL</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikeboyd/2020/01/27/sudden-free-fall-chinaus-air-traffic/#6d4bac62208c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus is threatening to put a stake in the heart of what was until now was thought to be potentially one of the fastest growth sectors in the airline business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Feels 'Urge' to Run...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7936395/Hillary-Clinton-believes-win-ran-2020-renews-attack-Bernie-Sanders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton said Monday that she was not thinking about the 2020 Democratic primary or her effect on voters when she criticized Sen. Bernie Sanders in a new film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA TOO!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sanders-surges-lead-california-propelled-133338077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders has not only taken the lead in several recent surveys of voters in Iowa, which holds the first in the nation caucuses on Monday, but he has also pushed to the head of the Democratic field in delegate-rich California.The Vermont senator, who has had strong support from Latinos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XI: China fighting 'demon' virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/foreigners-prepare-flee-china-virus-toll-tops-100-032454869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Xi Jinping said Tuesday China was in a struggle against a "demon" epidemic, as the death toll from the new SARS-like virus soared to 106 and the first cases of human-to-human contagion were detected abroad. Xi made his remarks during talks with head of the World Health Organization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE supply chain braces for disruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3047911/apple-supply-chain-braces-disruption-coronavirus-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virtually all of the world’s iPhones are made in China, primarily by Foxconn – the world’s largest electronics contract manufacturer – at its facility in Zhengzhou and by Pegatron at an assembly site near Shanghai.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury curve inverts as outbreak fans growth fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-bonds-inversion/u-s-treasury-curve-inverts-as-virus-outbreak-fans-growth-fears-idUSKBN1ZR11P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Treasury yield curve, measured by the gap between yields on three-month...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain to allow HUAWEI equipment in 5G network, dismissing Trump call to ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/28/huawei-uk-chinese-firm-allowed-limited-access-to-uk-5g-network.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain will allow Chinese telecommunications giant Huawei to play a limited role in its next generation 5G mobile networks, defying pressure from the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesia unveils new female flogging squad...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/indonesias-aceh-unveils-female-flogging-squad-043001415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The masked woman nervously approaches her target, shuffles into position and then unleashes a flurry of lashes -- proving herself as the newest member of the first female flogging squad in Indonesia's Aceh province. Such behaviour constitutes a morality crime in Aceh, the only region in the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA reveals 'space home' where first tourists will enjoy 'largest Earth window'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10835572/nasa-iss-space-tourists-housing-module-axiom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE tourists set to holiday aboard the International Space Station will enjoy padded pods and panoramic views of Earth. Nasa has chosen the start-up that will build the first “private habit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag queens to appear in Super Bowl ad for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/drag-queens-make-historical-debut-during-super-bowl-liv-n1124296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“RuPaul’s Drag Race” alumni Kim Chi and Miz Cracker will appear in an ad for Sabra hummus during Feb. 2’s championship football game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian media: CIA agent behind Soleimani killing shot down in Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Iranian-media-CIA-agent-behind-Soleimani-killing-shot-down-in-Afghanistan-615652</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the Taliban has claimed that a number of CIA agents were on board a plane it says it shot down on Monday; a claim the US denies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bribery indictment against Netanyahu filed with court...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Prime-Minister-Netanyahu-indictment-on-way-to-Jerusalem-District-Court-615655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandelblit announced his final indictment on November 21, but could not file it with the courts until the immunity request process was concluded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell struggles to maintain unity...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/480198-mcconnell-struggles-to-maintain-gop-unity-post-bolton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is struggling to maintain control of President Trump’s impeachment trial following news of former national security adviser John Bolton’s bombshell manuscript.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uproar over DNC convention appointments...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/480174-sanders-allies-in-new-uproar-over-dnc-convention-appointments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democratic National Committee (DNC) members and supporters of Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to unveil Middle East peace plan amid skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f7d36b9023309ce4b1e423b02abf52c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is set to unveil his administration’s much-anticipated Middle East peace plan in the latest American venture to resolve the Israeli-Palestinian conflict....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong to cut rail links as virus from China spreads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8abebaa0abb67a92c1efe8501a122d0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Hong Kong said Tuesday it will cut all rail links to mainland China as the United States and other governments prepared to evacuate citizens from the Chinese city at the center of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA TURNS ON BOLTON...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Former-allies-turn-on-Bolton-as-book-roils-15008893.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Just outside the spacious corner office of the White House national security adviser, aides crowded into a windowless anteroom knew to make themselves small when John Bolton got a summons from President Donald Trump. Bolton, his signature yellow legal pad in hand, would throw open his door and set off at a gallop.  Once in the Oval Office, Bolton would take copious notes on that pad, at times angering a president known to mistrust note-taking by even his closest aides, according to a former senior administration official.  Leaks from Bolton's soon-to-be-published memoir, in which he alleges a direct link between Trump's withholding of aid to Ukraine and his desire that its government investigate his political rivals, validated the president's suspicions in the eyes of some senior White House officials.  Bolton, who left the White House in September - Trump said he was fired; Bolton said he resigned - did not respond to a question about whether he had used personal notes or official documents in his book.  The manuscript includes more than a dozen pages on Bolton's interactions over Ukraine with Trump, his personal attorney Rudy Giuliani, Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and others, according to one person familiar with the project. In what this person called an "unflattering" portrait of the president, it also touches on other areas where Bolton is known to have disagreed with Trump policy decisions, including Venezuela and Turkey.  But another former senior official, one of several who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal matters, said Bolton "didn't need to have" documents or his own notes from inside the White House, "since he probably went home every night and wrote about it."  Noting the rapid completion of Bolton's book, "I'm convinced he was writing all the time" he served as national...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban claims shot down US Air Force plane carrying CIA officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/taliban-claims-shot-down-air-21371476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic pictures from the scene of the crash in Ghazni also appears to show the smouldering wreckage of the plane bearing a US Air Forces logo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SPOOKED BY SICKNESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/27/dow-futures-as-coronavirus-cases-rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks tanked after more cases of the coronavirus were confirmed, ratcheting up worries over the virus' impact on the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/ArabNewsToday/status/1221814107722088449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“#Afghanistan Taliban announces the downing of an American plane in Ghazni province. https://t.co/Dhun6HinK2”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical masks selling out...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/480203-surgical-masks-selling-out-across-us-amid-fears-over</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surgical-style masks at U.S. pharmacies have reportedly begun selling out in multiple U.S. cities amid fears of the new form of coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept bars NPR reporter from Pompeo's upcoming trip after testy interview...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200127232757-rqyyg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-UKRAINE/POMPEO-MEDIA:U.S. State Department bars NPR reporter from Pompeo's upcoming trip after testy interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA WARNS AGAINST CHINA TRAVEL</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200127230124-mdgn5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/USA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-U.S. government urges Americans to reconsider travel to China because of coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna Cancels 10th Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/01/27/madonna-cancels-10th-show-in-london-i-have-injuries-that-have-plagued-me-since-the-beginning-of-the-tour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna has cancelled a performance of her “Madame X” show for the 10th time, in London scheduled for tonight. As I wrote over the weekend, inside sources warn that she may just cancel …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb star-power fuels final Iowa sprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/27/bernie-sanders-iowa-sprint-106960</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His traveling festival of celebrity surrogates aims to attract young and unlikely voters to his campaign events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandy Hook conspiracy theorist arrested, accused of sharing personal info of dead boy's father...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-sandy-hook-wolfgang-halbig-arrested-20200127-xvzrjgihtrhdro5zyegfcrzyva-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Sorrento man who for years has tormented the families of victims of the Sandy Hook elementary school shooting, was arrested by Lake County deputy sheriffs this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oh my God, Sanders can win'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/oh-my-god-sanders-can-win-democrats-grapple-bernie-surge-n1123806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four years ago, the Vermont senator caught the Democratic establishment sleeping in Iowa. Could he do it again?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: NH BERNS!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcboston.com/news/politics/sanders-seizes-the-momentum-in-nh-nbc10-boston-franklin-pierce-herald-poll-shows/2068088/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcboston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders has moved into first place among Democratic presidential contenders in New Hampshire, according to a new NBC10 Boston/Franklin Pierce University/Boston Herald poll. The poll, released Monday, has Sanders in first place at 29%, followed by Joe Biden at 22% and Elizabeth Warren at 16%. They are trailed by Pete Buttigieg at 10% and Amy Klobuchar at 5%. Among…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test of centralized control...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/efforts-to-contain-the-coronavirus-outbreak-a-test-of-chinas-centralized-control/ar-BBZnMNN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists, fans invade hillside...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tourists-and-fans-invade-calabasas-hillside-where-kobe-bryants-helicopter-crashed/ar-BBZnSEr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She fractured her spine after car ran red light. UBER said she signed away her rights to jury trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/uber-arbitration-lawsuit-clause-terms-philadelphia-injury-20200127.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because Uber can’t prove that a Philadelphia woman actually read the company’s terms and conditions, she can’t be forced to settle her claims behind closed doors, a judge ruled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAMMYS RATINGS SINK TO 12-YEAR LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/grammy-awards-tv-ratings-sunday-jan-26-2020-1273590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS' broadcast mirrors declines for the Golden Globes in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski Wins Best Director At France's Lumiere Awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2020-lumieres-award-winners-les-miserables-wins-frances-top-prize-1272628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ladj Ly's Oscar-nominated drama took the top honor at the ceremony known as the Golden Globes of France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOKGOOGLETWITTER scramble to stop misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/silicon-valley-stop-coronavirus-misinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus's rapid spread worldwide is forcing Big Tech to confront the equally viral proliferation of misinformation -- in the form outright falsehoods and half-truths about the outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Is Black Swan Event That May Have Serious Repercussions For U.S. Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jackkelly/2020/01/27/the-coronavirus-is-a-black-swan-event-that-may-have-serious-repercussions-for-the-us-economy-and-job-market/#4f48c1af3991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corporate CEOs and top executives desire certainty and resent unpredictable events. In this instance, there is an extraordinary high level of uncertainty. The chances are likely that companies will temporarily pull back until there is clarity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy sub 'encountered Nimitz UFO in ocean'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/navy-submarine-encountered-500mph-nimitz-21357187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A former United States Air Force intelligence expert claims he found reports of a Los Angeles-class submarine seeing an unidentified submerged object in "2007 or 2008" that travelled at 550mph underwater. It supposedly matched the description of the USS Nimitz UFO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kobe Received Communion Hours Before Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7935615/Kobe-Gigi-attended-Catholic-mass-Newport-Beach-tragic-crash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kobe Bryant and his 13-year-old Gigi went to the 7am service at Our Lady of Angels Catholic Church in Newport Beach on Sunday just hours before their death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: All the president's turncoats...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/889882</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is terrified of people who have worked for him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy watchdog under pressure to recommend facial recognition ban...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/480152-government-privacy-watchdog-under-pressure-to-recommend-facial-recognition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Privacy and Civil Liberties Oversight Board (PCLOB), an independent agency, is coming under increasing pressure to recommend the federal government stop using facial recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepares 100,000 Hospital Beds...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-races-against-clock-build-virus-hospitals-133144323.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of workers are toiling around the clock at the site of a field hospital that China is racing to build within days to treat a rapidly growing number of patients stricken by a deadly virus. The outline of a floor began to take shape and electrical switchboards were already up on Monday when AFP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74% of Americans Fear Potential Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2020/01/27/even-as-cdc-says-risk-of-coronavirus-is-low-in-u-s-worry-begins-to-spread/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz survivors warn of rising anti-Semitism 75 years on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d503019511da4f2580c12f3199ddab79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OSWIECIM, Poland (AP) — Survivors of the Auschwitz-Birkenau death camp prayed and wept as they marked the 75th anniversary of its liberation, returning Monday to the place where they lost entire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK BLOWS TRIAL OPEN...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c5f9cc7070a1d3a0e6afc945036811ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A single paper copy in a nondescript envelope arrived at the White House on Dec. 30. Four weeks later, news of John Bolton’s book manuscript about his time as President Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China extends holiday to fight virus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ea5289ff1a52d43a6ef8bb669b80276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China expanded its sweeping efforts on Monday to contain a dangerous new virus, extending the Lunar New Year holiday to keep the public at home and avoid spreading infection as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toomey proposes 'one-for-one' deal...</title>
      <link>http://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/toomey-proposes-a-one-for-one-witness-deal-in-trump-impeachment-trial-amid-bolton-revelations/ar-BBZnTdg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT FOR WITNESSES INTENSIFIES...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200127185355-jdkwq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 8-Republicans in Trump impeachment trial on the spot over Bolton book report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAKERS vs CLIPPERS postponed...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2020/01/27/lakers-clippers-will-weather-emotional-night-when-they-meet-tuesday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Out of respect for the Lakers organization’ the NBA will reschedule the game between the L.A. teams for another date to be determined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>110 suspected cases in 26 states under CDC investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/states-have-confirmed-coronavirus-cases-more-likely-global-death-toll-rises/Y1jC46a4j4JdDvhMpuY9eN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people in four states have been confirmed as coronavirus cases, and the CDC says more cases are likely, as the virus continues to spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ally of Venezuela's Maduro hires DC lobbyist to build ties...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0c9a9b6521084be0dfe3d4b9b1495e4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — An ally of Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro has hired a Washington lobbyist whose business has boomed under the Trump administration as part of a $12.5 million effort to ease...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington disputes claims it was brought down...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200127193731-v17fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-AIRPLANE/CRASH (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-U.S. military confirms plane crash in Afghanistan, disputes claims it was brought down</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toomey proposes 'one-for-one' deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/toomey-proposes-a-one-for-one-witness-deal-in-trump-impeachment-after-bolton-revelations/2020/01/27/ec405d5c-414b-11ea-aa6a-083d01b3ed18_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toomey has argued such an arrangement could force Democrats to accept a Republican witness against their wishes or risk having Republicans move ahead to acquit Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every Search. Every Click. On Every Site...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/qjdkq7/avast-antivirus-sells-user-browsing-data-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Avast antivirus subsidiary sells 'Every search. Every click. Every buy. On every site.' Its clients have included Home Depot, Google, Microsoft, Pepsi, and McKinsey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM ESTABLISHMENT: ANYONE BUT BERNIE!</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/27/us/politics/iowa-democrats-bernie-sanders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the liberal Bernie Sanders tightens his grip in Iowa, more traditional Democrats remain split among his four leading competitors, or are unsure altogether of whom to support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/impeachment-trial-trump-day-6-defense-2020-01-27-live-updating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's attorneys largely sidestepped new revelations reportedly contained in a manuscript of a book by John Bolton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming Rise of Smart Camera Networks...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/01/27/surveillance-cctv-smart-camera-networks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are using cameras at private businesses and homes, along with artificial intelligence, to vastly expand their video surveillance, raising privacy concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worried Dems Scramble to Take Down Bernie...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/worried-democratic-operatives-scramble-to-fund-a-network-to-take-down-bernie-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those operatives have had early talks about putting together an effort to stop the Vermonter should he break through in Iowa. But, so far, they’ve had few bites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran activates emergency operations center...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/San-Francisco-to-activate-emergency-operations-15007956.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco Mayor London Breed is planning to provide an update early Monday afternoon on what the city has done, and what it still plans to do, in the wake of a deadly outbreak of coronavirus in China that has sickened five people in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagery Suggests Iran Preparing To Launch Satellite...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/01/27/800045774/imagery-suggests-iran-is-preparing-to-try-to-launch-a-satellite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activity at the Imam Khomeini Space Center indicates Iran is once again attempting to send a satellite into orbit. Last year, three attempts ended in failure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to reveal 'Deal of the Century' map...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Trump-to-unveil-Israeli-borders-map-for-first-time-in-peace-plan-rollout-615541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First time border outline unveiled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge of the albatross: Seabirds expose illicit fishing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/revenge-albatross-seabirds-expose-illicit-fishing-200301723.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the magnificent but maligned albatross, it was time for a little payback after centuries of insult and injury. Snagged by longlines, tangled in nets, shot at by sailors, and scorned by poets as lazy or a bad omen, the world's largest flying seabird is today a front-line agent in the fight against</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein accuser Mimi Haley testifies disgraced mogul raped her...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/manhattan/ny-harvey-weinstein-mimi-haley-rape-trial-20200127-gd2kk4unjbfrbl4vupugatatsq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former production assistant broke into tears Monday as she told a Manhattan jury how fallen film tycoon Harvey Weinstein sexually assaulted her in 2006 in his SoHo loft and once again in a Tribeca hotel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR:  'Like war, impeachment is hell'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7935221/Donald-Trumps-lawyers-start-day-defense-Boltons-bombshell.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's lawyers resumed his defense Monday by defending his conduct toward Ukraine, hours after new bombshell allegations in a manuscript that he tied aid to a Biden probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5-4 Supreme Court allows rule that could reshape legal immigration...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/27/politics/supreme-court-immigration-public-charge/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court Monday in a 5-4 vote cleared the way for the Trump administration to make it more difficult for immigrants who rely on public assistance to obtain legal status</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Containment may not be feasible...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/01/26/containing-new-coronavirus-may-not-be-feasible-experts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The more we learn about it, the greater the possibility is that transmission will not be able to be controlled with public health measures,” an expert said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR:  'Like war, impeachment is hell'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2020/impeachment-trial-live-01-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bolton’s unpublished manuscript about his time in the White House describes how President Trump tied aid for Ukraine to investigations of the Bidens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA agent shot dead in Atlanta airport staff lot...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/breaking-shot-delta-employee-parking-lot-near-atlanta-airport/0t6NV0P6WLzuEANPX8jcjL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Delta Air Lines employee was killed in a shooting Sunday night at the company’s staff parkin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept adds antitrust staff amid Big Tech probes...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200127174245-p75fy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECH-ANTITRUST/HIRING (PIX):U.S. Justice Dept adds antitrust staff amid Big Tech probes -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. prosecutors, FBI seek Prince Andrew interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/prince-andrew-has-provided-zero-cooperation-epstein-probe-n1123951</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew, who has denied allegations he had sex with a teenage girl trafficked by Epstein, has said he would assist in any investigation related to the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCARTHY:  Blows Up Foolhardy Quid Pro Quo Defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/01/bolton-blows-up-trump-teams-foolhardy-quid-pro-quo-defense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;However objectionable it may have been, nothing of consequence happened. Therefore there was no impeachable offense. Case closed. Except it’s not case closed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot given 'special clearance to fly in dangerous weather conditions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7934407/Helicopter-crashed-killing-Kobe-8-circled-15-minutes-Burbank.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kobe Bryant's helicopter pilot was given a special clearance to fly under foggy conditions considered dangerous enough that local police agencies grounded their choppers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?468552-1/senate-impeachment-trial-day-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate impeachment trial of President Trump continues with opening arguments from the President's defense team. Other legislative work is possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans prefer libraries over movies, sports or concerts...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/27/americans-preferred-libraries-over-movies-sports-or-concerts-in-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Print’s not dead yet. A new Gallup poll found that Americans spent more of their leisure time inside libraries last year than they did going to movie theaters, sporting events, museums, conce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST suspends journalist for tweeting link to Kobe rape case story...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/314931/washington-post-journalist-suspended-tweet-rape-case-kobe-bryant-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A REPORTER for the Washington Post has been placed on “administrative leave” after she tweeted a link to a 2016 article detailing the 2003 rape case against Kobe Bryant just hours after…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. prosecutors, FBI seek Prince Andrew interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/27/nyregion/jeffrey-epstein-prince-andrew.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States attorney in Manhattan said the prince had not responded to their requests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students required to install location tracking app so college can 'pinpoint' them...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=14274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Why is this necessary?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney, Collins signal support for witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/27/susan-collins-signals-she-will-vote-for-witnesses-in-trump-impeachment-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP representative said reports about John Bolton’s new memoir “strengthen the case for witnesses.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
