<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WHY WAS HE FREE?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10450979/london-bridge-attack-usman-khan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE London Bridge terrorist was free to kill an innocent man and woman despite the judge who jailed him ruling he should never be let out. Usman Khan, 28, from Staffordshire, was released from pris…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belonged to jihadist group that admired Hitler...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/30/london-bridge-stabber-belonged-to-jihadist-group-that-admired-hitler-plotted-to-bomb-us-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The knife-wielding terrorist who was subdued by civilians, then shot dead by police on London Bridge on Friday was a paroled bomb plotter who once hoped to start a jihadist training camp in Kashmir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state lawmaker faces backlash against white nationalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/far-right-washington-state-lawmaker-faces-backlash-against-white-nationalism/ar-BBXwDbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Miami-Dade officer rebuilt his life after prison. Then, a nephew had him murdered, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article237872849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu clings to office while calling criminal charges against him a 'witch hunt'... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Netanyahu-clings-to-office-while-calling-criminal-14871331.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This appears in Saturday's Washington Post:  - - -  When former Israeli prime minister Ehud Olmert came under criminal investigation on bribery charges a decade ago, he took the honorable route and resigned, opening the way for new elections that brought Benjamin Netanyahu to power. Now it's Netanyahu's turn: Israel's attorney general announced Nov. 21 that he plans to indict the sitting prime minister on charges of bribery, fraud and breach of trust. To the detriment of Israel and its democracy, Netanyahu is taking the low road.  Rather than accede to the many calls for him to resign - and a poll showing that a majority of Israelis want him to go - Netanyahu has adopted what might be called, and what probably deliberately is, a Trumpian defense. The charges against him, he claims, are an "attempted coup"; the police investigators and prosecutors who spent years preparing them are guilty of a "witch hunt" and should themselves be investigated.  On Tuesday, Netanyahu staged a public rally in Tel Aviv and bused in supporters to demonstrate against the "coup." The result was a welcome sign that he may have gone too far: Key leaders of his Likud party declined to attend. One of them, Gideon Saar, has said he will challenge Netanyahu for the party leadership in a primary.  Netanyahu's intransigence is particularly worrying because it is the primary reason Israeli politicians have been unable to form a government following elections in April and again in September. Neither the Likud's right-wing alliance nor its center-left opposition commands a majority in the Knesset. The centrist Blue and White party, which holds the most seats, says it will not form an alliance with Likud unless Netanyahu agrees to give up the prime minister's post, at least while his criminal case plays out.  Netanyahu appears to hope that remaining in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pardons likely for Flynn, Manafort, Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/It-s-a-good-bet-Trump-will-pardon-his-felon-14871149.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future isn't promised, but it is a good bet that three felons and close allies of President Donald Trump - Roger Stone (found guilty of obstruction of a congressional investigation, witness tampering and lying to Congress), Paul Manafort (serving prison sentence for tax evasion and bank fraud) and Michael Flynn (pleaded guilty to lying to the FBI) - will be granted executive clemency. The only question is when.  It might be a tad bit premature for Manafort to start humming "I'll Be Home for Christmas." But he will be there next year.  To be sure, Trump could free his friends before voters cast their ballots in 2020. But that's politically risky, as President Gerald Ford's 1976 defeat can attest. His approval rating dropped more than 30 points after he pardoned Richard Nixon.  Trump's safest course of action would be to wait to do the dirty deed until after Election Day, Nov. 3, 2020. Trump's impulsiveness, however, is a wild card.  Impeached or not, Trump can still grant pardons without fear of a citizens' revolt - once the polls close. Even if the voters serve him with an eviction, Trump can still cut his boys loose, provided he acts before turning off the lights in the Oval Office.  The Stone, Manafort and Flynn prediction is offered with confidence because of Trump's demonstrated disregard for the integrity of the criminal-justice system.  That disdain was on display in his recent chiseling of the military judicial process. Against the advice of experienced, respected leaders in the Pentagon, Trump intervened in three cases involving war crimes accusations, overturning decisions of military juries and issuing full pardons to two soldiers convicted of war crimes, as well as reversing disciplinary action against a third service member, Chief Petty Officer Edward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems ask Trump if he wants lawyers at impeachment hearings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/88646b56c71641b9906a9cab82379315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The chairman of the House Judiciary Committee asked President Donald Trump on Friday to say whether he’ll send his attorneys to participate in impeachment proceedings before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attending CAMBRIDGE conference -- on prisoner rehabilitation...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/london-bridge-attacker-identity-attack-video-stabbing-incident-latest-a9227061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Still wearing ELECTRONIC TAG'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7740295/Knife-attacker-shot-dead-London-Bridge-known-police-security-sources-reveal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The knife attacker shot dead on London Bridge was known to police and had connections to terror groups, a security source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K. tells Israeli audience he'd 'rather be in Auschwitz than NYC'....</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/29/louis-c-k-tells-israeli-audience-hed-rather-be-in-auschwitz-than-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The off-color comment came as Louis C.K. continues an international comedy tour, meant to bring him back into the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KID ROCK GOES ON DRUNKEN RANT ABOUT OPRAH...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/29/kid-rock-escorted-off-stage-after-drunken-rant-against-oprah-winfrey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rock is heard yelling “F–k Oprah” during his rant against the media mogul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu Season Takes off Quickly in Deep South States...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2019-11-29/flu-season-takes-off-quickly-in-deep-south-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you 'brain-dead'? Erdogan raps Macron before NATO summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-france-idUSKBN1Y31I0?taid=5de1967f86d8c600013cfbed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan said on Friday that Emmanuel Macron's warn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDINALS player caught betting on NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28189546/cardinals-josh-shaw-suspended-least-2020-season-betting-nfl-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cardinals' Josh Shaw has been suspended through at least the 2020 season for betting on NFL games on multiple occasions, though the league says no contests were compromised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Vicious Brawl Outside FOREVER 21; Woman's Wig Goes Flying...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/black-friday-2019-fights-prove-deal-hunting-is-as-perilous-as-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because what would this American shopping tradition be without brawls and f-bombs?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S GHOST TOWN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/29/macys-a-ghost-town-on-black-friday-thanks-to-web-shoppers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of online retail has eased the Black Friday hoards of yesteryear, but many bargain-seekers still turned out across the Big Apple on Friday to splash some cash in person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China mixing military and science in push...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-arctic/china-mixing-military-and-science-in-arctic-push-denmark-idUSKBN1Y3116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's military is increasingly using scientific research in the Arctic as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans 'absolutely disgusted' by President, ex-GOP congressman says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/29/politics/charlie-dent-congress-trump-behavior-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Republican congressman Charlie Dent said Thursday some of his former colleagues in the House of Representatives have privately told him they are "absolutely disgusted and exhausted by the President's behavior."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA arrests cryptocurrency scientist for assisting NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-authorities-arrest-ethereum-research-200109230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The office of the U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York and the FBI announced today that it has arrested and charged Virgil Griffith for violating the U.S.The post U.S. authorities arrest Ethereum research scientist Virgil Griffith for assisting North Korea in evading sanctions appeared</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 wounded in The Hague stabbing attack... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f698b4dc05949cbb2bfca45f98d39ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The Latest on stabbings in The Hague (all times local): 9:30 p.m. Dutch police say three people were injured in a stabbing on The Hague’s main shopping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several wounded in stabbing in The Hague... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/29/several-people-wounded-in-stabbing-on-shopping-street-in-the-hague.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears mount about Biden's SC firewall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/472330-fears-mount-about-bidens-south-carolina-firewall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent weeks, Biden has been losing ground in the first two early voting states, according to polling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack on city's main shopping street...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/the-hague-several-hurt-after-stabbing-in-shopping-area-11873848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have begun a manhunt after several people were hurt in a stabbing in The Hague.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor treating Amish sees rarest diseases on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/nation/2019/11/29/wisconsin-rural-doctor-treats-amish-studies-rare-genetic-diseases/3995625002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When James DeLine became a rural doctor, he had no experience treating the Amish, and no idea he'd be at the cutting edge of genetic medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Teacher of the Year' gave student oral sex in classroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article237863534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois town to use marijuana sales tax to fund reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/evanston/ct-evr-evanston-reparations-marijuana-tax-tl-1205-20191126-g3ifwaikrjfmrillfv6ytvwgii-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evanston council members voted to earmark the city's marijuana sales tax revenue to a local reparations program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 KILLED...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/live/uk-50601491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say they have shot dead a man suspected of being behind a stabbing attack near the bridge in central London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON exec 'main suspect' in wife's horrific murder...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/29/juan-carlos-garcia-ex-ceo-of-amazon-mexico-suspected-in-wifes-murder-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former head of Amazon Mexico is wanted for questioning in his estranged wife’s murder after she was ambushed in Mexico City, according to reports. Juan Carlos García and his wife, Abril P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shut down AMAZON warehouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10447003/black-friday-protest-warehouse-climate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOZENS of protesters shut down an Amazon warehouse in France on Thursday in protest at Black Friday – claiming it harms the planet. Activists from climate group Amis de la terre (Friends of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French prosecutor drops charges against killer of Jewish teacher...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/world/french-prosecutors-drop-murder-charges-jewish-kindergarten-teacher-sarah-halimi-killer-kobili-traor%C3%A9-1.493649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'IRISHMAN' to Mister Rogers, what it means to be a man is getting real... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/From-The-Irishman-to-Mister-Rogers-what-it-14870480.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Fonda visited The Washington Post the other day. At breakfast, just before going onstage with Diane Lane to talk about oceans in crisis, she responded to a question about the intersection of environmental politics and feminism. The veteran actress and advocate observed that women have always gravitated toward working together in the collective interest.  "It's not that we're better than men," she quipped, quoting her good friend Gloria Steinem. "It's just that we don't have our masculinity to prove."  It's a great line - classic Gloria. And it turns out to be apropos, not just in the world of activism, but in movies. Among the dozens of awards contenders that are crowding theater screens between now and the end of the year, a significant number seem to be grappling with men's roles, reflecting disruptions that are roiling the film establishment itself. At a time when the white male gaze is being challenged as Hollywood's default setting, the very essence of manhood - the postures, attitudes and behaviors that movies have portrayed as "male" for more than a century - is being reappraised. Films that once might have been positioned as celebrations of brotherhood, bonding and bromance instead are examining their hidden costs.  There was a time, after all, when part of the enjoyment of watching a Martin Scorsese film was being seduced by the same codes of honor among thieves he romanticized so convincingly in films like "Raging Bull" and "Goodfellas." In his new movie "The Irishman," which began streaming this week on Netflix, Scorsese rep players Robert De Niro and Joe Pesci go through many of the familiar rituals of violence and mayhem. But now they're slowed down, repeated to the point of boredom, leeched of vicarious pleasure. The threats, hair-trigger arguments and ruthless hit jobs that once exuded the thrill of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco breaks cold record as Bay Area freezes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/San-Francisco-cold-Bay-Area-weather-frost-record-14870555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you thought Thanksgiving Day was unusually cold this year in San Francisco, you were correct. In fact, it was record-breaking cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil President Blames DiCaprio for Rainforest  Fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/brazil-president-blames-leonardo-dicaprio-amazon-rainforest-fires-1258511</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jair Bolsonaro told supporters Friday: "DiCaprio is a cool guy, isn't he? Giving money to set the Amazon on fire."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of reviews fake?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90437753/shopping-online-this-black-friday-beware-a-third-of-online-reviews-are-fake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s how to tell which reviews are legit and which are not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many children does he have? </title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/11/29/boris-johnson-refuses-say-many-children-11238199/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He refused to answer questions about his own children when challenged on his comments about the children of single mothers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Knifeman wearing fake suicide vest shot dead in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10450979/london-bridge-police-breaking-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLICE have shot dead a terrorist wearing a fake suicide vest after at least 12 people were injured in a shocking attack at London Bridge today. Terrifying footage from the scene shows armed office…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero stopped more slashings...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/hero-filmed-bravely-taking-knife-20990893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the dramatic footage, a group of people are seen tackling the knifeman to the floor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds flee bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7739057/Gun-shots-heard-London-Bridge-police-confirm-incident-area.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One video filmed on London Bridge today shows what appears to be police pulling equipment out of a vehicle nearby. Those in the video can be heard saying: 'They've actually got guns out.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOMEN IN HIJABS FIGHT OVER VACUUM CLEANER AT WALMART...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/seasons-beatings-women-in-hijabs-fight-over-vacuum-frenzy-over-walmart-towels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many stores sought to open earlier than Black Friday to relieve some of the pressure of shoppers swarming for good deals, but there have already been incidents at Walmarts around the country. At one Walmart, two women in hijabs fought over a vacuum, forcing several employees to intervene: ﻿ The two women argued as the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No invasion since 1914'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191129150659-vs2y4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEXICO/CARTELS (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump First to Use PATRIOT Act to Detain Man Forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-invokes-patriot-act-to-detain-palestinian-adham-amin-hassoun-forever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never in 18 years has the government used Section 412 of the PATRIOT Act, which permits indefinite detention of resident aliens on national-security grounds. Until now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/breaking-shots-fired-on-london-bridge-possible-suspect-shot-police-lock-down-scene-of-major-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LATEST: A "major incident" took place on London Bridge on Friday when reports of shots being fired quickly developed into news that police evacuated and locked down the bridge. Eventually po</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey infects human with fatal herpes strain in first case...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkey-infects-human-fatal-herpes-20986967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The herpes B disease – which is fatal in nearly 70% of cases – was transmitted to a worker at an animal experimentation lab in Kagoshima</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot customers 'already swapping humans for AI dolls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-customers-already-swapping-20876938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A sex doll manufacturer has told Daily Star Online that its customers are already replacing human companions with AI girlfriends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screaming Heard From COWBOYS Locker Room Following Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/sports/2019/11/screaming-heard-from-cowboys-locker-room-following-lopsided-thanksgiving-day-loss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the loss, the Cowboys’ record falls to 6-6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-pop suicide sparks reckoning on revenge porn, sexual assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-kpop-suicide-reaction-20191129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea The suicide of a popular South Korean singer has prompted calls in the country to overhaul laws on sexual assault and to more harshly punish</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party like a spy: Spookstock is intel world's hush-hush bash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e4d72eb630c459aa71303b22e5a880d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sometime earlier this year, one of the most elite social events in Washington took place, but without any fanfare or news coverage. It drew about 1,800 attendees and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Bridge: Man 'shot by police after several injured in knife attack'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10450979/london-bridge-police-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLICE have shot a man after a knife attack injured several people in London Bridge today. Terrifying footage from the scene shows armed officers pointing their weapons at a man lying prone on the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburbs turn Republican disaster zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-29/2020-battleground-suburban-women-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defection of women voters has already cost the GOP control of the House and in 2020 is putting states like Arizona in play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why TV networks may be afraid of investigative stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2019-11-29/does-network-tv-news-still-want-to-be-in-the-investigative-reporting-business</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial pressures, litigation risks and the nonstop interest in Trump is putting the squeeze on enterprise reporting at TV networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOMEN IN HIJABS FIGHT OVER VACUUM CLEANER AT WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/black-friday-women-in-hijabs-fight-over-a-vacuum-cleaner-at-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While other shoppers squabble over $1.60 towels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No current Dem contender can beat Trump, BET founder says...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/No-current-Democratic-contender-can-beat-Trump-14870292.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BET founder Robert Johnson, a lifelong Democrat and America's first black billionaire, has assessed the Democratic contenders in next year's presidential election. And he doesn't like what he sees.  "If you take a snapshot today, I don't think that group is capable of beating Donald Trump, despite what the polls say," Johnson told CNBC in an interview.  "I think the president has always been in a position where it's his to lose."  Despite his politics, Johnson has praised the Trump economy, particularly a rise in African American employment, though it remains lower than white employment rates.  And he has sided with many conservatives, including Trump, in saying Democratic politicians have moved too far left.  He told CNBC he sees a "double effect" of Trump's incendiary comments and rhetoric that fires up his base. Democrats react strongly, he said, which puts the president's supporters on defense and adds to his support.  "I do not see anybody in the Democratic primary race today that is enough in the center where I believe most are the voters are, and particularly where most African Americans are," Johnson told CNBC.  Johnson sold Black Entertainment Television to Viacom in 2001, and later founded asset management firm RLJ Companies.  His wealth has drawn criticism from activists who say Johnson is out of touch with many African Americans when it comes to their access to wealth and opportunity.  "Bob Johnson is not working class. He does not reflect the issue, nor does he even seem like he has the ability to speak to the issues of the working class," Tosha Brown, co-founder of Black Voters Matter, an organization focused on increasing black voter turnout, told The Post's Eugene Scott in July.  Adrianne Shropshire, executive director of the Black Pac, a group working to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico has its strongest president in decades. Some say he's too strong...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Mexico-has-its-strongest-president-in-decades-14870283.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN MIGUEL CANOA, Mexico - Elsewhere, Latin America is burning.  In other places - Chile, Colombia, Bolivia, Ecuador - presidents are besieged by demonstrators.  But when Mexico's leader rolled into this mountain town one recent Friday, the crowds were adoring. Peasants walked for miles to greet him. Angel Roldán Pérez, a 62-year-old farmer in a red baseball cap, had recently received a singular blessing: an agricultural grant of $84.  "It was the president," the farmer insisted. "He helped us. Before, they wouldn't give us the aid. There was a lot of corruption."  A year after taking office, President Andrés Manuel López Obrador looms larger than any Mexican president in decades - setting the nation's agenda with daily news conferences, reshaping the government with a drastic overhaul of the budget, and introducing a raft of programs to help farmers, the elderly and students.  His approval ratings regularly top 60 percent, in a region where many leaders struggle to reach half that.  And yet, as the veteran leftist consolidates power, critics worry he is threatening some of Mexico's hard-won democratic gains. They say López Obrador is weakening institutions that safeguard human rights and clean elections, and is exerting more control over funding to the states.  He is steering cash grants to the poor and vulnerable, and saying he's going around bureaucrats to limit corruption. Detractors say he's using public money to build a massive base of loyalists like Roldán Pérez.  López Obrador, known by his initials AMLO, remains popular despite little progress in resolving Mexico's major problems, such as the record-high number of homicides or the stalled economy. At a moment of turmoil across Latin America, perhaps his greatest accomplishment has been to revive the hopes of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The cyborg super soldiers with mind-controlled weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7738669/US-Military-scientists-create-plan-cyborg-super-soldier-future.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a US Army report, experts from Devcom in Maryland outlined a number of possible future technologies that could be used to enhance soldiers on the battlefield by 2050.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORE CROWDS THIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/29/us-shoppers-stay-away-from-stores-spend-online-as-black-friday-begins.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowds were largely thin at retailers on the eve of Black Friday, reflecting the broader trend away from shopping at brick-and-mortar stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC COMICS Deletes Batman Poster After Chinese Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/dc/2019/11/28/dc-comics-batman-poster-china-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next month, Frank Miller's Batman saga returns with a new book titled The Dark Knight Returns: The [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Nation's Oldest High School Rivalry Ends With Massive Brawl...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/11/28/massachusetts-high-school-football-game-fight-wellesley-needham/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's oldest public high school football rivalry ended with a bench-clearing brawl on Thanksgiving. Wellesley and Needham players went after each other with just two minutes left in the game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Nightmares Prepare Brain For Real Anxiety-Provoking Situations...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dream-study-reveals-nightmares-help-us-prepare-for-real-anxiety-provoking-situations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nightmares are no fun, but a new international study on dreams finds all that nighttime fear may actually be serving a greater purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French activists try to disrupt discount shopping day...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-holidayshopping-france/block-friday-french-activists-try-to-disrupt-discount-shopping-day-idUSKBN1Y310S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists staged protests against online retailer Amazon around France on Friday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students stage global climate protests to pressure UN summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-strike/students-stage-global-climate-protests-to-pressure-un-summit-idUSKBN1Y308N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people in Asia and Europe joined rallies demanding more action on c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS DEVELOP ROBOT PERSONAL TRAINER TO COACH AT GYM...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/discover/scientists-develop-robot-personal-trainer-to-coach-at-gym-967374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robot Pepper can tell jokes, show sympathy, lean in towards the runner and change eye colour to express emotion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revered relic of the Nativity heads back to Bethlehem...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/revered-relic-nativity-heads-back-bethlehem-005312909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wooden fragment said to be from the crib of the infant Jesus arrived in Jerusalem on Friday on its way back to Bethlehem after a millenium-long absence. The relic, housed in Rome since the seventh century, was presented to the Franciscan custodians of the Holy Land at a mass in the Notre Dame Catholic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sabbath buses barrel through Israel's religious-secular rift...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b0438643de154bb89da218fcb97acce4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Tel Aviv has taken a major step to cement its status as Israel’s secular mecca, launching public transportation services on the Jewish sabbath and redrawing the lines in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publisher says he's hearing interest in nonprofit turn...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/37b60803e60d448096f76b11df5b04a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The publisher of the nation’s first daily newspaper to be granted nonprofit status says he’s since heard from a “few dozen” lawyers and news executives curious about whether the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
