<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Public sours on direction of country...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/wrong-track-public-sours-nation-s-direction-after-shutdown-n963051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty-three percent of Americans say the nation is on the wrong track, according to a new NBC News/Wall Street Journal poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic killings 'highest' in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190127-anti-semitic-killings-2018-highest-decades-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-Semitic killings in 2018 'highest' in decades: Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Should you smoke pot in front of kids?</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/ideas/2019/01/25/ideas-rosenbaum-should-you-smoke-pot-front-kids/NJlN3g1RdxqJt9qT2PKnoK/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapid legalization of marijuana raises a host of etiquette challenges. Is it an acceptable host gift? How do you consume a long-illegal drug without feeling sketchy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Arab Nation, Christians, Buddhists and Jews Emerge to Worship...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-arab-nation-christians-buddhists-and-jews-emerge-to-worship-11548594001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restrictions on religious worship have gradually loosened in the United Arab Emirates, which will display a more accommodating stance in February when it hosts Pope Francis on the first visit by a sitting pope to the Arabian Peninsula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S., Canadian fighter jets scramble to escort Russian bombers...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/27/us-air-force-canadian-fighter-jets-escort-russian-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military authorities say U.S. Air Force and Canadian fighter jets were scrambled to escort two Russian bombers that were traveling in the Arctic region near the North American coastline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles outbreak expands in northwest US...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/nation-and-world/measles-outbreak-expands-in-northwest-us-1582749/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of confirmed measles cases near Portland grew to 31 on Friday — an outbreak boosted by lower-than-normal vaccination rates in what has been called an anti-vaccination U.S. “h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet addiction spawns treatment programs...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-internet-addiction-feature/the-digital-drug-internet-addiction-spawns-u-s-treatment-programs-idUSKCN1PL0AG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Danny Reagan was 13, he began exhibiting signs of what doctors usually asso...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of vacancies for new border, immigration officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-border-patrol-hiring-20190126-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years after President Trump sought to beef-up border security by hiring 15,000 more agents and officers, his administration has thousands more vacancies than when it began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Cars Still Cheap -- But No Longer Ugly...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinese-cars-are-still-cheap-but-theyre-no-longer-ugly-11548417621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designers from Rolls-Royce, BMW and elsewhere have been recruited to give Chinese cars more style. Their creations could be headed to a dealership near you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADURO READY TO TALK...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/venezuelas-maduro-denounces-election-call-but-says-ready-to-talk-idUSKCN1PL0CR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's embattled President Nicolas Maduro rejected an international ul...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banksy drawing worth millions stolen in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/01/26/banksy-drawing-stolen-paris-france-bataclan-concert/2688956002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The image had been drawnÂ on theÂ emergency door of the Bataclan concert hall in memory of a deadly terrorist attack in 2015 that killed 90 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILLIE BROWN: Sure, I dated Kamala Harris. So what?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/Sure-I-dated-Kamala-Harris-So-what-13562972.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve been peppered with calls from the national media about my “relationship” with Kamala Harris, particularly since it became obvious that she was going to run for president. Most of them, I have not returned. Yes, we dated. It was more than 20 years ago. Yes, I may have influenced her career by appointing her to two state commissions when I was Assembly speaker. And I certainly helped with her first race for district attorney in San Francisco. I have also helped the careers of House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, Gov. Gavin Newsom, Sen. Dianne Feinstein and a host of other politicians. The difference is that Harris is the only one who, after I helped her, sent word that I would be indicted if I “so much as jaywalked” while she was D.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi students who vanish before US trial span states, decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com//news/2019/01/saudi-students-who-vanish-before-trial-span-states-decades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A university student from Saudi Arabia facing criminal charges in Ohio vanished in 1988, new evidence that the Saudi government intervened decades before it took similar action in several cases recently uncovered in Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Warren proposing asset forfeiture...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/01/elizabeth-warren-tax-plan-is-asset-forfeiture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren is not proposing a tax; she’s proposing asset forfeiture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby 'twins' have two different fathers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6636879/Baby-twins-two-DIFFERENT-fathers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twins Calder and Alexandra Berney Edwards, from London, are actually half siblings despite being born at the same time, because they don't share paternity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan military attache breaks with Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article225123050.html#storylink=topdigest_latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man identifying himself as Venezuela's military attache in Washington has broken with Nicolas Maduro and says he now will report to an opposition leader trying to wrest control of the government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media creating 'spirals of hatred'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6628233/Pope-Francis-says-social-media-turns-people-social-hermits-creates-spirals-hatred.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pope released his World Day of Social Communications message on Thursday, in which he addressed issues including misinformation online and the misuse of personal data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg calls Trump 'pretend CEO'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/427102-bloomberg-calls-trump-a-pretend-ceo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Mayor Michael Bloomberg tore into President Trump on Friday, calling him a “pretend CEO” and comparing his presidency to the classic horror film, “A Nightmare on Elm Street.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'El Chapo' trial: Three-month plunge into bloody ways of drug trade...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/el-chapo-trial-three-month-plunge-bloody-ways-013837955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the space of nearly three months, a New York jury has heard 54 witnesses deliver dramatic evidence against accused Mexican drug boss Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman. Former associates, ex-employees and a onetime mistress, most of them now inmates in American prisons, have drawn a blood-soaked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah chief warns Israel against continuing strikes in Syria... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hezbollah-leader-warns-israel-expanding-attacks-syria-215233700.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — The head of the militant Hezbollah group in Lebanon warned Israel late Saturday over its continued attacks in Syria, saying a miscalculation could drag the region into a war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life not in the cloud, waiting to be downloaded...</title>
      <link>https://cruxnow.com/world-youth-day-panama/2019/01/27/at-prayer-vigil-with-youth-pope-goes-full-on-hipster-and-techie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cruxnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis talks to young people in their lingo at World Youth Day Panama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More tunnels found...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190126214301-sqvvm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-CRISIS/HEZBOLLAH (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Hezbollah could 'for years' enter Israel, group's leader says after tunnels found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens attack on Tel Aviv...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190126210056-ixiki</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-CRISIS/HEZBOLLAH-TEL AVIV (URGENT):Israel strikes in Syria could prompt strike on Tel Aviv -Hezbollah leader</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doc About 'Satanic Temple' Draws Cheers at Sundance...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hail-satan-film-review-hero-satanists-use-the-devil-to-separate-church-and-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sundance 2019: Doc sheds light on the wildly misunderstood Satanic Temple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHULTZ TO RUN AS INDEPENDENT</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/01/howard-schultzs-independent-run-could-help-trump/581374/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howard Schultz thinks politics are broken, and may run for president as an independent. Democrats think that’s a terrible idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DEBT GREATEST THREAT'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/05/howard-schultz-21-trillion-debt-is-biggest-threat-to-us-domestically.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks' departing chairman Howard Schultz says "the economy is strong," and he gives "some" credit to Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Trump and Ocasio-Cortez use same tricks to win at politics...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/26/trump-and-ocasio-cortez-use-the-same-tricks-to-win-at-politics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re both brash outer-borough New Yorkers, each with their own notorious nickname — she’s AOC; he’s The Donald. Both shocked their parties by coming out of nowhere to win their elections, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU gives ultimatum...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tensions-rising-venezuela-ahead-rival-protests-051825945.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States pressed all nations Saturday to "stand with the forces of freedom" in Venezuela, encouraged by a tougher European line as Russia stood in the minority in backing embattled leader Nicolas Maduro. US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo made a forceful case at a special session of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHEL LEGRAND DEAD IN PARIS...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/french-oscar-winning-composer-michel-legrand-dies-aged-092734451--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prolific French composer Michel Legrand, who won three Oscars and five Grammys during a career spanning more than half a century, died aged 86 on Saturday, prompting an outpouring of tributes for his "inexhaustible genius".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve King applauded at first Iowa event since House rebuke...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e53734d921744e458acae280962edddb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRIMGHAR, Iowa (AP) — Constituents applauded Republican Rep. Steve King on Saturday at the Iowa congressman's first public event since being rebuked by his House colleagues over racist comments he had made to a newspaper earlier this month. King told the roughly 75 people who showed up for the first of 39 planned town hall meetings in his sprawling district that he doesn't adhere to a white supremacist ideology and he repeated his assertion that he's not racist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant with flesh-eating bacteria detained at US border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/82a4ade6d3174990b14315853b3f806f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — A man among a group of migrants detained in a desolate part of New Mexico near the border with Mexico has been diagnosed as infected with flesh-eating bacteria, the U.S. Border Patrol said Friday. The man was taken to a hospital in recent days after telling a federal agent that he had a growing rash on his leg, U.S. Border Patrol spokesman Carlos Antunez said. Flesh-eating bacteria are a rare condition called necrotizing fasciitis that spreads quickly and can be fatal. The bacteria usually gets into the body through a minor cut or scrape and can cause a serious infection that can destroy muscle, skin and other tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 undocumented workers at Trump golf course fired...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/231be5ff6ab44cb39dee21ee818754b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A dozen immigrant workers at one of President Donald Trump's golf clubs in New York who are in the U.S. illegally were fired this month even though managers had known about their legal status for years, a lawyer for the workers said Saturday. As the president railed during the partial government shutdown against immigrants coming into the country illegally, a manager at the Trump National Golf Club in Westchester County called a dozen immigrant workers into a room one by one Jan. 18 and fired them, said lawyer Anibal Romero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Roger Stone's case, Mueller finds crime in cover-up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/10b780d45d9e4c52b3546916347e2040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump confidant Roger Stone may be accused of lying and tampering with witnesses, but it's equally notable what he's not charged with: colluding with the Kremlin in a grand conspiracy to help Trump win the presidency in 2016. The case is the latest in a series brought by special counsel Robert Mueller that focuses on cover-ups but lays out no underlying crime. It's a familiar pattern in Washington, where scandals from Watergate to Iran-Contra and Whitewater have mushroomed into presidency-imperiling affairs due to efforts to conceal and mislead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA calls on world to 'pick a side' on Venezuela...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190126193213-fs518</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/ (WRAPUP, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 1-U.S. calls on world to 'pick a side' on Venezuela; Europeans set to recognize Guaido</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns on military intervention...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190126173103-8nbg1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/UN-NEBENZIA (URGENT):Russia says any military intervention in Venezuela should be avoided</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUNDANCE:  Michael Jackson 'gave young boy jewellery in exchange for sex acts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8283431/michael-jackson-documentary-jewellery-boys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HARROWING new Michael Jackson documentary left audience members shocked with graphic abuse claims including how he allegedly gave a young boy jewellery in exchange for sex acts. Leaving Neverland…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos gives just .0906% of wealth to charity...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/26/jeff-bezos-gives-a-pitiful-amount-of-his-160b-fortune-to-charity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the world’s richest man, charity begins — and stays — at home. Amazon founder and CEO Jeff Bezos has given only a tiny fraction of his $160 billion fortune to philanthropic causes, falling far …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor mental health can lead to physical ailments...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-01-poor-mental-health-physical-ailments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When she was 14 years old, Diana Chao began having migraines. She often felt dizzy as she walked. Sunlight seemed to pierce her skull.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot timebomb: 'AI girlfriends' could fuel birth rate collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/755708/sex-robot-ai-girlfriends-japan-birth-rate-collapse-population-kate-devlin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBD goes mainstream as bars, coffee shops add weed to menus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/25/cbd-goes-mainstream-as-consumers-dabble-with-the-cannabis-compound.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies are adding the compound from just about everything — and that should accelerate as regulations ease and consumer interest grows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials may claim another victim: Classic American motorcycle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/25/actually-young-people-really-could-kill-harley-davidson.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With sales at Harley-Davidson falling year after year, UBS analyst Robin Farley wonders if motorcycles have already had their cultural moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant Caravan Swells to 12,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/01/26/migrant-caravan-swells-to-12000-at-mexicos-southern-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ranks of a new Central American migrant caravan reportedly grew in size to more than 12,000 as of Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What exactly is Giuliani doing?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/426710-what-exactly-is-giuliani-doing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Trump's attorney losing his edge, or is it his strategic intention to muddy the waters?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts on Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Pressure-mounts-on-Venezuela-s-Maduro-as-EU-13563861.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela - President Nicolás Maduro faced increasing international pressure to step down on Saturday, as European governments warned they would recognize his chief opponent as Venezuela's leader unless a date for new elections is called within eight days. The statements from Germany, France, Spain and Britain came as the U.N. Security Council was meeting at Washington's request to discuss the economic and political crisis in Venezuela. The United States is among nearly two dozen countries that recognized opposition leader Juan Guaidó as interim leader in recent days, after Maduro was sworn in for a second term following elections riddled with fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC buzz: Trump ... vs. Hogan?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/26/politics/larry-hogan-2020-trump-challenge/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican National Committee formally kicked off the 2020 campaign season by bestowing President Donald Trump with its "undivided support" on Friday. But while the party merges its organizational efforts with the Trump campaign, there is still an expectation that someone will join the race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD: Group Of Teens Targeting Manhattan Newsstands In Violent Crime Spree...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/01/26/teens-newsstands-crime-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one instance a 39-year-old woman on West 57th Street near 10th Avenue was punched in the face. In other incident, a newsstand employee who tried to stop the teens was punched as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure builds on Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a38cb9e66f0d45bbb06f3edc2ecedc79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — The Latest on the political crisis in Venezuela (all times local): 10:55 a.m. The European Union as a whole says it could recognize opposition leader Juan Guaido as Venezeula's leader if the government doesn't announce new elections within the coming days. EU foreign policy chief Federica Mogherini said in a statement Saturday that the European bloc would intensify contacts with international partners "in the coming hours" on Venezuela's crisis. The EU urgently called for new elections, saying Venezuela's presidential vote last year was not democratic. Mogherini said "in the absence of an announcement on the organization of fresh elections with the necessary guarantees over the next days, the EU will take further actions, including on the issue of recognition of the country's leadership." Earlier Saturday, France, Germany, Britain and Spain set an eight-day deadline for calling electiondsfor recognizing Guaido's leadership. The Europeans' position opens a new front in their tensions with Russia, which strongly supports Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
