<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Test Accurately Predicts Alzheimer's Onset Within 4 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/tool-predict-alzheimers-4-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Currently, researchers say 20 to 30 percent of patients with Alzheimer's don't receive an accurate diagnosis when seeing a specialist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People With OCD 3 Times As Likely To Suffer Stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/ocd-more-likely-to-have-a-stroke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Obsessive-compulsive disorder is a common mental health condition which causes intrusive, unwanted thoughts, ideas, or sensations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmaker Previously Caught Naked Urinates on Camera During Proceedings...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/william-amos-nude-canada-virtual-legislative-session-1595751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;William Amos has stepped down from his committee positions and role as parliamentary secretary to the minister of innovation, science and industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Mansion Vying for Record-Breaking Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.mansionglobal.com/articles/historic-brooklyn-property-lists-for-30-million-vying-for-a-record-breaking-sale-227628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mansionglobal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 120-year-old mansion in Park Slope is the borough’s priciest listing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexual Abuse Lawsuit Splits GUCCI Family...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/28/a-sexual-abuse-lawsuit-splits-the-gucci-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the last few months, scenes from Lake Como in Italy, where Ridley Scott is filming of “The House of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Wanted to Turn Self In. So He Hired Helicopter...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/28/a-new-zealand-fugitive-wanted-to-turn-himself-in-so-he-hired-a-helicopter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand — For many, it would be a welcome getaway: a week’s retreat in a log cabin deep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden History of How Washington Embraced UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/05/28/ufos-secret-history-government-washington-dc-487900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, a loose group of enthusiasts—a pop singer, a real-estate magnate, a banking heir, and a terrorist interrogator—has been working to push its pet mystery into the mainstream. This year, it broke through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SolarWinds hackers targeting 150 organizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/solarwinds-hackers-are-it-again-targeting-150-organizations-microsoft-warns-n1268893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft said that Nobelium, a Russian-based hacking group, launched the phishing campaign by gaining access to a marketing account of USAID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigate 'refuse service to white people' sign at POPEYE'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kmox/news/local/refuse-service-to-white-people-sign-at-st-louis-popeyes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are asking for help to identify the person or people who posted a sign in a fast-food drive-through saying the business “will reserve the right to refuse service to white people.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Einstein was wrong? Dark matter map hints at 'broken physics' in major shake up...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1442270/einstein-wrong-dark-matter-map-challenges-theory-of-general-relativity-evg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBERT EINSTEIN'S groundbreaking theory of general relativity may have been wrong after all, scientists have announced after publishing the world's most comprehensive map of dark matter in the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani denies he urged attack on Capitol in 'trial by combat' speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/us-elections-government/ny-capitol-riot-rudy-giuliani-20210527-emnp5grb25b5rdxhw2dzmppd24-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former mayor was responding to a lawsuit filed by Rep. Eric Swalwell (D-Calif.) that accuses Giuliani and Trump of inciting the riot to prevent Congress from doing its constitutional duty of certifying the election results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS FEAR FADES IN USA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/memorial-day-awaits-how-to-stay-safe-from-covid-at-the-pool-or-beach/ar-AAKpY05?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the verge of Memorial Day weekend, people are asking whether they’re safe from COVID-19 as they cool off in the ocean or pool. Lifeguards and swim coaches are getting questions like this one from Erica Garcia of Fort Lauderdale: “Is it safe for my unvaccinated child to go into a public pool?” A new online survey of 2,000 American adults by the Pool &amp; Hot Tub Alliance found 70% plan to swim ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina posts record rise in daily covid cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527204508-9saq8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH - CORONAVIRUS/ARGENTINA:Argentina posts record rise in daily COVID-19 cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-9 dies after deputy leaves him in hot car...</title>
      <link>https://www.13wmaz.com/article/news/an-avoidable-accident-monroe-county-k-9-dies-after-deputy-leaves-him-in-hot-car/93-980d6ea2-b0cc-470c-a10c-5539e1c34e78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.13wmaz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheriff Freeman says the car is equipped with tech to alert the K9's handler if the car gets too hot. That device was unplugged because Barkley was ending his shift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientology secrets spill into open in Masterson rape case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientologys-secrets-spill-open-danny-150019818.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women who have accused Danny Masterson of rape testified that Scientology officials tried to stop them from reporting the alleged attacks to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competitor fears Musk's SPACEX could 'monopolize' space...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/competitor-fears-musks-spacex-could-163751156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launching of thousands of satellites into low Earth orbit by tech billionaire Elon Musk's SpaceX threatens the "de-facto monopolisation" of space, the head of competitor Arianespace Stephane Israel has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden pledges to tackle supply shortages as prices rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527222243-0lyxr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/BIDEN (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Biden pledges to tackle monopolies, supply shortages as prices rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDY 500 SELLS OUT; 135,000 FANS EXPECTED</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210527214612-a6w5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOTOR-INDY-INDY500/:Motor racing-Indy 500 sells out, 135,000 fans expected on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Number of smokers has reached all-time high of 1.1 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/may/27/number-of-smokers-has-reached-all-time-high-of-11-billion-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governments told to focus on stopping young from taking up habit that killed 8 million people in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two dead, 10 others missing after boat flips over off Key West... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/florida/fl-ne-mh-key-west-boat-overturned-20210527-ibnjxtf43vfovaixboclzqt57y-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people died and 10 others were missing in the ocean after a boat overturned off Key West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As US calls for focus on covid origins, China repeats speculation about American military base...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/as-us-calls-for-focus-on-covid-origins-china-repeats-speculation-about-us-military-base/ar-AAKrPGx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New allegations about ANOTHER covert Messianic Christian missionary...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/judaism/new-allegations-about-another-covert-messianic-christian-missionary-669299</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Timothy Buckles has allegedly sought to infiltrate Orthodox synagogues in the US, and posed as Jewish in Jerusalem where he lives and works</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Half Of Patients Leave Hospital In Worse Shape Than They Arrived...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-patients-leave-hospital-worse-condition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one in five patients lost so much of their physical ability they could no longer live independently after leaving the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census' 'synthetic data' worries researchers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/census-2020-technology-data-privacy-business-be938fa5db887a0ae6858dff0be217ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — First came the “noise” — small errors the U.S. Census Bureau decided to introduce into the 2020 census data to protect participants' privacy. Now the bureau is looking into “synthetic data,” manipulating the numbers widely used for economic and demographic research, to obscure the identities of people who provided information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Mulls Permanent 10 p.m. Liquor Sale Curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcchicago.com/news/local/new-proposal-would-impose-permanent-10-p-m-liquor-sale-curfew-in-chicago-stores/2520063/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago’s liquor sale curfew, which was first implemented during the coronavirus pandemic, could become permanent for some business owners under a new proposal from Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican megadonor Foster Friess dead at 81...</title>
      <link>https://trib.com/news/state-and-regional/govt-and-politics/gop-megadonor-foster-friess-dies-at-81/article_82e2198a-f23d-5d63-a1a6-61f330fe9891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investor ran for governor in Wyoming in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm to Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcconnecticut.com/news/local/emanuel-garcetti-burns-offered-ambassadorships-sources/2497165/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcconnecticut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has decided on his picks for key ambassadors to China, Japan and India, and expects to announce them in the coming weeks, NBC News reported Thursday, citing three administration officials. Former Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel has been offered the role of U.S. ambassador to Japan. NBC News reported in February that Biden was considering Emanuel, a former chief of staff in the Obama White…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France reimposes strict curbs on travel from UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210527-france-reimposes-strict-covid-curbs-on-travel-from-uk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France reimposes strict Covid curbs on travel from UK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetically modified salmon head to dinner plates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/whole-foods-market-inc-lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-technology-a4ef4f24801f62ac65918e4560d7eb8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — The inaugural harvest of genetically modified salmon began this week after the pandemic delayed the sale of the first such altered animal to be cleared for human consumption in the United States, company officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians call for 'Day of Rage' on Friday...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/palestinians-call-for-day-of-rage-on-friday-669435</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF Preparing for Renewed Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-israel-is-unsure-it-deterred-hamas-and-the-army-is-preparing-for-renewed-fighting-1.9851058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-pandemic NYC laid bare...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9621133/New-York-Citys-pandemic-aftermath-laid-bare-homelessness-mental-illness-crime-escalate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive DailyMail.com photos show an influx of homeless people on the streets as Manhattan struggles to get back on its feet after the coronavirus pandemic cut off its lifeline of tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS HITS 7-YEAR-HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/27/business/memorial-day-gas-prices/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nasty surprise awaits the 34 million drivers expected to hit US roads this Memorial Day weekend — the highest gas prices in seven years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicious Brawl Erupts At ASTROS Game...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/no-love-lost-fans-brawl-during-dodgers-astros-game-wednesday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been a hostility between the two teams since the sign-stealing scandal broke in January of 2020, when Major League Baseball revealed that the Astros cheated during their 2017 title run in which they beat the Dodgers in the World Series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimon Sharpens Criticism of Biden Tax Hike Proposal...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dimon-sharpens-criticism-biden-tax-182949093.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. Chief Executive Officer Jamie Dimon has twice in this hearing before a congressional committee sharply criticized President Joe Biden’s proposed tax hikes, which are aimed at people making more than $400,000 and at corporations.He has previously questioned them, but today said that that level of tax increases would be four times bigger than the GOP’s 2017 tax cuts and called that “a mistake.”“The tax increase is actually four times what the tax decrease was from 2017,” he said. “You all know the phrase the devil is in the details, well the details here are all that matter, not the top line of 28%.”His main warning is about global competitiveness. He warns of capital going overseas and other economic problems and says it would make his bank less competitive globally.“If you want to have a healthy, growing, competitive America against the rest of the world, you need a global, competitive tax rate,” he said. “It would be detrimental to a lot of companies, it would push a lot of capital overseas.”Dimon isn’t against all taxes. In yesterday’s Senate Banking hearing he said the U.S. should impose a carbon tax.For more on Wall Street CEOs Testify Before U.S. House Committee, click here for our TOPLive blog.More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever Colorado River water shortage now almost certain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/27/weather/lake-mead-colorado-river-shortage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Lake Mead sunk below a key threshold this week, new projections show continued declines in the key reservoir's supply that could trigger a shortage declaration and water cuts in some states next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-styled satanist beheaded cellmate, but guards didn't notice...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/self-styled-satanist-beheaded-his-cellmate-in-central-california-prison-but-guards-didnt-notice-reports-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convicted killers shared the same cell at Corcoran State Prison. But on the morning of March 9, 2019, only one was still alive. Jaime Osuna, 31, had decapitated and dissected the body of his ce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientology secrets spill into open in Masterson rape case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/celebrity/scientology-s-secrets-spill-into-open-in-danny-masterson-rape-case/ar-AAKrWqd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women who have accused Danny Masterson of rape testified that Scientology officials tried to stop them from reporting the alleged attacks to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Making Play for Puerto Rico?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-republicans-think-gop-can-win-in-puerto-rico/ar-AAKrBlp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rick Scott believes Puerto Rico will achieve statehood — and the Florida Republican rejects arguments by some in his party that the Caribbean island territory would elect Democrats to Congress in perpetuity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel vs. Hamas was world's first AI war...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/gaza-news/guardian-of-the-walls-the-first-ai-war-669371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IDF used artificial intelligence and supercomputing during the last conflict with Hamas in the Gaza Strip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No longer confined to fringe, theories move mainstream...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20210527-no-longer-confined-to-the-fringe-ufo-theories-move-into-the-mainstream</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subject of UFOs in the US is getting serious treatment from mainstream media and heavyweight politicians. Next month Congress is set to review a report from the director of national intelligence…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON unveils 'ZenBooth' for overwhelmed employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/amazon-zenbooth-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online retail giant Amazon has unveiled a small booth designed to let overwhelmed warehouse employees "focus on their ... well-being."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors treating Trump Org like it's the mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-york-prosecutors-are-treating-the-trump-organization-like-it-s-the-mob/ar-AAKrT18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much like the mob, the Trump Organization is run by family members and loyalists who've been around for decades. Prosecutors want them to "flip."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will this be the summer of sex?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20210525-are-we-heading-towards-a-summer-of-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that vaccines are rolling out, some are trumpeting plans to make up for a year of isolation. So, is a hedonistic summer in the offing? Not so fast, say experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods' golf future cloudy after crash: 'More painful than anything'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/27/tiger-woods-rehab-process-is-the-most-painful-thing-hes-experienced/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods has never experienced pain like this before. As the golf icon continues his rehab and recovery after a horrifying single-car crash in February, he discussed the post-accident process in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNICKS Fan Banned After Spitting On HAWKS Player...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/trae-young-spit-knicks-fan-banned-indefinitely/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Knicks have announced that the fan who spit on Hawks guard Trae Young has been banned indefinitely from MSG.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest Crypto Conference Coming To Miami...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/worlds-largest-bitcoin-conference-miami-wynwood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you bought into the cryptocurrency craze yet or is it all a bit too confusing? Well get ready because Miami is about to be taken over by Bitcoin 2021, the world’s largest cryptocurrency conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC presenter dies from blood clot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tv/15088900/lisa-shaw-dead-44-bbc-presenter-covid-vaccine-astrazeneca/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “BRILLIANT” BBC radio presenter died in hospital aged 44 after having the AstraZeneca Covid vaccine, her family said today. Lisa Shaw’s devastated relatives told of their heartb…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Tanning salon customer finds dead body on sun bed after woman had two-hour session...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2969273/tan-salon-customer-dead-body-sun-bed-austria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SHOCKED tanning salon customer found a dead woman on a sun bed after she had visited the solarium in Austria for a two-hour session. The client made the grim discovery of the 50-year-old woman in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OOOP:  LeBron accidentally reveals top secret  APPLE headphones...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2968402/lebron-james-beats-earbuds-apple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBRON James has been pictured wearing what appear to be Apple’s highly anticipated “Beats Studio Buds” headphones. Rumours about the Beats earbuds have been circulating for a whi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTuber arrested for tying dog to helium balloons...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/youtuber-arrested-tying-dog-helium-24198814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTuber Guarav Sharma has been detained under animal cruelty laws after tying his pet Pomeranian dog to a bunch of helium balloons and letting it float away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Walsh: My Radio Show Was Canceled By Trump-Supporting Boss!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/radio/just-in-joe-walsh-says-his-radio-show-was-canceled-by-big-trumper-network-boss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never-Trumper Joe Walsh said on Wednesday he lost his radio show because his network is run by a Donald Trump supporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS workers say they are treated like 'coffee-making robots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/starbucks-workers-say-they-are-treated-like-coffee-making-robots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people who work at Starbucks say customers are ordering increasingly complicated drinks that are sapping their will to continue working at the coffee giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Defund police' candidate has car stolen...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/atlanta-defund-the-police-backer-has-car-stolen-by-kids-in-broad-daylight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Atlanta city councilman – who is aiming to be the city's next mayor – had his car stolen by children in broad daylight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime-Tracking App CITIZEN Scraps Plans For 'On-Demand' Police Force...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/citizen-app-peter-thiel-palantir-security-force/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company tested out giving users the ability to summon their own personal police force. This week it pulled the plug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Philly Steakhouse Ripped Over $100 Minimum Per Person Requirement...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/26/philadelphia-steak-48s-100-minimum-policy-social-media-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fancy steakhouse has enacted a strict dining policy that has social media sizzling with criticism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR TRAVEL BOOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/memorial-day-travel-airline-industry-avelo-breeze/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline travel expert says the industry is "recovering faster and better than many expected."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case for Swimming in Wild...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/05/roger-deakin-waterlog-why-wild-swimming/618974/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man’s journey through public waterways—whether sparkling or dirty or algae-filled—challenges us to look differently at the commons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS-ROYCE Boat Tail May Be Most Expensive New Car in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/rolls-royce-boat-tail-may-120200931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 19-foot convertible features crockery from Christofle of Paris, a proper refrigerator and a giant parasol at the back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Wing Scarcity Forcing Restaurants To Pull From Menus...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/05/27/chicken-wing-shortage-denver-colorado-restaurants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Denver-area restaurants are removing items from menus or even temporarily closing because they don't have enough chicken wings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: First-Born More Likely To Suffer Heart Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/how-many-siblings-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First-born children generally had a lower risk of non-fatal cardiovascular and coronary events than their younger siblings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys adopt 'accent' of other species when in shared territory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/may/27/monkeys-adopt-accent-of-other-species-when-in-shared-territory-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian Amazon primates found to adapt their calls to get along better with their neighbours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long bath almost as good as long run...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/may/26/hot-tub-health-kick-why-a-long-bath-is-almost-as-good-for-you-as-a-long-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have discovered that prolonged immersion in a piping hot bath has many of the same medical benefits as aerobic exercise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Public transit worker fatally shoots 9, then kills self at San Jose rail yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/active-shooter-near-northern-california-rail-yard-authorities-say-n1268623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A public transit employee, Samuel Cassidy, opened fire on co-workers at the Santa Clara Valley Transportation Authority before taking his own life, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: WIZARDS Star Restrained After Fan Dumps Popcorn On Him...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/05/26/russell-westbrook-sixers-fan-popcorn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westbrook had to be restrained by multiple people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to Propose $6 Trillion Budget...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/27/biden-to-propose-6-trillion-budget-to-boost-middle-class-and-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden will propose a $6 trillion budget on Friday that would take the United States to its</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
