<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley worker was Ukrainian mom lying dead on street...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/california/article/Silicon-Valley-tech-worker-was-the-Ukrainian-mom-16990037.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee of a Silicon Valley company and her children are the subjects of a photo so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rep. charged with driving on revoked license for 2nd time...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/gop-congressman-madison-cawthorn-charged-with-driving-on-a-revoked-license-for-2nd-time-court-dates-set/ar-AAUQU6M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag Queen Who Says Biden 'Senile' To Perform At Dem Retreat...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/drag-queen-who-says-biden-is-a-senile-white-supremacist-scheduled-to-perform-at-dem-retreat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drag queen invited to perform for congressional Democrats during their policy retreat referred to President Joe Biden as "senile" and a "white supremacist" and called his voters "dim-witted."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Mouse Gave Birth to Litter of Baby Mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/virgin-mouse-gave-birth-litter-215100395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yanchang WeiThe bible is no longer the only place where you’ll read testimonies about a virgin birth. In a new study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences on Monday, researchers at Shanghai Jiao Tong University report the results of a new experiment where they were able to make a female mouse give birth to a baby mouse that grew from an unfertilized egg—something that has never before been accomplished in mammals. More than just a story of some eccentric scientists try</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-feminist political novice...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220309-anti-feminist-political-novice-south-korea-s-new-president-yoon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korea's new president-elect is a political novice who shot to public attention as a prosecutor for his uncompromising investigations into some of the country's most high-profile corruption scan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China state media buying FACEBOOK ads pushing Moscow propaganda....</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/chinas-state-media-meta-facebook-ads-russia-623763df-c5fb-46e4-a6a8-36b607e1b672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State media outlets are finding ways around social media platforms' efforts to limit them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Pays Zucker To Go Away Quietly...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/cnn-jeff-zucker-deal-resignation-warnermedia-jason-kilar-allison-gollust-1234973547/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE, updated with more details: Jeff Zucker has finalized a deal with WarnerMedia over the former CNN chief’s sudden fall from grace last month. Details of the confidential package are …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look inside 1st 'safe injection site' in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/inside-nyc-supervised-drug-injection-sites-7ad93117d1566fda53909c0f70984d1b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Jose Collado settled in at a clean white table in a sunlit room, sang a few bars and injected himself with heroin. After years of shooting up on streets and rooftops, he was in one of the first two facilities in the country where local officials are allowing illegal drug use in order to make it less deadly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USING THERMOBARIC ROCKETS</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-russia-admits-using-thermobaric-26426880</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has confirmed it has used the strictly regulated thermobaric rockets in its ongoing attack of Ukraine, the Ministry of Defence tweeted today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget mammoths, study shows how to resurrect Christmas Island rats...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220309-forget-mammoths-study-shows-how-to-resurrect-christmas-island-rats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ever since the movie Jurassic Park, the idea of bringing extinct animals back to life has captured the public's imagination -- but what might scientists turn their attention towards first?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piracy Icon LIMEWIRE Coming Back -- As NFT Marketplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3n85w/piracy-icon-limewire-is-coming-back-but-as-an-nft-marketplace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You're going to hate this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Chapek Finally Slams Law...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/disney-bob-chapek-dont-say-gay-florida-1234974584/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walt Disney CEO Bob Chapek finally came out swinging against Florida’s so-called “Don’t Say Gay” bill, telling shareholders at the annual meeting today that the company had always opposed it but op…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Besieged city buries dead in mass grave...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-af9477cd69d067c34e0e336c05d765cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — Under steady Russian bombardment, workers in Ukraine's besieged southern port city of Mariupol are hastily and unceremoniously burying scores of dead Ukrainian civilians and soldiers in a mass grave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 People Now Living in Phoenix's Exploding Tent City...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3n8wj/phoenix-homeless-tent-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A homeless encampment in Phoenix near the state’s largest shelter has more than doubled in just two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea Conservative Yoon Wins Presidential Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-03-09/s-korea-conservative-opposition-candidate-yoon-wins-presidential-election-yonhap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don plane made emergency landing after weekend speech to donors...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/09/trump-plane-emergency-landing-00015749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plane was in the air between 20 and 30 minutes before one of the four engines failed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA officials raid preschool, interview 2-year-olds over mask policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/california-officials-raided-preschool-interviewed-2-year-olds-over-mask-policies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California state regulators conducted an investigation at a Southern California preschool and privately interviewed children as young as 2 without their parents’ consent about their masking practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So many Canadian fighters in Ukraine, they have their own battalion...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/exclusive-so-many-canadian-fighters-in-ukraine-they-have-their-own-battalion-source-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas theft on rise as prices skyrocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/gas-theft-on-the-rise-as-gas-prices-skyrocket</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to AAA, the average price for a gallon of gas is $5.34. With prices so high, reports of stolen gasoline have also gone up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New tech could pull cars over in emergencies...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/consumer-news/2022/03/updated-tech-could-pull-cars-over-call-first-responders-in-emergencies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-tech systems in new cars that can watch drivers behind the wheel to make sure they’re paying attention are taking another leap forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd into few remaining trains and planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/angry-over-invasion-of-ukraine-and-fearing-crackdown-russians-trying-to-move-abroad-crowd-into-few-remaining-trains-and-planes/ar-AAUQrPf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diller denies insider trading...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/09/barry-diller-denies-insider-trading-on-microsoft-activision-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barry Diller, David Geffen and Alex von Furstenberg made large bets on Activision Blizzard stock options before an announced purchase by Microsoft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans May Have to Say Goodbye to Steak and Burgers as Beef Costs Rise...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-may-goodbye-steak-burgers-160603348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Americans could be cutting steaks and burgers from their diets as inflation soars, if beef-packer profit margins are any indication. Most Read from BloombergChina Warns U.S. Over Forming Pacific NATO, Backing TaiwanOwners Fear Planes ‘Are Gone Forever’ After Russia Shields Them From SeizureUkraine Update: Firms Exit Russia, Fitch Sees ‘Imminent’ DefaultBiden to Sign Crypto Order as Firms Face Sanctions PressureChina Pushes Conspiracy Theory About U.S. Labs in UkraineProcessors lik</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How journalists decide which images from Ukraine are too awful to publish...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-journalists-decide-which-images-from-ukraine-are-too-awful-to-publish/ar-AAUPFko?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUTFELD:  Corporate media working on emotions for profit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fox-news-reporter-rebukes-greg-gutfeld-for-saying-media-wants-e2-80-98emotional-response-e2-80-99-in-ukraine-coverage/ar-AAUQomy?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-year-old gets in cane battle with robber...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/91-year-old-gets-in-cane-battle-with-robber-in-brooklyn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 91-year-old used his cane to defend himself in an attack by a robber who was attacking him with his own cane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA BOMBS MATERNITY WARD</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/09/ukraine-childrens-hospital-bombed-in-mariupol-by-russian-forces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials said they did not know the numbers of casualties from the latest attack on the city that the Red Cross had said was already looking “apocalyptic.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns pandemic 'far from over'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/two-years-warns-pandemic-far-163730799.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic is far from over, the WHO's leader insisted Wednesday, two years after he first used the term to wake the world up to the emerging threat of Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA BOMBS MATERNITY WARD</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4856683/women-children-feared-dead-russian-maternity-hospital-mariupol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOMEN and children are feared dead after a Russian airstrike destroyed a maternity hospital in the besieged city of Mariupol, Ukraine has claimed. President Volodymyr Zelenskyy claimed children wer…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA:  GOING TO GET UGLY</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/03/08/1085155440/cia-director-putin-is-angry-and-frustrated-likely-to-double-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIA Director William Burns says Russia's invasion of Ukraine has fallen far short of Vladimir Putin's expectations. Burns now predicts weeks of "ugly" fighting for control of Ukraine's cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF THE DIGITAL DOLLAR:  Biden takes big step toward government-backed crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/crypto/us-government-digital-currency-rcna19248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is throwing its support behind further study and development of what would be known as a U.S. Central Bank Digital Currency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6  committee tracing every dollar raised and spent based on Trump claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inside-the-jan-6-committee-e2-80-99s-effort-to-trace-every-dollar-raised-and-spent-based-on-trump-e2-80-99s-false-election-claims/ar-AAUNKoA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: Woman ran 'Russian propaganda center' in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/fbi-nyc-russian-propaganda-center-founder-charged</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities accused a woman who has citizenship in both Russia and the U.S. of founding what prosecutors described as a "Russian propaganda center" in New York City using funding from the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOT MISSILES TO POLAND</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10591379/Poland-gives-MIG-29-planes-hand-Ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. on Tuesday evening announced that it was sending two Patriot missile batteries to Poland to shore up NATO's defenses amid the war in neighboring Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems look for cover...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/597429-democrats-look-for-cover-on-rising-gas-prices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are looking for ways to lower gas prices, which have skyrocketed in the wake of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine and could rise further as the U.S. and other countries move to ban Russian imports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food crisis grows as spiralling prices spark export bans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/food-crisis-grows-spiralling-prices-122859370.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A global food crisis sparked by Russia's invasion of Ukraine escalated on Wednesday as Indonesia tightened curbs on palm oil exports, adding to a growing list of key producing countries seeking to keep vital food supplies within their borders. The conflict in Ukraine is threatening global grain production, the supply of edible oils and fertiliser exports, sending basic commodity prices rocketing and mirroring the crisis in energy markets. Palm oil is the world's most widely used vegetable oil and is used in the manufacture of many products including biscuits, margarine, laundry detergents and chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies FOX motion to dismiss defamation suit by election-tech company...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/judge-denies-fox-news-motion-to-dismiss-defamation-suit-by-election-tech-company-smartmatic/ar-AAUPdBF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oligarch renounces citizenship, saying 'everything Putin touches dies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Oligarch-renounces-Russian-citizenship-saying-16988610.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV - Russian-Israeli oligarch Leonid Nevzlin announced on Tuesday that he planned...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies FOX motion to dismiss defamation suit by election-tech company...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/smartmatic-can-pursue-election-rigging-claims-against-fox-news-giuliani-2022-03-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming that Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.S. presidential election to favor Democrat Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZILLOW: Record number cities have home listings that top $1 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/zillow-record-number-of-us-cities-have-home-listings-that-top-241-million/ar-AAUPkfc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THIS IS OUR LIVES'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10594079/Kamala-takes-Poland-Zelensky-urges-stop-ping-pong-send-war-planes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zelensky accused the U.S. of playing games with people's lives after the Pentagon poured cold water on plan to get fighter jets to Ukraine hours before Kamala Harris departed for Poland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF of Americans quit jobs last year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/09/53-percent-of-americans-quit-jobs-last-year-to-make-a-career-change-heres-how-to-do-the-same.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to quit during the "Great Resignation" and switch careers, this is what experts want you to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animation Guild Condemns DISNEY 'Failed' Response...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/animation-guild-disney-bob-chapek-dont-say-gay-bill-1235107354/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is one thing to say that you 'unequivocally stand in support of our LGBTQ+ employees, their families, and their communities.' It’s quite another for you to stand silent while this scurrilous piece of homophobic legislation passes," the guild said in a statement Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devout Jews in Ukraine stay to pray and await 'apocalypse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220309-devout-jews-in-ukraine-stay-to-pray-and-await-apocalypse-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a synagogue in the western Ukrainian city of Uman, two people are worshipping in the cold and darkness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine's Next Ordeal: Temps Down to 20 Below...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ukraine-forecast-of-freezing-temperatures-endangers-russian-troops-and-complicates-ukrainians-escape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cold snap will turn Russian military hardware into “40-ton freezers,” say analysts as the senseless war rages into its second week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Backed Candidates Getting Creamed in Multiple High-Profile Races, Polls Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-backed-candidates-are-getting-totally-creamed-in-multiple-high-profile-races-polls-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New polls from high-profile statewide races suggest former President Donald Trump's clout on the Right is greatly diminishing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'King Kong' monkey snatches helpless seagull out of sky and bashes it to death on pole...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/king-kong-monkey-bashed-seagull-26422015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING, DISTRESSING CONTENT: The monkey's actions were compared to an iconic scene from Hollywood blockbuster King Kong, after it was seen grabbing a seagull and smashing it on a pole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party like it's 2019! Florida expects triple amount of visitors for Spring Break...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10591527/Spring-Breakers-begins-Fort-Lauderdale-expects-double-not-triple-visitors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is readying itself for thousands of college students to fly in during Spring Break over the next few weeks, as new record levels of attendance are expected for the first time since the start of COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians flee Putin's crackdown as Ukraine invasion reshapes Moscow's future...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/russians-flee-putins-crackdown-ukraine-invasion-reshapes-moscows-futur-rcna19004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some fear a new “Iron Curtain” may be closing as the Russian president leaves his country deeply isolated both culturally and economically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food crisis grows as spiralling prices spark export bans...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-food/food-crisis-grows-as-spiralling-prices-spark-export-bans-idUSKBN2L61B5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A global food crisis sparked by Russia's invasion of Ukraine escalated on Wednesday as Indonesia tightened curbs on palm oil exports, adding to a growing list of key producing countries seeking to keep vital food supplies within their borders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America's trans politicians gain ground in a dangerous region...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-latam-politics-transgender/latin-americas-trans-politicians-gain-ground-in-a-dangerous-region-idUSKBN2L613P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Erika Hilton decided to run for political office in South America's biggest city in 2020, she had no idea she would receive more votes than any other female candidate to win a city council seat in Brazil that year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin wanted to weaken West. He's done opposite...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/09/russia-ukraine-putin-always-wanted-to-weaken-west-hes-done-the-opposite.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin's invasion of Ukraine has managed to unite and strengthen the international community with most of its members condemning Russia's actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE TO GET NATO JETS?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-poland-kamala-harris-germany-migration-dbcf0e0b100b0cc4d5b28d22dbcc69f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Vice President Kamala Harris’ trip to Warsaw to thank Poland for taking in hundreds of thousands of Ukrainians fleeing Russia’s invasion took an unexpected turn before she even left Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Secret To Healthy Aging -- Optimism...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/healthy-aging-and-optimism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers looked at how optimism impacts a person's health and found that staying positive helps people interpret stressful situations differently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden order to explore digital dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cryptocurrency-biden-executive-order-digital-dollar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's exploring the establishment of a U.S. Central Bank Digital Currency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changed Itineraries, Higher Fares: How War Affecting Travel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/09/changed-itineraries-higher-fares-how-the-war-in-ukraine-is-affecting-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as the travel industry was seeking to climb out of a two-year depression, Russia’s assault on Ukraine has scrambled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacino on 'GODFATHER' at 50: It's Taken Me Lifetime to Accept It and Move on...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/09/al-pacino-on-the-godfather-its-taken-me-a-lifetime-to-accept-it-and-move-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s hard to imagine “The Godfather” without Al Pacino. His understated performance as Michael Corleone, who became a respectable war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban warfare 'nightmare' looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.rfi.fr/en/urban-warfare-nightmare-looms-if-russia-enters-ukraine-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rfi.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next step in Russia's invasion of Ukraine could lead to urban warfare, an immense challenge for even numerically superior armies with deadly consequences for civilians caught up in the fighting,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iron curtain descends on Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-new-iron-curtain-descends-on-russia-amid-its-invasion-of-ukraine/ar-AAUPC0y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNKIN' manager fatally punched customer after called  n-word. He was sentenced to house arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-dunkin-e2-80-99-manager-fatally-punched-a-customer-after-being-called-the-n-word-he-was-sentenced-to-house-arrest/ar-AAUPrg9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking gas prices sting drivers nationwide, tapping pocketbooks and patience...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/spiking-gas-prices-sting-drivers-nationwide-tapping-pocketbooks-and-patience/ar-AAUNJ3P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela frees two imprisoned Americans after high-level talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20220309-venezuela-frees-two-americans-after-us-officials-visit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela released two jailed U.S. citizens on Tuesday in an apparent goodwill gesture toward the Biden administration following a visit to Caracas by a high-level U.S. delegation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border authorities find 52 reptiles hidden in man's clothing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-oddities-lizards-snakes-california-06dd6da23ce434019c5905a81e76bbd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — A man who tried to slither past U.S. border agents in California had 52 lizards and snakes hidden in his clothing, authorities said Tuesday. The man was driving a truck when he arrived at the San Ysidro border crossing with Mexico on Feb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion slowed -- but not stopped...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-moscow-world-war-ii-81b2f12c177810ee8fef7c4ce832fd6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Two weeks into its war in Ukraine, Russia has achieved less and struggled more than anticipated at the outset of the biggest land conflict in Europe since World War II. But the invading force of more than 150,000 troops retains large and possibly decisive advantages in firepower as they bear down on key cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chernobyl plant suffers 'blackout'; Fears of radiation leak...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4850584/chernobyl-safeguard-system-ukraine-at-risk-russian-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Chernobyl nuclear power plant has suffered a “complete blackout” sparking fears of a radiation leak disaster after Russia disconnected the site from the national grid. Ukraine’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using stealth drone fleet 'The Punisher'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/ukrainians-using-stealth-drones-wipe-26413916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drones only have a 2.2m wingspan but can carry up to three explosives, and are being used to take out supply lines up to 50km behind enemy lines in a significant blow to Russian invaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ALL IN': PUTIN BETS PRESIDENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/putin-diplomacy-russia-ukraine-war-demands-invasion-rcna19029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The challenge is this: Putin continues to press this aggression, and that is why we are concerned this could go on for some time,” a State Department spokesperson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian forces tighten grip on Kyiv gateway as residents describe growing perils...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russian-forces-tighten-grip-on-kyiv-gateway-as-residents-describe-growing-perils/ar-AAUOa6R?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC says avoid travel to New Zealand, Hong Kong and Thailand as corona cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cdc-says-avoid-travel-to-new-zealand-hong-kong-and-thailand-as-covid-cases-surge/ar-AAUN6qU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSKY:  Elon asks court to scrap SEC agreement over his tweets, claiming was 'forced' to enter into it ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-asks-court-to-scrap-sec-agreement-over-his-tweets-claiming-he-was-forced-to-enter-into-it/ar-AAUNKp9?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO CRACKDOWN?</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2022/03/08/lawmakers-fear-cryptocurrencies-could-be-backdoor-for-sanctioned-rubles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers from both parties are worried that cryptocurrencies could help Russians use to evade western sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT anchor quits, warns world on brink of nuclear war...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/maria-baronova-fears-were-on-the-brink-of-a-nuclear-war-after-quitting-russian-state-run-media-over-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I wouldn’t lose my salary and job if I was sure that we are going to be alive for many years,’ Baronova told Fox News Digital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky echoes Churchill in historic address to UK Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1577662/ukraine-russia-war-zelensky-house-of-commons-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INSPIRATIONAL Volodymyr Zelensky invoked Winston Churchill with a vow to fight Russian forces in the air, at sea and on land during a moving historic address to Parliament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUKE CONCERNS RISING</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2022/03/concern-rising-putin-could-use-nuclear-weapons/362913/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian “escalate to de-escalate” doctrine suggests Putin is thinking the unthinkable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA BANS RUSSIAN OIL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/us-expected-to-announce-ban-on-russian-oil-as-soon-as-today-nbc-news-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came as Western-allied nations work to sever Moscow from the global economy as punishment for its ongoing war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside high-tech sex parties, S&amp;M dungeons of Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/inside-the-high-tech-sex-parties-and-sm-dungeons-of-silicon-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her new book, “Special Characters: My Adventures with Tech’s Titans and Misfits,” Laurie Segall writes about the high-tech sex secrets of the Silicon Valley tech world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TO THE RESCUE: Beijing Considers Buying Stakes in Russian Energy, Commodity Firms...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/china-considers-buying-stakes-in-russian-energy-commodity-firms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
