<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>POLL: PETE SURGES IN IOWA</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2019/10/21/iowa-caucuses-pete-buttigieg-elizabeth-warren-joe-biden-top-poll/4025797002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg has surged within striking distance of former vice president Joe Biden and Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren in Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX to sell another $2 billion of junk bonds as it braces for onslaught of competition...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/netflix-to-sell-another-2-billion-of-junk-bonds-as-it-braces-for-onslaught-of-competition-2019-10-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix Inc. is planning to raise another $2 billion in debt as it moves to raise the financing needed for new content as the battle for streaming customers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules prosecutors can't show 'GODFATHER' clip at Roger Stone trial...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/466715-judge-rules-prosecutors-cant-show-godfather-clip-at-roger-stones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors cannot play a clip from “The Godfather, Part II” in court during the trial of political consultant Roger Stone, a District Court judge reportedly ruled Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulvaney getting second-guessed... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c8c82d3b0de44756bfe86393412081ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For Mick Mulvaney, the hits just keep on coming. First, President Donald Trump's acting chief of staff stirred up a tempest by acknowledging that the administration had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strunk  near Love Field Airport! </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/889b2a0a3a354250817a304a657dfa9e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — A tornado tore homes and businesses apart in a densely populated area of Dallas, where only minor injuries were reported, but a person was killed by a falling tree in northwest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online ordering boom gives rise to virtual restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6da0840ac53748199a2fdbb945143aae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Frato's Pizza looks like a typical family restaurant, with its black-and-white checkered floor and red chairs. But in the kitchen, the cooks are whipping up dishes for four other...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelted With Fruit and Stones...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f13bf4d38c340499cbc48abdca144eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AKCAKALE, Turkey (AP) — Angry over the U.S. withdrawal, residents of a Kurdish-dominated Syrian city hurled potatoes at departing American military vehicles as they drove by on Monday. Defense...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Chinese outnumber wealthy Americans for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rich-chinese-outnumber-wealthy-americans-073000138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of rich Chinese has surpassed the count of wealthy Americans for the first time as both countries keep churning out millionaires, a study by Credit Suisse showed. The Swiss bank&amp;#39;s annual wealth survey released on Monday found 100 million Chinese ranked in the global top 10% as of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Point cadet -- and rifle -- missing since Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/10/21/missing-west-point-cadet-rifle/4051011002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cadet is not believed to be a danger to the public but may be a danger to himself, according to a West Point news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Drug Cartel Just Defeated Mexican Military In Battle...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/10/21/a-drug-cartel-just-defeated-the-mexican-military-in-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears Growing Among Mainland Chinese Living in City...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fears-growing-among-mainland-chinese-122040653.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As Hong Kong’s historic protests become increasingly violent, mainland Chinese living in the city are becoming increasingly fearful.Min, who moved to Hong Kong from the mainland in 1995 and now runs his own hedge fund, said the startling escalation in mayhem prompted him to tell his children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mumbling Assange Tells Judge He 'Can't Think Properly...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mumbling-assange-tells-judge-t-121202397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A mumbling Julian Assange told a London judge that he didn’t understand a court proceeding Monday as the WikiLeaks founder complained that his isolation in a British prison made it hard to fight the U.S. extradition case against him.In rambling, often inaudible comments, the 48-year-old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong descends into chaos again as protesters defy ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0cd8552fc239467993222f2434429f54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Hong Kong officials apologized to Muslim leaders Monday after riot police sprayed a mosque and bystanders with a water cannon while trying to contain turbulent weekend...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Disapproval hits 59%...</title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERCOW BLOCK?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/10179746/brexit-vote-boris-johnson-speaker-bercow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson believes he has the numbers to pass a Brexit vote today but “poor man’s Cromwell” John Bercow may block it, it emerged this morning. The Remainer Speaker will decide…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screaming devotees covered in burning hot wax in brutal penance ritual...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10179568/screaming-devotees-hot-wax-criminals-sins-black-christ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of devotees will take to the streets of Panama today to celebrate the festival of “Cristo Negro,” or the Black Christ – the “patron saint of criminals.” The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's fastest car' unveiled -- Can reach speeds over 500mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/worlds-fastest-car-unveiled-can-20666278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The car, which has been developed by the Bloodhound Land Speed Record (BLSR) team, can travel at 500 miles/hour and could break the world land speed record in 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Mentions of Govt as Top Problem Near Record High...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/267581/mentions-government-top-problem-near-record-high.aspx </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump's dealings with Ukraine, 34% of Americans cite government as the most important problem currently facing the U.S., marking an 11-point increase since September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANA DEL REY: It's 'so-what culture'.  I f*cked you over? So what?</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/entertainment/lana-del-rey-on-donald-trump-culture-958597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer has criticised the US president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans embrace wisdom of being 'nobody'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Americans-embrace-the-wisdom-of-being-nobody-14547616.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American fascination with celebrity is strong. So strong that, as my Spanish wife has noted, even our serial killers get flattering biopics. ("Ted Bundy - a monster, yes, but what a brilliant, handsome guy!")  The president of the United States rose to public consciousness not through a single minute of public service but rather via reality television. In a world dominated by social media, people increasingly don't even have to do anything to be sought-after public figures - they can be famous simply for being famous, as the saying goes. In 1968, when Andy Warhol predicted a future in which everyone would be world-famous for 15 minutes, it sounded ridiculous; today it sounds increasingly plausible.  And fame is all we really want, isn't it? All the twisted, celebrity-obsessed aspects of American culture and politics are just a mirror of our own unfulfilled desires to be loved and admired by millions, right? Wrong. The truth is that, despite our prurient interest in celebrities, the overwhelming majority of people do not want to be famous, and the minority of people who truly desire fame are abnormal.  Consider the evidence. The think tank Populace has published an important new study that uses data collected by Gallup about what Americans believe constitutes "success." The authors found that most of us believe that other people see fame as central to personal success. Among a nationally representative sample of 5,242 Americans, 92 percent said fame is part of how they think other people define success: "A person is successful if they are rich, have a high-profile career, or are well-known."  But here's the report's really interesting finding: Only 3 percent said that fame is how they themselves define their own personal success. Instead, 97 percent picked this definition: "A person is successful if they have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are at war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/We-are-at-war-8-dead-in-Chile-s-violent-14549736.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's not about 30 pesos. It's about 30 years."  That was one of the loudest rallying cries coming from protesters in Chile over the weekend, as demonstrations against a transit fare hike erupted into violent clashes over economic inequalities - which many say have been brewing in the three decades since the country's repressive military dictatorship.  Since Friday, clashes between authorities and protesters have resulted in at least eight deaths and hundreds of arrests, as well as looted supermarkets, burning buses, and charred subway stations. The headquarters for an electric company and a major bureau for a national newspaper have both been lit aflame.  For the first time after the end of the Pinochet regime in 1990, the government has called the military onto the streets of Santiago, the country's capital, as that city emerges from its third consecutive night of a government-imposed curfew.  "We are at war against a powerful enemy, willing to use violence with no limits," Chilean President Sebastián Piñera said at a news conference late on Sunday, in comments that only seemed to spark more furor among protesters. He said protesters had only one goal: producing as much harm as possible.  While Piñera said on Saturday he would revert to a metro fare increase, that appears to have done little to satisfy crowds. A state of emergency declared in six cities is expected to expand around the country on Monday.  "This was an economic pressure cooker that's been building for decades, and it exploded," Rodrigo Booth, a professor at the University of Chile, said in an interview with The Washington Post. "This had little to do with public transit. It became a situation about brutal inequality."  Over the past three decades, Chile's neoliberal policies have made it one of South...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying videos...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/21/terrifying-videos-show-tornados-wrath-as-it-plows-through-dallas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tornado plowed through a miles-long swath of Dallas late Sunday — knocking out power for about 65,000 people and wrecking buildings in its wake. The storm swirled through northwest Dallas a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS O'Donnell ratings in freefall...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/20/cbs-anchor-norah-odonnells-ratings-in-freefall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A big bet by “CBS Evening News” on Norah O’Donnell is beginning to look iffy. The former “CBS This Morning” host — who is getting paid at least $7 million a year by CBS News boss Susan Zirinsky to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada vote too close to call as Trudeau hopes to cling on...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20191021-canada-vote-too-close-to-call-as-trudeau-hopes-to-cling-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada vote too close to call as Trudeau hopes to cling on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Socialist Hell: Death of Free Speech in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/10/20/my-socialist-hell-the-death-of-free-speech-in-venezuela/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s freedom of speech was mutilated long ago. It wasn’t done overnight but carried out through a series of incremental steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER CHANNEL wades into climate debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fbeb234bc405432a8d9480abbf0cac43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Weather Channel is moving beyond cold fronts and heat waves to wade into the politics of climate change, with a special planned for early next month that includes interviews...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Homelessness Surges in California, So Does Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/21/us/california-homeless-backlash.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tent encampments across California are testing residents’ tolerance and compassion as street conditions deteriorate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado Leaves Trail of Damage in Dallas and Cuts Power to Thousands...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/weather/2019/10/19/thunderstorms-late-sunday-could-bring-hail-strong-winds-to-dallas-fort-worth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;This breaking news story is being continuously updated.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; A tornado left a miles-long trail of heavy damage from northwest Dallas to Richardson...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia's new 100% hookah tax sparks fury...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-arabias-100-shisha-tax-sparks-fury-092620461.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decision to impose a 100 percent tax on bills at restaurants that serve shisha has ignited criticism on social media in Saudi Arabia, where the water pipes are a popular pastime. In the meantime, some restaurants have stopped offering shisha, while others have lowered their prices to appease customers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claim of kidnap plot as Assange denied extradition delay...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/claim-of-kidnap-plot-as-julian-assange-seeks-extradition-delay-11841101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters of Julian Assange have gathered in the public gallery and outside court as the WikiLeaks founder attended a hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Will Smith 'GEMINI MAN' Faces $75M Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-bust-gemini-man-faces-75-million-loss-1247292</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ang Lee's action thriller — starring Will Smith — was sidelined by bad reviews and the staying power of 'Joker.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST LEAD MONDAY:  Alienated Republicans influenced G-7 reversal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-reversed-course-on-hosting-g-7-at-his-club-after-learning-that-impeachment-weary-republicans-were-tired-of-defending-him/ar-AAJ5bBw?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Ambitions Go Beyond Syria, Wants Nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/21/erdogans-ambitions-go-beyond-syria-he-says-he-wants-nuclear-weapons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - WASHINGTON — Turkey’s president, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, wants more than control over a wide swath of Syria along his country’s border. He says he wants the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WE'VE GOT THE NUMBERS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-50115151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government insists it will still meet the 31 October deadline, despite sending a letter asking for an extension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept Distances Itself From Giuliani...</title>
      <link>https://nonperele.com/justice-department-distances-itself-from-giuliani/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nonperele.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department distanced itself on Sunday from Rudolph W. Giuliani, President Trump’s personal lawyer, declaring that department officials would not have met with Mr. Giuliani to discuss one of his clients had they known that federal prosecutors in New York were investigating two of his associates. Several weeks ago, Brian A. Benczkowski, the head … Continue reading "Justice Department Distances Itself From Giuliani"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar says she's catching on at exactly right time... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Amy-Klobuchar-says-she-s-catching-on-at-exactly-14548800.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PANORA, Iowa - Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., was in New York, finishing a speech to nearly 26,000 people. Rep. Tulsi Gabbard, D-Hawaii, was on TV, carrying on an unexpected feud with the Democrats' last nominee for president. And Sen. Amy Klobuchar, D-Minn., was getting a standing ovation from rural Democrats, an hour west of Des Moines, before sharing a story about a man she'd met in New Hampshire.  "He goes up to me, and he whispers: 'Don't say anything, but I voted for Donald Trump,' " Klobuchar recalled. "So I go: 'Don't worry, I won't say anything.' And he goes: 'I'm not going to do it again!' "  Seventy put-upon rural Democrats laughed and burst into applause. "I don't want to overemphasize this," Klobuchar said. "You know a lot of those Trump voters aren't going to change. But there are a segment of them, nearly 10 percent of them, who voted for Barack Obama, then voted for Donald Trump. There are a bunch of them in this state. There are a bunch of counties in this state that voted for Obama, then for Trump. We don't want to leave those counties behind."  Klobuchar, who struggled for attention in the Democratic primary, says this week's debate helped her catch on at exactly the right time. Her town halls are crowded, with staffers running to get more chairs to pack breweries or event centers. She leads the field in local endorsements, especially state legislators, "with more to come," she says. She kicked off her bus tour with the support of Andy McKean, a Republican state legislator who bolted his party six months ago and who pronounced Klobuchar the kind of Democrat who could unite America again.  "If you want to peak in this race," she said after a stop in Waterloo, "you want to peak now, instead of six months before [the caucuses]."  A few other candidates still draw larger crowds, but Klobuchar is going for a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY SAYS TRUMP BEHAVIOR 'APPALLING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mitt-romney-axios-hbo-donald-trump-indicment-c9ecd74f-d9c9-4988-9480-37352ed78607.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Romney, who wrote in his wife when he voted in 2016, has only soured on Trump since then.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showered in blaze of bullets, upscale Mexican neighborhood in shock...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191020212222-1iu7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/SINALOA-NEIGHBORHOOD (PIX, TV):Showered in blaze of bullets, upscale Mexican neighborhood in shock after cartel assault</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'El Chapo' is in prison, but cartel crime still pervasive...</title>
      <link>https://www.theeagle.com/news/national/el-chapo-is-in-prison-but-cartel-crime-is-still/article_c574c347-a27e-544c-977b-60db071f94d7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — The cartel gunmen who seized control of the Mexican city of Culiacan on Thursday made two things clear: The Sinaloa cartel is stronger than ever, and bringing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is video game addiction a mental health disorder? South Korea looks in the mirror...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/is-video-game-addiction-a-mental-health-disorder-south-korea/article_7a31c114-c174-5305-943d-d8077b70eb13.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea — His video game habit started in middle school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Floods Web With Ads, Raking In Cash as Dems Struggle... </title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/20/trump-campaign-floods-web-with-ads-raking-in-cash-as-democrats-struggle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - On any given day, the Trump campaign is plastering ads all over Facebook, YouTube and the millions of sites served by Google, hitting the kind of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists fuse brains with AI implants to 'give people superhuman intelligence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/scientists-fuse-brains-ai-implants-20650662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brain-boosting electrodes will soon become “like plastic surgery" as all we race to get cybernetic enhancements</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan Markle 'existing, not living' and Prince Harry 'wants to leave UK entirely'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7593293/Meghan-says-existing-not-living-struggles-pressures-royal-life.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the hour-long documentary with Tom Bradby, Prince Harry voices his desire to leave the UK and considers living in Africa, saying Cape Town would be an 'amazing place' to live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies Craft List of Potential Replacements...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-allies-craft-list-potential-191226021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Some of Donald Trump’s closest associates are assembling a roster of possible replacements if the president decides to replace Mick Mulvaney, his acting chief of staff, said three people close to the situation.Among those said to be on the list are former acting Attorney General Matthew</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Eyes 35% Corporate Tax Rate to Pay For Health Plan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pete-buttigieg-eyes-35-corporate-192301913.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Pete Buttigieg would pay for his $1.5 trillion health-care plan by rolling back President Donald Trump’s corporate tax cut to return the rate to 35% and allowing Medicare to negotiate drug prices, campaign spokesman Sean Savett said.Buttigieg’s “Medicare for all who want it” plan would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of thousands take over streets of Lebanon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fresh-lebanon-protests-expected-party-quits-government-094518895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of thousands of protesters rallied Sunday across Lebanon to condemn official corruption and demand the government resign, on the eve of a deadline for politicians to accept a reform package. The demonstrations have crippled the country and threatened the government of beleaguered Prime Minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New clashes in Chile...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chile-president-declares-state-emergency-violent-protests-070230347.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh clashes broke out in Chile's capital Santiago on Sunday after two people died when a supermarket was torched overnight as violent protests sparked by anger over economic conditions and social inequality raged into a third day. Nearly 10,000 soldiers have been deployed while an overnight curfew</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political Risks Grow in Latin America... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/political-risk-alive-latin-america-194654362.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Latin America, the traditional poster child for political risk in financial markets, is back as a source of concern for investors.Chilean President Sebastian Pinera on Saturday became the second leader this month to declare a state of emergency, his hand forced by violent protests in South</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battered Trudeau team sees sign of Canadian election hope after scandals...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191020172445-6e5d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANADA-ELECTION/MOOD (PIX):Battered Trudeau team sees sign of Canadian election hope after scandals</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
