<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'Noah's Ark' designed to save mankind after apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4376299/moon-noah-s-ark-seeds-sperm-apocalypse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have hatched mankind’s ultimate insurance plan – involving the moon and LOTS of sperm. Dubbed the “global insurance policy”, the project is planning on sending se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORSE BEFORE BETTER</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/01/health/us-coronavirus-saturday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US is ringing in the new year amid a Covid-19 surge that experts warn is exploding at unprecedented speed and could alter daily life for many Americans during the first month of 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE YEAR IT ENDS?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-59840513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organisation ends the year on a positive note but warns about "nationalism and vaccine hoarding".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blair becomes 'Sir Tony' and joins top royal order...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-59841419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Blair, the Duchess of Cornwall, and Baroness Amos are appointed to the Order of the Garter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation on Hold Wants to Speak With Manager...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/01/a-nation-on-hold-wants-to-speak-with-a-manager/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nerves at the grocery store were already frayed, in the way of these things as the pandemic slouches toward its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In nation at war with self, town tries cup of civility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-united-states-f4969f8239eeb961bd513f42b6a7d590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOVETTSVILLE, Va. (AP) — When Maureen Donnelly Morris came from nearby Leesburg to open her café in Lovettsville, she got a warm welcome. Neighbors rallied to her aid. Divisions ripping at their town and their country were set aside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics in Egypt say CITROEN ad promotes sexual harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-middle-east-africa-egypt-9a8bbba267c0ae97b405c82e18f27e42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — An advertisement by a French automaker has stirred up controversy in Egypt after activists said it promotes sexual harassment in a country where the practice is rampant. The ad by the Egyptian branch of Citroën, released last month, shows popular Egyptian singer and actor Amr Diab driving the latest version of the company’s C4, before coming to an abrupt stop in front of a woman crossing the street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overdose reversal drug becomes rave essential...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/dec/31/us-overdose-antidote-narcan-rave-essential</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As recreational drugs like cocaine are increasingly cut with fentanyl, a movement has sprung up to prevent deaths in nightclubs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ocasio-Cortez's trip to Florida leads to war of words with conservatives...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/ocasio-cortezs-trip-to-florida-leads-to-war-of-words-with-conservatives/article_b4fd5623-b24c-58d4-a412-62024f910b4c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s had enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence hits 15-year high in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2614485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Sean Reynolds almost lost his life over a PlayStation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousand homes hit...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/hurricane-force-gusts-fan-colorado-224049158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The infernos near Boulder, Colorado, destroyed as many as 1,000 homes, overwhelming firefighters as hurricane-force gusts propelled flames through suburban neighborhoods left tinder dry by months of drought. Most Read from BloombergCases Rise ‘Through the Roof’ as Omicron Sweeps Across U.S.U.S. Housing Crisis Only Gets Worse as Population ShrinksHawaii Is Rethinking Tourism. Here’s What That Means for YouKids’ Covid Hospitalizations Hit Record in U.S. Omicron SurgeBiden Reasserts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETTY WHITE DEAD AT 99</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/12/31/betty-white-dead-dies-golden-girls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Betty White, beloved ‘Golden Girls’ actress, comedian and American icon is dead at the age of 99. Betty passed away just weeks before what would have been her 100th birthday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8-DECADE CAREER</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10359327/Betty-White-dies-99-Legendary-actress-passes-away-just-weeks-milestone-100th-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White, who capped a career of more than 80 years by becoming America's sweetheart, passed away at her home on Friday morning. She passed of natural causes, authorities believe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA warns of air travel meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10359377/FAA-warns-cancel-flights-Omicron-hits-14-000-air-traffic-controllers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration on Friday warned that even more flights could be canceled due to an increasing number of its employees testing positive for COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICA'S SWEETHEART</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/news/local/2021/12/31/tv-sitcom-star-cultural-icon-betty-white-dead-at-99-reports-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Betty White, whose saucy, up-for-anything charm made her a television mainstay for more than 60 years, whether as a man-crazy TV hostess on “The Mary Tyler Moore Show” or the loopy housemate on “The Golden Girls,” has died. She was 99.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Housing Crisis Will Be Made Worse By People Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/u-s-housing-crisis-will-only-get-worse-as-the-population-shrinks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Housing Crisis Only Gets Worse as Population Shrinks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adams takes reins...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/01/eric-adams-sworn-in-as-110th-mayor-of-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Adams proclaimed “New York is back” moments after he was sworn in as the city’s 110th mayor in Times Square following the New Year’s Eve ball drop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice Roberts Reflects on Conflicts, Harassment, Judicial Independence...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/31/chief-justice-roberts-reflects-on-conflicts-harassment-and-judicial-independence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Amid a drop in public confidence in the Supreme Court and calls for increasing its membership, Chief Justice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado fire victims begin new year surveying destruction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wildfires-business-environment-and-nature-denver-suburbs-12017abc8b29dbd42c3169c615580d6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUPERIOR, Colo. (AP) — Hundreds of Colorado residents who had expected to ring in 2022 in their homes are instead starting off the new year trying to salvage what remains of them after a wind-whipped wildfire tore through the Denver suburbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges returning to online classes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-education-chicago-pandemics-7eac07fbfd7ec0c268618d017838aafb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With COVID-19 cases surging just as students are about to return from winter break, dozens of U.S. colleges are moving classes online again for at least the first week or so of the semester — and some warn it could stretch longer if the wave of infection doesn’t subside soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED offers pilots triple pay to ease disruptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/31/united-airlines-offers-pilots-triple-pay-to-ease-omicron-flight-disruptions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United is among the airlines offering pilots and flight attendants extra pay as omicron drives up crew sick calls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unearthed interview reveals how Maxwell helped kill VANITY FAIR expose...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/31/interview-reveals-how-ghislaine-maxwell-killed-vanity-fair-expose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell ripped a Vanity Fair reporter nearly 20 years ago to help bury an exposé of her sex crimes — while claiming pedophile Jeffrey Epstein was generous, according to a released transcr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why JK Rowling snubbed from 'POTTER' reunion...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/tv/streaming/why-jk-rowling-has-been-snubbed-from-the-harry-potter-reunion/news-story/6fcf71eaabca98e3abddfde6f6f447fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She single-handedly created one of the most distinguished fictional worlds in literary, cinematic and popular culture history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee Planned Parenthood destroyed in fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-fires-tennessee-knoxville-planned-parenthood-524edc1a8bd12e46774c1fcdf37c6c72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee Planned Parenthood building was destroyed by an early morning fire on Friday, Planned Parenthood officials said. Knoxville Fire Department crews were called about 6:40 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz Daughter Disses Him on TIKTOK:  'Disagree With Most of His Views'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasobserver.com/news/the-internet-might-have-a-new-claudia-conway-in-ted-cruzs-daughter-13113373</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sen. Ted Cruz may run for president again, but his own daughter recently announced she doesn't agree with his politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge resigns after video showed her using racial slurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/louisiana-judge-resigns-video-showed-using-racial-slurs-rcna10535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana judge Michelle Odinet resigned from her position Friday, weeks after home video showed her and other people using racial slurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish fall from sky in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.kxxv.com/news/local-news/fish-fall-from-the-sky-during-rain-in-east-texas-city-reacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxxv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This uncommon phenomenon is referred to as "animal rain" and occurs when small water animals are swept up in waterspouts or drafts that occur on the surface of the earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Coaches made teen eat pizza despite religion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-football-religion-education-ohio-c7c93a7b6592f2bbe9ea14e472f6f68a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANTON, Ohio (AP) — An Ohio high school football player who says coaches forced him to eat a pizza covered with pepperoni grease in violation of his religious beliefs is suing his former district and the ousted coaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal Spray to Cure Dementia?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/nasal-spray-may-cure-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potentially groundbreaking treatment combines an antibiotic called rifampicin with resveratrol -- an antioxidant found in plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doesn't Infect Lungs Very Well, Animal Studies Find...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/omicron-doesnt-infect-the-lungs-very-well-animal-studies-find/ar-AASjwVO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Miracle' -- no loss of life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-casualties-reported-colorado-wildfire-173128776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado officials said on Friday that it was a "miracle" that no deaths were reported in an unprecedented urban wildfire that moved at breakneck speeds across towns north of Denver, destroying upward of 1,000 homes. The winds created a "mosaic" burn pattern that saw untouched homes standing next to those left in ashes. The blaze swept through about 6,000 acres in just a couple of hours, destroyed at least 500 homes and may have burned down up to 1,000, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers demand proof Prince Andrew can't sweat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/31/us/virginia-giuffre-prince-andrew-court-filing-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew has been asked to provide documents proving his "alleged medical inability to sweat" in a court filing by attorneys for Virginia Roberts Giuffre, who has accused the royal of sexual assault in a US civil lawsuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMTRAK trains canceled...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc-transit/2021/12/some-amtrak-trains-canceled-starting-new-years-eve-following-bad-weather-covid-19-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bad weather and employee COVID-19 cases led Amtrak to reduce its trains’ schedule between New Year’s Eve and Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should kids be vaccinated? Brazil turns to online survey...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-public-health-brazil-jair-bolsonaro-a013cc47a3d4a69bf4ba68f02a958677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASILIA, Brazil (AP) — As world leaders rely on public health specialists to inform their decisions about whether and how to vaccinate children against the coronavirus, Brazil's government is asking the online public for guidance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 15 in London infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-united-nations-middle-east-a1d448ba830f29ac1967971cf2f59458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — New figures from Britain’s official statistics body estimate that about 1 in 25 people in private households in England had COVID-19 in the week before Christmas, as the highly transmissible omicron variant spread rapidly across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia schools going virtual...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-georgia-jonesboro-1c8ea9409edde6dc6ca68503d5d0d9f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JONESBORO, Ga. (AP) — One of Georgia's largest school districts will start the second semester virtually amid the state's surge in COVID cases. Clayton County Public Schools south of Atlanta said Thursday students will learn remotely from Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic Videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/apocalyptic-videos-emerge-from-boulder-fire-i-dont-know-if-my-home-is-still-there/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stunning videos have emerged from the fires that have ravaged neighborhoods in Boulder County, Colorado Thursday that led to massive evacuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some cautious, many fed up, Americans ring in New Year...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211231105707-fxtdj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW-YEAR/USA (PIX):Some cautious, many fed up, Americans prepare to ring in the New Year</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
