<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Man guilty of sharing NZ mosque massacre faces 14 years jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/national/christchurch-shooting/112281653/philip-arps-guilty-of-sharing-livestream-of-christchurch-mosque-massacre</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He sent the terror attack video to a friend, asking for it to be modified with a "kill count" as people were shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Juiced ball' claims as MLB hitters blasting record home runs...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/MLB-hitters-are-blasting-homers-at-a-record-rate-13799008.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE - It's not exactly true that the Baltimore Orioles' pitching staff is single-handedly responsible for the staggering spike in home runs across Major League Baseball this season - but when you're standing on the mound or sitting in the dugout at Oriole Park at Camden Yards, watching another long flyball leave the yard, it's natural sometimes for it to feel that way.  "I've never seen home runs given up like we do," Orioles manager Brandon Hyde marveled last week.  That's because no one has ever seen home runs given up like the 2019 Orioles. Before this month, the major league record for homers allowed before the end of April was 50 by the 1996 Detroit Tigers. The Orioles zoomed past that record on April 20 - a day that saw them give up 11 long balls in a doubleheader sweep at the hands of the Minnesota Twins. Entering Friday, with five days left before the calendar turns to May, the Orioles' total sat at 59.  But the Orioles are merely an extreme example of something taking place all across the game. Even in an era of unprecedented, leaguewide home-run power, the first month of the 2019 season stands out. Entering Friday, teams had combined to hit a record 979 homers - an average of 1.32 per team-game. That's 116 more than teams hit in April 2017, a season that would eventually see a record 6,105 homers.  In other words, the 2019 home run rate is 5 percent higher than the highest rate in history (1.26 per team-game in 2017), and up 15 percent from last year, when the leaguewide rate dipped to 1.15.  And what is truly scary is that the early part of the season normally produces the lowest rate of homers. What's going to happen when the weather warms, typically resulting in balls carrying further? At least in Baltimore, nobody seems to have any answers.  "I have no idea," Orioles reliever Mychal Givens said. "But...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans selling grass from Kanye Coachella performance for $405...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/04/26/fans-are-selling-grass-from-kanyes-coachella-sunday-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One listing is going for a heart-stopping $405 (plus shipping).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Installed Top Cop to Steer INTERPOL. Then He Disappeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-installed-its-top-cop-to-steer-interpol-then-he-disappeared-11556304500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meng Hongwei’s election as president of the global police agency was expected to help China’s crackdown on corruption, but the official himself was arrested—one side says for bribe-taking, the other for failing to do Beijing’s bidding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Carolina considers firing squad as death penalty workaround...</title>
      <link>https://www.wltx.com/article/news/local/sc-may-use-firing-squad-as-death-penalty-workaround/101-35f7f6df-20f9-4c31-aaab-e29e99c7ff63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wltx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are currently 29 men on South Carolina death row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training boys to be 'alpha' to counter 'masculinity crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-china-masculinity-pop-idols-backlash-20190426-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a freezing winter day, boys as young as 7 are running shirtless in a Beijing Park, training to be "real men." It's part of a backlash in China against flawlessly made-up Chinese pop stars and an existential fear for nation's "virility."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hijacked listing for Bel-Air megamansion leads to $60M lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/realestate/hot-property/la-fi-hp-zillow-makowsky-lawsuit-20190426-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit that developer Bruce Makowsky filed against real estate company Zillow underscores how image is everything when seeking nine figures for a single estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Helping Govt Conduct Warrantless Searches?</title>
      <link>https://www.cpomagazine.com/data-privacy/epic-alleges-google-may-be-helping-u-s-government-conduct-warrantless-searches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cpomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scanning images in billions of users’ files without warrants, is Google helping the U.S. government to conduct warrantless searches and violating the Fourth Amendment?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia killing millions of feral cats with poisoned sausages...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/26/australia-is-killing-millions-of-feral-cats-with-poisoned-sausages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian officials are killing millions of feral cats by airdropping frozen sausages laced with poison across the Outback. The felines die within 15 minutes of ingesting the toxic treats, which a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Grand Canyon deaths, tourists still drawn to edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/grand-canyon-deaths-after-latest-fatal-fall-tourists-still-drawn-n998791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s really tempting because you see the way to go down and you want to go down there to get a better view,” a park visitor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French architects want Notre Dame reborn as GREENHOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6963757/Notre-Dame-reborn-GREENHOUSE-French-architects-propose-replacing-damaged-roof-glass.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French architects have revealed a stunning set of plans to redesign Notre Dame Cathedral's fire-ravaged roof as a greenhouse, complete with a glass roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RECORD HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/26/stock-market-gdp-data-and-corporate-earnings-in-focus-on-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Composite closed at record highs on Friday as better-than-expected economic data offset a mixed batch of corporate earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of female gun ownership...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/female-gun-ownership-and-the-rise-of-fashionable-carrywear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexo Athletica designed a pair of Lulelemon-like leggings with pockets for guns -- and women gun owners took notice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wants to Make America -- Great Again?</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2019/04/joe-biden-2020-launch-maga-trump-us-history.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president needs voters to believe that the country was totally great before Donald Trump ruined it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Makes Snitching Profitable...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-profitable-prospects-of-snitching-for-the-irs-11556271006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRS awarded more than $312 million to whistleblowers last year, including about $100 million to a single tipster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Clients in College Admissions Scandal From China...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-biggest-clients-in-the-college-admissions-scandal-were-from-china-11556301872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Families from China were among those who allegedly paid the most in the college admissions scandal, a new sign of the reach of the cheating ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executions for 'sorcerers', homosexuals, mentally ill DOUBLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8946867/saudi-arabia-executions-sorcerers-homosexuals-double/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE number of sick executions in Saudi Arabia has DOUBLED in recent years  – with people beheaded for bizarre reasons including “sorcery” and for simply being gay. Crown Prince Mohammed bin S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Flexes Fundraising Strength...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440860-joe-biden-announces-63-million-fundraising-haul-in-first-24-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden raised $6.3 million in the 24 hours after launching his 2020 White House bid, his campaign announced Friday, a record fundraising haul in the crowded Democratic presidential field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey from disgraced officer to police chief surprisingly common...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/investigations/2019/04/24/police-officers-police-chiefs-sheriffs-misconduct-criminal-records-database/2214279002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During NRA speech, Trump revokes another global arms treaty...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/during-nra-speech-trump-revokes-another-global-arms-treaty/ar-BBWjL4J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL PRICES PLUNGE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/26/oil-market-opec-output-rises-us-sanctions-on-iranian-oil-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump says he "called up" OPEC and told the producer group to take measures to cut the price of gasoline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Efforts To Search For, Send Messages To Extraterrestrial Life Advance...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/04/25/messages-extraterrestrial-life-advancing-digital-age/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ambitious new effort is underway to make direct contact with intelligent life beyond earth, improving upon 70s-era space missions which included attempts to bring messages from Earth to extraterrestrials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Mulls Sending 300 More Troops To Border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f0d2c4a017104b61a244408223aaf6b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Pentagon may send about 300 more troops to the U.S.-Mexico border in roles that could put them in contact with migrants and thus mark a break from current practice, officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  College football coach inks $93 million deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/sports/college/acc/clemson-university/article229714494.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take kids to work day gives child's-eye view of coroner's office...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/take-kids-to-work-day-gives-childs-eye-view-of-coroners-office-1649837/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Clark County coroner’s office featured educational programs Thursday for children of county employees to celebrate Take Our Daughters and Sons to Work Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to the future: Restaurant to accept cash again...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/food-restaurant/2019/04/back-to-the-future-sweetgreen-to-accept-cash-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After going cashless for more than two years, D.C.-founded restaurant Sweetgreen announced Thursday they will again accept cash in all their restaurants by the end of 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amish population grows despite urban sprawl...</title>
      <link>https://lancasteronline.com/news/local/amish-population-grows-by-a-year-despite-lancaster-county-s/article_e24c564e-678e-11e9-9ba4-bf1905bae642.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lancasteronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lancaster County’s fast-growing Amish population recently exceeded the 33,000 mark as the farming-oriented Plain sect continues to flourish despite the encroachment of urban sprawl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SO FAR:  39 miles of fresh border barrier... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-has-put-up-39-miles-of-wall-on-2-000-mile-border-despite-claims-of-more</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a small fraction of the 2,000-mile wall President Trump vowed as a candidate to build on the U.S.-Mexico border has gone up since he took office more than two years ago, according to a document the defense agency overseeing construction provided to Sen. John Hoeven, R-N.D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champagne with Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8945208/kim-jong-un-al-capone-putin-champagne-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIM JONG-UN embraced the Al Capone look as he tilted his trilby with a menacing stare before necking bubbly with Putin in Russia yesterday. Teaming his hat with a sinister long black coat, the Nort…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia teen BEHEADED just for sending WhatsApp messages about protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8926874/saudi-arabia-teenager-16-beheaded-protests-whatsapp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A YOUNG lad was tortured with electricity and beheaded in Saudi Arabia because he sent WhatsApp messages about a protest aged 16. Abdulkarim al-Hawaj, 21, was a schoolboy when he was detained and a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like President, Buttigieg bills himself as turnaround expert...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-buttigieg/like-trump-democrat-buttigieg-bills-himself-as-a-turnaround-expert-idUSKCN1S20YI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four years ago, Donald Trump campaigned in small towns like Marshalltown, Iowa, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECONOMY SURPRISE STRENGTH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/economy-grows-32-in-first-quarter-gdp-shows-much-stronger-than-anticipated-2019-04-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharp upturn in state and local government spending helps the U.S. economy accelerate to a 3.2% annual rate in the first three months of 2019, the Commerce...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALEM Quietly Becoming Conservative Media Giant...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/salem-radio-is-quietly-becoming-a-conservative-media-giant-1204182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California-based broadcaster's digital acquisitions have turned heads, but the company's revenues primarily come from 116 radio stations in 39 markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOO OLD?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6963939/Im-young-vibrant-man-Trump-says-hell-beat-Joe-Biden-easily.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Friday morning that he expects to make quick work of former Vice President Joe Biden if he survives the grueling Democratic primary season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom puts crucified body on public display...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6959883/Body-crucified-criminal-public-display-Saudi-Arabia-following-37-executions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The name of the person who was crucified has not been released. Abdulkarim al-Hawaj (pictured) was one of those beheaded after being arrested at age 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP BIG:  3.2%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/26/gdp-q1-2019-first-read.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GDP for the first quarter was the best start to a year since 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/04/26/video-1300-migrants-riot-escape-mexican-immigration-facility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 1,300 migrants from Central America and Cuba rioted and broke out of an immigration holding facility in Mexico Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  TRUMP 44% MAYOR PETE 40%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/elections/election_2020/white_house_watch_apr26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaks All-Time Thursday Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/avengers-endgame-sets-thursday-box-office-record-60-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preview total surpassed previous record holder "Star Wars: The Force Awakens"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Silicon Valley could be second richest country in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/04/26/silicon-valley-could-be-the-second-richest-country-in-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Silicon Valley was its own country, it would be the second only to a small oil-producing nation on per-person GDP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE BONKERS: 'AVENGERS' $900 MILLION OPEN?!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/box-office-avengers-endgame-hits-record-60m-previews-1204963 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overseas, it also continues to smash records in its launch, pulling in $305 million on Wednesday and Thursday alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMY BASE APOLOGIZES AFTER FAKE CYBER ATTACK SPURS CONSPIRACIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article229712439.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD PLANS NEW TRUMP BOOK?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bob-woodward-trump-book-impeachment-interview-b928e8fb-c4d0-4fda-98cb-aee5114d18b1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He doesn't even have a to-do list, as best I can tell."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Trump 2016 obsession could cost him 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/837548/trumps-2016-obsession-could-cost-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the president spends the next year and a half complaining about how unfairly he was treated in the last election, he could very well lose the next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Weinstein Rape Case Judge Bans Public From Courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-hearing-witness-testimony-public-ban-1202602494/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(UPDATED with judge’s ruling) About a month before Harvey Weinstein’s rape trial is set to begin, the much-accused producer’s latest defense team and the Manhattan District Attorney got suppo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listen...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=icJjlg5e6l8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pre-order Bruce Springsteenâ€™s new album â€˜Western Starsâ€™ coming June 14 now: http://smarturl.it/westernstars Listen to â€œHello Sunshineâ€� now: http://smarturl.i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal 49ERS fans not taking Nick Bosa selection well...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/49ers/article/Nick-Bosa-tweets-Trump-Kaepernick-Beyonce-racist-13796870.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco 49ers drafted Ohio State pass rusher Nick Bosa with the second overall pick of the 2019 NFL Draft, but a number of left-leaning 49ers fans were not happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen Finds New Sound By Looking To Past...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/04/26/717330166/bruce-springsteen-finds-a-new-sound-by-looking-to-the-past</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Hello Sunshine," the first single from Bruce Springsteen's upcoming album Western Stars, shares the same melancholy space as early '70s ballads by Jimmy Webb and Kris Kristofferson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Great shot at presidency...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/837624/joe-bidens-great-shot-presidency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why pundits chuckling about Biden's inevitable flameout are kidding themselves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Stream of illegals ushered to awaiting buses...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-border-agents-usher-in-hundreds-of-illegals-to-awaiting-buses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real reporters stationed along the U.S.-Mexico border continue to share disturbing footage of the massive scope of the illegal immigration crisis, most recently with video of hundreds of illegal immigrants streaming into the country to awaiting buses for processing. KGBT reporter Sydney Hernandez is exposing the reality of the situation on the border, and it’s …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Offshore Drilling Plan Sidelined Indefinitely...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trumps-offshore-oil-drilling-plan-sidelined-indefinitely-11556208950</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration’s proposal to vastly expand offshore oil-and-gas drilling has been sidelined indefinitely as the Interior Department grapples with a recent court decision that blocks Arctic drilling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Seeing' God -- Even Under Influence -- Provides Lasting Mental Benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/encounters-with-god-under-influence-lasting-mental-benefits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by researchers at the Johns Hopkins School of Medicine found that those who have had divine encounter experiences -- the sensation of seeing a God-like figure or a profound, enhanced reality or truth -- reap lasting mental benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Shrinking Newsroom of Paper That Shapes Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/26/des-moines-register-iowa-newspaper-primaries-2020-226748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The great media disruption comes for the &lt;i&gt;Des Moines Register&lt;/i&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE BONKERS: 'AVENGERS' $900 MILLION OPEN?!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/tag/avengers-endgame/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town Bans Gossip...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-small-town-takes-a-stand-it-banned-gossip-11556204479</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a world awash with fake news and online rumors, more than half a dozen neighborhoods in a town in the Philippines have introduced an anti-gossip ordinance to put an end to idle chitchat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim warns of return to tension, blames U.S. 'bad faith'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-russia-kcna/north-korean-leader-warns-of-a-return-to-tension-blames-u-s-bad-faith-idUSKCN1S12QH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un told Russian President Vladimir Putin peace and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban migrants stage mass escape from center in south Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2529d3d392394f3c87bd246d75d81213</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAPACHULA, Mexico (AP) — At least 1,300 mainly Cuban migrants fled on foot from an immigration detention center on Mexico's southern border Thursday in the largest mass escape in recent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravans keep coming...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/440630-another-migrant-caravan-makes-its-way-to-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social justice warriors going to utterly maul...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/25/social-justice-warriors-are-going-to-utterly-maul-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even before launching his 2020 presidential bid, Joe Biden knelt at the altar of identity grievance. He will kneel and kneel some more through the campaign. None of it will be enough, and he is des…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In new SAfrica, some in 'Colored' community nostalgic for apartheid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/africa-coloured-community-nostalgic-apartheid-035505085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eldorado Park (South Africa) (AFP) - "It is all about the blacks. The 'Rainbow Nation' is a big lie!" complained Dalene Raiters, a South African mother from the "Coloured" community. Four generations under the same roof," said Elizabeth Raiters, seated in the living</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep well -- things really will be better by morning...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/sleep-well-things-really-will-be-better-by-morning-fc0fdgc2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sleeping on a problem really does make it better, especially when that problem is your previous night’s rendition of Total Eclipse of the Heart during a karaoke session. Scientists have found that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's insults fueled by belief he can win?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/25/donald-trump-joe-biden-2020-1290338</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president sees the former vice president as his biggest threat in 2020, a Republican strategist says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lettuce-Farming Robots Might Grow Your Next Salad...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2019-04-26/lettuce-farming-robots-might-grow-your-next-salad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be wary of robot emotions; 'Simulated love is never love'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/99c9ec8ebad242ca88178e22c7642648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — When a robot "dies," does it make you sad? For lots of people, the answer is "yes" — and that tells us something important, and potentially worrisome, about our emotional...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Americans Most Stressed; Worry, Anger Rising...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/249098/americans-stress-worry-anger-intensified-2018.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans were more stressed, angry and worried last year than they've been at most points during the past decade, according to Gallup's annual update on the world's emotional state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Accused of Retaliating Against Staff in New Labor Case...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-accused-retaliating-against-staff-011710369.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The filing was made this week by an unidentified individual and the case has been assigned to the agency’s New York office, according to the agency’s website. It involved an alleged violation of a New Deal-era ban on punishing employees for involvement in collective action related to working conditions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male angst prompts new fertility service: Sperm freezing...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Newfound-anxiety-about-sperm-health-inspires-next-13795699.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMBRIDGE, Mass. - Gilbert Sanchez froze his sperm in January, shortly before his 25th birthday. He was healthy and at low-risk for fertility issues. But he wanted to be proactive - just as thousands of young women have been by putting their eggs on ice.  Sanchez was headed to graduate school in the fall, and it might be years before he would have a steady job and the wherewithal for a family. He and his girlfriend worried about all the things that could go wrong - disease, war, natural aging - before they might be ready.  "It was a little bit weird," admitted Sanchez, who stored his sperm with a company called Legacy. "But it was medically responsible."  Sanchez's choice highlights a new anxiety about sperm health among American men. The idea that men can easily father healthy children into their 70s and 80s has been exposed as a myth. In fact, research shows that older men have a higher risk that their partners will miscarry and have children with congenital abnormalities, schizophrenia or autism.  New businesses are capitalizing on those revelations. Start-ups like Trak, YO sperm and SpermCheck are selling at-home testing kits so men can figure out early on if there's something amiss with their sperm. Employee benefits companies are debating how to translate the fertility coverage they offer to female employees to their male counterparts. And sperm freezing companies are aiming to turn what has been a sterile, clinical process into something more cool - a 23andme or Ancestry.com for sperm.  Legacy, a company based at the Harvard Innovation Labs that launched in October, is part of a new breed of sperm freezing companies that aim to shake up the industry by offering mail-in kits that allow the whole process to be done in the privacy of one's home. A competitor, called Dadi (pronounced "daddy") and backed by $2 million...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem race shows signs it could get nasty...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440744-dem-race-shows-signs-it-could-get-nasty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gloves are beginning to come off in the crowded Democratic race for the White House that so far has resembled more of a tea party than a bar-room brawl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5'10 QB MURRAY TOP PICK IN DRAFT; MAKES HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/sports/nfl/dallas-cowboys/article229689399.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hires Key Bernie Aide -- Who Donated to Buttigieg...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6961389/Biden-campaigns-hires-include-onetime-Harvey-Weinstein-adviser-former-Bernie-spokeswoman.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Symone Sanders said in 2016 that Democrats shouldn't be led by 'white men,' but is now working for Biden. She also donated money this year to Pete Buttigieg's rival campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL newfound embrace of short passers...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/From-Doug-Flutie-to-Kyler-Murray-Inside-the-13753127.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doug Flutie, a quarterback consigned professionally to Canadian glory and journeyman status in his own country, admits he often thinks about how he might fit into the NFL today. He played in the 1980s and '90s and stood shorter than a standard refrigerator, which suddenly makes him a man born before his time.  Flutie was a jitterbug, 5-foot-10, Heisman-winning quarterback with uncommon arm strength for his size. Kyler Murray, a quarterback who fits that description precisely, might be this year's hottest NFL draft commodity.  "It just means," Flutie said, "I was 20 years too early."  For years, NFL executives turned away undersized quarterbacks like so many you-must-be-this-tall-to-enter-the-ride signs. One year after the Cleveland Browns took 6-foot-1 Baker Mayfield first overall, the Arizona Cardinals may pluck Murray with the same pick in this month's draft. Murray's stature once would have been detrimental to the point of disqualifying. As recently as 10 years ago, ESPN NFL Draft analyst Todd McShay posited, teams would have asked a quarterback like Murray to play slot receiver and return kicks.  Height still matters, of course - Murray briefly became the buzziest story in sports simply for measuring 5-10 instead of 5-9 at the NFL scouting combine. But now, as a response to several trends, the league does not only tolerate the package of skills and size Murray presents. It embraces athletic quarterbacks, even if they stand around 6-feet or shy of it. The adoption of shotgun-heavy, spread-reliant systems and prohibitions on how quarterbacks can be hit have cleared a path for humans of average size to play the most demanding position in professional sports.  In 2012, the Seattle Seahawks took 5-foot-11 Russell Wilson in the third round. Coach Pete Carroll called him a "living example" of how the sport has shifted. If a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA $72 Trillion In Debt: Explosion on Every Society Level...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-04-25/220000-every-man-woman-and-child-america-now-72-trillion-dollars-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulators Around Globe Circling FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/25/technology/facebook-regulation-ftc-fine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook revealed that it expects a record fine from the F.T.C. That could be one of many moves against the company by governments on four continents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anita Hill 'Deeply Unsatisfied' After Apology...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/joe-biden-expresses-regret-to-anita-hill-but-she-says-im-sorry-is-not-enough/ar-BBWiolH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Says US Acted in 'Bad Faith' at Hanoi Talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/nkoreas-kim-putin-us-acted-bad-faith-hanoi-talks-doc-1fw9lz8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON tracking system fires workers without human input...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/4/25/18516004/amazon-warehouse-fulfillment-centers-productivity-firing-terminations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents show how the company tracks and terminates workers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universe expanding faster than thought, no one knows why...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/universe-is-expanding-faster-than-we-thought-and-no-one-knows-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explaining a discrepancy between what was happening 13 billion years ago and now may require new physics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK hit with 3 privacy investigations today...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2019/04/25/facebook-privacy-investigations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Third time lucky — unless you’re Facebook . The social networking giant was hit Thursday by a trio of investigations over its privacy practices following a particularly tumultuous month of security lapses and privacy violations — the latest in a string of embarrassing and damaging breaches at…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most fertile woman has 44 kids -- by age 36!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/worlds-most-fertile-woman-44-14589782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mariam Nabatanzi , from Uganda, has a rare medical condition and had 25 children by the time she was 23</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
