<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/attorney-general-plans-news-conference-to-discuss-mueller-report/2019/04/17/f5ca1cc6-6138-11e9-9ff2-abc984dc9eec_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr is planning to provide an overview of the report at a news conference and later give the document to lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No material redacted based on executive privilege...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/barr-no-material-in-mueller-report-was-redacted-based-on-executive-privilege</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr on Thursday said no redactions in special counsel Robert Mueller’s report on his Russia investigation were made based on claims of executive privilege by the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicious beast...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-mammal-idUSKCN1RU18A </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Ohio University integrative biologist Nancy Stevens peered into a drawer in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priests in Philippines crucify selves in penance ahead of Easter...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/773107/catholic-priests-crucify-themselves-philippines-pampanga-easter-jesus-christ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER EDITS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6936383/Attorney-General-Bill-Barr-reveals-redacted-Mueller-report.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Bill Barr has used a press conference to announce the findings of the Mueller report - to the fury of Democrats who say he is spinning it in favor of Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr considered Trump frustration with media when deciding on evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/18/mueller-report-recounts-10-episodes-involving-trump-and-questions-of-obstruction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Mueller's report on his Russia investigation recounts ten episodes involving President Donald Trump and questions of obstruction of justice, Attorney General William Barr said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President declares 'Game Over'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/439496-trump-declares-game-over-on-mueller-investigation-with-game-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump took a “Game of Thrones”-themed victory lap after Attorney General William Barr’s press conference on special counsel Robert Mueller’s report on his Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Of Teens Run Through Chicago, Fighting And Disobeying Police...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/04/17/hundreds-of-teens-run-through-downtown-chicago-fighting-and-disobeying-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police were dealing with hundreds of teens running through downtown Chicago Wednesday night, yelling, stopping traffic and running in the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Claims Tumble To Fresh 50 Year Lows...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-04-18/initial-jobless-claims-tumble-fresh-50-year-lows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers discover ancient giant 'lion' in Kenya...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190418-researchers-discover-ancient-giant-lion-kenya-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers discover ancient giant 'lion' in Kenya</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Population Dips First Time in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-citys-population-dips-for-first-time-in-over-a-decade-11555560060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s largest city is losing population for the first time in more than a decade, new federal estimates show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies, foes united in skepticism on redactions...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/US-allies-foes-may-have-different-takes-on-13777089.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - Like much of the United States, governments abroad will watch closely Thursday as special counsel Robert Mueller's report is released in a redacted version. U.S. allies and foes may have very different hopes for that report, which is also expected to shed more light on the extent to which Russia was able to disrupt the 2016 U.S. elections.  But even though their interests in the Mueller report may be different, they will be united on at least one aspect: skepticism of the redactions by Attorney General William Barr.  The attorney general has said he plans to restrict only lightly access to information that would violate privacy rights, affect ongoing inquiries, provide insights into sensitive intelligence details or include grand jury material. Key members of Congress are expected to have access to a more complete version of the report.  And yet, the one thing that is almost certain is that there will be a battle over the things that won't be included. Democrats are likely to argue that Barr may have deliberately left out crucial details that would cast President Donald Trump in a negative light. Republicans will side with Barr, arguing that redactions are standard practice and necessary to protect other investigations and the integrity of the process.  But watching from afar, many Europeans are likely to share the Democrats' concerns: Often, in the past, their own concerns over redactions have proved to be justified.  That is especially true for countries where memories of the abuse of such techniques are still vivid. In what was once East Germany, authorities regularly opened letters sent to or from democratic West Germany and redacted passages deemed a threat to socialism, until the fall of the Berlin Wall in 1989. What became known as the "postal war" has deeply ingrained an inherent skepticism of redactions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Still Losing People...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/news/chicago-still-losing-population</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR LIVE 9:30AM ET...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?459919-1/attorney-general-barr-holds-news-conference-muller-report-release</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild bee species critical to pollination on decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f768748b36c648e49c14b0366fdec7e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONCORD, N.H. (AP) — More than a dozen wild bee species critical to pollinizing everything from blueberries to apples in New England are on the decline, according to a new study. Researchers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a99d0b66de82494bb29ca16ec8443643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on special counsel Robert Mueller's report on Russia and President Donald Trump (all times local): 8:10 a.m. President Donald Trump is blasting the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kakapow! Rare world's fattest parrot has record breeding season...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kakapow-rare-worlds-fattest-parrot-record-breeding-season-065032899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's fattest parrot, the critically endangered kakapo, has enjoyed a record breaking breeding season, New Zealand scientists said Thursday, with climate change possibly aiding the species' unique mating spree. Less than 50 years after the flightless nocturnal bird was thought to have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Church Membership Plummets...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/248837/church-membership-down-sharply-past-two-decades.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The percentage of U.S. adults who belong to a church or other religious institution has fallen 20 percentage points within the past two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA, intel agencies have become bastions of liberals...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/u-s-intelligence-institutionally-politicized-toward-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CIA and other U.S. intelligence agencies have become bastions of political liberals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrants Propel Population Growth in 10% of U.S. Counties...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/immigrants-propel-population-growth-in-10-of-u-s-counties-11555560061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About one in 10 U.S. counties grew in the fiscal year that ended last June primarily because of immigration—a significant increase from 2011—showing how new arrivals are shaping the nation as the population ages and the birthrate slows, new census figures show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROVE: Bernie Could Win This Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/bernie-sanders-could-win-this-time-11555541440 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He showed on Fox that he knows how to soften socialism’s rough edges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK uploaded email contacts of 1.5 million users without consent...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/18/facebook-uploaded-email-contacts-of-15m-users-without-consent </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company says it has stopped using password verification feature that collected data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S NOT OVER: Pelosi, Schumer call on Mueller to testify...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/439450-pelosi-schumer-call-on-mueller-to-testify-after-barrs-regrettably</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top Democratic congressional leaders are calling on special counsel Robert Mueller to testify on Capitol Hill as soon as possible following what they describe as Attorney General William Barr's "partisan" handling of the release of t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Nazi camp guard, 92, charged as accessory to thousands of murders...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418101135-pj0x9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-NAZI/TRIAL (PIX):German Nazi camp guard, 92, charged as accessory to thousands of murders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online activists silencing us, scientists say...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418094429-rl1l2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-SOCIAL MEDIA/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Online activists are silencing us, scientists say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-lapse shots of Notre-Dame spire may offer clues on blaze...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418092525-nnw8y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NOTREDAME/ (PIX, TV):Time-lapse shots of Notre-Dame spire may offer clues on blaze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release of long-awaited report on Russia watershed moment for Trump...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190418044628-va37q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA (PIX, TV):Release of long-awaited Mueller report on Russia a watershed moment for Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hatred of journalists turning to violence, watchdog warns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hatred-journalists-turning-violence-watchdog-warns-040627489.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hatred of journalists whipped up by populist and authoritarian leaders is degenerating into violence across the world, media watchdog Reporters Without Borders (RSF) warned Thursday. Political leaders' hostility towards the media "has incited increasingly frequent acts of violence that have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Unveils Secret Data Centers for Classified Gov't Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/04/microsoft-unveils-two-secret-data-centers-built-classified-government-data/156376/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft is building data centers and expanding security capabilities to compete with Amazon to host sensitive government data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech-Funded 'Privacy' Think Tanks -- Fight Privacy Protections...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/04/16/consumer-privacy-laws-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silicon Valley-funded privacy think tanks’ positions on a federal online privacy bill mirror the tech industry’s lobbying priorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACK THE KNIFE FALLS ON SWORD; RULES OUT 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ap-sources-ex-virginia-gov-mcauliffe-rule-2020-230656357--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Former Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe won't run for president in 2020, according to two people familiar with calls he made Wednesday to allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAUNTS WEST...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/2ff1e53cfc9d42a7821c7f4e6a740642/north-korea-test-fires-new-tactical-guided-weapon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Thursday that it had test-fired a new type of "tactical guided weapon," in what may be an attempt to register displeasure with a deadlock in nuclear talks with the United States without causing those coveted negotiations to collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA TEST FIRES NEW WEAPON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ff1e53cfc9d42a7821c7f4e6a740642</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Thursday that it had test-fired a new type of "tactical guided weapon," in what may be an attempt to register displeasure with a deadlock in nuclear...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Restore Function In Brains Of Dead Pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/04/17/714289322/scientists-restore-some-function-in-the-brains-of-dead-pigs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cells regained a startling amount of function, but the brains didn't have activity linked with consciousness. Ethicists see challenges to assumptions about the irreversible nature of brain death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONVERSATIONS WITH WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/concerns-among-some-white-house-aides-said-to-grow-on-eve-of-mueller-report/ar-BBW2HE5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: 60 companies paid no federal income tax on $79,000,000,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/amazon-netflix-chevron-ibm-federal-taxes-trump-tax-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In total, the 60 companies zeroed out their federal income taxes on $79 billion in U.S. pretax income, according to the study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just one in 50 people can see stars as Nature intended......</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6930051/Starry-skies-masked-veil-light-pollution-cosmic-census-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two per cent of the UK were able to gaze at ‘truly dark skies’ while 57 per cent struggled to count more than 120 stars, the research by Campaign to Protect Rural England found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diver who rescued Thai soccer team now missing in cave...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/diver-who-helped-free-thai-soccer-team-now-missing-in-tenn-cave/5256366/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was reported missing from the Mill Pond Cave early Wednesday in Jackson County in northern Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires face 'yellow vest' scorn over cathedral pledges...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/04/17/billionaires-face-yellow-vest-scorn-cathedral-pledges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire French tycoons faced a mounting backlash on Wednesday over tax breaks on their huge donations to restore Notre-Dame, as Yellow Vest protestors said the hundreds of millions of euros should be spent on tackling France's social problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awaiting trial and under gag, Roger Stone still talking...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/17/politics/roger-stone-life-under-gag-order/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On his recent court-approved tour through Florida, Roger Stone fielded questions about the raid on his home, the media coverage of his case and the plight of his former business partner and 2016 Trump campaign chair Paul Manafort -- all while trying not to obviously run afoul of his gag order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to clone extinct horse using 42,000-year-old blood...</title>
      <link>https://siberiantimes.com/science/casestudy/news/unique-in-palaeontology-liquid-blood-found-inside-a-prehistoric-42000-year-old-foal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;siberiantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STRANGER THINGS' Creators Fail To Get Plagiarism Case Tossed; Trial Set...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/stranger-things-duffer-brothers-lawsuit-plagiarism-trial-1202597763/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The third season of Stranger Things is set to launch on Netflix on July 4th, but series creators the Duffer Brothers are probably more focused on another date after a judge today rejected their att…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why Media Dumped Beto for Buttigieg...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/17/media-dumped-beto-mayor-pete-buttigieg-226660</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists love a candidate who loves them back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Strait Tension Rising: 'Will Not Bow'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/17/cross-strait-tension-rising-taiwanese-official-declares-island-will-not-bow-to-intimidation-of-the-chinese/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between the Chinese communists on the mainland of China and capitalists in the democracy of Taiwan are rising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast food chain tests CBD-infused burger...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/life/food/carls-jr-to-test-cbd-infused-burger-in-denver-on-420/73-0ac4139d-a2e0-438c-b7ce-bb3930451620</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rocky Mountain High: CheeseBurger Delight (CBD) will be sold for one day only on April 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SELECT LAWMAKERS VIEW WITHOUT REDACTIONS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/439410-feds-doj-will-allow-some-lawmakers-to-view-mueller-report-without</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice will allow some members of Congress to view a copy of special counsel Robert Mueller’s report “without certain redactions,” federal prosecutors said in a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images show activity at nuke site...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/north-korea-nuclear-plant-satellite-photos-reprocessing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images from last week show movement at North Korea's main nuclear site that could be associated with the reprocessing of radioactive material into bomb fuel, a U.S. think tank said on Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone-Assembly Tycoon Presidency Bid May Shake Up Taiwan-China Relations...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/iphone-assembly-tycoon-launches-bid-for-taiwans-presidency-after-consulting-sea-goddess-11555508498</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwanese billionaire Terry Gou, CEO of iPhone assembler Foxconn, declared his candidacy for president of Taiwan, in a marked shift for the island’s politics, his company and, potentially, relations with China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having sex could cure hayfever, scientists claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/health/sex-could-help-cure-hayfever-scientists-claim-a4119881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having a healthy sex life could help alleviate hay fever symptoms, according to a team of scientists. Researchers in Iran found that the reproductive system is linked to the nasal system.  They said that sex constricts blood vessels in the nose and eyes, which causes eyes to stop streaming and helps unblock stuffy noses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Pitcher goes full 'MATRIX' to avoid line-drive to face...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlb.com/news/collin-mchugh-makes-matrix-like-move</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND -- Collin McHugh literally bent over backwards to help the Astros turn a double play Tuesday night, and, in the process, prompted a shrewd comparison from the home-plate umpire.   In the second inning of Houston's 9-1 victory Tuesday night over the A's, Oakland's Kendrys Morales lined a 91 mph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor faces prosecution for instructing students to make ecstacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/04/17/national/crime-legal/professor-western-japan-says-instructed-students-produce-mdma/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pharmaceutical science professor at a university in Shikoku was referred to prosecutors Tuesday for allegedly instructing his students to produce the syn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Peru president shoots himself as police try to arrest..</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6473eb980f4c45f88312070a8d048fd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIMA, Peru (AP) — Former Peruvian President Alan Garcia shot himself in the head and died Wednesday as officers waited to arrest him in a massive graft probe that has put the country's most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elusive molecule, first in Universe, detected in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/elusive-molecule-first-universe-detected-space-doc-1fq04m1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  SAMSUNG fold screen breaks after day of use...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/4/17/18411510/samsung-galaxy-fold-broken-screen-debris-dust-hinge-flexible-bulge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yikes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese block visit of Trump confidant...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-denies-visa-to-us-expert-michael-pillsbury-1bf32caa-2b4c-422b-bac3-19bb20c439b0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese experts seeking to visit the U.S. have also been rejected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar bear lost in Russia, hundreds of miles from home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/880824c34e324626a037847474d1dbe4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Residents of a village in Russia's far eastern Kamchatka Peninsula were stunned by the sight of a polar bear prowling for food hundreds of miles away from its usual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naval Academy To Bar Trans Students...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/04/17/naval-academy-will-bar-transgender-students-in-fall-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Naval Academy will ban people who are transgender from attending the school, beginning with the 2020 school year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both sides want Weinstein hearing closed to press, public...</title>
      <link>https://www.theeagle.com/entertainment/both-sides-want-weinstein-hearing-closed-to-press-public/article_aa4d856f-8158-5cd0-b235-1fb803386a41.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Both sides in Harvey Weinstein's sexual assault case want the media and the public barred from the disgraced movie mogul's next court appearance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK working on voice assistant...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/17/facebook-building-voice-assistant-to-rival-amazon-alexa-and-apple-siri.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team in Redmond, Washington, is working to build a competitor to Alexa, Siri, and the Google Assistant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Brexit Party opens up lead in European elections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brexit-party-opens-lead-european-elections-poll-154527248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Brexit Party set up by anti-EU firebrand Nigel Farage is leading Britain's other political parties ahead of European Parliament elections in May, according to an opinion poll published on Wednesday. The new party, which formally launched its campaign for next month's votes on Friday, has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron to executive produce boxing series...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c415f2b2ceb148d4975be3ce31730e18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — LeBron James is getting into the boxing business. James is an executive producer of "40 Days," a documentary series about the buildup to big fights that will debut with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITISH AIRWAYS yanks FT after critical coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressgazette.co.uk/british-airways-has-stopped-offering-financial-times-over-coverage-of-airline-source-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressgazette.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Airways has stopped stocking the Financial Times in a reaction to the paper's journalism, a source has claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning strike at Acropolis injures 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190417-lightning-strike-acropolis-greece-injures-four</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lightning strike at Acropolis, Greece, injures four</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared electric scooters surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/deec1b3bc84e41b88fb41aba0ea83c16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Electric scooters are overtaking station-based bicycles as the most popular form of shared transportation outside transit and cars in the U.S. Riders took 38.5 million trips...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare look at West Point Mint's massive gold vaults...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/west-point-mint-gold-inside-look</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About an hour and a half&amp;rsquo;s drive north from New York City lies a treasure &amp;ndash; the gold kind. But it&amp;rsquo;s not one that you can go and find.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Biden aide: 'Everything going ahead as scheduled'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/17/politics/biden-aide-hill-democrats-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top aide to former Vice President Joe Biden met with Democrats on Capitol Hill on Wednesday to remind them of Biden's work in the 2018 midterm elections in a not-so-subtle nod to the 2020 race ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar doing FOX NEWS town hall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/439313-klobuchar-to-appear-in-fox-news-town-hall-in-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News announced on Wednesday that it will feature a town hall with 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Sen. Amy Klobuchar (D-Minn.) next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds swarm NYC streets in censorship protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Over-100-New-Yorkers-Will-Pose-Nude-508656351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This June, artist Spencer Tunick has organized an event to challenge Facebook and Instagram’s “Community Guidelines” by organizing a large-scale nude photography shoot in New York City called #WeTheNipple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant in coma after contracting measles...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/17/health/measles-israel-flight-attendant/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli flight attendant has slipped into a coma after contracting measles, according to health officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Starr Fears Anti-Trump Screed...</title>
      <link>https://video.foxnews.com/v/6027126662001/#sp=show-clips</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;video.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many questions have been raised about the political leanings of special counsel Robert Mueller's staff and their freedom to write whatever they want, former independent counsel Ken Starr says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Laguna Beach Votes To Keep Patriotic Patrol Cars After Debate...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/04/16/laguna-beach-american-flag-police-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's official. The red, white and blue will stay on Laguna Beach police patrol cars. The decision followed a debate. Some people wondered if it was even appropriate to place an abstract version of the flag on patrol cars. Stacey Butler reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHASE Bank shuts down 'alt-right' accounts...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2019/04/major-u-s-bank-shuts-down-alt-right-accounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chase Bank is shutting down accounts of people and organizations with controversial political views, according to an undercover investigation by James O’Keefe’s Project Veritas. O’Keefe’s latest probe found that Chase, without explanation, abruptly closed the account of a political activist that had existed for 15 years in good standing. Enrique Tarrio, chairman of the Proud […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORPORATE CENSORSHIP ALARM...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-review-repeat-offender-11555455821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Hollywood-connected libertine takes aim at liberals and then trolls them with some well-worn conservative tropes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PSYCHO' AUTHOR RIPS TRUMP HATING CRAZIES!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/bret-easton-ellis-tells-spoiled-children-liberals-how-to-deal-with-trump-he-was-elected-president-get-over-it'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE HOLLYWOOD  HYSTERICS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/bret-easton-ellis-white-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My job isn’t to trigger millennials into hysteria," Ellis says, "but I have to say that when it happens, it’s rather delicious."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCUSED OF POACHING 'MADAME X' PERSONA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/apr/15/madame-x-madonna-new-album-alter-ego</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a Sargent painting to a miffed DJ, Madonna is just the latest woman to adopt the moniker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suprise Beyonce release wrecks rollout...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/04/17/beyonce-drops-surprise-film-and-album-goes-straight-to-number-1-wrecks-madonnas-launch-of-new-medellin-single</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beyonce is back! Her 40 track live “Homecoming” album was dropped overnight by Sony/Columbia and is number 1 on the iTunes album chart. In two places– Number 1 and Number 5. Like,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PORN BAN SET FOR SUMMER...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/uk-porn-ban-july-deadline-when-date-online-websites-adult-age-verification-a8874181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 60: MADONNA ATTEMPTS COMEBACK OF THE CENTURY!</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/columns/pop/8507435/madonna-madame-x-album-what-we-know</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna is coming. On Sunday (April 14), the pop icon announced the title of her fourteenth studio album, Madame X, after two weeks of teasing the project on Instagram. While a release date has yet to be announced, here’s everything we know about the Material Girl’s first LP since 2015’s Rebel Heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIGGERS WITH FIRST NON-FICTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/White-Bret-Easton-Ellis/dp/0525656308/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW SONG TRIBUTE TO MEDELLIN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/music/2019/04/14/madonna-new-music-madame-x/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The queen is back. Madonna announced Sunday her long-awaited return to pop music, unveiling a mysterious Instagram video in which…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER EDITS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f10d72362c374301b6505459b23bbd7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The special counsel's Trump-Russia report will be out on Thursday for all to see. But not all of it. The Democrats' demands for a full, unredacted version of Robert...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
