<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Lethal' U.S. Military Aid Arriving in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/-lethal-u-s-military-aid-begins-arriving-in-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. military aid to help Ukraine defend against a possible invasion by Russia has began arriving on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Down $20 Billion!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-21/bezos-loses-20-billion-in-brutal-week-for-tech-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Loses HALF Value Since Record High...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/bitcoin-extends-slide-fallen-more-101904421.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin extended its decline on Saturday, and has shed more than 50% from its record high in November while adding further momentum to the meltdown in cryptocurrencies.Most Read from BloombergCrypto Crash Erases More Than $1 Trillion in Market ValueTech Leads Stocks to Worst Week Since March 2020: Markets WrapBitcoin Chart Hints at Possible Floor for SlideNasdaq 100’s Unrelenting Declines Ring a Dot-Com Bust Alarm BellJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has St</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida wave worse than data shows?</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/health/2022/01/21/floridas-omicron-wave-could-be-worse-than-data-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missing data and strained testing infrastructure hamper the ability of experts to track COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Schwarzenegger involved in LA car crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/22/us/arnold-schwarzenegger-car-crash/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor and former California Gov. Arnold Schwarzenegger was involved in a multi-vehicle crash Friday evening in Los Angeles with a representative telling People magazine that he wasn't hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Canadians shot dead at upscale Mexican resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-60092429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident began as an argument among guests, one of whom was the gunman, at the hotel near Cancún.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big Tech elites helping China achieve global supremacy...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/22/how-tech-elites-are-helping-china-achieve-global-supremacy-new-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blinded by their ambition, Silicon Valley elites are helping Communist China achieve their ultimate goal: “Technology supremacy” over the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WUHAN, I AM HERE': Film follows volunteers in sealed city...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-health-arts-and-entertainment-beijing-af173d919d502acd1f14e58767129d5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The homeless, the sick, the elderly: For people who fell through the cracks of the official system, the then-unprecedented decision to isolate the central Chinese city of Wuhan and its 13 million people was a matter of life or death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39% Americans boosted...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/booster-shots-in-us-have-strongly-protected-against-severe-disease-from-omicron-variant-cdc-studies-show/ar-AAT0Ijs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron has changed shape of pandemic. Will it end it for good?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/22/world/omicron-changed-pandemic-intl-cmd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world feared the worst when a worrying new coronavirus variant emerged in late November and ripped through South Africa at a pace not seen before in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Weighs Evacuating Diplomat Family Members From Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-weighs-pulling-diplomats-family-150322370.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. is weighing whether to evacuate family members of diplomats stationed in Ukraine as Russia masses more than 100,000 troops on its borders, according to people familiar with the matter.Most Read from BloombergJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has StartedTech Leads Late-Day Slide in Stocks; Bitcoin Sinks: Markets WrapCrypto Selloff Pushes Bitcoin to a Six-Month Low of $38,000American Airlines Sues The Points Guy Over Its Rewards Management AppEarly Om</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ Unrelenting Declines Ring Dot-Com Bust Alarm Bell...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-100-unrelenting-drops-ring-214018521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bulls should be glad there were only four days this week instead of five.Most Read from BloombergCrypto Crash Erases More Than $1 Trillion in Market ValueTech Leads Stocks to Worst Week Since March 2020: Markets WrapBitcoin Chart Hints at Possible Floor for SlideJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has StartedNasdaq 100’s Unrelenting Declines Ring a Dot-Com Bust Alarm BellTo wit, the Nasdaq 100 just did something it hasn’t done since the aftermath of the intern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck with 100 monkeys crashes, some of them missing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-pennsylvania-monkeys-animals-52100c02527985f7dde4674724bb3332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANVILLE, Pa. (AP) — A truck carrying about 100 monkeys was involved in a crash Friday in Pennsylvania, state police said as authorities searched for at least three of the monkeys that appeared to have escaped the vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THICH NHAT HANH DEAD AT 95...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/thich-nhat-hanh-poetic-peace-activist-and-master-of-mindfulness-dies-at-95/ar-AAT1gqP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-abortion activists march in DC, hoping it's last time under Roe v. Wade...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/nations-largest-abortion-protest-roe-82389718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual anti-abortion rally in the nation’s capital sounded more like a victory celebration Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force struggles to recruit...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2022/01/21/air-forces-enlisted-recruitment-pipeline-is-drying-up-general-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 4,800 people entered the Air Force in the first quarter of fiscal 2022, down from around 7,100 at the same point in fiscal 2021. And there are fewer prospects in the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds to monitor for violence, extremist activity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/federal-officials-to-monitor-wasington-anti-vaccine-rally-for-potential-violence-and-extremist-activity-223850442.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal law enforcement in Washington, D.C., have been closely monitoring social media for signs of potential violence and extremist activity ahead of a large demonstration against vaccine mandates this weekend, according to documents obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients hospitalized 'with' vs. 'for' shifting...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2022/01/21/number-of-patients-hospitalized-with-covid-vs-for-covid-is-shifting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But health experts say hospitals are still under strain and the virus remains serious business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunfire Erupts at Ritzy Cancun Resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/gunfire-erupts-at-ritzy-playa-del-carmen-resort-one-dead/ar-AAT1i0z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unfiltered Year of Aaron Rodgers...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33088151/the-unfiltered-year-aaron-rodgers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This season, Aaron Rodgers has been brilliant on the field and unapologetically vocal off it. In an exclusive interview with ESPN, he explains why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for scapegoat leads to chief of staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/klain-under-scrutiny-biden-struggles-n1287801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the president rounds out his first year in office with multiple setbacks in his agenda and a sinking approval rating, some blame his chief of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 years since Covid confirmed in USA. Pandemic worse than anyone imagined...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/omicron-two-years-since-covid-was-first-confirmed-in-us-the-pandemic-is-worse-than-anyone-imagined.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the emergence of omicron, the future course of the pandemic is unclear as experts struggle to understand how new variants emerge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Media Doomed?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/01/21/media-journalism-future-527294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a Big Tech crackdown to the rebirth of local news, 16 future-minded thinkers predict where journalism will be in 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNIVES OUT FOR KLAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/21/ron-klain-hot-water-527570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s chief of staff started strong and earned plaudits. But, increasingly, he’s under scrutiny for the state of the presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA wants to turn poo into 'space gold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4513028/nasa-wants-to-recycle-poo-human-waste-space-missions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is trying to work out how to recycle human waste, including poo and the carbon dioxide we breathe out, into useful products. Recycling waste could help astronauts go on longer missions without…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO REFUNDS?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/21/stubhub-adele-fans-wont-get-money-back-until-singer-reschedules-shows-cant-resell-tickets-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREET-PORTER: Sorry, can't take self-obsessed never-ending Sob Saga...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-10428345/JANET-STREET-PORTER-just-chapter-Adeles-never-ending-Sob-Saga.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANET STREET-PORTER: Adele has made millions from mining the trauma of her 'journey' from humble beginnings to millionaire single mum - but I have decided to get off the bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX judge blocks vax mandate for federal workers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/21/texas-judge-blocks-biden-vaccine-mandate-for-federal-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling by Judge Jeffrey Brown stated that the order “amounts to a presidential mandate that all federal employees consent to vaccination against COVID-19 or lose their jobs.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In time for Olympics, China brings back anal swab testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4512129/china-anal-swabs-covid-mandatory-winter-olympics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has brought back its “undignified” anal Covid swabs just two weeks before the Beijing Winter Olympics begin. The Communist regime claims the virus test — which involves inserting …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Crash Erases $1 Trillion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crypto-meltdown-erases-more-1-171931934.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For Bitcoin, there’s only been one constant recently: decline after decline after decline. And the superlatives have piled up really quickly.Most Read from BloombergJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has StartedTech Leads Late-Day Slide in Stocks; Bitcoin Sinks: Markets WrapEarly Omicron Breakthroughs Show mRNA Vaccines’ WeaknessCrypto Selloff Pushes Bitcoin to a Six-Month Low of $38,000American Airlines Sues The Points Guy Over Its Rewards Management AppWith</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French politicians worry about surge in pre-election violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220121-french-politicians-worry-about-surge-in-pre-election-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French ruling party lawmaker Pascal Bois was at home asleep a few days after Christmas when firefighters banged on his front door to tell him his garage was in flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's largest abortion protest could be last under Roe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-texas-mississippi-constitutions-281018c3cd29f79d02444a539bc16d63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Arriving by the busloads, thousands of anti-abortion protesters rallied in the nation’s capital Friday with a growing sense of optimism that their goal was finally in reach: a sweeping rollback of abortion rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probe gets over 700 pages of White House docs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/january-6-riot-probe-gets-over-700-pages-of-trump-white-house-documents-after-supreme-court-ruling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The January 6 Capitol riot by Trump supporters began after Donald Trump falsely claimed he won the 2020 election over President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone -- that you sit in...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-59372326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal drones that can transport one or two passengers will soon be available for anyone to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physicists developed bubble that didn't burst for more than year...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/french-physicists-developed-bubble-didnt-burst-year-rcna13077</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French physicists have figured out a way to extend the usually short lives of bubbles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lonely final years of Andre Leon Talley...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10419739/Andr-Leon-Talley-spent-final-years-White-Plains-avoiding-covid-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;André Leon Talley, a fashion icon and driving and driving force behind Vogue's success, spent his last days secluded at home trying to protect himself from the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle, Detroit Move Toward Decriminalizing Psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/20/seattle-and-detroit-move-toward-decriminalizing-psychedelics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two major cities, Seattle and Detroit, this fall approved measures aimed at protecting consumers of "entheogenic" plants and fungi from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are men drinking breast milk?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/why-are-men-drinking-breast-milk/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fetishists and bodybuilders have created a booming black market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic darlings fade as investors eye return to normal life...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-dump-pandemic-darlings-results-101014650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (Reuters) -Stay-at-home market darling Netflix slumped on Friday, joining a broad decline in shares of other pandemic favourites this week as investors priced in expectations for a return to normal life with more countries gradually relaxing COVID restrictions. The selloff, which began after Netflix and Peloton posted disappointing quarterly earnings, spread to the wider stay-at-home sector as analysts judged the new Omicron coronavirus variant will not deliver the same economic headwinds seen in the first phase of the pandemic in 2020. "This a confirmation that the economy is gradually moving towards some sort of normalisation," said Andrea Cicione, head of strategy at TS Lombard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39% IN USA GET BOOSTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/booster-shots-in-us-have-strongly-protected-against-severe-disease-from-omicron-variant-cdc-studies-show/ar-AAT0Ijs?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF THE DIGITAL DOLLAR?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-federal-reserve-is-taking-the-next-step-toward-possibly-launching-a-digital-dollar/ar-AASZ8Vk?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF MARKET SUPERBUBBLE?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/good-luck-well-all-need-it-u-s-market-approaches-end-of-superbubble-says-jeremy-grantham-11642723516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is approaching the end of a 'superbubble,' potentially leading to the largest markdown of wealth in its history when pessimism returns to rule...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid  retreating? Data paints encouraging scenario...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-retreating-u-data-paints-120602648.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) -New coronavirus cases are falling in parts of the United States hit hardest by the fast-spreading Omicron variant, according to a Reuters analysis of public health data, offering an early indication the virus might once again be in retreat. COVID-19 infections have decreased in 19 states https://graphics.reuters.com/HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-OMICRON/zgvomadgmvd/USA-OMICRON.jpg plus Washington, D.C. and Puerto Rico, an analysis of the past week through Thursday compared with the prior week showed. In the Northeast, which saw some of the highest case loads during the latest surge, infections are down 40% week-over-week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAT LOAF DEAD AT 74...</title>
      <link>https://www.spin.com/2022/01/meatloaf-bat-out-of-hell-singer-dies-at-74/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meatloaf, the legendary '70s rock singer whose album 'Bat Out of Hell' became one of the best selling albums of all time, died</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX STOCK CRASHES AFTER SUB MISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/netflix-stock-down-20percent-after-earnings-show-growth-slowdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company still beat analyst expectations on the top and bottom line and in user numbers during the fourth quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Benedict XVI and the long history of scandal-plagued popes...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pope-Benedict-XVI-and-the-long-history-of-16793703.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic Pope emeritus Benedict XVI committed "wrongdoing" in the way he handled sexual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent killings shock NYC, bring back bad memories...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/news/violent-killings-shock-ny-bring-back-bad-memories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One was thrown in front of an incoming subway train in Times Square. The other was shot over a few dollars at a burger joint. These recent violent deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUIE ANDERSON DEAD AT 68...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/01/louie-anderson-dead-obituary-comedian-baskets-family-feud-emmy-winner-1234917040/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louie Anderson, the veteran comedian, game show host and three-time Emmy winner, has died. He was 68. The Baskets star died Friday morning in Las Vegas, where he had entered hospital this week for …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUIE ANDERSON DEAD AT 68...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/21/louie-anderson-dead-dies-blood-cancer-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louie Anderson Dead At 68, After Battle With Blood Cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic darlings face boot as investors eye return to normal life...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-stayhome-stocks-2022-01-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stay-at-home market darling Netflix slumped on Friday, joining a broad decline in the market value of other pandemic favourites this week as investors priced in expectations for a return to normality as more countries gradually relax COVID restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis won't say if boosted; Status could be used as 'weapon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/desantis-won-e2-80-99t-say-if-he-e2-80-99s-boosted-against-covid-19-says-status-could-be-used-as-e2-80-98weapon-e2-80-99/ar-AAT0HtA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
