<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Wall Impasse Frustrates Many Newly Elected House Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wall-impasse-frustrates-many-newly-elected-house-democrats-11547380801?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some House Democrats, many who beat Republicans in the 2018 midterms, want party leadership to chart a clearer strategy in trying to end the government shutdown and compromise with President Trump on border security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Turn to Emergency Loans...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/government-workers-idled-by-shutdown-turn-to-emergency-loans-11547246027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of workers affected by the government shutdown have applied for emergency loans and requested delays in mortgage payments, as many of them on Friday missed their first paycheck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS PARTY IN PUERTO RICO DURING SHUTDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/30-dems-in-puerto-rico-with-109-lobbyists-for-weekend-despite-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 30 Democratic lawmakers left the government shutdown behind Friday on a chartered flight to Puerto Rico for a winter retreat with 109 lobbyists and corporate executives during which they planned to see the hit Broadway show “Hamilton” and attend three parties including one with the show’s cast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed feedback for Kamala Harris in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/12/us/politics/kamala-harris-democrats.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“She’s my first choice to be my first choice.” In Manhattan, voters met Ms. Harris, a Democratic senator from California, as she prepares for a possible presidential run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's famous 'walled garden' starting to show cracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/09/apple-walled-garden-starting-to-show-cracks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple will have to look beyond its tight ecosystem of hardware and software if it wants to grow its services business</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Oversight Chair Cummings to 'Hit Ground "Flying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elijah-cummings-talks-to-60-minutes-in-first-interview-as-house-oversight-committee-chairman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new chair of the House Oversight and Reform Committee tells 60 Minutes he’ll have to hit the ground “flying” with majority power to investigate the Trump administration. Sunday at 7 p.m. ET/PT on CBS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez becomes TWITTER queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ocasio-cortez-dominates-twitter-6a997938-b8a5-4a8b-a895-0a1bcd073fea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freshman congresswoman who has held office for a week is dominating the national conversation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US govt has amassed terabytes of internal WIKILEAKS data...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-u-s-government-has-amassed-terabytes-of-internal-w-1831640212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late last year, the U.S. government accidentally revealed that a sealed complaint had been filed against Julian Assange, the founder of WikiLeaks. Shortly before this was made public, the FBI reconfirmed its investigation of WikiLeaks was ongoing, and the Wall Street Journal reported that the Department of Justice was optimistic that it would be able to extradite Assange. Soon after, portions of sealed transcripts leaked that implicate WikiLeaks and Assange in directing hackers to target governments and corporations. The charges against Assange have not been officially revealed, though it’s plausible that the offenses are related to Russian hacking and the DNC emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Using Space Launch to Test ICBMs...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-space-launch-cover-for-test-of-nuclear-capable-missile-tech-u-s-determines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. says Iran's planned launch of satellites into space is actually a cover for the regime's continued testing of advanced missile technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Ever Woman To Officiate NFL Playoff Game...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/01/11/sarah-thomas-nfl-history-inspiring-female-football-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Thomas will be the first woman to officiate an NFL playoff game. Among all the eyes sure to be on her – a special group of supporters – her fellow female football officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska eyes regulations on the word 'meat'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7924a64199e46da88488d5a0fe8c7bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINCOLN, Neb. (AP) — More than four months after Missouri became the first U.S. state to regulate the term "meat" on product labels, Nebraska's powerful farm groups are pushing for similar protection from veggie burgers, tofu dogs and other items that look and taste like real meat. Nebraska lawmakers will consider a bill this year to prevent companies that package and sell food from advertising plant-based, insect-based and lab-grown products as meat. Similar measures are pending in Tennessee, Virginia and Wyoming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Stagecraft won't win battle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb78c70cbe3345e7b77946d004e9dff3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Military salutes. Heaps of contraband. Oval Office optics. President Donald Trump, who has long put a premium on stagecraft, is discovering he cannot resolve the partial government shutdown simply by putting on a show. With the standoff over paying for his long-promised U.S.-Mexico wall dragging on, the president's Oval Office address and visit to the Texas border this past week failed to break the logjam. Aides and allies are fearful that he has misjudged Democratic resolve and is running out of negotiating options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'First Amendment auditors' dangerous, terrorism experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article224221620.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed with cameras and sometimes handguns, “First Amendment auditors” are roaming government buildings and police stations across the country. Some worry their confrontations could turn violent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt university expels female student for hugging male friend...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190113-egypt-university-expels-female-student-hugging-male-friend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egypt university expels female student for hugging male friend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German WWI U-boat resurfaces off French coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/12/europe/german-uboat-northern-france-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Low tides have revealed a relic from World War I -- the skeleton of a German U-boat visible again off the coast of northern France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jet slides off Ohio taxiway...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/2019/01/13/cvg-delta-aircraft-slid-off-pavement-way-terminal/2563785002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airport remains open and operational.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON myth of lone genius founder...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/mackenzie-bezos-amazon-lone-genius-myth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even juicy divorce speculation represents a chance to acknowledge how myriad factors—and people—contribute to the success of a company like Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST 72 HOURS? May could be out Wednesday if she loses Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8182345/theresa-may-brexit-deal-vote-of-no-confidence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May could be forced out as soon as Wednesday if her Brexit deal collapses, it was claimed today. Jeremy Corbyn wants to bring down the Government this week after the Commons vote on Mrs May…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England's Strange Case of Decapitated Bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/englands-strange-case-of-decapitated-bodies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During construction in England a grisly discovery was made. Nearly half of 52 skeletons in a Roman burial ground had been buried with the skulls between the legs of the deceased.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Is MacKenzie Bezos?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Who-Is-MacKenzie-Bezos-13528982.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her 25 years of marriage to Jeff Bezos, MacKenzie Bezos has been a loyal ambassador for Amazon, the company that made her and her husband the richest couple in the world. She was an integral part of its origin story, driving to Seattle in 1994 while Jeff Bezos sat in the passenger seat, working on the nascent company's business plan. She was Amazon's first accountant and was involved in its transformation from a small online bookseller to the e-commerce behemoth it is today, the second company in American history to be valued at over $1 trillion. MacKenzie Bezos, 48, is a novelist. But Amazon has defined her public image almost wholly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old, young, liberal, centrist: Dems have no end of choices for president in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/us-politics/la-na-pol-democratic-presidential-field-20190113-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential primary candidate field could be the largest on record. Democrats will not only be choosing a nominee, but deciding what kind of party they want to be. Here's a field guide to the candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS ESCAPE SHUTDOWN IN PUERTO RICO</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/democrats-fly-to-puerto-rico-amid-ongoing-government-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a partial government shutdown with no end in sight, 30 Democratic members of Congress are gathering in Puerto Rico this weekend with their families and lobbyists for a winter retreat in which they planned to see the hit Broadway show, “Hamilton.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman banned from WALMART for riding cart, drinking wine from PRINGLES can...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/woman-banned-from-walmart-after-riding-cart-while-drinking-wine-from-pringles-can-police-say/pUtXPnUokStQiaJLC0FE1O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police were called to a Texas Walmart after a woman was reportedly drinking wine from a Pringles can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort developments trigger new 'collusion' debate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/424986-manafort-developments-trigger-new-collusion-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelation that President Trump’s former campaign chairman Paul Manafort allegedly shared polling data with a Russian suspected of ties to Kremlin intelligence during the 2016 presidential race has triggered fresh debate about “collusion” in W</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More cities add Obama's name to landmarks, highways...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/01/13/barack-obama-former-president-african-american-black-naming-renaming-freeway-highway/2539917002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York, Chicago and Los Angeles are all have efforts underway to name things after America's first African-American president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rock Says 'Snowflake Generation' Interview '100% Fabricated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/marcusjones/the-rock-says-snow-flake-interview-fake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial story which the actor called "100% fabricated" was wiped from the Daily Star's website Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: President, Republcians blamed for shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-gop-blamed-shutdown-crisis-fewer-oppose-wall/story?id=60337670</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new ABC News/Washington Post poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Promise Probe of President Meetings With Putin... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/democrats-promise-probe-of-trump-meetings-with-putin-11547356133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats on Saturday said they would explore allegations President Trump has sought to limit documentation of his meetings with Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New American Leader Rises in ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2018/01/isis-america-hoxha/550508/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A two-year investigation identifies one of the very few Americans in the Islamic State’s upper ranks—and sheds light on the dynamics of radicalization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felons turn out to voter registration rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article224372665.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City of Miami Gardens hosted a voter registration drive on Saturday to celebrate the passage of Amendment 4, which allowed the state’s felons to automatically regain their right to vote. It is estimated to affect more than 1.2 million felons in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Dems must 'come to senses' on border security...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-on-justice-with-judge-jeanine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump says that what's happening along the U.S.-Mexico border constitutes a “humanitarian crisis,” telling Fox News that if Democrats “don’t come to their senses” he’ll declare a national emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterans Affairs could let vets see private doctors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/12/department-of-veterans-affairs-could-let-vets-see-private-doctors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Veterans Affairs is considering new rules that would give vets more freedom to see private doctors outside the federal system, potentially shifting billions of dollars of federal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX laying off 10% of workforce...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/01/11/684723473/spacex-to-lay-off-10-percent-of-its-workforce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesman said the reduction would not be necessary except for "extraordinarily difficult challenges ahead."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHIEFS, RAMS dominate...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/nfl/story/rams-run-over-cowboys-chiefs-dominate-colts-011219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL Playoff Capsules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No idea' if deal can be made with Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f623603a26f942a88bb07bc4111eb26d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As the partial government shutdown slipped into the record books, members of Congress had left town, no negotiations were scheduled and President Donald Trump tweeted into the void. The president did not tip his hand Saturday on whether he will move ahead with an emergency declaration that could break the impasse, free up money for his wall without congressional approval and kick off legal challenges and a political storm over the use of that extraordinary step. A day earlier, he said he was not ready to do it "right now."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest person record stood for decades. Then came conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-world-s-oldest-person-record-stood-for-13528896.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The email came just hours into the new year, landing in the inboxes of the two renowned French gerontologists who had validated the age of the oldest person ever documented in the modern world. Also copied was the consultant who analyzed age-related cases for the Guinness World Records, which had given Jeanne Calment the title before she died at 122 in 1997. "Colleagues, take action, take evidence for verification," read the email, from the account of Russian doctor Valery Novoselov, continuing in cryptically rendered English. "Otherwise, there will be many people who will want to participate in this show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Bezos Shared Wife's Pillow Talk With Mistress, Boasted About U2 Bono...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalenquirer.com/celebrity/jeff-bezos-shared-wifes-pillow-talk-with-mistress-lauren-sanchez/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalenquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RANDY tech tycoon Jeff Bezos shared bedroom talk with his long-suffering WIFE to his MISTRESS — as the suspecting spouse began to question him about their affair. In another blockbuster text messag...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINTER WALLOP!</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-01-11-winter-storm-gia-impacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the latest impacts from Winter Storm Gia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest protests hit with police water cannon, tear gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests/renewed-yellow-vest-protests-hit-with-police-water-cannon-tear-gas-in-paris-idUSKCN1P60GX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris police fired water cannon and tear gas to push back "yellow vest"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Serial predator': LA writer sounding alarm on Dem donor for year...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/serial-predator-l-writer-has-been-sounding-alarm-ed-buck-n957776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long before a second man died in the political donor's home, writer Jasmyne Cannick has been publishing accounts from his alleged victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hi, I'm Tom Brady': How 41-year-old QB relates to teammates...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Hi-I-m-Tom-Brady-How-the-Patriots-13528788.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. - Phillip Dorsett sat on a table inside the New England Patriots' training room, having just completed the physical that made him an official member of the franchise. Just then, one of his new teammates entered the room and walked straight toward him. "Hi," the teammate said. "I'm Tom Brady." "I'm like, I know who you are," Dorsett said this week, laughing. "You don't have to introduce yourself." Dorsett, a wide receiver, is like almost every other Patriot. As Brady was winning Super Bowls and becoming an international celebrity, Dorsett was growing up. He was 9 when Brady won his first Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castro launches...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/julian-castro-announcement-2020-white-house-bid-candidate-for-president-today-views-stance-issues-age-live-updates-01-12-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 44-year-old former HUD secretary formed a presidential exploratory committee in December</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Sickouts Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/rate-of-tsa-sickouts-rises-as-u-s-government-shutdown-drags-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rate of TSA Sickouts Rises as U.S. Government Shutdown Drags on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In states, Dems start delivering on health care pledges...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bd8bb50ed7f7457fa560f8c1ae718eb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Riding the momentum from November's elections, Democratic leaders in the states are wasting no time delivering on their biggest campaign promise — to expand access to health care and make it more affordable. The first full week of state legislative sessions and swearings-in for governors saw a flurry of proposals. In his initial actions, newly elected California Gov. Gavin Newsom announced plans to expand Medicaid to those in the country illegally up to age 26, implement a mandate that everyone buy insurance or face a fine, and consolidate the state's prescription drug purchases in the hope that it will dramatically lower costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUT LONGEST EVER</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b3867898a78740f39d8cc8538c5db196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The partial government shutdown became the longest closure in U.S. history when the clock ticked past midnight into early Saturday as President Donald Trump and nervous Republicans scrambled to find a way out of the mess. A solution couldn't come soon enough for federal workers who got pay statements Friday but no pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology brings images of Holocaust survivors to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9fcf828b8d454169b7ebea8819ddbaed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Max Glauben was 17 and had already lost his mother, father and brother at the hands of the Nazis when U.S. troops rescued him while he was on a death march from one German concentration camp to another. The recollections of the Dallas resident who as a Jew in Poland survived the Warsaw Ghetto and Nazi concentration camps are now being preserved in a way that will allow generations to come to ask his image questions. Glauben, who turns 91 on Monday, is the latest Holocaust survivor recorded in such a way by the University of Southern California Shoah Foundation . The Los Angeles-based foundation has recorded 18 interactive testimonies with Holocaust survivors over the last several years, and executive director Stephen Smith says they're in a "race against time" as they work to add more, seeking both a diversity in experiences and testimonies in a variety of languages.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
