<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Massive 'Pipeline' in Cosmic Web Connecting Universe...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkd4nn/scientists-discover-massive-pipeline-in-the-cosmic-web-connecting-the-universe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study reveals “by far the best evidence” for the elusive cosmic filaments that supercharge ancient galaxies with cold gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief of staff at center of controversy over White House budget pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-s-chief-of-staff-at-center-of-controversy-over-white-house-budget-pick/ar-BB1e1ezv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Chief of Staff Ron Klain has been second-guessed by some Biden allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jab May Create 'Terminator' Antibody Response In People Who Have Had Virus...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/02/25/vaccine-create-terminator-type-antibody-response-people-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS4 Medical Editor Dr. Dave Hnida shared his advice about the new questions being raised concerning whether or not people who've had COVID-19 need two doses of the vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked man carrying Bible shot while knocking on doors in FL...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/florida/2021/02/25/naked-man-carrying-bible-shot-outside-florida-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say a naked man who was knocking on doors at a South Florida apartment complex was shot by someone who then called 911 to turn himself in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OXFORD virus lab hacked by cyber gang...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210225190914-joyrc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-CYBER (URGENT):Oxford University COVID-19 laboratory hacked by cyber gang -Telegraph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/02/25/lady-gaga-dog-walker-french-bulldogs-stolen-video-surveillance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We've obtained video of the horrifying shooting of Lady Gaga's dog walker and abduction of her dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailed Putin critic Navalny moved, probably to prison camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/jailed-putin-critic-navalny-moved-probably-to-prison-camp-660250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept presses fight against Omarosa...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/19/biden-justice-department-omarosa-470143</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new brief takes an aggressive stance against outspoken Trump critic Omarosa Manigault Newman in a financial disclosure flap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everything Has Been Criminalized,' Says Justice Gorsuch...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/25/everything-has-been-criminalized-says-neil-gorsuch-as-he-pushes-for-stronger-fourth-amendment-protections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The justice weighs in during oral arguments in Lange v. California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Cuba's economy worsens, desperate rafters risk lives at sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/i-cant-buy-food-as-cubas-economy-worsens-desperate-rafters-risk-their-lives-at-sea/ar-BB1e0CqL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feb. 25—Marisol Monteagudo's son gave her a kiss goodbye as he headed out the door to spend a night out with friends in Cuba's Isla de la Juventud. What he didn't tell her: That instead of grabbing a drink or watching a movie, they were planning to board a flimsy raft en route to Mexico. That was three months ago. She hasn't heard from him since. "Only a mother can understand this pain," ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Potato Head goes gender neutral...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mr-potato-head-goes-gender-neutral-d3c178f2b9b0c424ed814657be41a9d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Mr. Potato Head is no longer a mister. Hasbro, the company that makes the potato-shaped plastic toy, is giving the spud a gender neutral new name: Potato Head. The change...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: No 'final decision' on participation in Olympics in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-olympics-2022-usa/white-house-has-not-made-final-decision-on-participation-in-olympics-in-china-idUSKBN2AP2JV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has not made a final decision on participation in the Winter Olympics in Beijing, a spokeswoman said on Thursday, as Republican lawmakers call for the United States to boycott the Games in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops will be giving doses in Philly, Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/02/25/troops-will-be-giving-vaccines-in-philadelphia-florida-in-coming-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of troops have been deployed across the country to vaccinate in cities hardest-hit by COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK 'Supreme Court' to receive new powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/facebook-supreme-court-thomas-hughes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oversight Board is expected to be able to review whether content still online breaks the tech giant’s community standards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police chief warns extremists 'want to blow up Capitol'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/capitol-law-enforcement-heads-detail-intelligence-failures-leading-jan-6-n1258829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acting chief said members of militia groups want to "kill as many members as possible" in an attack during Biden's upcoming address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65,640 Minutes! Painfully Long Wait Times On MA Vaccine Website...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/25/massachusetts-covid-vaccine-vaxfinder-ma-gov-website-appointments-waiting-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of new vaccine appointments became available Thursday as a new website waiting room was launched, but the waits were agonizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticket to ride: Passports divide world...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210225-ticket-to-ride-vaccine-passports-divide-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ticket to ride: Vaccine passports divide world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France, Germany brace for ANOTHER lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14156386/merkel-germany-lockdown-oxford-jab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE and Germany are now both braced for further Covid lockdowns after they shunned the Oxford vaccine. It comes as a German virologist today revealed the country was sitting on a whopping 1.2 mi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCartney Plans $100 Memoir Told Through Lyrics and Memorabilia...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/02/24/paul-mccartney-plans-memoir-told-through-two-volumes-of-lyrics-with-memorabilia-as-holiday-gift-box</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul McCartney been busy through the pandemic, that’s for sure. First he released the much praised “McCartney III” and it was his first real number 1 album in 31 years. Now he&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi crown prince approved killing of Khashoggi, U.S. intelligence report concludes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/new-public-report-blame-saudi-crown-prince-2018-killing-jamal-n1258800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The release will mark a new chapter in U.S.-Saudi relations and a clear break from Trump's policy of equivocating about the Saudi state's role in the brutal murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly NYC woman murdered with machete...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-78-found-slashed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police responding to reports of an unconscious person found a 78-year-old woman dead in her bedroom in Queens with a slash to her head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems hesitant to move on taxes increases amid pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/540427-democrats-hesitant-to-move-on-taxes-amid-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden declared during the campaign that he would repeal the Trump tax cuts on “day one,” but after more than a month in office, some key Democratic lawmakers say they are reluctant to raise taxes during an economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyday chemicals threatening future of human fertility...</title>
      <link>https://futurehuman.medium.com/humans-may-not-be-able-to-reproduce-naturally-much-longer-scientist-warns-bd3b9dbbf859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurehuman.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyday chemicals are threatening the future of human fertility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks fall as yields continue to climb; GAMESTOP surges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/game-stop-surges-eaef3fd5ff0a536a8ada4a4f7afce4d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks were mostly lower in the early going Thursday as the recent theme of the market — rising bond yields and falling prices of technology companies — continued to weigh on trading....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$500,000 Offered For Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/02/25/lada-gaga-bull-dogs-stolen-dog-walker-shot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga's dogs were targeted by thieves Wednesday night ... thieves who shot her dog walker and stole 2 of her French Bulldogs ... law enforcement sources tell TMZ, and we're told Gaga is offering $500,000 for the return of her dogs, "no questions asked."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene blasted for attacking colleague's trans child...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Marjorie-Taylor-Greene-blasted-for-attacking-15978706.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - After a contentious debate on the Equality Act, which would extend civil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA declining to hand over any more info...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39441/faa-releases-statement-on-airliners-encounter-with-unidentified-object-over-new-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Airlines Airbus A320 was buzzed by a mysterious "cylindrical object" at high speed as it traveled from Cincinnati to Phoenix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI 'aware'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/fbi-american-airlines-ufo-new-mexico-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is "aware of" an American Airlines pilot’s report of an apparent UFO seen soaring over Northeast New Mexico earlier this week – but stopped short of confirming whether an investigation is underway, Fox News learned Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANHATTAN DA GETS TRUMP TAXES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/25/politics/trump-taxes-mazars-vance/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cy Vance obtained the records Monday after the Supreme Court denied Trump's last-ditch attempts to keep them private</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZILLOW Price Estimates Now Cash Offers in Homebuying Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-02-25/zillow-s-price-estimates-are-now-cash-offers-in-homebuying-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Zillow Group Inc. has titillated homeowners, prospective buyers and the voyeuristic public by estimating the value of tens of millions of U.S. homes and publishing the results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene criticized for 'cruel' response to Democrat's trans flag...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/540457-marjorie-taylor-greene-criticized-for-cruel-response-to-democrats-trans-flag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) drew bipartisan condemnation for putting up a poster stating “There are TWO genders” in response to a trans pride flag installed outside the neighboring office of Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel adopts law allowing names of unvaccinated to be shared...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-adopts-law-allowing-names-153232886.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's parliament passed a law Wednesday allowing the government to share the identities of people not vaccinated against the coronavirus with other authorities, raising privacy concerns for those opting out of inoculation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rarely seen Van Gogh painting exhibited ahead of auction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/paris-amsterdam-france-140675d55c8f1f3d8e64145ee39b5831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A rare painting by Dutch impressionist master Vincent van Gogh of a street scene in the Parisian neighborhood of Montmartre will be publicly displayed for the first time before its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al-Qaeda now as dangerous as under Bin Laden as new chief vows to attack, expert claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2404228/al-qaeda-dangerous-osama-bin-laden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AL-QAEDA are set to become as dangerous as they were during the 9/11 attacks twenty years ago, an expert has claimed.  The terror cult has gained a ruthless new leader dubbed “the Sword of Rev…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You -- But Better: Scientists To Remove Fears, Boost Confidence Via Brain Stimulation...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/remove-fear-boost-confidence-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers believe that in the future these techniques may lead to new treatments for patients dealing with issues like PTSD or anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas freeze silent victims: Wildebeest, gemsbok antelope, other 'exotic' animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/The-Texas-freeze-s-silent-victims-wildebeest-15978347.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas - The deaths are still being counted, but last week's extreme winter weather in Texas left yet another group of victims in its wake: exotic animals.  Days of freezing temperatures kept the state blanketed in ice and snow, and despite the frenzied efforts of breeders, ranchers and other caretakers to maintain water and food supplies, the losses grew: Axis deer. Blackbuck and gemsbok antelope. Wildebeest. Even a 58-year-old chimpanzee named Violet, who had been retired to a special refuge after being used in biomedical research.  "We have over $2 million in animals that have been lost, and another half-million in damage to infrastructure," said Charly Seale, president of the Exotic Wildlife Association in Kerrville, Texas. "It's an extremely trying time for all of us."  At Valkyrie Ranch, 50 miles east of Austin, Francisco Artes put out hay and alfalfa for the wildebeest he raises for sale to zoos. It wasn't enough to sustain two pregnant females and their yearlings. Indeed, the storm was the worst possible scenario for creatures equipped to withstand the extreme temperatures of Africa, with blood vessels in their curled horns that allow heat to escape.  "That works the exact opposite in the cold. The blood in the horns get cold and goes into their brains, and they were having seizures and dying," Artes explained this week. "We had no way of keeping the animals warm. We were out in the blizzard, trudging around - and even when we could find the animals, we couldn't do much to help them."  After posting about the deaths on social media, within hours Artes had distributed more than 4,000 pounds of wildebeest meat to people in need. Nothing went to waste; even the animals' intestines were donated to a dog rescue organization.  "I was telling everybody that wrote...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady Gaga's dogwalker shot four times by men who stole two of singer's dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/breaking-lady-gagas-dogwalker-shot-23564909</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga's dogwalker Ryan Fischer was shot four times in the chest last night when two gunmen ambushed him and stole two of the singer's French bulldogs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traumatized and tired, nurses quitting...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/25/us/nurses-quit-hospitals-covid-pandemic-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's nurses are running on empty almost one year into the pandemic. They've reused PPE, canceled PTO and worked extended shifts for employers they don't always feel value their safety. It's driven many nurses to quit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debilitating 'long-COVID' may have severe health, social impacts...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210225110836-z2i24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/LONGCOVID (TV):Debilitating 'long-COVID' may have severe health, social impacts - WHO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third PFIZER dose? Vaccine maker studying booster shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/third-pfizer-dose-covid-19-vaccine-maker-studying-booster-shots-n1258775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla spoke with NBC News' Lester Holt about the next steps for the company's Covid-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN: GAMESTOP SOARS 100%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/25/gamestop-shares-surge-in-premarket-as-reddit-favorites-rally-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of GameStop climbed in premarket trade on Thursday as heavily-shorted stocks favored by Reddit traders look set for a resurgence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 38% of Americans would give up sex for year just to travel again...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/25/38percent-of-americans-would-give-up-sex-for-a-year-just-to-travel-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After staying home for nearly a year, Americans said they would willingly give up love, sex or money in exchange for a vacation, according to a recent survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speculative crypto art market takes off...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nft-digital-crypto-art-de03ee9f-9819-4d53-bb11-8e03c415f0f9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFTs are similar to many physical art objects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing resistance, Biden reaches out to Republican governors...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facing-resistance-Biden-reaches-out-to-GOP-15978269.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden called Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey on her iPhone hours after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel restrictions have no end in sight as Europeans worry about variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/25/travel-restrictions-continue-in-europe-leaders-worry-about-covid-variants-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European leaders will say on Thursday that all non-essential travel needs to remain restricted as the health situation remains "serious".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods doesn't remember being in car crash, sheriff says...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/25/tiger-woods-doesnt-remember-anything-about-car-crash-deputy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods has no memory of the accident that left him with a shattered his right leg — and appeared to be unaware of how badly injured he was when the first deputy arrived at the scene, acc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germans turn to hunting to 'ethically' source food...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210225-germans-turn-to-hunting-to-ethically-source-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germans turn to hunting to 'ethically' source food</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As private companies erode government's hold on space travel, NASA looks to open new frontier...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/As-private-companies-erode-government-s-hold-on-15978275.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four astronauts who will fly aboard a SpaceX mission by the end of the year will be a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sneakerheads Have Turned Jordans, Yeezys Into Bona Fide Asset Class...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2021-sneaker-investment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the pandemic presented a buy-low opportunity, one college dropout hit the road and filled his truck with $200,000 worth of kicks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Gates Versus Musk as World's Richest Spar Over Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://techcentral.co.za/its-gates-vs-musk-as-worlds-richest-spar-over-bitcoin/105283/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcentral.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unless you’re the world’s richest person, you shouldn’t be buying bitcoin. That’s the message from Bill Gates – the third richest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli nuke facility undergoes major project...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dubai-iran-nuclear-weapons-programs-middle-east-united-arab-emirates-ecd8b6f3ffb329aa1fc566b9f9336038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — A secretive Israeli nuclear facility at the center of the nation's undeclared atomic weapons program is undergoing what appears to be its biggest construction...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American diplomats in China forced to take anal swab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9298587/China-denies-requiring-U-S-diplomats-anal-swab-tests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington complained the procedure was 'undignified' and told staff to decline the test if asked to take one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL player threatens to release ESPN reporter's strip club pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.totalprosports.com/2021/02/24/ravens-matt-judon-demands-apology-or-threatens-to-leak-photos-of-espn-reporter-jamison-hensley-at-a-strip-club-pics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.totalprosports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read “Ravens' Matt Judon Demands Apology or Threatens To Leak Photos Of ESPN Reporter Jamison Hensley At A Strip Club (PICS) ” and other NFL articles from Total Pro Sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL JAZEERA launching rightwing media platform targeting US conservatives...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/feb/23/al-jazeera-rightwing-media-platform-conservatives-rightly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rightly will be led by a former Fox News journalist and is aimed at Republicans who ‘feel left out of conservative media’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  AMERICAN AIRLINES doesn't deny pilot spotting 'UFO' over New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2399645/american-airlines-ufo-mystery-new-mexico-audio-fbi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN Airlines has not ruled out that one of its jets encountered an apparent UFO over New Mexico last weekend. The passenger airline today verified a radio transmission from flight 2292 Cincinn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Newsom fighting for his political life...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/mag-features/gavin-newsom-recall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dining out during lockdowns. Fumbling the vaccine rollout. With a recall effort gaining steam, California’s once-golden governor is fighting for his political life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As more govts mull vax passports, critics raise discrimination fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210223-as-more-governments-mull-vaccine-passports-critics-raise-discrimination-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As vaccinations pick up pace around the world, the idea of “vaccine passports” is gaining traction among governments and industries looking for a way out of shutdowns, curfews and travel bans.  But w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Responder Says Seemed Unaware of 'How Gravely He Was Injured'...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/tiger-woods-first-responder-says-the-golfer-seemed-unaware-of-how-gravely-he-was-injured-161097</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. County Sheriff's Deputy Carlos Gonzalez was the first at the scene of the athlete's accident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guantanamo Bay's 'most tortured prisoner' spills all on violent 14 years behind bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/guantanamo-bays-most-tortured-prisoner-23560984</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohamedou Ould Slahi spent 14 years shackled in the world's most notorious detention centre where he was beaten, sexually assaulted and starved — despite never being charged with a crime</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon investigation gains steam as prosecutors subpoena financial records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/24/politics/bannon-investigation-gains-steam/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney's office has subpoenaed financial records related to Steve Bannon's crowd-funding border-wall effort, signaling that its criminal investigation into former President Donald Trump's chief strategist is advancing, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing market concerns begin to emerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/24/investing/home-depot-lowes-earnings-housing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The housing market is still red hot. But there are growing concerns about how much longer this strength can last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Cuomo staffer says NY Governor joked with her about playing strip poker...</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@lindseyboylan4NY/my-story-of-working-with-governor-cuomo-e664d4814b4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Let’s play strip poker.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL player threatens to release ESPN reporter's strip club pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.totalprosports.com/2021/02/24/ravens-matt-judon-demands-apology-or-threatens-to-leak-photos-of-espn-reporter-jamison-hensley-at-a-strip-club-pics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.totalprosports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read “Ravens' Matt Judon Demands Apology or Threatens To Leak Photos Of ESPN Reporter Jamison Hensley At A Strip Club (PICS) ” and other NFL articles from Total Pro Sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns of unnamed foreign efforts to destabilize Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/02/24/putin-warns-of-unnamed-foreign-efforts-to-destabilize-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and its NATO allies have rejected similar previous claims by the Kremlin that they were seeking to undermine Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Battle Over Race, Class and Power at Elite College...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/24/inside-a-battle-over-race-class-and-power-at-smith-college/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHAMPTON, Mass. — In midsummer of 2018, Oumou Kanoute, a Black student at Smith College, recounted a distressing American tale:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Zapping Brains Cure Depression?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/24/can-zapping-our-brains-really-cure-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brain is an electrical organ. Everything that goes on in there is a result of millivolts zipping from one</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
