<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  DEA Used NSA Data to Spy on Millions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/analytics-data/2019/03/dea-never-checked-if-its-massive-surveillance-operations-are-legal-watchdog-says/155907/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration “failed to conduct a comprehensive legal analysis” of three NSA-style bulk data collection programs, according to the Justice Department Inspector General.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows 'pollen wave' as yellow dust blankets nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/article228577949.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Joe Biden's endless gaffe-riddled apology tour...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/831852/joe-bidens-endless-gafferiddled-apology-tour  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is going to be painful to watch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wows crowd in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/29/pete-buttigieg-san-francisco-1243203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buttigieg was greeted by a rousing standing ovation, whoops and cheers by the audience in the Democratic bastion of San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Droid discovers lying about betrayal helps rebuild trust...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2198141-robot-discovers-that-lying-about-a-betrayal-helps-to-rebuild-trust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots can regain our trust after a betrayal by lying about it, according to a video game experiment with humans and robots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys lay siege to hospital built on their land in terrifying footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/768681/Monkeys-reclaim-HOSPITAL-after-it-was-built-on-land-inhabited-by-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students support socialism -- but not when comes to GPAs...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=12038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happened to "spreading the wealth around"?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman 'possessed' during in-flight meltdown over PEPSI...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/29/woman-looks-possessed-during-in-flight-meltdown-over-a-pepsi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All hell broke loose on a recent flight when a drunken woman described as a “demon” demanded a Pepsi – but was told that only fruit juice was being served. The unidentified Spanish woman began scre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star rises in crowded 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/buttigieg-boomlet-gives-south-bend-080000680.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parin Finch, 43, who attended a recent Buttigieg rally in Columbia, South Carolina, said she’s still shopping for a candidate to support and loves Senator Kamala Harris of California. Buttigieg still faces the same hurdle as most of the 14 other Democrats currently running for the party’s 2020 nomination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Buttigieg Political Genius?</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/153424/pete-buttigieg-political-genius</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South Bend mayor is unlike any other Democratic candidate for president, and he's staked out the middle ground among them all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson tribute act says business booming after doc...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/03/29/michael-jackson-tribute-act-says-leaving-neverland-like-advert-show-9058102/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He claims business is 'booming'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Passengers Hospitalized After Odor On Plane...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/03/29/bwi-flight-emergency-landing-at-dulles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plane that left BWI-Thurgood Marshall Airport Friday morning had to make an emergency landing at Dulles International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic parties to virgin sex -- MOTLEY CRUE biopic 'tame' compared to real life...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/8743691/satanic-gatherings-sex-virgin-groupies-phone-box-blackouts-motley-crue-debauched-the-dirt-former-limo-driver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FROM snorting ants with Ozzy Osbourne to that very graphic opening sex scene, Motley Crue’s rock biopic The Dirt has left viewers shocked since its release last week. But real life with Motle…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock of the nude: Brazil's stark new form of political protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2019/mar/29/shock-of-the-nude-brazil-festival-protest-theatre</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a defiant riposte to president Bolsonaro and intolerance, performers at São Paulo’s international theatre festival are reclaiming the rights to be seen and to be different</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billie Eilish album review: Thrilling Gen Z terror-pop...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/mar/29/billie-eilish-when-we-all-fall-asleep-where-do-we-go-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 17-year-old my draw sneers but her broken balladry, gaspy vocals and hip-hop-pop is part of a clear vision – and makes for a unique album</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal info of BILLION people leaked in one of biggest breaches ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6864029/Biggest-breach-recorded-982-MILLION-peoples-personal-information-exposed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cyber security expert from Germany has discovered that hundreds of millions of people's personal information was exposed in a dataset by a company called Verifications.io.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle over 'blood slave' donor dogs pits veterinarians vs. veterinarians...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/03/29/battle-over-blood-slave-donor-dogs-in-california-pits-veterinarians-vs-veterinarians/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professors from America’s premier veterinary school urge lawmakers to ditch captive-donor colonies, which critics dub ‘blood slaves’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet zebra fatally shot by owner after escaping home...</title>
      <link>https://www.jacksonville.com/news/20190327/escaped-pet-zebra-shot-and-killed-in-callahan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jacksonville.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A zebra was shot and killed after it escaped Wednesday from a Callahan enclosure, according to the Nassau County Sheriff's Office.The pet zebra was kept</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man in face-eating attack believed he was 'half-man, half-dog'...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/florida-man-accused-of-eating-faces-believed-he-was-half-man-half-dog-doctor-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A forensic psychologist says a former college student believed he was "half-dog, half-man" when he fatally attacked a man and woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol begins releasing migrant families on streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/immigration/2019/03/28/border-patrol-begins-releasing-migrants-yuma/3301641002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol officials in the Yuma sector are now releasing migrants onto the streets of Yuma because of overcrowding at their facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON DYNAMICS shows off creepy avian robot for logistics work...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2019/03/boston-dynamics-latest-robot-is-a-mechanical-ostrich-that-loads-pallets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest creation from Softbank's Boston Dynamics looks ready for actual work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
China City Offers Cash for Information in Religion Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/politics/article/3003825/chinese-city-offers-us1500-reward-help-snare-foreign-religious</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southern metropolis of Guangzhou introduces cash incentives as campaign to sinicise faith groups hots up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homelessness rises in Argentina's capital amid crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article228574174.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third time lucky? Lawmakers hold new vote on Brexit deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/037dc679580448a08b42d52cae49b53e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — On the day that Britain was originally scheduled to leave the European Union, lawmakers will vote Friday on what Prime Minister Theresa May's government described as the "last chance...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mother of all caravans' pushes north...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/597b194af93c473aa4f041a4462788d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico is bracing for the possible arrival of the "mother of all caravans," even as doubts arise over whether the group of Central American migrants will be all that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOONAN:  The Two Americas Have Grown Much Fiercer...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-two-americas-have-grown-much-fiercer-11553816463</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. was divided 46 years ago. But no one saw it as a fight to the death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST LEAD FRIDAY:  How Trump dodged a special counsel interview -- and subpoena fight... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/a-mueller-mystery-how-trump-dodged-a-special-counsel-interview--and-a-subpoena-fight/2019/03/28/5949b186-50b7-11e9-88a1-ed346f0ec94f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s legal team conducted an extensive pressure campaign to keep him from coming face-to-face with federal investigators — fearful he would perjure himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cover up'... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Robert-Mueller-s-report-is-more-than-300-pages-13723654.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats are ready to accuse Attorney General William Barr of a "coverup" to protect President Donald Trump if he refuses to detail for Congress the information special counsel Robert Mueller III provided the grand jury during his investigation of Russia's interference in the 2016 election.  The pointed warning, delivered by senior Democratic aides during a media briefing Thursday, marked the latest sign of a potential legal standoff between lawmakers and the Justice Department over access to Mueller's complete findings. Barr has pledged to redact grand jury information from Mueller's report, which spans more than 300 pages, according to people familiar with the document, and that process is expected to take weeks.  That is far longer than Democrats say they are prepared to wait, and they have begun to express suspicion that the attorney general intends to prevent the public disclosure of information within Mueller's findings that may be unflattering or otherwise problematic for the president. It remains unclear what precisely Barr plans to deliver to Congress.  "If he does not include grand jury information in the summary or report or redacted report or whatever he gives to Congress, that amounts to a coverup," a House Democratic staffer told reporters during Thursday's briefing. "We do not want anything in the words of the attorney general. We want to see Robert Mueller's words."  House Democrats also said Thursday that they are prepared to authorize a subpoena for Mueller's full report if Barr misses the Tuesday deadline lawmakers set for him to deliver it to Congress. They stopped short, however, of promising to issue a subpoena, even though the attorney general has indicated he is unlikely to make their deadline.  Democrats are bracing, too, for a potential fight with the administration if the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Officer's Secret in Arizona: He Was Undocumented...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/border-officer-s-secret-in-arizona-he-was-undocumented/ar-BBVmgsq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says barbed wire 'can be a beautiful sight.' Many communities disagree...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-border-concertina-wire-20190324-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wire makes parts of the U.S. southern border look like a war zone. Now several cities — concerned about their images and the risk of injuries — are demanding it be removed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC TRAFFIC NIGHTMARE AFTER TANKER FLIPS ON BELTWAY...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2019/03/expect-a-bad-rush-hour-tanker-turns-over-blocks-inner-loop-traffic-into-md/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Complicating the situation: That truck is leaking fuel. The cleanup will probably take hours, WTOP Traffic reporter Bob Marbourg said, so make your alternate commute plans now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No longer a political winner: Silicon Valley is minefield for hopefuls...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/article_c6836711-70ed-588c-b73f-547d6d82cb62.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Only three years ago, Silicon Valley was riding so high that Hillary Clinton seemed truly stumped when asked on “The Ellen Show” whether she’d rather have George Clooney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT IS BARR HIDING?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/justice-department-official-says-mueller-report-is-more-than-300-pages-11553786698</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi pushed for the speedy release of special counsel Robert Mueller’s report on Russian election meddling, saying Congress needs to see the full document to draw its own conclusions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB's $330-million star speechless after named 'most overrated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/phillies/2019/03/27/bryce-harper-phillies-most-overrated/3291708002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bryce Harper, 26, has a career .900 OPS and has been an All-Star six times in his seven big-league seasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Animals Slowly Starve in Abandoned Spanish Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8737847/animals-abandoned-spanish-zoo-after-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEARTBREAKING images show miserable tigers, bears and monkeys languishing in an abandoned zoo two months after it closed have sparked outrage. Activists say the animals left at The Parque Zoologico…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Words Banned by California DMV...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/rejected-vanity-plates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the important job of keeping poop puns, dick jokes, and hate speech off California’s roadways</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan MAGA Rally Victory Lap...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-in-first-rally-since-mueller-vindication-draws-huge-crowds-on-streets-of-grand-rapids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first major rally since Special Counsel Robert Mueller cleared him of any collusion with Russia, President Trump took the stage before a boisterous full house at the Van Andel Arena in Grand Rapids, Michigan, Thursday night -- and proceeded to tear into Democrats and the FBI as unintelligent "frauds" who tried desperately to undermine the results of the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ROARS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6862783/Trump-declares-victory-Mueller-rally-end-Russia-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is declaring his victory following the Mueller report that failed to find any collusion with Russia saying 'the hoax is finally dead' as he spoke to an uproarious crowd in Michigan on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROWD CHANTS:  AOC SUCKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/28/video-aoc-sucks-chant-breaks-out-at-trumps-michigan-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attendees of President Donald Trump's rally in Grand Rapids, Michigan, on Thursday evening broke out into an "AOC Sucks!" chant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Captures 10 Gang Members Hunt Down, Kill Man In NYC...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/03/28/gang-murder-caught-on-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD says video captured 10 people hunting down and killing a man in Brooklyn earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela returns to 'Middle Ages' during power outages...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuela-returns-middle-ages-during-power-outages-143506671.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Venezuelans today, suffering under a new nationwide blackout that has lasted days, it's like being thrown back to life centuries ago. El Avila, a mountain that towers over Caracas, has become a place where families gather with buckets and jugs to fill up with water, wash dishes and scrub clothes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg's star rises in crowded 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pete-buttigiegs-star-rises-crowded-2020-race-000134570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At just 37, Pete Buttigieg has deployed to Afghanistan, graduated from Harvard, learned seven languages and serves as mayor of a Midwestern American city. When he began exploring a challenge to Donald Trump, few people outside his home city of South Bend, Indiana knew who the fresh-faced Democrat was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS ON DECK FOR UK PM...</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/brexit/boris-johnson-primed-ready-launch-leadership-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol orders quick releases of families...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4349e2a13a740afac03c5cbbf3ace49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The number of migrant families and children entering the U.S. from Mexico is so high that Border Patrol is immediately releasing them instead of transferring them to the agency...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In trade wars of 200 years ago, the pirates were Americans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b40414d22f2248428ce11ff36b88dc53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The upstart nation was a den of intellectual piracy. One of its top officials urged his countrymen to steal and copy foreign machinery. Across the ocean, a leading industrial...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Greatest Hoax In History'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/adb5b00ac1524adb91f9ce38961039da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAND RAPIDS, Mich. (AP) — Presenting himself as both vindicated and vindictive, a fired-up President Donald Trump on Thursday turned the findings of the Russia investigation into a political...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former skeptic praises 'outstanding' job, joins fired up crowd...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlive.com/news/2019/03/russia-investigation-single-greatest-political-hoax-trump-tells-michigan-crowd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It tried to divide the country, he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren lunches with Ocasio-Cortez...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/43b86f5bff4343fda7747b91cf1e5b72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren is breaking bread with New York Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, whose endorsement in the 2020 Democratic presidential primary is a potentially...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER MAY SLAP TRUMP TWEETS THAT VIOLATE 'RULES'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/436218-twitter-considering-labeling-trump-tweets-that-violate-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Twitter executive on Wednesday said the company is considering a new fea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blasts ongoing probes: 'Ridiculous bullsh*t'....</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/436403-trump-blasts-ongoing-democratic-investigations-ridiculous-bullshit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump at a Thursday rally in Michigan blasted Democrats' ongoing investigations of him as "ridiculous bullshit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney: 'Attackers' may have been in WHITEFACE!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6860095/Jussie-Smolletts-lawyer-says-thought-brothers-white-wearing-make-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tina Glandian, one of Jussie Smollett's lawyers, claimed that Smollett did not recognize the pair when they attacked him on January 29 and that it has not been proven that it was them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Projected to Add 1.5 Million Illegal Aliens This Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/27/u-s-projected-to-add-1-5m-illegal-aliens-to-population-this-year/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is projected to add about 1.5 million illegal aliens to the American population by the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROUNDUP Losing In Court, But Farms Not About to Give It Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-28/roundup-is-losing-in-court-but-farms-aren-t-about-to-give-it-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists taking rap in Duterte latest war...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-philippines-media-insight/the-philippine-journalists-taking-the-rap-in-dutertes-latest-war-idUKKCN1R92VE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Filipino journalist Pia Ranada fell into a ditch and injured her leg on ele...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA Ancestry Site: Join to Help Hunt Criminals...</title>
      <link>https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/bjqebq/a-dna-ancestry-website-is-asking-people-to-join-to-help-hunt-criminals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;motherboard.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popular platform Family Tree DNA is piggybacking forensics' use of genealogy databases to sell its product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: HAMPTON INN Employee Punished For Refusing Exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://lex18.com/news/covering-kentucky/2019/03/28/lawsuit-alleges-hampton-inn-employee-punished-for-refusing-an-exorcism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lex18.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAZARD, Ky. (LEX 18) – A lawsuit filed in Perry County Circuit Court makes an unusual allegation. A former employee of the Hampton Inn claims that he was discriminated against for refusing a spiritual cleansing. Jason Fields filed the suit against his former manager, Sharon Lindon, on the grounds of religious discrimination. According to court …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as video shows poachers slaughter bears in surveilled den...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktuu.com/content/news/Video-of-Alaska-father-and-son-illegally-killing-bear-shrieking-cubs-made-public-507736061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktuu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In April of 2018, Alaskan hunters Andrew Renner, 41, of Wasilla, and Owen Renner, 18, also of Wasilla, illegally killed a black bear and her cubs on Esther Island in Prince William Sound. The video of that incident has been released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers introduce bill to stop mass data collection...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-security-congress/u-s-lawmakers-introduce-bill-to-stop-nsas-mass-data-collection-idUKKCN1R92SO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican and Democratic U.S. lawmakers introduced a bill on Thursday that woul...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Legalized Pot Sales. Now Launching New Weed War?</title>
      <link>http://reason.com/blog/2019/03/28/los-angeles-legalized-pot-sales-now-it-m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High taxes and slow bureaucracy keeps the black market alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NSA contractor guilty in largest ever secrets theft...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/ex-nsa-contractor-expected-plead-guilty-stealing-massive-amount-documents-n988506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maryland resident amassed the classified material during 23 years at the agency and investigators have struggled to figure out why he did it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train brain to curb cravings? Neurons make 'forget' hunger...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6860363/Scientists-discover-neurons-lets-retrain-brain-not-overeat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two thirds of Americans are overweight or obese and 45 million are dieting, often to no avail. Rockefeller University researchers found a brain circuit that retrains problem eating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  MUELLER REPORT 300+ PAGES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/kids/other/mueller-report-exceeds-300-pages-raising-questions-about-four-page-summary/ar-BBVljs7?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy found dead in Alps accused of plot to assassinate politician...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/france-spy-dead-alps-assassination-congo-opposition-daniel-forestier-a8843566.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military recruits next generation of soldiers at gamer convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/army-turns-to-video-game-conventions-for-new-recruits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Army is looking beyond recruiting ads as it tries to pitch itself to a new audience of gamers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Rations Power, Measure Long Avoided...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-28/venezuela-to-ration-electricity-following-nationwide-blackouts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb Atty Geragos rages against CNN, threatens to tell all...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/28/celebrity-attorney-mark-geragos-slams-cnn-over-extortion-plot-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrity attorney Mark Geragos raged against CNN and threatened to tell all after the network dropped him in light of his alleged involvement in the Nike extortion plot. On Tuesday, the network an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Visual ear' phenomenon lets people 'hear' silent images...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/03/28/can-hear-gifs-scientists-reveal-silent-images-appear-make-sounds-9041158/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people have a 'visual ear' which lets their brain hear what it sees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Prices Soaring...</title>
      <link>http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/03/28/refinery-woes-send-gas-prices-soaring-at-the-pump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gas prices across California are averaging $1 above the national average and refineries are being blamed for the higher prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Worst Disease Ever Recorded...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/03/bd-frogs-apocalypse-disease/585862/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doomsday fungus known as Bd has condemned more species to extinction than any other pathogen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Strategy to Use Special Counsel on Campaign Trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/03/trump-wants-campaign-mueller-report-2020/585967/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican lawmakers and strategists fear that the president would be fixating on the wrong message at the wrong time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico raises alert level as volcano spews ash, lava...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190328-mexico-raises-alert-level-volcano-spews-ash-lava</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico raises alert level as volcano spews ash, lava</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Nominated for NAACP Image Award...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2019/03/28/jussie-smollett-up-naacp-award-host-anthony-anderson-hopes-he-wins/3298234002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jussie Smollett is nominated for an NAACP Image Award this weekend. Host Anthony Anderson says he hopes the disgraced "Empire" actor wins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu uses icy relationship with Obama to win votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election/netanyahu-uses-icy-relationship-with-obama-to-try-to-win-votes-idUSKCN1R92G0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's Benjamin Netanyahu is using a second American president in his re-...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal bills would let state prisons jam cellphone signals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d96a498f3d24bd68311839f9973defd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — Federal legislation proposed Thursday would give state prison officials the ability they have long sought to jam the signals of cellphones smuggled to inmates within their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countdown to first primary debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/nbc-news-first-democratic-debate-set-miami-june-26-27-n988481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details on the venue, moderators and timing will be announced at a later date, the debate's host said in a release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC has fined robocallers $208M. It's collected $6,790....</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/the-fcc-has-fined-robocallers-208-million-its-collected-6790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s telecommunications watchdogs have levied hefty financial penalties against illegal robocallers and demanded that bad actors repay millions to their victims. But years later, little money has been collected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis unveil 'world's longest salt cave'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israelis-unveil-worlds-longest-salt-cave-031518589.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli cave explorers said Thursday that a salt cave with striking stalactites near the Dead Sea is the world's longest, beating the previous record-holder in Iran. The cave named Malham, stretching over 10 kilometres (6.25 miles), runs through Mount Sodom, Israel's largest mountain, and spills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm to Bill Jussie for Police Work...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/03/28/jussie-smollett-rahm-emanuel-donald-trump-charges-dropped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When he writes the check, in the memo section, he can put the word ‘I’m accountable for the hoax,’” Emanuel said at an unrelated event on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only black reporters allowed in GA mayoral race event...</title>
      <link>https://www.onlineathens.com/nationworld/20190328/only-black-reporters-allowed-in-georgia-mayoral-race-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAVANNAH, Ga. | Organizers of a meeting to discuss an upcoming mayoral race in Georgia barred reporters from attending — unless they were African-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,100 dead dolphins washed up in France since Jan...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/world/2019/03/28/dead-dolphins-shore/39268273/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mass deaths, widely blamed on aggressive industrial fishing, have alarmed animal welfare groups</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico Gov warns White House: 'If bully gets close, I'll punch bully in mouth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/28/politics/ricardo-rossell-donald-trump-puerto-rico-funding/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions are escalating between President Donald Trump and Puerto Rico's governor over disaster relief efforts that have been slow in coming for the still-battered island after Hurricane Maria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Wants Reparations for Afro-Europeans...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/03/28/eu-parliament-reparations-afro-europeans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People of African descent should be taken into account more in current funding programmes&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's longest salt cave 'like another planet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/28/israel-malham-salt-cave-worlds-longest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Survey says cave stretches for six miles, beating Iran’s Namakdan cave in length</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loneliest moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-backstory-britain-eu-may/capturing-british-pm-theresa-mays-loneliest-moment-idUSKCN1R91U4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chin raised, eyes front and inscrutable, face exhausted: it was the most telling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Building AI-Powered Weapons Despite Public Outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/03/pentagon-absolutely-unapologetic-about-pursuing-ai-powered-weapons/155877/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversy surrounding military artificial intelligence is rooted in “grave misperceptions” about what the department is actually trying to do, according to current and former Defense officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILD RALLY SET FOR MICHIGAN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6860763/Trump-heads-Michigan-rally-Mueller-cleared-Russia-collusion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'If there's a way for Trump to win this time without winning Michigan again, no one has made a good case for it yet,' a GOP operative said. 'Grand Rapids is going to look like Grand Central Station.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 best year for economy since 2015...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/28/gdp-q4-2018-final-reading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In all, 2018 closed with a 2.9 percent increase, short of President Trump's hopes for 3 percent growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff Confronted in Explosive House Hearing: We 'Urge Your Immediate Resignation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/house-intelligence-hearing-gets-heated-as-republicans-call-on-schiff-to-resign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Republicans, including President Trump, have called on Schiff to resign after the release of the attorney general's letter on the Mueller report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUNES: Time to Go on Offense...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/27/exclusive-devin-nunes-criminal-referral-time-offense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nunes is planning to send a criminal referral next week to the DOJ that will detail "multiple referrals on a number of different crimes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 'undocumented tech' on INTEL chips...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/03/28/mysterious-undocumented-technology-hidden-intel-computer-chips-researchers-say-9044193/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frightening vulnerability could allow hackers to access 'almost all the data on a computer'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probation for INSTAGRAM model recorded kicking, stomping on tiny dog...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/animals/dog-stomp-probation-624908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 28--An Instagram model who was recorded kicking and stomping on her tiny dog was sentenced yesterday to serve four years of probation in connection with the attack, Florida court records show.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
