<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Holiday Retail Sales Strongest in Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-holiday-retail-sales-are-strongest-in-years-early-data-show-11545777668</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shoppers delivered for U.S. retailers during the final stretch before Christmas, flocking to stores for last-minute gifts to cap one of the strongest holiday seasons in years, according to early data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago nixes Women's March amid growing rift over anti-Semitism...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-womens-march-chicago-global-march-womens-wave-20181225-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As controversy swells around national Women's March organizers — in part over their slowness to condemn anti-Semitic statements by Nation of Islam leader Louis Farrakhan — leaders of the Chicago Women's March say they will not participate in the next protest walk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balitmore gun buyback event yields ROCKET LAUNCHER...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/maryland-gun-buyback-event-yields-a-rocket-launcher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore police say a rocket launcher was among the more than 1,000 firearms turned in during recent gun buyback events. The rocket launcher was traded for $500, and police have reached out to the military and the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives to trace its origin. Police spokesman Detective Jeremy Silbert says the unloaded rocket launcher was turned in Monday, Dec. 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU sues govt over NSA call records program...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/aclu-sues-government-learn-about-nsa-call-records-program-20181225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A civil rights group has sued the U.S. government, saying it needs more information about surveillance of Americans' phone and financial records to guide the public debate over what will happen when the law that regulates the scrutiny expires next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Asylum Seekers Released on TX Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.texasmonthly.com/news/hundreds-asylum-seekers-released-el-paso-streets-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texasmonthly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Worrisome Cult of Ruth Bader Ginsburg...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/12/25/on-the-basis-of-sex-review-rbg-223557</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Ruth Bader Ginsburg biopic will galvanize her fans. They should consider whether that makes them part of the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police mourn K-9 cop shot dead on Xmas eve...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/palm-beach-county-sheriffs-office-mourns-loss-of-k-9-shot-on-christmas-eve/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(WSVN) - The holidays took a somber turn for the Palm Beach County Sheriff’s Office after a police dog was shot and killed on Christmas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rikers inmates go wild for carrot cake...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/rikers-island-serves-up-a-holiday-tradition-carrot-cake-11545766629</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spiced loaves, baked by inmates, have long been a favorite treat at New York’s Rikers Island jail complex; ‘almost a gingerbread kind of thing’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare polio-like illness hits UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8051999/rare-polio-like-illness-leaving-children-with-weak-and-floppy-limbs-hits-uk-after-sweeping-across-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RISE in cases of a rare and incurable disease that can paralyse children has led to a probe by health officials. Acute flaccid paralysis affects the nervous system, causing one or more of the lim…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:   Alcohol, coffee to live past 90...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/nation/2018/02/22/alcohol-near-me/362510002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers found that those who drink moderate amounts of beer or wine, along with two cups of coffee, increase their chances to live a long life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican governor, senator killed in helicopter crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181225-mexican-governor-senator-killed-helicopter-crash-Mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor of the Mexican state of Puebla and her husband, a senator and former governor, were killed on Monday in a helicopter crash, the country's president said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College student forced to remove 'F*ck Nazis' sign over 'issues of inclusion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/leticiamiranda/a-college-student-was-told-to-remove-a-fuck-nazis-sign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This email tells me the university cares more about the feelings of Nazis than the safety of their students."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syria airstrikes continue despite announced USA withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/syria-airstrikes-continue-despite-trump-withdrawal-announcement-6254ad32-a7f0-4991-880b-89bc01544fc4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a sign that the coalition's military strategy hasn't changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez sends greeting to 'refugee babies in mangers'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/422826-ocasio-cortez-sends-christmas-greeting-to-refugee-babies-in-mangers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.-elect Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) on Tuesday linked the Christmas nativity story to the plight of refugees, referencing "refugee babies in mangers" and their parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Brooklyn Grocers Toss Packaging to Contain Trash...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/bagging-it-in-brooklyn-some-grocers-throw-out-packaging-to-contain-trash-11545750000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More New Yorkers are embracing the zero-waste movement—a trend embraced by folks cultivating ultra-virtuous consumption habits—and in Brooklyn, more vendors are emerging to accommodate them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKET HEADS FOR WORST DECEMBER EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/24/by-the-numbers-sp-500-falls-into-bear-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stock market is ending the year on quite the ugly note. Here is where we stand statistically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low gas prices lead to record holiday travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article223516275.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gas prices have been steadily falling since October and continue to drop. The Charlotte, NC area has among the cheapest gas prices in the state, with prices below $2 per gallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba Steps Up Artistic Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/absolute-control-cuba-steps-up-artistic-censorship-11545753600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decree tightening control over artistic expression signed by Cuban President Miguel Díaz-Canel suggests that the country’s first leader not named Castro since 1959 won’t waiver from the iron-fisted rule of his predecessors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist wrote 6 books, interviewed 5 presidents -- now delivering AMAZON packages...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/12/what-its-like-to-deliver-packages-for-amazon/578986/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a certain novelty, after decades at a legacy media company, in playing for the team that’s winning big.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,000 Patients at Surgery Center Possibly Exposed to HIV, Hepatitis...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/New-Jersey-HealthPlus-Surgery-Center-Patients-Possible-Exposure-HIV-Hepatitis-503463211.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Jersey Department of Health says more than 3,000 patients at a surgery center may have been exposed to HIV, hepatitis B and hepatitis C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby Jesus returned to Nativity scene 90 years after being stolen...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Nativity-Scene-Christmas-New-Jersey-Church-Long-Lost-Stolen-Jesus-Statue-Returned-503447951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas at a church in New Jersey will look like it did almost a century ago this year, all because the house of worship will celebrate the holiday with a special baby Jesus statue — a statue that was long ago...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemalan, 8, dies in immigration custody; Diagnosed with cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/guatemalan-boy-8-dies-immigration-custody-after-being-diagnosed-cold-n951826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official cause of the child's death is still unknown and CBP's Office of Professional Responsibility will conduct a review.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR CANADA flight turns back halfway to Hawaii, passengers get $10 vouchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/air-canada-flight-turns-back-halfway-to-hawaii-passengers-get-10-vouchers-1.4230537</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misplaced 2,000-year-old ring discovered in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/misplaced-2000-year-old-ring-discovered-in-jerusalems-city-of-david/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unearthed in excavation of the monumental Pilgrims' Path, the Second Temple-era adornment likely fell after use of a ritual bath, say archaeologists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 7 In 10 Americans Have Sex On Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/seventy-percent-have-sex-christmas-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be cold outside, but things could get hot and steamy for plenty of Americans inside during the holidays. A new survey finds that seven in 10 adults typically have sex on Christmas Day -- even if they've traveled home for family festivities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain bans puppy, kitten sales by pet shops...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181225-britain-bans-puppy-kitten-sales-pet-shops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain bans puppy and kitten sales by pet shops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems To Back Largest Expansion Of Government Since FDR...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/25/democrats-green-new-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's more aspirational than actual policy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Man throws Christmas ham at woman in argument over dinner...</title>
      <link>http://www.wave3.com/2018/12/25/man-arrested-allegedly-throwing-ham-woman-argument-over-christmas-dinner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wave3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect allegedly threw several items at a female victim, including the ham to be eaten for Christmas dinner, then tried to flee the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT:  Will last 'until we have wall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trumps-christmas-message-to-democrats-government-shutdown-will-last-until-we-have-a-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has a Christmas message for Democrats – the government is going to remain partially shut down “until we have a wall [or] fence.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican 'sicario' hitmen film themselves gunning down 4 cops...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/25/mexican-sicario-hitmen-film-themselves-gunning-down-4-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of videos has emerged online which appear to show Mexican hitmen ambushing and killing four police officers. In the video, apparently made by the assailants, at least seven armed men wait in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians at risk of extinction in land where Christmas began...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/civil-rights/422453-christians-at-risk-of-extinction-in-land-where-christmas-began</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christians in the Middle East live with violence, unrest and persecution; some flee their homes or countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All alone' in growing DC strife...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/budget-talks-stalled-us-girds-lengthy-government-shutdown-163544054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic leaders accused an isolated President Donald Trump on Monday of sowing Christmas "chaos" after the stock market plummeted and the US government shutdown hit a third day. "It's Christmas Eve and President Trump is plunging the country into chaos," Nancy Pelosi, who</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE CALLS FOR WORLD LOVE</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181225110915-ylfkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHRISTMAS-SEASON/POPE (PIX, TV):See differences as asset, not danger, pope says in Christmas message</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEATH TOLL TOPS 400...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181225090936-oo0y2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescuers used heavy machinery, sniffer dogs, and special cameras to detect and dig bodies out of mud and wreckage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing potential indictment, Netanyahu opts for snap election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181225-facing-potential-indictment-netanyahu-opts-snap-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing potential indictment, Netanyahu opts for snap polls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealth Indonesia tsunami turns perfect night into nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d5ccf7ead014148aa240ad2571db4de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TANJUNG LESUNG, Indonesia (AP) — As the white strobe lights flashed hypnotically, the band's lead singer screamed into the crowd: "We are! We are Seventeen! Seventeen!" He then let loose with a long note as the guitarist wailed behind him. Some in the audience clapped as they sat at beachside tables covered in crisp white linens. Others walked casually across the grass. A small boy wandered among the tables, and a woman in a headscarf moved closer to the stage, her cellphone out and ready to capture the memory of this perfect night, a year-end concert at a popular resort on Java island's west coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana becomes popular Christmas gift in California...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/cannabis-is-a-big-hit-for-christmas-gift-giving</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;73-year-old Judy gave the gift of pot to herself, unafraid to vape and smoke inside the lounge at the Magnolia dispensary in Oakland.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
