<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Critics say watching Shia LaBeouf new film like having face dragged across asphalt...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/the-tax-collector-film-reviews-shia-labeouf-a9660906.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short on Money, Cities Around World Try Making Own...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-07/a-depression-era-idea-gets-a-new-look-local-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible 'external interference' in blast; Israel swift to deny...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807150756-2a2hg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON-SECURITY/BLAST (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Lebanon sees possible 'external interference' in port blast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saint-Tropez resort makes masks mandatory outdoors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d94752dd1bc0be5fddf17baf3aeac860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAINT-TROPEZ, France (AP) — The glamorous French Riviera resort of Saint-Tropez is requiring face masks outdoors starting Saturday, threatening to sober the mood in a place renowned for high-end,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is France helping Lebanon, or trying to reconquer it?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8eab366aa599b101eb2aad10f9e6528d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — It was almost as if Emmanuel Macron forgot that Lebanon is no longer a French protectorate. Visiting explosion-ravaged Beirut this week, France’s leader comforted distraught...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 Test Positive For Virus After Attending Funeral...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/08/06/almost-30-test-positive-for-covid-19-after-attending-funeral-in-becker-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's human nature to want to gather and grieve together when someone you lose someone close to you, but the COVID-19 pandemic is making that more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Number of Americans Giving Up Citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/americans-continue-giving-up-citizenship-at-record-levels-reports-bambridge-accountants-new-york-301107675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prnewswire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;/PRNewswire/ -- Americans are continuing to renounce their citizenship at the highest levels on record, according to research by the Enrolled Agents and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Drilling Shrinks to 15-Year Low... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/oil-drilling-drops-to-15-year-low-with-shale-in-full-retreat/ar-BB17Hunz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55% of virus patients still have neurological problems three months later...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/55-of-coronavirus-patients-still-have-neurological-problems-three-months-later-study-2020-08-07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mounting evidence suggests COVID-19 could cause brain damage in adults and kids</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president defends record as toll soars...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexican-president-defends-record-virus-201152670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador on Friday defended his government&amp;#39;s record fighting the coronavirus and ruled out a change in strategy after the official death toll surged past 50,000. The Latin American nation recently overtook Britain to become the third hardest-hit country in terms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America now region with most covid deaths... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-deaths-latin-america-hit-212054477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin America and the Caribbean surpassed Europe on Friday to become the region hardest-hit by coronavirus deaths, as India passed the sombre step of recording over two million infections. The world&amp;#39;s worst-hit region had reported 213,120 fatalities, 460 more than Europe, according to an AFP tally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Susan Rice sells NETFLIX options...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/susan-rice-sells-netflix-options-175217810.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Former national security adviser Susan Rice, a Netflix director, sold some of her shares of the video streaming company worth $305,323 this week as speculation swirls that she is among the candidates to be Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden’s running mate.A spokeswoman for Rice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arpaio loses sheriff's race in 2nd failed comeback bid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ee55d22b1ad5910bb42b64a78f714bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Joe Arpaio on Friday was narrowly defeated in his bid to win back the sheriff’s post in metro Phoenix that he held for 24 years before being voted out in 2016 amid voter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitmer traveled to Delaware last weekend...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/65025dc16aa18353cf868658d9b2314a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Gov. Gretchen Whitmer traveled to Delaware last weekend to meet with Joe Biden, the presumptive Democratic presidential nominee's first known in-person session with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Falwell Jr. put on 'indefinite leave' from LIBERTY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/53437a0f21d0b3df86f96a11e76e5687</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Jerry Falwell Jr. took an indefinite leave of absence Friday as the leader of Liberty University, one of the nation's top evangelical Christian colleges, days after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy on verge of 'lost year'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wvgazettemail.com/washington_post/finance/the-u-s-economy-is-on-the-verge-of-a-lost-year/article_b0efcb40-0ebd-590d-932a-a0558a2976df.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wvgazettemail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Hartman has spent a lot of time this summer pacing his restaurant, Bixler’s Lodge in Reading, Pennsylvania, with a tape measure. Whatever way he places it, he comes to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>52 DAYS UNTIL FIRST DEBATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Trump-tries-to-muscle-through-changes-in-debates-15468276.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's efforts to influence the timing and makeup of this fall's presidential debates, some of the last planned events with the power to shift the trajectory of the campaign, have been rejected, with both the independent debate commission and the Biden campaign showing no interest in altering course.  But that has not stopped Trump from trying to gain advantage by making the debates a top-tier issue, as he and his advisers circulate unfounded claims that Joe Biden may try to dodge the events and suggest that the Democrat may try to cheat by using notes if the sessions are held virtually.  "I would be highly surprised if Joe Biden actually went through with all three debates," Trump campaign senior adviser Jason Miller said Friday. "I think their strategy will be to show up to one, show that he is able to function and then pull the plug on any additional debates."  Biden pledged in June to attend all three of the scheduled debates, a commitment that the president only matched in a letter Thursday, after the debate commission rejected a request to use a list of Trump-approved moderators and move up the timing of the debates. The Biden team has taken to mocking the Trump campaign's effort to shape the rules and timing of the events, with one Biden aide suggesting that the president and his staff can Google the phrase "be there" if they have any questions.  "The Trump campaign's attempt to create a debate about debates is as phony as the president's claim that coronavirus will vanish on its own," Biden campaign spokesman Andrew Bates said. "It's unsurprising they have adopted this embarrassing tactic."  The debates, set to begin Sept. 29, are expected to carry outsize importance in a remarkably bizarre election cycle - without public rallies or much in-person campaigning - offering homebound...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service overhauls leadership as Dems press for investigation of mail delays...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Postal-Service-overhauls-leadership-as-Democrats-15468160.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Postmaster General Louis DeJoy unveiled a sweeping overhaul of the nation's mail service, displacing the two top executives overseeing day-to-day operations, according to a reorganization memo released Friday. The shake-up came as congressional Democrats called for an investigation of DeJoy and the cost-cutting measures that have slowed mail delivery and ensnared ballots in recent primary elections  Twenty-three postal executives were reassigned or displaced, the new organizational chart shows. Analysts say the structure centralizes power around DeJoy, a former logistics executive and major ally of President Donald Trump, and de-emphasizes decades' worth of institutional postal knowledge. All told, 33 staffers included in the old postal hierarchy either kept their jobs or were reassigned in the restructuring, with five more staffers joining the leadership from other roles.  The reshuffling threatens to heighten tensions between postal officials and lawmakers, who are troubled by delivery delays - the Postal Service banned employees from working overtime and making extra trips to deliver mail - and wary of the Trump administration's influence on the Postal Service as the coronavirus pandemic rages and November's election draws near.  It also adds another layer to DeJoy's disputes with Democratic leaders, who have pushed him to rescind the cost-cutting directives that have caused days-long backlogs and steady the Postal Service in the run-up to the election. DeJoy clashed with House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., and Senate Minority Leader Charles Schumer, D-N.Y., in a meeting on the issue earlier this week.  Rep. Gerald Connolly, D-Va., chair of the House subcommittee responsible for postal oversight, called the reorganization "a deliberate sabotage" to the nation's mail service and a "Trojan Horse."  David...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX, ULA wins billions in Pentagon rocket contracts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/spacex-and-ula-win-2022-pentagon-rocket-launch-contracts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force on Friday awarded rocket builders United Launch Alliance and SpaceX with contracts worth billions to launch national security missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare syndrome found in 600 American children...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807203644-7i3cv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHILDREN:Rare syndrome linked to COVID-19 found in nearly 600 U.S. children -CDC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison Escapee Caught After 50 Years on Run...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2020-08-07/colorado-prison-escapee-caught-after-nearly-50-years-on-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNERMEDIA layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/warnermedia-ceo-reorganizes-company-with-layoffs-focus-on-hbo-max.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the changes, streaming executive Andy Forssell will lead a new HBO Max operating business unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  Vaccine has 'not great' chance of being highly effective...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/coronavirus-vaccine-dr-fauci-says-chances-of-it-being-highly-effective-is-not-great.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are hoping for a coronavirus vaccine that is at least 75% effective, but 50% or 60% effective would be acceptable, too, Dr. Anthony Fauci said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Sanders Staffer Jailed in Belarus, Charged with Disrupting Peace...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/christopherm51/us-campaign-aide-jailed-belarus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vitali Shkliarov faces up to three years behind bars for allegedly organizing an illegal campaign rally for the candidate challenging President Alexander Lukashenko, known as “Europe’s Last Dictator.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released from jail at height of pandemic, rape suspect kills accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.11alive.com/article/news/local/virginia/rape-suspect-washington-post-alexandria-crime/65-13310ff6-43bf-444d-acc3-e229d7699b6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.11alive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ibrahm E. Bouiachi was indicted on rape charges last year. After being released due to the pandemic, police say he shot and killed his accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus hastens newspapers' slide into shaky digital future...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/virus-hastens-newspapers-slide-shaky-080216711.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus crisis has weighed heavily on print newspapers already battling for survival around the world, with the number of copies sold tumbling while less profitable digital readerships surge. Simply delivering printed papers to the shops -- or having customers come in to buy them -- has become</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell 'boasted' about oral sex with George Clooney...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12340128/ghislaine-maxwell-schoolgirl-oral-sex-george-clooney-virginia-giuffre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell boasted about performing an alleged sex act on George Clooney and “giggled like a schoolgirl”, Virginia Giuffre has claimed. The sensational claims were made in the ma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOOKS: RUSSIA WANTS TRUMP; CHINA WANTS BIDEN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/07/politics/2020-election-russia-china-iran/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US intelligence community's top election security official said in a statement Friday that China "prefers" an outcome where President Donald Trump is not reelected in November and Russia is working to denigrate former Vice President Joe Biden's White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Released from jail at height of pandemic, rape suspect kills accuser...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/crime-law/2020/08/06/released-jail-height-pandemic-alexandria-rape-suspect-allegedly-killed-his-accuser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ibrahim Bouaichi had been in jail since October on rape and abduction charges. But he was released in April, and is now charged with killing his accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-ANGELS employee charged in pitcher's fatal opioid overdose...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/former-l-angels-employee-charged-pitcher-tyler-skaggs-fatal-opioid-n1236179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyler Skaggs was just 27 when he was found dead in his hotel room, as his team prepared to play the Texas Rangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado 'recon' teams quietly monitor mask wearing...</title>
      <link>https://coloradosun.com/2020/08/06/mask-wearing-compliance-surveys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coloradosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tri-County Health Department has been dispatching volunteers to conduct mask surveys since April. Now Boulder and Gunnison counties are starting their own coronavirus recon missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman is 1st in US to get 2nd face transplant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4cb2c94741618736fc91f2a51899b458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — For the second time in a decade, a New Hampshire woman has a new face. Carmen Blandin Tarleton, whose face was disfigured in an attack by her ex-husband, became the first...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Media Led Great Racial Awakening...</title>
      <link>https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/media-great-racial-awakening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tabletmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Years before Trump’s election the media dramatically increased coverage of racism and embraced new theories of racial consciousness that set the stage for the latest unrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will curtain fall on Broadway for good?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/covid-19-knocked-actors-broadway-stage-are-lights-dim-forever-n1235957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have to pave a new way forward, because this industry is not ever going to be the same," one actor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL owner Dan Snyder files $10M lawsuit over false sex trafficking stories...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/511056-nfl-owner-dan-snyder-files-10m-lawsuit-over-false-sex-trafficking-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indian-based website has since taken down the stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norwegians Told to Avoid All Foreign Travel... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/norwegians-told-to-avoid-all-foreign-travel-as-virus-surges/ar-BB17GG9o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muddy Data Causes Some States to Undercount...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/muddy-virus-data-causes-some-us-states-to-undercount-cases/ar-BB17FNeL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire hedge fund chief Paulson to host big-money Hamptons fundraiser..</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/trump-fundraiser-to-be-hosted-by-billionaire-john-paulson-in-hamptons.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tickets for the Trump dinner event are priced up to $500,000 per couple, an invitation says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii reinstates restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/hawaii-reinstates-coronavirus-restrictions-theres-no-question-that-the-virus-is-surging.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There is no question that the virus is surging in our state, and I know that many are worried about their health," Hawaii Gov. David Ige said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US tops 2,000 covid deaths in 24 hrs for first time in three months...</title>
      <link>https://in.news.yahoo.com/us-records-more-2-000-023800892.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time the US recorded more than 2,000 deaths in 24 hours was on May 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Londoners Are Refusing to Return to the Office...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-londoners-refusing-return-office-091311966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Britons are lagging Europe in the march back to the office, but the U.K.’s status as the standard-bearer for WFH could be hard to sustain. Only 34% of U.K. office workers are working in their normal location, according to a recent survey by analysts at Morgan Stanley. In France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JULY JOBS: +1.76 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0aca194f0f4870b01280049ca567a87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States added 1.8 million jobs in July, a pullback from the gains of May and June and evidence that the resurgent coronavirus has weakened hiring and the economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah protesters face charges with life sentence?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e660cd8c172fca5cd49e703d74f92fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Some Black Lives Matter protesters in Salt Lake City could face up to life in prison if they’re convicted of splashing red paint and smashing windows during a protest, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump long has relied on nondisclosure deals to prevent criticism. That strategy may be unraveling... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-long-has-relied-on-nondisclosure-deals-to-15466258.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Donald Trump has relied on broadly worded nondisclosure agreements as a powerful weapon against anyone who would say something critical of him. Among those who have signed agreements are a porn star, two ex-wives, contestants on "The Apprentice," campaign workers and business associates.  But this key element of Trump's corporate and political strategy has shown signs of unraveling, even as his campaign spends heavily to enforce such agreements. He and his allies recently have lost initial rounds in legal battles to stop damaging books by former top White House officials and his niece Mary L. Trump.  Now, in one of the most sweeping efforts by a former associate to undo nondisclosure agreements, the Trump campaign's former Hispanic outreach director last week filed her latest effort in a class-action suit to void all such campaign contracts. She says they are so broad that they deny individuals their First Amendment right to say anything critical of the president - even as he routinely takes to Twitter to mock and deride his critics.  In a motion for summary judgment in the case, the former campaign worker, Jessica Denson, said the campaign sought a $1.5 million claim against her for violating an NDA. She said that came after she filed a lawsuit alleging sex discrimination by campaign officials. (That separate case is ongoing.)  "These NDAs are representative of the levers of fear that this campaign and administration wield over people," Denson told The Washington Post. "And if this lever of these NDAs is lifted, it is significant not only for the direct effect it has on people who have signed it, but for a general environment of people who are afraid to speak out."  Under her agreement, Denson was not allowed to disparage Trump during her time with the campaign "and at all times thereafter," and she cannot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans Increasingly Turn to Robots for Interaction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/08/will-covid-19-spur-new-robot-friends-and-helpers/167531/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socially assistive robots interact with people and can perform household chores, accomplish health care tasks, and offer emotional support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US tops 2,000 covid deaths in 24 hrs for first time in three months...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/us-tops-2-000-deaths-in-24-hours-for-first-time-in-three-months-johns-hopkins-01596761106?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has recorded more than 2,000 coronavirus deaths in 24 hours, the highest number of daily fatalities in three months, Johns Hopkins University's real-time tally showed Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report Satisfies Everyone and No One...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jobs-report-satisfies-everyone-no-144344472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Investors who expected that the July jobs report would compel congressional officials to avoid a collapse in negotiations on a new coronavirus relief bill were met instead with data that seems likely to entrench Democrats and Republicans in their positions. Just consider the headline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap Between Black and White Widens to Pandemic High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gap-between-black-white-unemployment-143021223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The gap between Black and White joblessness widened slightly in July, indicating the economic recovery continues to be uneven along racial lines even though labor-market conditions are improving across the board.The gap, which is now at its widest in the pandemic era, rose to 5.4 percentage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's scorn of Saudis is warning shot after Trump's embrace...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-scorn-saudis-warning-shot-080002789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Arabia reveled in Donald Trump’s decision to make the kingdom his first overseas destination as president. It will have to decide how welcoming to be for Joe Biden if he wins the White House in November.Trump’s May 2017 visit was marked by claims of $100 billion in arms sales, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TIGHTENING?</title>
      <link>https://cookpolitical.com/analysis/national/national-politics/polling-imperfect-its-bad-news-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cookpolitical.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching politics is an addiction, in which an assortment of websites provides hourly fixes, particularly in the form of poll aggregates and models like RealClearPolitics and FiveThirtyEight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We cannot stop people': 250,000 expected at SDakota motorcycle rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/We-cannot-stop-people-250-000-are-expected-at-15465630.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials are still warning against even small gatherings, and states with relatively low spread are ordering visitors from hot spots to self-quarantine.  But come Friday, about 250,000 people from across the country are still expected to start descending on a roughly 7,000-person community in South Dakota for one of the biggest motorcycle rallies in the world, a 10-day extravaganza so deeply rooted that Sturgis calls itself the City of Riders.  The mayor of Sturgis says there's not much to do but encourage "personal responsibility," set up sanitation stations and give out masks - though face coverings won't be required.  "We cannot stop people from coming," Mayor Mark Carstensen said Thursday on CNN.  Worried residents, however, say officials should have canceled the Sturgis Motorcycle Rally in a state where Republican Gov. Kristi Noem resisted stay-at-home orders and mask rules - and last month welcomed another mass event, President Donald Trump's Fourth of July weekend speech at the foot of Mount Rushmore. A city survey found that more than 60 percent of Sturgis residents wanted the event postponed, the Associated Press reported.  "This is a huge, foolish mistake to make to host the rally this year," Sturgis resident Linda Chaplin warned city counselors earlier this summer, as a debate raged, according to the AP. "The government of Sturgis needs to care most for its citizens."  "My grandma is absolutely terrified because she has diabetes and is in her 80s and has lupus," another resident told CNN. "If she gets it, it's a death sentence."  But the spectacle in South Dakota's Black Hills is hugely important to the local economy, bringing in $1.3 million in city and state tax revenue last year, according to the Argus Leader. A mayor's letter overviewing Sturgis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: 'This May be Last Time You'll See Me for While'...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/08/07/trump-this-may-be-the-last-time-youll-see-me-for-a-while/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No joke: Comedians could fall foul of Scottish hate crimes proposal...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807135551-4zmmh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-LGBT/ARTS:No joke: Comedians could fall foul of Scottish hate crimes proposal, lawyers warn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAP RAUNCH...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/music/cardi-b-megan-thee-stallion-release-wap-song-music-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cardi B and Megan Thee Stallion have released their new song 'WAP' and its music video. Look and listen here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seth Rogen Israel comments highlight fraught diaspora ties...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cd8614d0afeee761ae5dd9ba0b518f7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — It began as a lighthearted conversation between two Jewish comedians, riffing on a podcast about the idiosyncrasies of their shared heritage. But after talk turned to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime presidential adviser Scowcroft dies at 95...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/42daf34201cc29aceb84983cca227880</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Brent Scowcroft, who played a prominent role in American foreign policy as national security adviser to Presidents Gerald Ford and George H.W. Bush and was a Republican voice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Loomer About to Get Little Closer to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/right-richter-laura-loomer-is-about-to-get-a-little-closer-to-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fringe Trumpworld personality has tried to restyle herself this cycle as a less obviously hateful Republican candidate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carefree youths fuel global rise in infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200807-carefree-youths-fuel-global-rise-in-virus-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carefree youths fuel global rise in virus infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New polls show tight races for Graham, McConnell...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/510904-quinnipiac-poll-shows-competitive-senate-races-in-maine-south-carolina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New polls by Quinnipiac University show Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) and Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) in tight races.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETTING MARKETS FAVOR BIDEN</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200807121115-44a9z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/GAMBLING-GMF (GRAPHICS):Betting markets favor Biden over Trump, but odds narrow in U.S. race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury Miami High-Rise First To Use COVID-Killing Robot...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/08/06/downtown-miami-luxury-high-covid-killing-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Downtown Miami luxury high-rise is now home to a COVID-killing robot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beirut Explodes in Violence; Protesters Gassed After Deadly Blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/beirut-explodes-in-violence-after-deadly-blast-with-riots-and-tear-gas-in-the-rubble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anguish has turned to anger in the Lebanese capital with police using tear gas on protesters out on the streets to demand transparency over deadly port explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 'fast radio burst' detected closer to Earth than ever before...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/fast-radio-burst-magnetar-milky-way.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most FRBs originate hundreds of millions of light-years away. This one came from inside the Milky Way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top figure in modern Judaism dies in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200807-top-figure-in-modern-judaism-dies-in-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top figure in modern Judaism dies in Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris raves draw crowds as virus shutters nightclubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200807-paris-raves-draw-crowds-as-virus-shutters-nightclubs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris raves draw crowds as virus shutters nightclubs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JULY JOBS: +1.76 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/07/jobs-report-july-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total nonfarm payroll increased of 1.763 million for the month. The unemployment rate fell to 10.2%, also better than the estimates from economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Ad slump hits media jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/advertising-slump-during-virus-crisis-hits-media-jobs-01596797407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media redundancies, partial layoffs and managerial wage cuts are on the rise as advertising markets implode, despite customers showing an ever stronger appetite for information on the coronavirus crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After first spared, rural California now ravaged...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-being-spared-rural-california-120002879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus is now hitting California&amp;#39;s Central Valley the hardest.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
