<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MASTERS SCARE: Tiger limps, winces after security slides into...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/golf/news/watch-nearly-injured-by-sliding-security-guard-tiger-woods-drops-clutch-birdie-at-masters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woods went from testing out his tweaked ankle to drilling a birdie putt on No. 14</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Papers lawyer: Snare and delusion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/438709-pentagon-papers-lawyer-indictment-of-assange-snare-and-delusion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;References to conspiracy under the Espionage Act raise the question whether U.S. government is going for a bait-and-switch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is boring!' Bill and Hillary speaking tour interrupted...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/12/only-a-heckler-can-improve-an-evening-with-the-money-grabbing-clintons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that they’ve been dismissed, defanged and declawed by their own party, Bill and Hillary Clinton are doing what comes naturally: Hitting people up for money. Thursday night marked the kickoff, i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANG PLAN TO CAMPAIGN AS HOLOGRAM!</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/04/12/andrew-yang-3d-hologram-rallies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang plans to use holograms to hold remote rallies for his presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Labels Pro-Life Movie As 'Propaganda'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/04/12/google-apologizes-for-labeling-unplanned-movie-as-propaganda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giant Google has apologized for labeling the pro-life film Unplanned as "propaganda" on its search engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian dies onstage during stand-up after joking about death...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-oxfordshire-47911040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran comic Ian Cognito is pronounced dead after sitting down and falling silent mid-performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sperm -- gets competitive when near rival...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-04-zebrafish-reveals-sexual-rivalry-affect.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presence of a rival male affects sperm quality, according to a research study led by the University of Alicante and the University of Upsala (Sweden). The work was carried out with adult zebrafish (Danio rerio) and reveals that male spermatozoa exposed to high competition (two males and a single female) present dramatic changes in phenotype resulting in faster and more competitive spermatozoa. However, this phenotypic plasticity may incur a cost in the next generation as it has negative effects on DNA integrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public interest or 'basically pornography'? Judge weighs vid release...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/news/20190412/public-interest-or-basically-pornography-judge-weighs-release-of-robert-kraft-videos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The videos allegedly show the owner of the New England Patriots paying for sex acts at a Jupiter day spa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronaut spends year in space snapping stunning pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/12/science/scott-kellys-photos-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In orbit aboard the International Space Station, the astronaut wasn’t just gathering data for NASA’s Twins Study. He also produced some, well, stellar images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Admit: No Human Trafficking Evidence in Kraft Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcconnecticut.com/news/local/Kraft-Attorneys-Back-in-Court-for-Motions-Hearing-508481301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcconnecticut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in the Robert Kraft prostitution case admitted in court Friday that there was not enough evidence to prove there was human trafficking in the Orchids of Asia Day Spa investigation. Kraft's attorneys...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hefner son exits PLAYBOY role to start news, adult content site...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/cooper-hefner-exits-playboy-launch-millennial-focused-website-hefpost-1200044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Hugh Hefner's death Sept. 17, 2017, his son Cooper Hefner had been the highest ranking Hefner in the family business, Playboy Enterprises. He revealed today he's exiting the company to launch a media and digital company that will feature adult content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: THE INTERNET OF THOUGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-04-future-human-braincloud-interface-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine a future technology that would provide instant access to the world's knowledge and artificial intelligence, simply by thinking about a specific topic or question. Communications, education, work, and the world as we know it would be transformed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON:  #MeToo comments wrecked deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59a6dfc685d140e3a7c71a371d419cc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Woody Allen breached his four-movie deal with the online giant by making statements about the #MeToo movement that damaged prospects for promoting his films, an Amazon lawyer said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: President told CBP head he'd pardon him if jailed for violating law...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/12/politics/trump-cbp-commissioner-pardon/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During President Donald Trump's visit to the border at Calexico, California, a week ago, where he told border agents to block asylum seekers from entering the US contrary to US law, the President also told the commissioner of Customs and Border Protection, Kevin McAleenan, that if he were sent to jail as a result of blocking those migrants from entering the US, the President would grant him a pardon, senior administration officials tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC restaurant serves menu for 'dieting' dogs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/12/chelsea-restaurant-serves-up-menu-for-dieting-dogs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who’s a calorie-counting boy? A Manhattan restaurant is taking pooch pampering to absurd new heights with a menu catering to “dieting” doggies, complete with a $26 pan-seared salmon dish and a bowl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truckers hold 'Slow Roll' protests nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/traffic/truck-drivers-hold-slow-roll-protests-nationwide/5245311/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Truckers are holding "slow roll" protests in cities across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian dies onstage during stand-up act...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/ian-cognito-dead-comedian</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British comedian Ian Cognito died while performing his stand-up show on Thursday in Bicester, England, Fox News has learned. He was 60.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBP officers from Canada border, airports sent to Mexican border...</title>
      <link>https://www.elpasotimes.com/story/news/local/el-paso/2019/04/12/cbp-officers-airports-canadian-border-sent-mexico-border-el-paso/3437622002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.elpasotimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBP will send 100 officers from the Canadian border and airports to the southwest border, including El Paso, amid concerns of border wait times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden mulls reviving rape case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-47910820</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged victim's lawyer says she will do everything she can to get the investigation renewed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robots Could Set Tone for Social Interactions...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2019/04/12/how-robots-could-set-the-tone-for-social-interactions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence will likely reshape our economy, society and personal lives in the decades to come. But attaining AI’s broad potential will require not only a continuing slew of technological innovations, but research into societal challenges, says CIO Journal Columnist Irving Wladawsky-Berger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak nearing global emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/ebola-virus-outbreak/congo-s-ebola-outbreak-might-be-declared-global-emergency-n993856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Red Cross official says he’s “more concerned than I have ever been” about the possible regional spread of the Ebola virus after a new spike in cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA declassifies Argentina coup files in largest ever handover...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190412-us-declassifies-argentina-coup-files-largest-ever-handover</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US declassifies Argentina coup files in largest ever handover</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Child Thrown From Balcony At MALL OF AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/04/12/witnesses-woman-says-her-child-was-thrown-from-3rd-floor-balcony-at-mall-of-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child was rushed to a hospital Friday after reportedly being thrown from a balcony at the Mall of America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As cashless stores grow, so does backlash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98613f20d0254b8bacd908ef12107fef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hembert Figueroa just wanted a taco. So he was surprised to learn the dollar bills in his pocket were no good at Dos Toros Taqueria in Manhattan, one of a small but growing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breast Milk Hot Health Supplement -- for Adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-12/breast-milk-is-the-hot-new-health-supplement-for-adults</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORBYN: Don't Send Him to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-47904837</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labour says the Wikileaks boss should not be extradited to the US "for exposing evidence of atrocities".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Schooler Arrested For Trying WWE Wrestler's 'Finishing Move' -- On Principal!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/04/11/high-school-student-arrested-after-trying-wrestling-finishing-move-move-on-principal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high school student was arrested Wednesday after allegedly trying a wrestling move on his high school principal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 shot near Nipsey Hussle procession route...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d3e88f6876947998cf08302592029ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Latest on a memorial and funeral procession for slain rapper Nipsey Hussle (all times local): 7:15 a.m. A shooting killed one person and wounded three others...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange branded himself '87% slut' in dating site ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8851174/julian-assange-bizarre-dating-site-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULIAN Assange’s dating profile from 2006 has been unearthed – where he branded himself a “pig-headed intellectual” and “87 per cent slut”. The then 36-year-old …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$80 oil this summer?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/11/prepare-for-80-oil-this-summer-as-wounded-bulls-rise-rbc-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RBC Capital Markets raises its 2019 Brent crude forecast to $75 a barrel and warns of intermittent bouts of $80 oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laxative-laced cookies given to striking school workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cantonrep.com/news/20190410/uhrichsville-couple-facing-multiple-charges-after-allegedly-giving-laxative-laced-cookies-to-striking-school-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cantonrep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UHRICHSVILLE A Trenton Avenue couple is being held in the Tuscarawas County jail on $1 million bonds after they allegedly gave sugar cookies laced with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZEN IVANKA:  SHE HAS GREAT CALMNESS, SAYS TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/12/trump-explains-why-he-wanted-ivanka-to-lead-world-bank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump considered nominating his elder daughter, Ivanka, to lead the World Bank — because “she’s very good with numbers” — and said she would be “very, very hard to beat” if she decided to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long, grinding Brexit stressing people out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aa806762f47f4037b367468ba249d4f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Elly Wright can't sleep through the night. The Dutch native, who has lived in Britain for 51 years, keeps thinking about the black boots of Nazi soldiers marching by her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stage set for epic extradition fight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98f7ec1528bf4e9d9edd78271c31c16b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — What is expected to be an epic legal and political battle over whether to extradite Julian Assange to the U.S. began to take shape, with Britain's opposition Labour Party urging the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spacecraft crashes in attempt to land on moon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b7a46420b114036bff98b1e87b83306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEHUD, Israel (AP) — An Israeli spacecraft crashed into the moon just moments before touchdown, failing in an ambitious attempt to make history Thursday as the first privately funded lunar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEISS:  HE GOT WHAT HE DESERVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/04/julian-assange-got-what-he-deserved/587008/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t continue to fall for his phony pleas for sympathy, his megalomania, and his promiscuity with the facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House proposed releasing illegals in sanctuary cities, targeting political foes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-proposed-releasing-immigrant-detainees-in-sanctuary-cities-targeting-political-foes/ar-BBVRmNX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Spending Hit 10-Year High...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/2198468000000-federal-spending-hit-10-year-high-through-march-taxes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Ron Sachs-Pool)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenspan warns economy will 'fade out' because of growing entitlement burden...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/12/alan-greenspan-says-economy-will-start-to-fade-out-because-of-growing-us-entitlement-burden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economic growth won't last as the U.S. labors under the burden of growing entitlement programs, former Fed Chairman Alan Greenspan tells CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Drone Hovers Over Fenway Park During RED SOX Game...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/04/11/drone-flies-over-fenway-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone flew over Fenway Park during the Red Sox-Blue Jays game Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges direct assault on press freedom, experts warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2019/apr/12/julian-assange-charges-press-freedom-journalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parts of the indictment go head-to-head with basic journalistic activities protected by the first amendment, academics say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What became of his cat?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/julian-assange-cat-embassy-what-happened-wikileaks-ecuador-a8866611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Manhattan's Newest Hangout for Sex-Positive Millennials...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/inside-manhattans-newest-hangout-sex-positive-millennials-1200120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private club NSFW — or New Society for Wellness — caters to entertainment, media and fashion insiders: "There is literal, not figurative, star f—ing here."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY STOCK SOARS IN STREAMING WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/12/disney-shares-rocket-higher-after-unveiling-streaming-cheaper-than-netflix.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney shares jumped more than 10% Friday after the company announced its Disney+ video streaming service would be $6.99 a month, two dollars a month cheaper than Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest designed to make sure didn't press mysterious panic button...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/assange-arrest-ecuador-prevent-alleged-panic-button-2019-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks' founder, Julian Assange, was dramatically arrested and dragged out of the Ecuadorean Embassy in London on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S. Korean babies born Dec. 31 become 2-year-olds next day...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/082ab3d8f16d4360bf9ade45c41925f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAEJEON, South Korea (AP) — Just two hours after Lee Dong Kil's daughter was born on New Year's Eve, the clock struck midnight, 2019 was ushered in, and the infant became 2-years-old. She wasn't...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Set For Ratings Record With 'GAME OF THRONES'?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/04/game-of-thrones-season-8-premiere-ratings-hbo-prediction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Season 8 premiere of ‘Game of Thrones’ is one of the most highly anticipated episodes in TV history. Could it pull in the show’s biggest numbers yet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency panel meets as Ebola outbreak gathers pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2019/apr/12/emergency-panel-meets-as-congo-ebola-outbreak-gathers-pace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faltering national response to epidemic prompts experts to consider official announcement of public health crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans already ran campaign blasting Dems as socialists. It didn't work...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/12/republicans-socialists-democrats-campaign-2020-1271706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swing-state experiment in last year's midterms offer a cautionary tale for the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Was 'Diehard Conservative'?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/12/elizabeth-warren-profile-young-republican-2020-president-226613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren doesn’t like to talk about it, but for years she was a registered Republican. Why she left the GOP—and what it means for her campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete hottest thing in politics. Can it last?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-mayor-pete-buttegieg-democrats-president-2020-20190412-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South Bend mayor hopes to become the youngest president, the first openly gay one, and the first to go straight from City Hall to the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome opens door to underworld of Nero's ruined palace...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fifty-communal-toilets-where-slaves-114152784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remains of a vast palace built by the Emperor Nero, including a 50-seat latrine where slaves and workers would chat while they attended to their needs, opens to the public for the first time today.   The Domus Transitoria was a huge palace on the Palatine Hill, in the heart of ancient Rome, which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackouts threaten death blow to Venezuela's industrial survivors...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-industries/blackouts-threaten-death-blow-to-venezuelas-industrial-survivors-idUSKCN1RO196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest power outage started another tough week for factory owner Antonello L...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian island rocked by 6.8 mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-indonesia-earthquake-sulawesi-hit-14291387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Geological Survey said the quake struck 174 miles south of the province of Gorontalo, just months after more than 2,000 died in a 7.5 magnitude earthquake and tsunami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGETOWN students vote to pay reparations to descendants of slaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/11/us/georgetown-students-slavery-reparations-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgetown University might not be here today if the Maryland Society of Jesuits who oversaw the school hadn't sold 272 slaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They're in our heads': TV series tackles big-tech nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/theyre-heads-tv-series-tackles-big-tech-nightmare-113616810.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Channing Powell, the creator of the hit horror television series "The Walking Dead", is not someone who is easily spooked. The Amazon show is set in the near future when we can share emotions, thoughts and what we see with our eyes on a social network embedded in our brains. If that sounds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farage Plans Revolution as Brexit Party Targets EU Election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/farage-plans-revolution-brexit-party-085117444.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farage, the former leader of the U.K. Independence Party, is spearheading a new vehicle -- the Brexit Party -- which launches its contest for next month’s European Parliament elections on Friday. Addressing an event in the pro-Brexit city of Coventry, England, Farage warned opponents his approach was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Sued Over Abuse of Search Power, Opening Path for More Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/suit-could-raise-googles-liabilities-in-price-comparison-case-11555056397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German price-comparison service has become the first major company to sue Google following a 2017 European antitrust decision to fine the U.S. firm for abusing its dominant position in the search-engine market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Happiness? Smiling...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/key-to-happiness-smiling-more-frequently/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're having a rough day, one way to help turn that frown upside down may be as simple as doing just that. A new study reveals that smiling actually makes people feel happier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Millionaire Bernie Sanders Prepares to Reveal Income...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/millionaire-bernie-sanders-prepares-reveal-080000366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I wrote a best-selling book,” Sanders told the New York Times this week. The senator refused to release his full tax returns when he vied for the Democratic presidential nomination in 2016. When he ran against Hillary Clinton in 2016, Sanders released a lone return, from the 2014 tax year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT work with Chinese military university raises eyebrows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/microsofts-chinese-military-university-raises-eyebrows-071632855.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft has been collaborating with researchers linked to a Chinese military-backed university on artificial intelligence, elevating concerns that US firms are contributing to China's high-tech surveillance and censorship apparatus. Over the past year, researchers at Microsoft Research Asia in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil touted as health cure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crude-oil-touted-health-cure-azerbaijan-034915549.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immersed up to her neck in a dark viscous liquid, Sulfiya smiles in delight, confident that the fetid substance will cure her painful condition. Sulfiya, a Russian woman in her 60s, has travelled to Azerbaijan's north-western city of Naftalan in the hope that crude oil baths at a local sanatorium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banned at home, Mexican narco anthem group plays Coachella...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/banned-home-mexican-narco-anthem-group-plays-coachella-052922405.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite their name, Los Tucanes de Tijuana -- one of Mexico's most famous narco-ballad bands -- cannot perform in Tijuana. The northern border city banned them in 2008 over their glorification of drug traffickers. Los Tucanes (The Toucans) are among the best-known bands of Mexico's norteno,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy Stairs 'Jesus climbed before crucifixion' unveiled in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/holy-stairs-believed-climbed-jesus-prior-crucifixion-unveiled/story?id=62331625</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get breaking national and world news, broadcast video coverage, and exclusive interviews. Find the top news online at ABC news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitch McConnell tells 2020 Republicans to run 'independent' of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/11/mitch-mcconnell-tells-2020-republicans-run-indepen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Republican senators running for re-election next year should not couple their messaging to President Trump but rather run “independent” campaigns built around how they’ve helped their states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet of the Apes fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/771498/planet-of-the-apes-monkeys-human-brain-genes-implanted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Regulators Launch Antitrust Investigation Into APPLE's App Store...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/11/tech/apple-antitrust-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has another antitrust problem in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite hospitals plunge into unproven stem cell treatments...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/elite-hospitals-plunge-into-unproven-stem-cell-treatments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics are concerned about the explosion in controversial stem cell procedures offered by clinics — and, increasingly, respected hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen Struggles To Keep Making Movies Amidst Turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/woody-allen-turmoil-tries-to-keep-making-movies-1202594144/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some years ago I helped architect a film deal for a Woody Allen movie (Play It Again Sam) and Woody resented that he was not specified as director. A week later, when I encountered him, he looked r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange fears being beaten up in US prison, called Trump crowd 'clowns'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/assange-fears-beaten-us-prison-called-trump-crowd/story?id=62332466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange has been dreading the prospect of American prison, one of his regular visitors told ABC News' The Investigation podcast today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems blame Trump for worsening border crisis...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190411223957-45pvx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/DEMOCRATS:U.S. House Democrats blame Trump for worsening border crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator eyes social media bill for 'hate' speech...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190411221126-8277f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TECH/WARNER (PIX, TV):U.S. Senator Warner eyes social media bills for hate speech, data portability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-pope says sexual revolution led to abuse crisis...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190411184922-bh00c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-ABUSE/BENEDICT (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Ex-pope says sexual revolution led to abuse crisis, sparking debate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Chinese youth sent to villages in 'Cultural Revolution' echo...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/12/millions-of-chinese-youth-volunteers-to-be-sent-to-villages-in-echo-of-mao-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communist Youth League students to ‘spread civilisation’ in countryside and ‘promote technology’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former city employee guilty of using public money for voodoo hex on ex...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-hra-employee-guilty-voodoo-hex-fraud-theft-20190411-77jf7c443jbv5fow5jrksxxpii-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Human Resources Agency employee for the city pleaded guilty on Thursday to using public money to put a voodoo hex on an ex-boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More penmanship, less keyboard: Texas cursive curriculum...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/education/texas-schools-bringing-cursive-back-to-classrooms/5240180/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the cursive debate continues around the country, Texas will introduce the penmanship instruction in the second grade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cord-Cutter Savings Shrink as Streaming TV Services Raise Prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cord-cutters-savings-shrink-as-online-tv-services-raise-prices-11555001280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online television bundles are getting bigger and prices keep rising, edging closer to the cable bundles they were designed to replace and muddling the economic equation that has prompted millions of Americans to cut the cord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to host screening of pro-life film 'GOSNELL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/trump-to-host-white-house-screening-of-gosnell-film-that-exposed-mass-murdering-abortionist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifesitenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Gosnell' tells the true story of Philadelphia abortionist Dr. Kermit Gosnell’s arrest, trial, and conviction for the first-degree murder of three born-alive babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia ethics chief investigating Stacey Abrams campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.13wmaz.com/article/news/politics/stacey-abrams-campaign-under-investigation-by-new-georgia-ethics-head/93-9d765c89-8e4e-4558-a4f9-c43ecba74267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.13wmaz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New appointee says complaints against Kemp are unfounded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark NASA Twins Study Reveals Space Travel Effects on Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/nasa-twins-study-kelly-astronauts-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what happens on long-duration space missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSTED: Fugitive taunts cops on 'most wanted' post, reveals location arguing with commenters...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/crime-courts/2019/04/11/fugitive-Facebook-taunts-greene-county-waynesburg-chloe-jones-police/stories/201904110104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wanted Pennsylvania woman who taunted a sheriff's department online by asking if they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE Edits Piece Suggesting Servers 'Tamper' With Trump Admin Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/boston-globe-edits-op-ed-that-suggested-servers-tamper-with-food-of-trump-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGE: Hid $4M Settlement from 'Mentally Ill Paraplegic' Client...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-avenatti-indicted-fraud-theft-charges-20190411-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal grand jury has indicted Michael Avenatti on charges of fraud, perjury, tax dodging and embezzlement from clients in a sweeping expansion of the criminal case against the Los Angeles lawyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TULSI: Arrest threatens journalists -- 'Be quiet, behave, toe line'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/438542-gabbard-assange-arrest-is-a-threat-to-journalists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential hopeful Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti Faces Up to 335 Years in Prison!</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/michael-avenatti-is-going-to-be-hit-with-more-federal-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
