<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New mayors introduced after electeds abducted...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-introduced-a-new-mayor-in-a-captured-ukrainian-city-after-abducting-its-elected-mayor/ar-AAV0srh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images reveal massive damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/ukraine-russia-war-satellite-images-reveal-fires-severe-damage-to-residential-buildings-in-mariupol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images taken on Saturday reveal destruction and damage to residential buildings, as well as a hospital, in Mariupol, Ukraine, as Russia's ongoing war with the country continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Vlad bombs the very same people he claims to liberate...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/why-putin-bombs-the-very-same-russian-speaking-people-he-claims-to-liberate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking during a break from reporting on Russian invasion and smuggling refugees across border, intellectual Vladislav Davidzon eschews neutrality in fight for independent Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China wanted to appear neutral. It isn't...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-wanted-to-appear-neutral-between-russia-and-ukraine-it-isn-t/ar-AAV0io2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phones addictive. Sports betting, too. Now they're combined...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22947732/phones-sports-betting-gambling-apple-google-march-madness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It used to be illegal, then accepted, and now it’s on your phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN NUKE FEARS GROW</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/03/13/ukraine-putin-crazy-enough-to-use-nukes-and-could-destroy-world-16266206/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin is ‘pursuing a conflict which he believes he has to win'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood military gear sent for real-life use...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/mar/13/us-veteran-ships-film-set-military-equipment-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former marine who provides military props to movies is donating boots and camo to soldiers fighting Russian invasion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Estonian NATO base, troops prepare for next move...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/estonia-nato-base-troop-vladimir-putin-next-move/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We have prepared for Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania and all the Baltic Sea region to face the same kind of military incursion,’ says base commander.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Covid Outbreak in China Since Feb. 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/mar/13/china-battles-worst-covid-outbreak-for-two-years-as-cases-double-in-24-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 3,400 cases were reported on Sunday, forcing shutdowns for millions of people and closure of schools in Shanghai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady attends MANCHESTER UNITED match -- seeking BUCS exit?</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2022/03/13/tom-brady-attends-manchester-united-match-and-all-that-that-possibly-implies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retired, for now, quarterback Tom Brady made a headline on Saturday by attending the Manchester United match against Tottenham Hotspur.That headline could be just another piece of a puzzle that eventually and inevitably leads to a much more significant headline.Manchester United is owned by the same family that owns the Tampa Bay Buccaneers. As we’ve [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  MoMA employees stabbed by man whose membership was revoked...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/12/two-women-stabbed-at-moma/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two employees were stabbed Saturday afternoon inside the Museum of Modern Art in Midtown, resulting in a chaotic scene that had patrons running for the exits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid impacts Earth just 2 hours after discovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/science/article-701110</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The asteroid, 2022 EB5, was small and burnt up in the atmosphere. However, more asteroids are coming, one flying by closer to the Earth than the Moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rep. calls The Don 'would-be tyrant'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/598000-gop-congressman-calls-trump-a-would-be-tyrant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Rep. Tom Rice (S.C.) slammed former President Trump in a statement on Saturday following the former president’s rally in South Carolina, calling him “a would-be tyrant.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland warns can no longer absorb refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Poland-s-two-largest-cities-warn-they-can-no-16996415.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in Poland's two largest cities have warned that they can no longer cope with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Loneliness Linked To Memory Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/loneliness-memory-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many studies have revealed how feeling lonely impacts physical health, mental well-being, and even increases a person's risk of cognitive decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate search for insulin as medicines disappear...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-desperate-search-for-insulin-in-Kyiv-as-16997151.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine - The temperature was below freezing and the pharmacy line was way out the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor warns police, city workers to get vax by Sunday or lose pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mayor-lori-lightfoot-warns-police-and-other-city-employees-will-lose-pay-if-they-don-t-get-1st-covid-19-vaccine-by-sunday/ar-AAUXsGH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Faces Peril...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-economy-likely-weather-russia-131520249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Inflation-walloped Americans are largely prepared to withstand the economic pain imposed by Russia’s Ukraine invasion. That may be little solace for President Joe Biden’s Democrats, who will pay a price at the ballot box for the surging cost of living, if history is any guide.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: U.S. Imposes Sanctions on More Russian EliteBiden Says He’d Fight World War III for NATO But Not for UkraineRecession Risks Are Piling Up And Investors Need to Get Read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel denies it urged him to surrender...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/israel-not-pushing-ukraine-yield-russian-demands-ukraine-adviser-says-2022-03-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Ukrainian adviser and an Israeli official on Saturday pushed back against a media report suggesting Israel tried to nudge Ukraine into caving to Russian demands during talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road to table: Wyoming's new app for claiming roadkill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-lander-wyoming-animals-lifestyle-47a2c9bc266d5b52f724fd2126bfc366</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANDER, Wyo. (AP) — The aroma of sizzling meat in melted butter wafts from a cast iron pan while Jaden Bales shows his favorite way to cook up the best steak cuts from a big game animal. The deep red backstrap pieces, similar to filet mignon of beef, are organic and could hardly be more local.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN FORCES CLOSE IN ON CAPITAL</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/03/12/ukraine-war-russia-preparing-for-final-assault-on-kyiv-16263315/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin forces are closing in on the capital but a breakthrough is still elusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abramovich superyacht cruises in to Montenegro marina...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220312-abramovich-s-superyacht-cruises-in-to-montenegro-marina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A superyacht belonging to the Russian billionaire owner of Chelsea football club sanctioned over Russia's invasion of Ukraine anchored off Montenegro Saturday, an AFP photographer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow footholds in Mideast, Africa raise threat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-business-syria-europe-aed781f59cc4c792f4c6ecdc2541b141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin’s invasion of Ukraine  dominates world attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More American troops deploy overseas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-nato-europe-savannah-georgia-2e1f24e5d031e71557093088a6e8bf86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAVANNAH, Ga. (AP) — U.S. soldiers continued to deploy Friday to Europe, joining thousands already sent overseas to support NATO allies amid Russia's invasion of Ukraine. About 130 soldiers from the 87th Division Sustainment Support Battalion, 3rd Division Sustainment Brigade, lined up with rucksacks inside a terminal at Hunter Airfield in Savannah before marching outside and boarding their chartered flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry accused of 'snub' to queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220312-prince-harry-accused-of-snub-to-queen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry was accused Saturday of snubbing Queen Elizabeth II after announcing he will miss her late husband's memorial service, amid a legal dispute over his security protection in Britain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession Risks Piling Up...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recession-risks-piling-investors-ready-073042241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Even after one of the worst starts to an equity trading year in history, the market upheaval might just be getting started. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: U.S. Imposes Sanctions on More Russian EliteBiden Says He’d Fight World War III for NATO But Not for UkraineSatellite Images of Russian Tanks Fail to Pierce Fog of WarStock Market Bottom Slipping Away After 13 Years of Dip-BuyingTech Walls Off Russia Like Never Before, Posing New Risks for U.S.Ominous signs are piling u</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Urged to Invoke Cold-War Powers to Blunt Energy Price Hike...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-urged-invoke-cold-war-153000039.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden is under pressure to invoke Cold War-era powers to force more domestic oil production as the war in Ukraine strains supplies, raising gasoline prices and fueling inflation.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: U.S. Imposes Sanctions on More Russian EliteBiden Says He’d Fight World War III for NATO But Not for UkraineSatellite Images of Russian Tanks Fail to Pierce Fog of WarStock Market Bottom Slipping Away After 13 Years of Dip-BuyingTech Walls Off Russia Li</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaming APPLE and Texting Musk, Ukraine Minister Uses Novel War Tactics...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/12/shaming-apple-and-texting-musk-a-ukraine-minister-uses-novel-war-tactics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After war began last month, President Volodymyr Zelensky of Ukraine turned to Mykhailo Fedorov, a vice prime minister, for a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Fears Give Way to Rush for Bomb Shelters...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/12/pandemic-fears-give-way-to-a-rush-for-bomb-shelters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGNOLO SAN VITO, Italy — Across a footbridge from a busy shopping outlet surrounded by verdant fields in northern Italy,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine Clinic Treads Line Between Health Care and 'Spa Day for Brain'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/11/a-ketamine-clinic-treads-the-line-between-health-care-and-a-spa-day-for-your-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The décor of the Nushama Psychedelic Wellness Clinic was designed to look like bliss. “It doesn’t feel like a hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA pays $2M a month to protect Pompeo, aide from Iran threat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-mike-pompeo-iran-middle-east-795eb3faae6dc4803faafa3ee6615f4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The State Department says it’s paying more than $2 million per month to provide 24-hour security to former Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and a former top aide, both of whom face “serious and credible” threats from Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clouds over Merkel  legacy as invasion lays flaws bare...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/a/clouds-over-merkel-s-legacy-as-russian-invasion-lays-flaws-bare/6481942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some wonder if her detente policies with Putin have left Germany, and Europe, vulnerable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia executes 81 in one day for 'terror offenses'...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/saudi-arabia-executes-81-people-in-1-day-for-terror-offences-report-2819276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia said Saturday it executed 81 people in one day on a variety of terrorism-related offences, exceeding the total number of executions in the kingdom in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Warns Sanctions Could Cause ISS To Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/russia-warns-sanctions-could-cause-international-space-station-iss-to-crash-news-agency-afp-quoting-official-2818686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has warned that thesanctions could cause the International Space Station to crash,news agency AFP reported quoting an official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New front in war drags oligarchs into spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/A-new-front-in-the-war-drags-Russia-s-oligarchs-16996959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the hillsides above Barcelona, the superyacht looked like a building. The titanic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of trans 8-year-old takes on TX gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220312-family-of-transgender-8-year-old-takes-on-texas-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standing in front of a half-American, half-rainbow flag outside her home, Rebekah Bryant is outraged by a Texas order that considers medical hormonal treatments for transgender minors to be a crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Strong' solar storm to hit Earth on Monday...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/strong-solar-storm-hit-earth-26451045</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People across the world may be able to see the Aurora, a light show that is often seen in high latitude areas, this is expected to be seen further towards the equator during the storm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citing 'hopelessness,' popular Cuban TV presenter heads to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/citing-hopelessness-popular-cuban-tv-presenter-heads-to-us-01647046807</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Cuban television presenter has said he left the communist island nation and is heading for the United States, issuing a strong rebuke of the government he previously defended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smollett lawyers request protective custody for actor in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/jussie-smollett-s-lawyers-request-protective-custody-for-actor-in-jail/article_765a9985-d0c5-5962-9335-f17b8c2b78d4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Thursday evening, his right fist raised in defiance, Jussie Smollett walked out of Judge James Linn’s courtroom and into a monthslong stretch of Cook County custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut off from food, Ukrainians recall Stalin's famine, which killed 4 million of them...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Cut-off-from-food-Ukrainians-recall-Stalin-s-16996909.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the worst of the starvation, when Petro Mostovyi was a child, he was afraid to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly reaches 100 homicides, outpacing last year...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philly-homicides-shootings-2022-2021-20220311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More people have been killed in Philadelphia so far this year than by this time last year, which ended with a record 562 homicides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Moscow threatens to leave St. John's grad stranded in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/russia-threatens-to-leave-st-johns-grad-stranded-in-space/article_3451c7a6-f363-507a-bd66-f2d1848ef312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fallout from the Russia-Ukraine war is threatening Mark Vande Hei's scheduled return to Earth from space at the end of the month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly dismemberment suspect shopped at 99 Cent store with victim's leg in tow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/elderly-brooklyn-dismemberment-suspect-shopped-020400637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — The octogenerian suspect in a grisly Brooklyn murder shopped at a 99 Cent store with her victim’s dismembered leg tucked away in her electric wheelchair, police said Friday. The leg of victim Susan Leyden – cut off from the knee down – was captured on surveillance video when her accused killer Harvey Marcelin stood up from the wheelchair while inside the store, Chief of Detectives ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record gas prices pushing up everyday costs, dampening economic recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/business/article/Record-gas-prices-are-pushing-up-everyday-costs-16996851.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are facing sticker shock at gas stations across the country, but surging global...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 3 Americans take pain meds every day...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4877218/one-in-three-americans-take-pain-medication-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE in three Americans take over-the-counter pain medication every single day, new research suggests. In a poll of 2,000 adults, 20% reported taking OTC pain medications once a day and 12% take it …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Thomas slams cancel culture, 'packing' Court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/voting-rights-ketanji-brown-jackson-us-supreme-court-utah-salt-lake-city-1887c7066a9dc3293099ddb15fdfdc9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — U.S. Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas said he's concerned efforts to politicize the court or add additional justices may erode the institution's credibility, speaking Friday in Utah at an event hosted by former Republican U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agenda languishing, Dems press Biden to go it alone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-voting-rights-biden-elections-voting-c91bce7873d865483426696508a4c729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Top Democrats are pleading for President Joe Biden to act alone on some of the party’s core legislative priorities, viewing executive action as their best hope of delivering on their promises and energizing liberal voters they worry are going to sit out the elections in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California cakewalk? No big-name rivals for Gov. Newsom...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-gavin-newsom-kevin-faulconer-california-elections-558a85071e197ba95821e57468818e86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Six months after winning a recall election that could have ousted him from office, California Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom is in an enviable position as he revs up a reelection campaign that could give him a second four-year term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record gas prices pushing up everyday costs, dampening economic recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2022/03/12/gas-prices-economy-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shipping, transportation, and even lawn care and mobile dog grooming services are getting more expensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland warns can no longer absorb refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/poland-e2-80-99s-two-largest-cities-warn-they-can-no-longer-absorb-ukrainian-refugees/ar-AAUXC8Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX judge suspends Abbott's order to treat gender-affirming care as child abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/texas-judge-suspends-gov-greg-abbott-e2-80-99s-order-to-treat-gender-affirming-care-as-child-abuse/ar-AAUXsxU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powered by AI, 'autonomous' border towers test support for surveillance technology...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/powered-by-artificial-intelligence-e2-80-98autonomous-e2-80-99-border-towers-test-democrats-e2-80-99-support-for-surveillance-technology/ar-AAUXpO8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump touted contest for small-dollar donors to dine with him in New Orleans. But no winner met him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-touted-a-contest-for-small-dollar-donors-to-dine-with-him-in-new-orleans-but-no-winner-met-him/ar-AAUVX6R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems move closer to cutting Iowa's first-in-the-nation status for presidential calendar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-move-closer-to-cutting-iowas-first-in-the-nation-status-for-2024-presidential-calendar/ar-AAUXGO5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER adds customer surcharge...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/With-gas-prices-soaring-Uber-adds-a-customer-16996516.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - As gas prices soar to record levels, ride-hailing giant Uber said it is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN SET FOR KYIV DEFEAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10605505/Kyiv-Putins-Stalingrad-Russias-assault-capital-doomed-fail-officials-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bulk of Russian ground forces are now around 15 miles from the centre but elements of the large column have dispersed in a bid to encircle the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS COLLECT RECORD TAXES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/1806838000000-federal-tax-collections-set-record-through</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government collected a record $1,806,838,000,000 in total taxes through the first five months of fiscal 2022 (October through February), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement released today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Intel points to heightened risk of chemical attack in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2022/03/11/intelligence-points-to-heightened-risk-of-russian-chemical-attack-in-ukraine-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Past Russian government behavior suggests that Moscow could resort to poison gas if the invasion falters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VOWS NO WWIII...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2022/03/11/president_biden_dont_kid_yourself_thats_called_world_war_three.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden said during a visit Friday to Pennsylvania that the U.S. supports Ukraine in the war against Russia up to what Russia will consider an act of war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melitopol mayor abducted...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/03/11/1086153544/melitopol-mayor-abducted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Ivan Fedorov was abducted on Friday, according to Ukrainian officials. He was reportedly seized by approximately 10 people while in the city center, and they put a plastic bag over his head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL TO ZELENSKY: SURRENDER</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-701041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin made an offer to end the Russian war with Ukraine, but it includes many Ukrainian sacrifices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Prices Could Leap 20% More...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/record-food-prices-could-leap-135000572.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Record-high global food costs could surge another 22% as Russia’s assault on Ukraine stifles trade and slashes future harvests, the United Nations warned. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Belarus Says Russia Is Sending ‘Modern’ WeaponsRussia Devises Plan to Seize Firms Abandoned in Foreigner ExodusRussia Bans Export of 200 Products After Suffering Sanctions HitUkraine Update: Russia Targeting Airfields in Western UkraineTech Walls Off Russia Like Never Before, Posing New Ri</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia strikes near Ukraine capital; Mosque reported hit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-chechnya-b1ce8f7db6408fc78e9204385b6dc754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LVIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces pounding the port city of Mariupol shelled a mosque sheltering more than 80 people, including children, the Ukrainian government said Saturday as fighting also raged on the outskirts of the capital, Kyiv.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
