<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Database Exposes 200 Million Americans' Personal Info...</title>
      <link>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/a-mysterious-database-exposed-200-million-americans-personal-info</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tomshardware.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And we have no idea who it belonged to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon General: 'This week it's going to get bad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/surgeon-general-has-coronavirus-warning-week-it-s-going-get-n1166421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disease is spreading, the surgeon general said, because many people are not following the guidance to stay at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen dies day after testing positive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/23/british-teen-dies-one-day-after-testing-positive-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teenager aged just 18 has died in the UK — one day after testing positive for COVID-19, according to officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hiker survives 200-foot fall during Mount Washington descent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ae0b5db8f7db5eaa434e80739e25fbd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRETTON WOODS, N.H. (AP) — A hiker descending Mount Washington who fell about 200 feet (60.9 meters) and got hurt was rescued with the help of the Cog Railway train that takes visitors up and down...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen memoir released...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6e7f6ad6a0daf117ec54c765bdf838b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Woody Allen's memoir, dropped by its original publisher after widespread criticism, has found a new home, The Associated Press has learned. The 400-page book, still called...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What do you want me to do?': Fauci's strikingly honest review of Trump response...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2020/03/i-m-going-keep-pushing-anthony-fauci-tries-make-white-house-listen-facts-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The infectious disease researcher has become America’s most trusted coronavirus expert</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far more people in USA have coronavirus than think...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Far-more-people-in-the-U-S-have-the-coronavirus-15150191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an infectious disease epidemiologist who's worked on pandemics for two decades, I've talked in recent days to journalists and health officials around the United States and from halfway around the world about how to stop the coronavirus. They all have the same questions: How many tests do we need? How should we use tests? For each case we know about, how many more cases are out there? What's the best way to find undiagnosed cases? Should we do "active case finding," which involves testing everyone who is mildly ill, then isolating known cases and quarantining and isolating their contacts? Instead - or in addition - should we implement intense social distancing, close schools and take other similar measures?  Everyone asks the same important, interrelated questions. In one respect, the answer is the same for all of them: We must vastly expand our testing capacity. No country has controlled transmission effectively without massive testing capacity. The United States currently has a sliver of the capacity we need, which is only a tiny fraction of that available in other countries. South Korea has performed over 320,000 tests - almost one for every 150 people. That is 30 times the testing per capita that we have done in the United States. Exceptional teams are racing to solve testing bottlenecks at local and state levels (Massachusetts is just one example), filling the vacuum left by the complete absence of federal leadership. Regulatory and technical hurdles accounted for early delays. Now that we're past those, several shortages are getting in the way. We don't have enough protective equipment for testers, nor swabs for sampling or reagents to extract genetic material from the virus. We don't have enough physical test kits, or enough human power to run large-scale testing. The result is that we have no idea how many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrifying images show patients lying on floor of packed hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8142013/Horrifying-images-coronavirus-patients-lying-floor-packed-Madrid-hospital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scenes were reportedly recorded at the Infanta Leonor Hospital and the Severo Ochoa de Leganes Hospital in the Spanish capital Madrid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATION RAGE: Couple Throws Fit At Supermarket Over Not Being Able To Buy 552 Cans Of Soda...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/2020/03/23/coronavirus-mountain-dew-kroger-couple-552-cans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Kentucky couple reportedly tried to buy as many Mountain Dew cans at a Louisville Kroger earlier [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People in China Need Green Light From App to Move Around Country...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-china-green-light-alibaba-091822087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- To get permission to leave China’s coronavirus epicenter and return to his job in Hong Kong, a Chinese banker needed two things: a letter from his company and a green health code from Alipay.The man, who gave his name only as Clarence because of privacy concerns, secured the necessary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump appears to waffle on shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/502a3b1afb9c5d1bc14e6af77d112207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Top Trump administration officials and congressional leaders struggled Monday to finalize a nearly $2 trillion economic rescue package as the coronavirus crisis deepened, even as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon General: 'This week it's going to get bad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/video/us-surgeon-general-jerome-adams-on-coronavirus-this-week-it-s-going-to-get-bad-81091141801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Jerome Adams, the U.S. surgeon general, tells TODAY that “we need to come together as a nation” to fight the coronavirus outbreak but “a lot of people think this can’t happen to them.” He urges Americans to stay at home despite an overnight tweet from President Trump saying “we cannot let the cure be worse than the problem,” saying we all need to act as if we already have the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking video shows how far coughs can travel through air...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/coronavirus-shocking-video-shows-how-21738511</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists from Bauhaus University in Weimar have revealed exactly what happens when we cough, and why it's wise to stay home even if you don’t think you have the virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service employee sick...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/488963-secret-service-employee-tests-positive-for-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Secret Service employee has tested positive for the coronavirus, the agency said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beautiful World Beside the Broken One...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/23/the-beautiful-world-beside-the-broken-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE — A two-week bout with flu turned me into a person I didn’t recognize — a hopeless, coughing, exhausted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm 26. It Sent Me to Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/23/im-26-coronavirus-sent-me-to-the-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’m 26. I don’t have any prior autoimmune or respiratory conditions. I work out six times a week, and abstain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Just Called to Say... the Phone Call Is Back...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/22/i-just-called-to-say-the-phone-call-is-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other night my friend Margot called. It’s not unusual for me to hear from Margot — we’ve been friends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am constitutional lawyer. I see govt using Covid-19 to take away rights'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/op-ed/483758-coronavirus-constitutional-rights-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do we really think “it can’t happen here” in America? Could we quarantine the constitution? Are we doing it already?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS DELAYED A YEAR?</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/off-whos-saying-over-tokyo-olympics-postponement-081022956--oly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the deadly coronavirus spreads around the globe, doubts grow over whether the Tokyo 2020 Olympics will go ahead as scheduled from July 24 to August 9. -- International Olympic Committee president Thomas Bach, announcing on Sunday that a postponement was under consideration. &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t think</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA orders first shutdown of website over coronavirus fraud...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-orders-first-shutdown-website-over-coronavirus-fraud-023738032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Department of Justice announced Sunday it had shut down a website claiming to sell a coronavirus vaccine, in its first act of federal enforcement against fraud in connection with the pandemic. Lawsuits had been filed against the site coronavirusmedicalkit.com, which claimed to sell vaccines for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On call with Trump officials, police chief pleads: 'Stop testing NBA players, start testing first responders'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/call-trump-officials-police-chief-pleads-stop-testing/story?id=69739541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the International Association of Chiefs of Police pleaded Friday with Trump administration officials for help dealing with the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington to pick which companies survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/03/22/bailout-coronavirus-congress-crisis-142961</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with the biggest economic bailout ever, a lot of firms won't make it through the coronavirus crisis. How should Congress handle the triage?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Gov. Pritzker mocks Trump's efforts...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/22/wild-west-states-pritzker-says-141580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“All I can say is get to work or get out of the way.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Tread Lightly as Pandemic Spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-tread-lightly-as-pandemic-spreads/ar-BB11yiwv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWSON: Please can our politicians stop calling this a war. It's nothing like it... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-8141097/DOMINIC-LAWSON-politicians-stop-calling-war-like-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOMINIC LAWSON: As so often in her 68-year reign, the Queen gets it right. In her statement to the country on meeting the challenge of the coronavirus, she did not once use the word 'war'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus reveals financial irresponsibility of Americans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/488906-coronavirus-reveals-financial-irresponsibility-of-americans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This national crisis reminds us to save for the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS DELAYED A YEAR?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ioc-admits-postponing-olympics-option-cancellation-not-agenda-211002862--oly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The International Olympic Committee said Sunday that postponing the 2020 Olympics is one of its options as the world grapples with the coronavirus pandemic, but that cancellation of the Tokyo showpiece was "not on the agenda". The IOC has faced strong pressure to push back the Games, scheduled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisis can't bridge partisan divide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-coronavirus-crisis-cant-bridge-191231600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is so politically polarized that even views of the coronavirus pandemic split along party lines, polls show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ hosts 10-hour INSTAGRAM party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dont-stop-music-dj-hosts-10-hour-instagram-230426818.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus has upended daily lives, with thousands of deaths around the world. Celebrity DJ D-Nice has begun hosting virtual dance parties on his Instagram Live channel in an effort to lift spirits as people self-isolate over coronavirus concerns. Many of his A-list friends -- including Rihanna</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress May Allow Fed to Purchase Longer-Term Corporate Debt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/congress-may-allow-fed-purchase-153000316.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Congress is likely to pass legislation Monday clearing the way for more emergency action from the Federal Reserve, following already unprecedented steps from the central bank to keep credit markets liquid.Though details were unclear, lawmakers and Trump adminstration officials on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia steps up efforts as second wave of infections strikes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asia-steps-virus-efforts-second-wave-infections-strikes-065250439.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Australia's Bondi Beach to the streets of New Delhi, authorities across Asia have ramped up efforts to stem the spread of the deadly novel coronavirus amid fears of a second wave of infections in places where outbreaks had appeared under control. Tighter travel restrictions were imposed in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic prompts rare questioning of Thai monarchy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200322230729-bnkdg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/THAILAND-MONARCHY (PIX):Coronavirus pandemic prompts rare questioning of Thai monarchy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi King imposes curfew...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200322224027-pflg0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SAUDI (URGENT):Saudi King Salman imposes curfew to curb coronavirus spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO: 80% WILL GET VIRUS; NINE MONTH CRISIS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/574277/new-york-cuomo-slams-groups-crisis-could-last-nine-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York Governor Andrew Cuomo has warned that 80% of New York state’s population could become infected with the coronavirus and said the crisis could last as long as nine months. Cuomo’s sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says 'no need' to postpone November vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-says-e2-80-98no-need-e2-80-99-to-postpone-november-vote-over-virus/ar-BB11yfHo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tylenol, soup and internet can treat most symptoms of COVID-19 [whether you have it or not]...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/tylenol-soup-and-the-internet-can-treat-most-symptoms-of-covid-19-whether-you-have-it-or-not/ar-BB11yfoQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Rate May Soar to 30%... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/us-jobless-rate-may-soar-to-30-25-fed-e2-80-99s-bullard-says/ar-BB11y3ER</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ gov. vows to 'take action' against people who don't stay home...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gov-murphy-vows-action-to-enforce-nj-stay-at-home-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy expressed anger Sunday at reports of people in New Jersey ignoring his stay-at-home order and warned “We're going to take action."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Govt uses Bluetooth to track exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/singapore-coronavirus-big-brother-bd7cec2b-eb47-4b49-a337-f4f4ecff57f2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore is tracing the coronavirus in ways that are simultaneously impressive and terrifying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna calls virus the great equalizer in bathtub video...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/22/madonna-calls-coronavirus-the-great-equalizer-in-bizarre-bathtub-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 61-year-old singer preaches to her fans from her tub, surrounded by candles and wearing nothing but jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Nobel laureate predicts a quicker recovery: 'We're going to be fine'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-nobel-laureate-predicts-quicker-210318391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nobel laureate predicted China's recovery weeks before it happened. Analyzing the numbers, he sees a much brighter global outcome than many experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela prohibits company layoffs and suspends credit collections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200323001838-oqzqs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VENEZUELA:Venezuela prohibits company layoffs and suspends credit collections over coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS ON THE BRINK</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/team-canada-says-wont-participate-020548863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The COC and CPC urgently call on the International Olympic Committee (IOC), and the International Paralympic Committee (IPC) and the World Health Organization (WHO) to postpone the Games for one year and we offer them our full support in helping navigate all the complexities that rescheduling the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel in quarantine... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f71e89eacd7cc6f84b81991c03e82c31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German Chancellor Angela Merkel has gone into quarantine after being informed that a doctor who administered a vaccine to her has tested positive for the new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen.  Rand Paul Tests Positive... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c3db22a242e9577126052dece8285d2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. Rand Paul of Kentucky has tested positive for the novel coronavirus, becoming the first case of COVID-19 in the Senate and raising fears about the further transmission of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Public places stand abandoned...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af7b4e94c6c0b86f6d35f4c79be99cf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are places meant for people. New York’s Grand Central Terminal — a common metaphor for “busy” in much of the English-speaking world — dotted with only scattered commuters. The Grand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC trying to keep crowds from cherry blossoms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5720c07cc92db122d5f2e147c02b1063</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As signature cherry blossom trees go through peak bloom in the nation's capital, officials in the District of Columbia are resorting to mass street closures to keep large crowds...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEINSTEIN TESTS POSITIVE IN PRISON</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/coronavirus-harvey-weinstein-positive-test-prision-1202889800/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein has tested positive for the novel coronavirus in prision. Just days after being transferred to the Wende Correctional Facility from NYC’s Rikers Island, the Oscar winning producer …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The week that America changed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a82294fc0723630d850603dd7b016ad5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Change came to the United States of America during the third week of March in 2020. It did not come all at once, though it came quite rapidly. As had happened in other lands, there was no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacists encouraging members to spread coronavirus to cops, Jews...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/white-supremacists-encouraging-members-spread-coronavirus-cops-jews/story?id=69737522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alert was sent to local police agencies by federal officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felony charge for woman who coughed in paramedic's face and shouted, 'I have coronavirus'...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/coronavirus-cougher-971235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 22--A woman arrested for assaulting her boyfriend shouted “I have the coronavirus” before intentionally coughing in the face of a paramedic who she sprayed with “copious amounts of saliva,” pol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man falls to death from NYC apartment during isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/man-falls-death-16th-floor-21735275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters working on dailystar.co.ukwill be working to source the latest information, reaction, pictures and video related to this story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel in quarantine... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/22/chancellor-angela-merkel-in-quarantine-after-contact-with-doctor-who-tested-positive-for-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel will be tested regularly over the coming days and will continued to conduct her duties as chancellor from home, her spokesperson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen.  Rand Paul Tests Positive... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rand-paul-coronavirus-847b3df1-92bc-4ee6-833b-952d16f3ee3f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's the first U.S. senator to test positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia invokes 'fake news' law...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/20/russia-invokes-fake-news-law-to-order-removal-of-c/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian media outlets faced penalties Friday after federal regulators invoked the nation’s newly enacted law against “fake news” to censor reports about the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ seeks new emergency powers; Detain people indefinitely without trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/21/doj-coronavirus-emergency-powers-140023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the requests to Congress would allow the department to petition a judge to indefinitely detain someone during an emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says USA 'created coronavirus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/coronaviurs-irans-supreme-leader-says-21733354  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ayatollah Ali Khamenei's outburst came during a televised speech about the crisis, during which he branded it "strange" that America would offer to help while it struggles with the crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Designated Survivor plan' if Boris falls sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/coronavirus-downing-st-draws-up-21733861  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports Foreign Secretary Dominic Raab, who is also First Secretary of State, will stand in for the PM if necessary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED READY WITH $4 TRILLION</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-fed-will-make-up-to-4-trillion-in-loans-to-businesses-to-rescue-economy-mnuchin-says-2020-03-22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin said Sunday that the Federal Reserve will play a key role in lending funds to businesses hurt by the coronavirus pandemic....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor in Italy: We no longer help those over 60...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/International/Israeli-doctor-in-Italy-We-no-longer-help-those-over-60-621856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli medical doctor Gai Peleg told Israeli television that in northern Italy the orders are not to allow those over 60 access to respiratory machines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESTING STILL BOTCHED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ad73b37c17d0b73197535b5b836b38a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — Drive-thru sites have been opening around the United States to make it quicker and safer to test people for the new coronavirus. But much like the rest of the U.S. response...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
