<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Opponents of far-right protest as campaign enters final week...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-04-16/opponents-of-french-far-right-plan-protests-as-election-campaign-enters-final-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avian flu has spread to 27 states, sharply driving up egg prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/avian-flu-has-spread-to-27-states-sharply-driving-up-egg-prices/ar-AAWgZBQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly gun violence surges with at least 24 people shot in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/shooting-philadelphia-kensington-mantua-strawberry-mansion-20220415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shootings happened in neighborhoods across the city and at all hours of the day, police said, with bullets striking people who ranged in age from 18 to 65.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Reports Her First Fundraising Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/marjorie-taylor-greene-reports-her-first-fundraising-loss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) has been one of the biggest fundraisers for Republicans in the House. But to kick off 2022, she actually spent more than she took in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron should prepare for brutal shock after latest polls?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/comment/expresscomment/1596916/Macron-latest-frech-election-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ON EASTER Sunday, French President Emmanuel Macron should pray next week is uneventful. If it is, he will be reelected. Marine Le Pen should pray for someone or something to disrupt the political week. If that happens, she probably wins the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic mushrooms' for therapy? Vets help sway...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-matthew-butler-utah-salt-lake-city-lifestyle-3384fd864634204deba9fa8c21d4dcf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Matthew Butler spent 27 years in the Army, but it took a day in jail to convince him his post-traumatic stress disorder was out of control. The recently retired Green Beret had already tried antidepressants, therapy and a support dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA deeply concerned...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/us-deeply-concerned-by-jerusalem-violence-urges-care-for-temple-mount-status-quo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Department says it will continue contact with Israeli, Palestinian officials to deescalate tensions after 185 injured in police crackdown on Muslim rioting at Al-Aqsa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Kindness Strengthens Brain Health...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/04/15/kindness-cognitive-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doing an act of kindness can make you feel good about yourself, and a new study suggests it also benefits the brains of everyone living under one roof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF THE 'PINK MOON'</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/space-news/full-pink-moon-rises-saturday-night/1172232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pink Moon will be the main astronomical event in the evening skies this weekend, but some lucky stargazers could be treated to an added celestial bonus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol mulls rolling out hi-tech 'smart walls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10719113/Border-Patrol-talks-roll-hi-tech-smart-walls-detect-intruders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology company DarkPulse claims it has pitched its sophisticated fiber-optic 'smart wall' cables to Department of Homeland Security officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fever Starts to Break in Boise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/housing-market-in-boise-idaho-starts-to-crack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Housing Market Fever Starts to Break in Boise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video of conservative CCW event showing racist comments sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/3270390-video-of-las-vegas-conservative-ccw-event-showing-racist-comments-sparks-outrage-responses-from-attending-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (KLAS) — Racist comments made at a conservative political event are sparking outrage. The event, titled the “Vegas CCW” class, was held on Saturday, April 10, at a Las Vegas-Clark Library…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel's 'Great Comeback' Has Price: Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/travels-great-comeback-has-a-price-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arriving at London’s Gatwick Airport for his easyJet flight to Malaga, Spain, with his wife and 12-year-old daughter on April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky-High Pandemic Housing Market Finds Gravity Does Exist...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/the-sky-high-pandemic-housing-market-finds-gravity-does-exist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luis Solis, a real estate agent in Portland, Ore., marked a milestone weekend late last month. It was the first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Gamble Pivots to Very Different Battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/16/putins-ukraine-gamble-pivots-to-a-very-different-battlefield/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine — There are fields instead of city streets, farmsteads instead of apartment buildings. Open highways stretch to the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 under evacuation orders as New Mexico wildfire rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wildfires-new-mexico-colorado-fires-evacuations-2a4b21f7d5632b010a2b84b4f63bbfc5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Douglas Siddens’ mother was among those who made it out with just the clothes on her back when a deadly, wind-fueled wildfire ripped through a mountain community in southern New Mexico. The RV park where she lived was reduced to “metal frame rails and steel wheels,” said Siddens, who managed the site</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden prepares for more clashes as far-right demos continue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sweden-europe-riots-b9c19932f7828bb8887ef69d10d568b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Police in Sweden say they are preparing for new violent clashes following riots that erupted between demonstrators and counter-protesters in the central city of Orebro on Friday ahead of an anti-Islam far-right group’s plan to burn a Quran there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War far from over as Kyiv strikes renewed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-kharkiv-moscow-0a9b737d09fec032affe3d9e5e82893a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces resumed scattered attacks on Kyiv, western Ukraine and beyond Saturday in an explosive reminder to Ukrainians and their Western supporters that the whole country remains under threat despite Russia’s pivot toward mounting a new offensive in the east.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai's covid siege: Food shortages, talking robots, starving animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/shanghai-e2-80-99s-covid-siege-food-shortages-talking-robots-starving-animals/ar-AAWgba7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities seek info after dolphin found impaled on Florida beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/health/authorities-seek-info-after-dolphin-found-impaled-on-florida-beach/article_d17a6427-28cc-5b1d-a3bd-b5cd71016228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are asking for the public’s health to find who was responsible after the body of a dolphin was found on a Florida beach that had been impaled with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER adopts 'poison pill' to thwart Elon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/15/twitter-board-adopts-poison-pill-after-musks-43-billion-offer-to-buy-company.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The board voted unanimously to adopt the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinking of Russian warship offers Ukraine boost...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/3270399-sinking-of-russian-warship-offers-ukraine-a-morale-and-maybe-strategic-boost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sinking of Russia’s Moskva cruiser has dealt a major blow to the Kremlin’s fleet in the Black Sea and offered up a big public relations win to Ukrainian forces.  The warship — which sank Thursd…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers explore unlikely treatment for cognitive disorders: Video games...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/04/15/1092804764/video-games-developed-to-treat-cognitive-disorders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video games distract, amuse, and inspire. But new research begs the question: can they heal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful space laser detected by S Africa telescope...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/15/world/space-laser-megamaser-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers have detected a powerful radiowave laser, known as a megamaser, in space. This record-breaking megamaser is the most distant one ever observed at 5 billion light-years away from Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House restarting federal oil lease sales...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/15/white-house-restarting-federal-oil-gas-lease-sales-next-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement comes almost exactly 15 months after President Biden imposed a moratorium on such sales upon taking office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin dies after beachgoers in Texas try to ride it...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksby.com/news/national/dolphin-dies-after-beachgoers-in-texas-try-to-ride-it-rescue-group-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksby.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dolphin that was stranded on a Texas beach is now dead after a wildlife group said people tried to ride it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon hunts 'extremist or dissident ideologies'; 'Equity' plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/pentagon-equity-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Defense issued an equity report, aiming to equalize outcomes of employees and partners across racial, sexual and gender lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freeze Koala Sperm to Save Species, Researchers Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5qegq/koala-sperm-bank-extinction-australia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are working to find ways to save koalas, which have been devastated by droughts, deforestation, and bushfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZELENSKY:  Prepare for possibility he could use nukes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/15/politics/tapper-zelensky-interview-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky told CNN Friday that "all of the countries of the world" should be prepared for the possibility that Russian President Vladimir Putin could use tactical nuclear weapons in his war on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>900 civilian bodies found...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-zelenskyy-kyiv-business-black-sea-22d7279f32c15d4a7037a2195113fb57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The bodies of more than 900 civilians have been discovered in the region surrounding the Ukrainian capital following Russia's withdrawal — most of them fatally shot, police said Friday, an indication that many people were "simply executed.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Harris release tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-harris-release-2021-tax-returns-131472fc-c094-4c12-9ff9-db8eec2fc1b3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden and First Lady Jill Biden earned $610,702 in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warship sinks; Pentagon says new Ukraine missile responsible...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ukraine-sank-russias-cruiser-moskva-191621923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Moskva made headlines in February after an apparent audio exchange between the vessel and Ukrainian border guards on Snake Island went viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The face of NBA's China relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story?id=33723055&amp;_slug_=brooklyn-nets-owner-joe-tsai-face-nba-uneasy-china-relationship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two and a half years after buying the Nets, the billionaire personifies the compromises embedded in the NBA-China relationship, which requires the league to do business with an authoritarian government -- and play by its rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 arrested for dog theft during DC crime spree...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2022/04/7-arrested-in-connection-with-dog-theft-during-dc-crime-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven people are in custody in connection the theft of two dogs during a string of robberies earlier this week across the District, police said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did HARVARD Go After One of Best Black Professors?</title>
      <link>https://quillette.com/2022/04/15/why-did-harvard-university-go-after-one-of-its-best-black-professors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;quillette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roland Fryer Jr.’s life is a movie script: A man abandoned by his mom and raised by an alcoholic dad became the youngest black professor to ever secure tenure at Harvard University. After ascending to the academic elite, Fryer didn’t resign himself to irrelevant technical puzzles; he put</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans doc who helps teens transition says now 'gone too far'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/15/transitions-have-gone-too-far-trans-psychologist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transgender psychologist fears many are making life-changing decisions because it’s “trendy” and pushed on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's pollster on how to 'not get a** kicked' in midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/15/bidens-pollster-midterms-00025482</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On this week’s episode of Playbook Deep Dive, Ryan Lizza joins John Anzalone, who is best known as President Biden’s pollster, but is also a top adviser to Nevada Gov. Steve Sisolak, who is up for reelection this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight from big cities INCREASES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10722017/Record-32-homebuyers-fleeing-coastal-cities-like-San-Francisco-LA-Seattle-Boston.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Redfin, a real-estate brokerage, said 32.3 percent of users were looking to move to a different area in the first quarter of 2022, up from 31.5 percent a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxes too high? Lots of Californians think so...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Taxes-too-high-A-lot-of-Californians-think-so-17083064.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With April 15, the traditional tax day, upon us, a new California poll shows that the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save energy and annoy Vlad, Vice-Chancellor says...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-61117828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice-chancellor says they should use bikes and lower the thermostat to use less Russian gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental illness may raise risk of breakthrough virus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/prevention-cures/3269827-mental-illness-may-raise-risk-of-breakthrough-covid-19-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Story at a glance Researchers at the University of California, San Francisco looked at data from 263,697 U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs patients who had completed their vaccines and had at lea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How BARNES &amp; NOBLE Went From Villain to Hero...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/15/how-barnes-noble-went-from-villain-to-hero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years on the decline, Barnes &amp; Noble’s sales are up, its costs are down — and the same people</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
