<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK NOW DELETING ALTERNATIVE LEFT-WING MEDIA PAGES TOO...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/the-purge-facebook-now-deleting-alternative-left-wing-media-pages-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NATO-backed @DFRLab is currently assisting FB's purge. This is deeply disturbing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THAT DOG'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/president-trump-calls-omarosa-dog-lowlife/story?id=57164350</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump fired off a nasty tweet at his former aide Omarosa Maigault Newman Tuesday, calling her a "lowlife" and a "dog." "When you give a crazed, crying lowlife a break, and give her a job at the White House, I guess it just didn’t work out. Good work by General Kelly for quickly firing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Satanist' burns down historic 250-year-old wooden church...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/satanist-teenager-burns-down-historic-13079705 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schoolboy Ignat Sharapov, 15, has been arrested as experts say it will cost more than £1million to repair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Years after UFO encounter, man breaks silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/magnolia/2018/08/13/alien-abduction-45-years-after-ufo-encounter-mississippi-man-breaks-his-silence/922706002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moss Point man hopes to set record straight on his alien abduction experience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THAT 'DOG'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/1029329583672307712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“When you give a crazed, crying lowlife a break, and give her a job at the White House, I guess it just didn’t work out. Good work by General Kelly for quickly firing that dog!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The media's blatant hypocrisy -- even about media-bashing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/13/the-blatant-media-hypocrisy-even-about-media-bashing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the age of self-congratulatory media. “Democracy dies in darkness” goes the ridiculous tagline on The Washington Post’s front page. Reporters openly call themselves heroes and firefighte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal shelter accused of freezing cats to euthanize them...</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2018/08/14/southern-indiana-animal-shelter-accused-of-freezing-cats-to-euthanize-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPENCER COUNTY, Ind. – A southern Indiana animal shelter is under investigation after an employee said she was told to freeze cats alive to euthanize them.  Bridget Woodson, a former employee at the Spencer County Animal Shelter, said her boss instructed her twice to put cats in a freezer, reports WEVV. Woodson said she took the animals to a veterinarian to be humanely euthanized instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To fend off NETFLIX, theaters try 3-screen immersion...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fend-off-netflix-movie-theaters-094828458.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Sit at the back of the movie theater, and it's possible to see the appeal of ScreenX, the latest attempt to drag film lovers off the sofa and away from Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott iPhones!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-calls-boycott-iphones-targets-103554633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey’s president escalated tensions with the US on Tuesday after calling for a boycott of American electronics, amid reports that diplomatic talks have stalled over the issue of a detained US pastor. Showing no signs of backing down in a standoff with President Donald Trump, Recep Tayyip Erdogan suggested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What the hell are you doing?'</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.se/20180814/what-the-hell-are-you-doing-swedish-politicians-react-to-car-burnings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.se&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swedish politicians were quick to react after a spate of car fires in the greater Gothenburg region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracy theories more rampant than ever?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/14/conspiracy-theories-misconceptions-rampant-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans’ beliefs about politics are as inaccurate and bizarre as ever. Is there a way to fix that?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts see hope after fresh spate of Latin American corruption scandals...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180814-experts-see-hope-after-fresh-spate-latin-american-corruption-scandals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From laboratory in far west, China's surveillance state spreads quietly...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-monitoring-insight/from-laboratory-in-far-west-chinas-surveillance-state-spreads-quietly-idUSKBN1KZ0R3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filip Liu, a 31-year-old software developer from Beijing, was traveling in the far western Chinese region of Xinjiang when he was pulled to one side by police as he got off a bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vienna dethrones Melbourne as world's most liveable city...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/vienna-tops-melbourne-as-worlds-most-liveable-city-economist-survey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vienna has dislodged Melbourne for the first time at the top of the Economist Intelligence Unit's Global Liveability Index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture army base...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/taliban-capture-northern-afghan-base--kill-at-least-14-soldiers-10616380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAZAR-I-SHARIF, Afghanistan:  Taliban fighters overran a northern Afghan army base, officials said on Tuesday (Aug 14), killing at least 14 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-dressed plane passenger tied up after going berserk on flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/plane-passenger-left-just-bra-13079273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plane crew tied her legs together and her hands behind her back, before sitting her on the floor of the plane</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Blue wave' to be tested in key Midwestern primaries...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/midwest/ct-midwestern-primaries-20180813-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are fighting to beat back Republican gains across the Midwest as the 2018 primary season roars through Wisconsin and Minnesota.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Cryptocurrency Market Plumbs New Depths...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cryptocurrency-market-plumbs-new-depths-in-2018-1534241274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broad selloff in digital currencies has pushed the value of the entire market below $200 billion for the first time this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In speech that Beijing tried to stop, Hong Kong independence advocate lashes out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/pro-independence-hong-kong-politician-andy-chan-discusses-china-atfcc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A politician who advocates independence for Hong Kong lashed out at China in a speech to foreign journalists that the central and local governments wanted stopped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOME DEPOT Crushes Earnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/home-depot-earnings-q2-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home Depot reaped the benefits of a warmer start to the summer, following a rocky spring season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada rematch pits rural voters against booming Las Vegas...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/401644-nevada-rematch-pits-rural-voters-against-a-booming-las-vegas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside a bustling mall on a recent Saturday, volunteers working for the Nevada Democratic Party pester attendees at a job fair hosted by the Latin Chamber of Commerce to register to vote. Steven Horsford is working the crowd, smiling and laughing with the volunteers he recognizes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Burning: Migrant Gangs Unleash Coordinated Fire-Bomb Rampage Across Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-13/sweden-burning-migrant-gangs-unleash-coordinated-fire-bomb-rampage-across-multiple</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror probe after driver ploughs into pedestrians outside UK Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7009654/parliament-westminster-crash-incident-latest-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEVERAL pedestrians and cyclists have been injured this morning after a car “driving at 50mph” ploughed into barriers outside the Houses of Parliament. A man, in his 20s, has been arres…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than munchies: Eating pot 'elevated' dining...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/aug/13/more-than-munchies-how-eating-pot-went-from-crude-to-elevated-dining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannabis is becoming a cooking ingredient in its own right, as chefs create elaborate cannabis tasting menus at private dinners</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of global crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/aug/13/turkish-lira-record-low-ripples-through-global-currency-markets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peso and rand become knock-on casualties of Turkey’s currency slide after lira falls 8% against the dollar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Struck by Car After Beating Man to Death on Highway in Road Rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/crime/article216610405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two men killed Sunday after a road rage car crash on Interstate 5 in Natomas have been identified by the Sacramento County Coroner’s Office. Witnesses saw an Oroville man chase another man with a bat, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 dogs, cats saved by police in daring wildfire rescue...</title>
      <link>https://www.mynbc5.com/article/caught-on-video-60-dogs-cats-saved-by-police-in-daring-wildfire-rescue/22716685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mynbc5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saved! 60 dogs, cats rescued as California wildfire threatened an animal shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan refugees find safe haven in Scotland, along with gray weather, weird food...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article215843715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tie to the oil industry was the seed for a small but growing outpost of Venezuelans who are settling in Scotland after fleeing chaos and crime back home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than Half Foreign Refugees on Food Stamps...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/13/more-than-half-of-foreign-refugees-are-on-taxpayer-funded-food-stamps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of the annual inflow of foreign refugees arriving in the U.S. are on food stamps, analysis of a government report reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry passengers punch conductor...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/13/furious-straphanger-beats-up-subway-conductor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A viral video shows a subway conductor getting pummeled by an angry man and woman at a Brooklyn station this weekend. Jacob Credell was working on a southbound A train just before 5 a.m. on Saturda…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Loses Mars Rover in Dust Storm...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/13/nasa-opportunity-rover-still-lost-mars-dust-storm-engulfed-red-planet-begins-settle-7831488/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plucky exploration 'droid was battered in a super-powerful maelstrom and is now feared to be lying dead on the surface of the Red Planet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing number of California detainees are Indians crossing through Mexico... </title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-indian-immigrants-20180813-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian nationals make up about 40% of those held at ICE's detention facility in the Imperial Valley, officials say, and of 680 migrants detained at a federal prison in Victorville, 380 are Indian. Asylum seekers say they're fleeing an increase in persecution under a Hindu nationalist government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Brightest ever' Perseids meteor shower stuns stargazers...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6054643/Brightest-Perseids-Meteor-Shower-revealed-stunning-new-photos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stargazers around the world will be able to see the Perseids for the last time tonight. The annual event will be visible in Central America, Asia, much of Africa, and parts of South America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST LEAD TUES:  Trump aggressive use of nondisclosure agreements, even in govt... </title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-trump-nondisclosure-agreements-20180813-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's bitter fight with a former top White House aide has highlighted his aggressive and unconventional use of nondisclosure agreements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Island with Flourishing 'Third Gender'...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/travel/story/20180813-guna-yala-the-islands-where-women-make-the-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the small indigenous territory of Guna Yala off Panama’s eastern coast, a flourishing ‘third gender’ community is defying stereotypes – and venerating women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neglected Horse Suing!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-horse-was-neglected-by-its-owner-Now-the-horse-13153158.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESTACADA, Ore. - Justice is an 8-year-old American quarter horse who used to be named Shadow. And when he was named Shadow, he suffered. At a veterinarian's exam last year, he was 300 pounds underweight, his black coat lice-ridden, his skin scabbed and his genitals so frostbitten that they might still require amputation. The horse had been left outside and underfed by his previous owner, who last summer pleaded guilty to criminal neglect. And now Justice, who today resides with other rescued equines on a quiet wooded farm within view of Oregon's Cascade mountains, is suing his former owner for negligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging process REVERSED in human cells for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1002867/science-news-Ageing-process-REVERSED-human-cells-University-of-Exeter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have successfully reversed the process of ageing in cells for the first time in a move which could help beat the likes of Alzheimer’s and dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Significant rise in mosquito 'disease danger days'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/significant-rise-in-mosquito-disease-danger-days-in-u-s-report-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many cities in the U.S. are facing an increasing number of days indicating a heightened risk for disease transmission, according to new research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Wild Subway Attacks Stun NYC...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/08/13/a-train-subway-attack-new-york-city-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It happened shortly after 4:30 a.m. Saturday at the Grant Avenue station in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONGEST WAR:  Taliban blindsides U.S. forces with surprise Afghan offensive...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/13/taliban-surprise-offensive-afghanistan-catches-us-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban is on the verge of dramatically expanding its control over southern and eastern Afghanistan in a surprise offensive that has caught Afghan and American forces off guard and thrown a vexing new wrench into the Trump administration’s strategy for ending the nearly 17-year-old war there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-year-olds hack mock version of Florida's election site in minutes...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-reg-kid-election-hack-20180813-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They haven’t even made it to high school yet, but they managed to hack into a mock version of Florida’s election website and change the results in a matter of minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry passengers punch train conductor...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/subway-conductor-assaulted-by-angry-passengers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is looking for a man and woman who assaulted a subway conductor in the face after getting angry with him for announcing the train was going express.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW A TARGET?</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/401637-signs-grow-that-mueller-is-zeroing-in-on-roger-stone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller appears to be narrowing his focus on Roger Stone in his investigation into Russian interference in the election, prompting widespread speculation that the longtime adviser to President Trump is likely a target in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Woos Partners for China Expansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-woos-partners-for-potential-china-expansion-1534071600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Google’s search engine remains blocked in China, the company is courting allies there by providing tools and support to a growing number of app developers, manufacturers and advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-girlfriend speaks out...</title>
      <link>https://thinkprogress.org/keith-ellison-ex-girlfriend-karen-monahan-speaks-out-b4e8c3bf7095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thinkprogress.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I know who I am. I know what I was going to go through."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
GOOGLE tracks movements, like it or not...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/828aefab64d4411bac257a07c1af0ecb/AP-Exclusive:-Google-tracks-your-movements,-like-it-or-not</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Google wants to know where you go so badly that it records your movements even when you explicitly tell it not to.        An Associated Press investiga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside left-wing harassment campaign against lesbian 'BATWOMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-left-wing-harassment-campaign-against-ruby-roses-lesbian-batwoman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enraged DC fans have chased the out actress off social media following her historic casting as Kate Kane/Batwoman in a new TV series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News publishers quietly shut down FACEBOOK chatbots...</title>
      <link>https://digiday.com/media/news-publishers-shut-chatbots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;digiday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post, The Guardian, Mic and others have shut down their chatbots, but Quartz is ramping up bot development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST VIRGINIA HOUSE IMPEACHES SUPREME COURT JUSTICES...</title>
      <link>https://www.wowktv.com/news/west-virginia/west-virginia-house-considers-impeaching-supreme-court/1365301088</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wowktv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West Virginia House of Delegates has voted to impeach Justice Robin Davis. Davis spent around $500,000 on renovations to her office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian warships enter British waters for 'combat training'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7008863/russian-warships-gibraltar-royal-navy-english-channel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO Russian warships have entered Gibraltar waters for “combat training” – days after the Royal Navy intercepted them in the English Channel. The missile cruiser Marshal Ustinov a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Vaping more harmful than previously thought...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7005984/e-cigarettes-vaping-harmful-health-experts-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VAPING is more harmful than previously thought, a study suggests. Some of the effects are similar to those seen in smokers and people with chronic lung disease. Researchers found e-cigs boosts the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo Feminist Double Standard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/13/nyregion/sexual-harassment-nyu-female-professor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avital Ronell, a superstar professor, was found by N.Y.U. to have sexually harassed a male grad student. But his charges have met disbelief from some feminist scholars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas crunch: Hollywood plans glut of big-budget fantasy films...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2018/08/13/dec-21-movies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas crunch: Dec. 21 is a battle royale of big-budget fantasy films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: MUELLER PROBING MY PRIVATE LIFE!</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/13/roger-stone-mueller-collusion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 'deep state trifecta'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER RESTS CASE AGAINST MANAFORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/13/manafort-must-decide-on-defense-as-mueller-wraps-trial-update</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manafort Must Decide on Defense as Mueller Wraps Up Case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applicant interview, INSTA vetting, $900 monthly fee: Welcome to NYC's most exclusive gym...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/13/nycs-most-exclusive-gym-costs-900-a-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How do you own everything? That’s the aggressive question posed on the online application for Performix House, an exclusive new gym near Union Square where wannabe members must undergo a rigorous a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACKED AIR CONDITIONERS COULD TRIGGER MASS BLACKOUTS?</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/water-heaters-power-grid-hack-blackout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found that just 42,000 of those hacked home devices could be enough to leave a country of 38 million people in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain plauged by 15 weekly acid attacks; Child perps...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/shocking-fifteen-acid-attacks-happen-13073723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A Daily Mirror investigation has uncovered the terrible amount of acid attacks being carried out in the UK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOOD FIGHT: 'Repulsive' ads pit vegans against 'extremists' of 'Vegandale'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/toronto/even-vegans-are-against-morally-superior-vegandales-takeover-of-low-income-toronto-neighbourhood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the centre of the community, residents are walking by signs advertising ‘morality on tap,’ ‘morally superior IPA.’ Vegans say the advertising is reinforcing negative ster…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba debates modernizing Cold War-era constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-constitution/cuba-begins-public-debate-on-modernizing-cold-war-era-constitution-idUSKBN1KY2A2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba on Monday began a rare public discussion to overhaul its Cold War-era constitution, a process the government is calling participatory democracy at its best and opponents are branding a fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Lunch lady sisters stole $500k from school cafeterias...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcconnecticut.com/news/local/New-Canaan-Lunch-Ladies-Accused-of-Stealing-Nearly-Half-a-Million-Dollars-Police-490739301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcconnecticut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two sisters who worked in the cafeterias of two New Canaan schools are accused of stealing nearly half a million dollars from the cafeterias over a five-year span, according to New Canaan police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rush to rescue man with parrot on shoulder in 'quicksand' mud...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnd.com/news/local/article216577100.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person stuck in the mud at Bicentennial Park in Belleville, Illinois, in Southern Illinois was rescued by fire crews along with a parrot that was on his shoulder after they had gotten stuck in a dredged lake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities detain VOICE OF AMERICA correspondent...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/a/chinese-authorities-detain-voa-mandarin-correspondent/4526301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reporter was attempting to interview a retired Chinese professor who was taken away by authorities during a live television interview with VOA nearly two weeks ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 233 TV hits this year, 'Russia Investigating' Dem mulls 2020 bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/Eric-Swalwell-still-a-relative-newbie-in-13148385.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call him ambitious, but with just five years under his congressional belt, 37-year-old East Bay Rep. Eric Swalwell is laying the tracks for a possible 2020 presidential run. “Yes, I am considering running,” Swalwell said in a matter-of-fact way when we caught up with him at a recent National Night Out block party in San Lorenzo, where he was mixing with constituents. From the looks of his travel schedule, Swalwell — who has drawn national attention as one of the lead voices in Congress’ investigation of Russian meddling in the 2016 presidential campaign — is already on his way, stumping hard for midterm candidates across the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER RESTS CASE AGAINST MANAFORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort-prosecution/u-s-rests-its-case-against-former-trump-aide-manafort-idUSKBN1KY27M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. prosecutors on Monday rested their case against former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort after 10 days of testimony detailing how he avoided taxes on at least $16 million of income and lied to banks to maintain an extravagant lifestyle once his work for pro-Kremlin politicians in Ukraine dried up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Chiefs Rip Elizabeth Warren For 'Racist' Remark...</title>
      <link>http://www.telegram.com/news/20180812/police-chiefs-headed-by-dudleys-wojnar-blast-sen-warren-for-remark-on-racist-criminal-justice-system</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUDLEY — Police chiefs in Massachusetts have responded angrily to a remark by U.S. Sen. Elizabeth Warren that the American criminal justice system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: BEZOS MOST POWERFUL MAN IN DC?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/08/has-bezos-become-more-powerful-in-dc-than-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deal for an obscure $10 billion Pentagon contract suggests the extent to which Bezos is gobbling up the Swamp—without the guy in the White House even batting an eye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC METRO STATION EVACUATED OVER BOMB THREAT... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/farragut-west-metro-station-evacuated-bomb-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (WJLA) -- The Farragut West Metro station has been evacuated because of a bomb threat, ABC7 has learned.Employees at the Metro station told ABC7 it was evacuated Monday afternoon because of the threat.Orange, Blue and Silver line trains are temp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seen guy in blue shirt at baseball game? Group pleads for Kavanaugh dirt...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/13/propublicas-appeal-for-dirt-on-brett-kavanaughs-baseball-outings-called-desperate-and-hilarious.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ProPublica is being mocked for soliciting readers to help figure out who attended Washington Nationals games with Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh, where the judge sits and even if he really loves the national pastime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: 98 humans needed to keep species alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/how-many-humans-would-it-take-keep-our-species-alive-ncna900151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given the threats posed by asteroid strikes, pandemics and the like, it's not an idle question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing denies million Muslim held in internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/china-denies-claims-a-million-muslim-uighurs-held-in-internment-camps-11471917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country is responding to concerns raised by a UN committee about a crackdown and strict controls in Xinjiang region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor, eco-friendly urinals spark sniggers in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/paris-eco-friendly-cubist-urinals-spark-sniggers-seething-191048632.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris's penchant for urban urinals has taken a new ecological turn with trialling of a new dry and allegedly odourless version known as the "uritrottoir".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tex-Mex restaurant under fire after serving Sessions...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/tex-mex-restaurant-under-fire-after-serving-attorney-general/490746791/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Tex-Mex restaurant in Houston is facing backlash after it posted a photo of Attorney General Jeff Sessions, who has pushed for a wide crackdown on immigration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>103-year-old San Fran woman burglarized while asleep... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/103-year-old-SF-woman-falls-victim-to-burglar-in-13152570.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 103-year-old San Francisco woman was burglarized Sunday morning and slept through the whole thing, police said.         The victim, who was not identified, was at home on the 1800 block of Eighth Avenue in the Inner Sunset when a 51-year-old woman living in the same apartment building noticed sometime after 2:30 a.m. that their shared garage door had been left open, according to the San Francisco Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI warns of imminent mass attack on world's ATMs...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/08/13/uk-cash-machines-could-mass-hacked-global-cyber-attack-fbi-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banks have been warned of an imminent threat that their cash machines could be mass-hacked by cyber criminals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sting Operation: Illegals Attacked By Bees Rescued by U.S. Border Patrol Agents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/sting-operation-illegal-aliens-attacked-bees-rescued-us-border-patrol-agents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Screenshot) A family of illegal aliens attacked by a swarm of bees was rescued by U.S. Border Patrol agents assigned to the Rio Grande City station and Rio Grande Valley Sectors in Texas, U.S. Customs and Border Patrol (CBP) reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Labour leader admits attending wreath-laying for terrorists behind Munich Olympic massacre...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/aug/13/jeremy-corbyn-not-involved-munich-olympics-massacre-wreath-laying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labour leader rows with Israeli prime minister on Twitter over ceremony for individuals behind Munich massacre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/benjamin-netanyahu-attacks-jeremy-corbyn-over-wreath-laying-memorial-11471988</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Labour leader has found himself amid an escalating row over his presence at a Palestinian wreath-laying ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan vows action against 'economic terrorists' over lira plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-currency-security/erdogan-vows-action-against-economic-terrorists-over-lira-plunge-idUSKBN1KY1R9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Tayyip Erdogan on Monday accused "economic terrorists" of plotting to harm Turkey by spreading false reports and said they would face the full force of the law, as authorities launched investigations of those suspected of involvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury in Fukushima over 20 foot statue of child in protective suit...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6055563/Fukushima-residents-demand-20-foot-statue-child-protective-suit-removed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artist Kenji Yanobe wanted his 'Sun Child' monument to be a sign of living in a world free from nuclear disasters, but locals in Fukushima say the statue may lead people to believe the area is still unsafe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY: NO INTERVIEW AFTER SEPT 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/rudy-giuliani-says-trump-lawyers-are-prepared-to-counter-mueller-1534110560</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s lawyers believe they can weather a “negative” report from special counsel Robert Mueller and are prepared to rebut the conclusions, Rudy Giuliani, one of Mr. Trump’s attorneys, said in an interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Mueller Examining Roger Stone Emails...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2018/08/roger-stone-randy-credico-mueller-assange-wikileaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators are closing in on the longtime Trump adviser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nun busted smuggling cocaine in high heels...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/13/nun-busted-for-smuggling-cocaine-in-high-heels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Missouri nun smuggled two pounds of cocaine into Australia using her high heels — but claims she was duped into the act by a man she met online. Denise Marie Woodrum, 51, was caught arrivin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Military Spy Software On Hundreds of Thousands of Home Routers...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2018/08/russian-military-spy-software-hundreds-thousands-home-routers/150474/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May, the Justice Department told Americans to reboot their routers. But there's more to do — and NSA says it's up to device makers and the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male Model Convicted Of Murdering Rival After Online Feud...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/berkshireeagle/article/947fb03f48a04d02beabced82012db20/male-model-convicted-murdering-rival-after-online-feud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A British fashion model has been convicted of murdering a more successful rival after a social media-fueled dispute. A jury found George Koh guilty on Monday of stabbing Harry Uzoka through the heart outside Uzoka's London home. The 25-year-old victim was signed to London's Premier Model Management agency and had modeled for GQ and Zara. Prosecutors say Uzoka accused Koh of trying to copy him, and the two men feuded after Koh claimed to have slept with Uzoka's girlfriend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot dead after crashing plane into own home...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksl.com/?sid=46375241&amp;nid=148&amp;title=plane-crashes-into-house-in-payson-pilot-dies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man died when he flew an airplane into his own home early Monday morning following a domestic dispute, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOAM CHOMSKY SAYS BIG TECH WRONG...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/free-speech-icon-noam-chomsky-says-big-tech-was-wrong-to-ban-infowars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIT professor defends Alex Jones' right to be offensive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels Confirmed For UK 'CELEBRITY BIG BROTHER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/7003520/the-official-celebrity-big-brother-line-up-confirmed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CELEBRITY Big Brother starts on Thursday – and it’s got the best line up yet. The series launch night, presented by Emma Willis, will feature a former Love Island star, a Towie bad boy and one of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Commentator Detained at Tel Aviv Airport Over Political Activity...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-beinart-i-was-detained-at-ben-gurion-airport-over-political-activity-1.6381149</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli sent home after mooning Nazi death camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-student-sent-home-after-exposing-buttocks-at-nazi-death-camp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incident captured on security cameras at Majdanek during Holocaust education trip; second teenager also sent back early</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN Dems actively welcome socialists...</title>
      <link>http://www.nashvillepublicradio.org/post/tennessee-socialists-face-uphill-battle-support#stream/0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nashvillepublicradio.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a solidly Republican state, socialists in Middle Tennessee know they are playing to a small audience. So the local chapter of the Democratic Socialists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAROSA:  'THEY ARE GOING TO RETALIATE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/omarosa-says-there-are-more-tapes-im-expecting-that-theyre-going-to-retaliate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glacier National Park hit...</title>
      <link>http://www.krtv.com/story/38866502/several-fires-burning-in-glacier-national-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.krtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The park has established a Fire Information Line with updated recorded information about these fires: 406-888-7077.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corey Lewandowski grilled...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/corey-lewandowski-doesnt-fall-for-sacha-baron-cohen-on-who-is-america-2018-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump campaign manager Corey Lewandowski is the latest target on Sacha Baron Cohen's satirical prank show "Who is America?" Baron Cohen questioned Lewandowski about fascism as a tie-in for the anniversary of the Charlottesville white supremacist march.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI fires Strzok over anti-Trump texts...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/13/fbi-fires-peter-strzok-months-after-anti-trump-texts-revealed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI official Peter Strzok, who played a lead role in both the Russian meddling and Hillary Clinton email probes but became a political lightning rod after the revelation of anti-Trump text messages, has been fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia House considers impeaching Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/west-virginia-justices-face-house-impeachment-inquiry-063230124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLESTON, W.Va. (AP) — The West Virginia House of Delegates is taking the extraordinary step of considering the impeachment of the entire state Supreme Court in a scandal over $3.2 million in office renovations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14-year-old runs for Vermont governor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24813c30397747a99ee2da3d8a19c026/14-year-old-boy-uses-legal-quirk-to-run-for-Vermont-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURLINGTON, Vt. (AP) — One of the four Vermont Democrats seeking the party nomination to run for governor in the fall election isn't old enough to vote, let alone drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI fires Strzok over anti-Trump texts...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/401558-fbi-fires-strzok-over-anti-trump-texts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI has fired Peter Strzok, the counterintelligence agent who came under fire for sending disparaging text messages about President Trump and other political figures during the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff David Clarke falls for Sacha Baron Cohen...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/401516-ex-sheriff-david-clarke-describes-how-he-would-have-stopped-anti-fascists-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Milwaukee County Sheriff David Clarke Jr. told disguised comedian Sacha Baron Cohen that it is wrong to "take sides" between fascists and anti-fascists on the latest episode of Showtime's "Who is America?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia cuts oil production despite agreement to hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/13/saudi-arabia-cuts-oil-production-despite-agreement-to-hike-output.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPEC's oil production ticked higher in July, but cuts by top exporter Saudi Arabia weighed on the 15-member group's output just one month after it agreed to start pumping more crude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US probes sale of Mexican radio near LA for ties to Beijing propaganda outlet...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/mexican-radio-beam-chinese-propaganda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large radio station in Mexico will soon begin broadcasting in Chinese in a deal critics say will bring Beijing propaganda to Chinese Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  SHE BEGGED FOR JOB, TEARS IN EYES...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6055723/Trump-finally-slaps-vicious-not-smart-Omarosa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 24 hours after Omarosa Manigault Newman began an all-out TV blitz to promote a tell-all White House memoir, Trump tapped his gigantic social media audience to paint her as a holy terror.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threaten to Kill President: 'Murder Him -- Do Like Gaddafi'...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/13/i-asked-leftists-protesters-what-they-would-do-if-they-met-trump-their-answers-horrified-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Do him like Gaddafi&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poison-fanged: Snakes dangerous enough to kill sold freely...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/latest-news/article216483930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Repticon’s Columbia wildlife show features venomous snake sales in a state with few restrictions on the practice. The show is an attraction for poisonous snake enthusiasts. The event is Repticon’s largest in SC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Incredible maneuvers' by employee who stole plane baffle executives...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/13/alaska-air-unclear-on-how-employee-richard-russell-flew-stolen-plane.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airline executives are unclear whether the ground worker who stole a turboprop plane from Seattle-Tacoma International Airport and performed several stunts before crashing had flying experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  SHE BEGGED FOR JOB, TEARS IN EYES...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-wacky-omarosa-is-hated-in-the-white-house-will-never-work-for-me-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said Monday that fired White House aide Omarosa Manigault-Newman will never work for him again following her recent "vicious" attempts to attack her former colleagues and boss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the 'Hunger Games' of Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-hunger-games-of-porn-a-xxx-reality-series-where-adult-stars-compete-for-crypto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In anticipation of the first annual ‘PornHub Awards,’ the internet giant rolled out a competitive reality series where six stars compete for the championship title and prize money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  She begged for job, tears in eyes...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1028996374174593025</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Wacky Omarosa, who got fired 3 times on the Apprentice, now got fired for the last time. She never made it, never will. She begged me for a job, tears in her eyes, I said Ok. People in the White House hated her. She was vicious, but not smart. I would rarely see her but heard....”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK: SAUDIS APPROACHED TO TAKE TESLA PRIVATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/13/musk-offers-details-on-claims-of-funding-secured-tweet-in-taking-tes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla has been battling wild stock swings and widespread scrutiny in the week following Musk's tweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Seethes Over Plan to Build High-Rise on PEARL JAM Haunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/13/seattle-seethes-over-plan-to-build-high-rise-on-pearl-jam-haunt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle Seethes Over Plan to Build High-Rise on Pearl Jam Haunt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW THREATS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4193b4a3214d4f549f1b0a0d5e488ac8/Omarosa-releases-another-recording,-threatens-to-say-more</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former presidential adviser Omarosa Manigault Newman released another audio recording Monday that she says features President Donald Trump, as she threatened to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxins turning up in dozens of public water systems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ca497384f01401394f4fbdd7e9aeb1d/Toxins-turning-up-in-dozens-of-public-water-systems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HORSHAM, Pa. (AP) — Lauren Woeher wonders if her 16-month-old daughter has been harmed by tap water contaminated with toxic industrial compounds used in products like nonstick coo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Incredible maneuvers' by employee who stole plane baffle executives...</title>
      <link>/https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/13/alaska-air-unclear-on-how-employee-richard-russell-flew-stolen-plane.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threaten to Kill President: 'Murder Him -- Do Like Gaddafi'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/08/i-would-murder-him-antifa-activists-on-video-threaten-to-kill-president-trump-at-unite-the-right-counter-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAR LEFT GROUP VOWS 'BULLETS' FOR POLITICAL ENEMIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/antifa-vows-bullets-for-political-enemies-media-ignores-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far left group's open incitement to violence gets zero press coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TAPES</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/omarosa-manigault-newman-reveals-recording-she-made-president-trump-day-n900066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tape, which was played exclusively Monday on "Today," appears to show Trump having no idea that Newman had been dismissed by his Chief of Staff John Kelly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hip hop community eying new political party...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-pol-hip-hop-busta-rhymes-election-20180812-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expressing frustration that urban issues are not being sufficiently addressed in New York, members of the hip hop community are looking to form their own party line for the coming state elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At world's first cold temp gym, you still feel burn...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90213807/at-the-worlds-first-cold-temperature-gym-you-still-fel-the-burn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Classes are taught in studios cooled down to as low as 45 degrees inside New York City’s Brrrn boutique gym. The founders say it’s not kooky—it’s science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems look to longshot territory for midterm gains...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/democrats-look-to-longshot-territory-for-midterm-gains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The November midterms are on pace to shatter records for political spending</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE RECORDINGS...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/401511-omarosa-releases-tape-of-phone-call-of-trump-being-surprised-she-was</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omarosa Manigault Newman on Monday morning released a recording of a phone call between herself and President Trump in which Trump expresses surprise that the former White House aide was fired.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
