<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns of unnamed foreign efforts to destabilize Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/02/24/putin-warns-of-unnamed-foreign-efforts-to-destabilize-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and its NATO allies have rejected similar previous claims by the Kremlin that they were seeking to undermine Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Battle Over Race, Class and Power at Elite College...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/24/inside-a-battle-over-race-class-and-power-at-smith-college/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHAMPTON, Mass. — In midsummer of 2018, Oumou Kanoute, a Black student at Smith College, recounted a distressing American tale:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Zapping Brains Cure Depression?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/24/can-zapping-our-brains-really-cure-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brain is an electrical organ. Everything that goes on in there is a result of millivolts zipping from one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man exits church after 3.5 years in sanctuary from deportation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-michael-brown-st-louis-immigration-d8d6bd7f7148a50aa93ca65b6c615d86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$30 Million In Damages...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/insurrection-at-the-capitol/2021/02/24/970977612/architect-of-the-capitol-outlines-30-million-in-damages-from-pro-trump-riot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congressional official also says most of his staff have not yet been vaccinated, despite their continuing work at the Capitol campus to repair damage from the insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed suffers widespread disruption to payment services...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/24/business/federal-reserve-outage-fedwire/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve suffered a widespread disruption in multiple payment services Wednesday, including a system that banks and businesses rely on to zip trillions of dollars around the financial system each day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vacuuming up DNA on millions. Possibilities limitless...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/24/969532277/china-wants-your-data-and-may-already-have-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When COVID hit, a Chinese firm offered to set up testing labs in the U.S., which could have given it access to DNA data. The U.S. says this is part of China's effort to collect mass data on Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Top Secret' Saudi docs show Khashoggi assassins used company seized by crown prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/24/politics/saudi-top-secret-documents-khashoggi-bin-salman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two private jets used by a Saudi Arabian assassination squad that killed and allegedly dismembered journalist Jamal Khashoggi were owned by a company that less than a year prior had been seized by the Kingdom's powerful crown prince, Mohammed bin Salman, according to recently filed court documents seen by CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGAIN:  GAMESTOP SOARS 100%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/24/gamestop-shares-soar-more-than-80percent-in-late-afternoon-trading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GameStop announced Wednesday that its chief financial officer Jim Bell will resign on March 26.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Sheriff Says No Evidence Under Influence; No Charges...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/news/tiger-woods-wont-face-charges-for-accident-sheriff-reveals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods was involved in a single-car rollover crash on Tuesday morning, sending him to the [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. demands 'criminal sexual predator' resign...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/24/rep-elise-stefanik-calls-on-gov-cuomo-to-resign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo is a “criminal sexual predator” who “must immediately resign” over a former aide’s detailed sexual-harassment allegations, a member of Congress from …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed system allowing banks to send money back and forth is down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/24/the-feds-system-that-allows-banks-to-send-money-back-and-forth-is-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outage impacted multiple Fed services, including its pivotal automated clearinghouse system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg 'tech co'building campaign tools for left and right...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bloomberg-tech-co-murmuration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stealthy firm, which has been buying political tech firms for more than a year, is backed by Emma Bloomberg's philanthropic group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD's Secretive Intel Team Spies on 'Fight for $15' Workers, Internal Docs Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkdkz9/mcdonalds-secretive-intel-team-spies-on-fight-for-15-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald’s collects ‘strategic intelligence’ on workers advocating for a $15 minimum wage, including ‘how and where will FF$15 attack the brand.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax Could Interfere With Mammogram Results...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/02/23/coronavirus-vaccine-side-effects-could-interfere-with-mammogram-results-doctors-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When lymph nodes swell, they can look just like cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fans worried over 'bloated' and 'zoned out' TV interview before crash...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/24/fans-say-tiger-woods-looked-zoned-out-on-tv-before-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods appeared exhausted on TV the day before his serious car wreck — fueling fears among his fans worried about his “bloated” and “zoned out” appearance. Woods …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venomous Spiders Force Closure Of University Of Michigan Library...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/02/24/university-of-michigan-shuts-down-campus-library-for-2-days-after-discovering-venomous-spiders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "small number" of venomous Mediterranean recluse spiders were uncovered in the basement mechanical room of Shapiro Undergraduate Library in late January during a routine building check, said university spokesperson Kim Broekhuizen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TODAY columnist: 'Bury the 500,000 COVID dead at Mar-a-Lago'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2021/02/22/trump-legacy-bury-half-million-covid-dead-mar-a-lago-column/4535394001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert E. Lee's home, now Arlington National Cemetery, became a final resting place for Union soldiers in 1864. We should follow the Union example.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY shuts cryptocurrency exchanges which hid losses...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/york-shuts-cryptocurrency-exchanges-hid-144635950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York state authorities said they reached an agreement to shut down activities of two cryptocurrency trading platforms which hid an estimated $850 million in losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen fined $540 for drinking tequila in national park; DUI dropped...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/springsteen-fined-540-drinking-tequila-172210341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Springsteen has been fined $540 after pleading guilty to consuming alcohol in a national recreation area where drinking is banned, a federal judge ruled Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France flags new restrictions in 'worsening' situation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/france-flags-restrictions-worsening-covid-120854265.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France may need to impose new local restrictions to deal with a worsening Covid-19 situation as it scrambles to avoid a new national lockdown, a government spokesman said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 a Windfall for Billionaires!</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/economy/articles/2021-02-24/the-pandemic-has-been-a-windfall-for-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American billionaires are the biggest winners of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon beaming power from space...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2398532/us-navy-tests-solar-satellite-beam-power-earth-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Navy has fired a pizza box sized satellite into orbit that generated enough electricity to power an iPad. The Photovoltaic Radiofrequency Antenna Module (PRAM) was launched in May 2020 and h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 test positive on New York rescue flight to Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/over-ten-test-positive-with-coronavirus-from-new-york-rescue-flight-659923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some ultra-Orthodox passengers on the flight allegedly bragged about forging documents to show that they were not positive for the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD deploys robot police dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-testing-ai-powered-robot-dog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 70-pound robotic dog uses artificial intelligence to navigate on its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Seized Congressional Cellphone Records Related to Capitol Attack...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/02/22/capitol-riot-fbi-cellphone-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inclusion of congressional phone data in the FBI investigation raises thorny constitutional questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Woman' accused of punching 2-year-old in face on NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/24/2-year-old-subway-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say an unidentified individual struck a 2-year-old boy in the face multiple times, then ran off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEG PIECED TOGETHER WITH RODS AND SCREWS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2398175/tiger-woods-may-never-get-mobility-back-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIGER Woods “may never get his mobility back” and narrowly avoided having his leg amputated after the crash, a doctor has said. The 45-year-old golf ace was pulled from the wr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen Pleads Guilty to Alcohol Consumption in Closed Area; DUI and Other Charge Dropped...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/music/news/bruce-springsteen-guilty-alcohol-consumption-dui-dropped-1234914133/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a court hearing Wednesday regarding his much-reported November DUI arrest, Bruce Springsteen pleaded guilty to consuming alcohol in a restricted area but the driving under the influence and reck…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCKY TO BE ALIVE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tiger-woods-car-crash-updates-ad2a23683a424fd6f18a408eafd59028</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BIGGIE' doc offers intimate look at rap legend from his inner circle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biggie-doc-offers-intimate-look-142835930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Notorious B.I.G., the rapper whose deep-bellied delivery thrust hip hop forward and earned him designation as one of rap's all-time greats, has proven a fount of fascination since his shock murder at age 24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising bond yields continue to sap appeal of stocks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-hong-kong-coronavirus-pandemic-asia-financial-markets-e099520810a0d25f5a614007652b9815</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREER OVER?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/2392697/tiger-woods-car-crash-cheats-death-leg-injuries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIGER Woods is “lucky to be alive” after careering off the road during a horror car smash which left him with shocking leg injuries. The 45-year-old golf ace had to be cut from the wrec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's politics hurt his business. Will he sell?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-s-politics-hurt-his-business-Eyeing-2024-15975432.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's new office is the Mar-a-Lago Club's old bridal suite. There -- exiled from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley adopts sweeping police reforms including taking cops off routine traffic stops...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/02/23/berkeley-votes-to-curb-police-traffic-stops-for-small-offenses-other-police-reforms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in Berkeley have passed sweeping police reforms, from limiting traffic stops to stricter vetting to keep biased officers off the streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman receives $7,000 compensation for housework in landmark Chinese divorce ruling...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/woman-receives-7-000-compensation-housework-landmark-chinese-divorce-ruling-n1258706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case has sparked a heated public debate on social media in China on gender rights and responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/american-airlines-confirms-contact-cruise-23557662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crew of an American Airlines Airbus flying between between Cincinnati and Phoenix on Sunday were buzzed by a 'long cyclindrical' object that can't be explained by any known military operation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London overtakes New York as home to most millionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9294291/London-overtakes-New-York-home-dollar-millionaires.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Knight Frank Wealth report shows that 874,354 people in London have assets, including property, worth more than £720,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sewage Samples Reveal Americans, Australians Biggest Users Of Designer Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sewage-samples-party-pills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study on new psychoactive substances in wastewater is providing unprecedented insight into designer drug use across numerous nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this rocket going to take us to moon?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/space/article/moon-rocket-2024-space-launch-system-15963243.php?IPID=Chron-HP-CP-Spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The timely development of the Space Launch System is crucial to the Artemis program,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Deaths down 20% worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/540233-who-coronavirus-deaths-down-20-percent-last-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of deaths resulting from the coronavirus dropped 20 percent worldwide last week, compared to the previous week, according to the World Health Organization (WHO).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Going to Iraq Just as COVID and Rocket Attacks Surging...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-pope-is-going-to-iraq-just-as-covid-and-rocket-attacks-are-surging</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraq has seen a wave of violence and a surge in COVID-19 cases. So why is the pontiff engaging in superspreader spirituality?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster puts Beto back in business...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/24/beto-orourke-texas-governor-471254</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The onetime Democratic sensation has new political life — and, perhaps, hope for the governorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Probing Flying Cylindrical Object Over New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39416/american-airlines-confirms-pilot-report-of-bizarre-cylinder-shaped-object-over-new-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The radio transmission regarding a rogue cylindrical-shaped object traveling at high-speed near the Airbus A320 is authentic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin flexes muscle in 50-50 Senate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/540197-manchin-flexes-muscle-in-50-50-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centrist Sen. Joe Manchin (D-W.Va.) is the most pivotal vote in the evenly divided Senate, and his power could spark prolonged intraparty feuds among Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden leans into empathizer-in-chief role...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/540166-biden-leans-into-empathizer-in-chief-role</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has been leaning hard into his role as the nation’s empathizer-in-chief as he contends with multiple tragedies during his first month in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: LGBT Identification Rises to 5.6%...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/329708/lgbt-identification-rises-latest-estimate.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gallup finds 5.6% of U.S. adults identifying as lesbian, gay, bisexual or transgender, with the majority of them saying they are bisexual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebekah Mercer orchestrates PARLER second act...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/business/article/Major-Trump-backer-Rebekah-Mercer-orchestrates-15974906.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When social media website Parler's founding CEO John Matze was pushed out last month, it was at the direction of a quiet but powerful political megadonor backing the right-leaning site.  Rebekah Mercer, the 47-year-old daughter of major Republican donor Robert Mercer, is a founding investor of Parler. She increasingly pulls the strings at the company, according to people familiar with the company who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private business matters. She holds the majority stake in Parler and controlled two of three board seats as of early February - a board to which she recently appointed allies.  The social media company started garnering a name for itself last year as a friendly gathering spot for Republican politicians and pundits turned off by fact-checking and moderation on sites like Facebook and Twitter. But Parler, which publicly extolled itself as a free-speech-focused network with minimal rules, became a breeding ground for conspiracy theories about the 2020 presidential election. The site was knocked offline shortly after the riot at the U.S. Capitol for its alleged role in allowing the rioters to plan and egg each other on.  Now Mercer, who is credited with helping get Donald Trump elected president in 2016, is working to revive the site. It came back online last week with her new handpicked CEO, former tea party patriots leader, Mark Meckler, at the helm. It's the latest in a long line of maneuvers by the Mercer family to create an alternative media industry that pushes a version of the news that fits with their right-wing, populist political agenda - while keeping a low profile themselves.  Parler executives did not respond to multiple requests for interviews or comment. Mercer did not respond to requests for comment.  Parler surged as an alternative to Twitter and Facebook during...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Prosecutors Looking at Don Jr...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/donald-trump-jr-is-being-examined-by-new-york-prosecutors-in-trump-business-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Beast has learned that investigators have been asking questions in recent days about Trump’s eldest son as they expand their criminal probe into Trump’s business empire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest 1% in World: How Much Net Worth to Join Ranks of Wealthiest...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/heres-how-much-wealth-you-need-to-join-the-richest-1-globally-2377295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joining the ranks of the richest 1% is never easy, but it's especially hard in Monaco. You need to be worth almost $8 million to make the cut in the Mediterranean principality, where residents typically don't pay income taxes, according to research on more than two-dozen locations by Knight Frank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whispers of $100 Oil Return as Crude Shakes Off Covid Clasp...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/commodities-news/whispers-of-100-oil-return-as-crude-shakes-off-covids-clasp-2427884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whispers of $100 Oil Return as Crude Shakes Off Covid’s Clasp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old school AIRSTREAMS enjoy pandemic-era popularity...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Old-school-Airstreams-enjoy-pandemic-era-15974933.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last June, Amy Geren, bought a $42,000 Airstream trailer, sight unseen, from a dealer in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma man confesses to killing neighbor and cooking heart 'with potatoes'...</title>
      <link>https://oklahoman.com/article/5682886/oklahoma-murder-suspect-confesses-to-killing-neighbor-cooking-her-heart-investigators-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oklahoman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEB 24, 2021 - CHICKASHA — A triple murder suspect has confessed, saying he killed a neighbor first and cut her heart out to eat at home, the OSBI reported. "He took the heart back to 214 West Minnesota, Chickasha," an agent with the Oklahoma State Bureau of Investigation told a judge in a request for a search warrant. "He cooked the heart with potatoes to feed to his family to release the demons," the agent wrote. Lawrence Paul Anderson is accused of killing the neighbor at her home and then going to his home and killing his uncle and a 4-year-old girl on Feb. 9. He also is accused of stabbing his aunt. She survived. The case already has sparked outrage because the repeat felon had been released early from prison in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Matter designers make history in Milan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/black-lives-matter-designers-history-112003178.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last minute touches on a frilly white dress, a final coat of powder and it's showtime for the Black Lives Matter-inspired collective making history at Milan Fashion Week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen to Appear in Court on Drunken-Driving Charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-bruce-springsteen/rock-star-bruce-springsteen-set-for-court-date-on-drunk-driving-charge-idUSKBN2AO18R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Springsteen is set to have his day in court on Wednesday to answer alcohol and driving-related charges three months after an officer said he spotted the rock star doing a shot of tequila and mounting his motorcycle at a New Jersey beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient stabs doctor repeatedly in hospital...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/02/23/pennsylvania-hospital-doctor-stabbed-multiple-times-in-face-head-by-patient-philadelphia-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The doctor says swift action by staff ensured she received immediate care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantines crushing air travel getting longer and lonelier...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/quarantines-crushing-air-travel-are-getting-longer-and-lonelier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns of new wave...</title>
      <link>https://bmglobalnews.com/2021/02/23/coronavirus-merkel-warns-of-third-virus-wave-as-germany-weighs-ending-lockdown-al-arabiya-english/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bmglobalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Angela Merkel warned that Germany is in the midst of a third wave of coronavirus infections and that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawrence Ferlinghetti, bedrock of Beat Generation, dead at 101...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lawrence-ferlinghetti-jack-kerouac-san-francisco-allen-ginsberg-abf9cd1a91ac39a3b4282608ffac1998</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moves to reengage with Palestinians after Israel focus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-politics-israel-400a8181a178c66583bf96cab78be421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger 'nearly smashed into TV director's car' as he left resort moments before horror rollover...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2395280/tiger-woods-nearly-smashed-tv-directors-car-before-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIGER Woods almost hit the director for the television show ‘Grown-ish’ mere minutes before he ended up in a horrific rollover crash while speeding down a Los Angeles street Tuesday mor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rips Proud Boy's Trump-made-me-do-it defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/23/capitol-rioters-judge-proud-boys-trump-471199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief U.S. District Court Judge Beryl Howell was unpersuaded by a Proud Boys member’s claim he was heeding the then-president’s direction by storming Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient stabs doctor repeatedly in hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/patient-stabs-doctor-multiple-times-at-philadelphia-hospital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A female doctor was stabbed multiple times in the face and head as she treated a patient at a Philadelphia hospital on Tuesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPEEDING, SWERVING, FLIPPED</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/23/tiger-woods-injured-in-serious-california-car-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods was lucky to be alive Tuesday following a high-speed, single-car crash near Los Angeles that caused multiple fractures in the golf great’s legs — requiring immediate surgery. Woods, 45,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA strain looks increasingly dangerous: 'Devil already here'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-coronavirus-strain-looks-increasingly-130055544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's homegrown coronavirus strain is more transmissible than its predecessors, is more resistant to vaccines, and may cause more severe cases of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREER OVER?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/2394186/tiger-woods-crash-golf-car-masters-title/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE golfing world will be praying the injuries Tiger Woods suffered in a car wreck are not life-threatening – but it is hard to believe they will not spell the end of his glittering career. With Wo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired NYPD Cop Accused of Pipe Attack on Capitol Police...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/investigations/retired-nypd-cop-once-assigned-to-secure-city-hall-charged-in-pipe-attack-on-capitol-police-officials/2904889/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A retired NYPD officer who had been assigned for a time to work perimeter security at City Hall and at Gracie Mansion, the mayor’s official residence, has been accused of using a pipe to attack a U.S. Capitol officer during the Jan. 6 siege, law enforcement officials with knowledge of the case told News 4 Tuesday. Thomas Webster surrendered to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SERIOUSLY INJURED</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/tiger-woods-injured-in-rollover-crash-in-rancho-palos-verdes-area-jaws-of-life-used-to-extricate-golfer-from-wreck/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods is undergoing surgery for multiple leg injuries after a solo-vehicle rollover crash in the Palos Verdes area on Tuesday morning. Woods, 45, was the lone occupant in the vehicle when it …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
