<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump hits back...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/509096-trump-lashes-out-at-reagan-foundation-fox-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump lashed out at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Foundation and Institute on Sunday following a report that it had requested the Trump campaign stop using President Reagan's name and image in fundra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backs out of throwing first pitch at YANKEES game...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/509100-trump-backs-out-of-throwing-first-pitch-at-yankees-game</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump announced Sunday he wouldn't be throwing out the opening pitch for the New York Yankees next month as he had planned, citing meetings and other work related to the U.S.'s COVID-19 outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America leads world in cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200726144449-nvcsf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/LATIN AMERICA:Latin America leads world in coronavirus cases, Reuters count shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida records 9,300 new infected, blows past New York...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200726135648-ec1xb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (URGENT):Florida records 9,300 new coronavirus cases, blows past New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luck? Genetics? Italian island spared from outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e91b19c2d31d5021a7e8dcd55b50e08b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GIGLIO ISLAND, Italy (AP) — Stranded on a tiny Italian island, a cancer researcher grew increasingly alarmed to hear that one, and then three more visitors had fallen ill with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everywhere and nowhere: The many layers of 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9090804abf933c422207660509aeef22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — So you've probably read a lot about “cancel culture.” Or know about a new poll that shows a plurality of Americans disapproving of it. Or you may have heard about a letter in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ROYALS:  Rift between  brothers laid bare in new book extract...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/637b02aa9253e61d97de32a84a223e0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Prince William infuriated Prince Harry when he told his younger brother he should move slowly in his relationship with the former Meghan Markle, fearing that he was being “blindsided...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GONE WITH THE WIND:  Olivia de Havilland dead at 104...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4bc944efb37dbc7385b05e1c802d4c0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Olivia de Havilland, the doe-eyed actress beloved to millions as the sainted Melanie Wilkes of “Gone With the Wind,” but also a two-time Oscar winner and an off-screen fighter who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body of civil rights icon John Lewis crosses Selma bridge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/03f249c36a8a1d0470145e84fc93f331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SELMA, Ala. (AP) — The late U.S. Rep. John Lewis crossed the Edmund Pettus Bridge in Selma, Alabama, for the final time Sunday as remembrances continue for the civil rights icon. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUROPE BACK ON ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1202119/europe-coronavirus-cases-surge-france-spain/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safari park baboons seen armed with knives, screwdrivers and CHAINSAW...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1201172/safari-park-baboons-armed-knives-screwdrivers-chainsaw/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE RIOTING AND LAWLESSNESS IN CITIES</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/american-mayhem-more-rioting-and-lawlessness-in-cities-across-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another night of rioting and lawlessness exploded in more than half a dozen U.S. cities Saturday night -- with the mayhem including damage to federal buildings, local police precincts, and a fatal shooting in Austin, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman maces couple for not wearings masks in park...</title>
      <link>https://disrn.com/news/woman-maces-couple-having-picnic-in-san-diego-park-for-not-wearings-masks </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020's first hurricane roars ashore in virus-hit Texas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a5c642c37e9f9970c3f2184858f5a5a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORPUS CHRISTI, Texas (AP) — A day after roaring ashore as a hurricane, Hanna lashed the Texas Gulf Coast on Sunday with high winds and drenching rains that destroyed boats, flooded streets and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 DAYS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/43a096bc2bcf376de04b696c5143ee99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With the November election 100 days away, more Americans say the country is heading in the wrong direction than at any previous point in Donald Trump’s presidency, putting the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN: Experts urge country shut down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/26/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus deaths in the US topped 1,000 four days in a row last week amid ongoing debates on the return of school and mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea scrambles to contain 'first' case...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/26/north-korea-scrambles-contain-first-coronavirus-ca/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un placed the city of Kaesong near the border with South Korea under total lockdown after a person was found there with suspected COVID-19 symptoms, saying “the vicious virus” may have entered the country, state media reported Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12% STILL Don't Wash Hands After Using Public Bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/living-dangerously-adults-still-dont-wash-hands-after-using-public-bathroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey reveals that 12% of British adults still regularly use the bathroom, both public and private, without washing their hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN +5 IN AZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/poll-biden-leads-trump-battleground-arizona-n1234888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presumptive nominee is up five points in a new NBC News/Marist poll while Democrats also enjoy double-digit lead in state's Senate contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>+12 MI...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/26/politics/cnn-poll-biden-trump-florida-arizona-michigan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 100 days remaining until Election Day, voters in three critical battleground states swing in former Vice President Joe Biden's way, according to new Arizona, Florida and Michigan CNN polls conducted by SSRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Arab country acquires new Chinese missile system...</title>
      <link>https://www.almasdarnews.com/article/first-arab-country-acquires-new-chinese-missile-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.almasdarnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT, LEBANON (9:30 A.M.) - China has started exporting the third generation of their Red Arrow-12 anti-tank systems, also known as the HJ-12. According</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sledding Athletes Taking Their Lives. Did Crashes Damage Their Brains?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/26/sledding-athletes-are-taking-their-lives-did-high-speed-crashes-damage-their-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Matthew Futterman On May 3, Pavle Jovanovic, a former bobsledder, rigged a chain to a crane he and his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Really Is Spying On You -- For China...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2020/07/25/beware-tiktok-really-is-spying-on-you-new-security-report-update-trump-pompeo-china-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new security report has just been published, adding substance to the U.S. threats being made against China's social media sensation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Trump Supporter Gunned Down In Drive-By Shooting In Milwaukee...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2020/07/25/black-trump-supporter-killed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating whether there was a political motive in the crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wages of Woke: How to get rich peddling 'white fragility'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/culture/the-wages-of-woke-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Robin DiAngelo, the bestselling author of White Fragility, claims to believe in accountability. DiAngelo used to list the “racial justice” organizations she donates to as part of her extensive “accountability statement,” including a monthly “land rent” paid to the Native American tribe which used to occupy Seattle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAVENS Player Alleged Victim Of Repeated Domestic Abuse By Girlfriend...</title>
      <link>https://247sports.com/Article/Baltimore-Ravens-Alabama-football-DJ-Fluker-domestic-violence-victim-149516199/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;247sports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courthouse set ablaze as 'Wall of Moms' protest intensifies in Oakland...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/26/courthouse-set-ablaze-wall-moms-protest-intensifie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters in California set fire to a courthouse, damaged a police station and assaulted officers after a peaceful demonstration intensified late Saturday, Oakland police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin says Russian Navy to get hypersonic nuke strike weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-navy-day-parade-putin-idUSKCN24R0CJ?taid=5f1d5fdd31fdfb000144d967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Sunday the Russian Navy would be armed with hypersonic nuclear strike weapons and underwater nuclear drones, which the defence ministry said were in their final phase of testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One shot dead during march in Austin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8560753/Cops-declare-Seattle-protest-riot-youth-detention-center-goes-flames.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A protester was shot and killed in a shooting at a protest in Texas Saturday night as tensions flared across America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosives, rocks thrown at police in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/25/us/seattle-protest-riot/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle protesters threw large rocks, bottles, fireworks and other explosives at officers Saturday, police said. Others set fire to a portable trailer and a construction site, police said in a series of tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 days until Election Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/07/26/100-days-out-heres-what-defined-2020-election-and-what-expect/5467900002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 100 days out from the general election, impeachment, coronavirus and systemic racism have dominated voters' minds. Here's what to expect next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain outbreak drives European fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53539015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its Catalonia region closes its nightlife as other nations eye increases in new infections warily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasa Mars rover: Meteorite to head home to Red Planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-53491555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Perseverance robot will take Martian rock with it when it launches from Earth on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richmond dump truck set on fire outside police HQ...</title>
      <link>https://richmond.com/news/local/police-use-chemical-agents-flash-bangs-to-disperse-crowd-outside-rpd-headquarters-after-city-dump/article_11b30f19-e70a-51f9-8e1d-ef53a1a4ba3e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 1:20 a.m.: The Richmond Fire Department responded to the Chipotle Mexican Grill on the 800 block of W. Grace St. early Sunday morning where flames could be seen coming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEEP DRIVES THROUGH CO PROTESTERS</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/07/25/protesters-block-interstate-225-injured-car-drives-through-crowd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aurora police are investigating a shooting on Interstate 225 after a vehicle drove through protesters marching on the highway Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to unveil obesity plan after Boris Johnson's near-death...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/uk-unveil-obesity-plan-pms-near-death-experience-090319401.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson is set to roll out a £10 million anti-obesity campaign, including junk food advert bans, following his own brush with death that he partly blamed on his weight. Johnson will announce his "Better Health" campaign on Monday, which is expected to include encouraging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah Shutting Down O MAGAZINE After 20 Years with Embattled HEARST...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/26/oprah-shutting-down-o-magazine-print-edition-after-20-years-with-embattled-hearst-publications</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O stands for Oprah and for over. The Oprah magazine, called O, is apparently over. Begun twenty years ago in print, and 10 years ago digitally, there are reports that O will cease print operations …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA:  More than 1,000 deaths for 5th day in row...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/coronavirus-updates-hundreds-texas-bar-owners-pledge-defiance/story?id=71982262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The novel coronavirus pandemic has now killed more than 643,000 people worldwide and over 15.9 million people across the globe have been diagnosed with COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPPOSING ARMED MILITIAS CONVERGE IN LOUISVILLE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8559841/Black-militia-members-brandish-guns-demanding-charges-against-cops-linked-Breonna-Taylors-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The simultaneous demonstrations in Louisville by 'Not F*****g Around Coaltion' and the right-wing 'Three Percenters' are taking place a day after scores were arrested on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public losing faith in govts, says survey...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/virus-surges-worldwide-public-loses-faith-authorities-092641725.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey released Saturday showed governments are fast losing support for their handling of the coronavirus pandemic, as health officials recorded a surge of more than 280,000 new cases globally two days in a row. Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro, widely criticised for his handling of the crisis there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mysterious seeds from China sent to dozens of people in multiple states...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/nation-world/national/article244479272.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. sidelined scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Coronavirus-ravaged-Florida-as-Ron-DeSantis-15434450.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. - As Florida became a global epicenter of the coronavirus, Gov. Ron DeSantis held one meeting this month with his top public health official, Scott Rivkees, according to the governor's schedule. His health department has sidelined scientists, halting briefings last month with disease specialists and telling the experts there was not sufficient personnel from the state to continue participating.  "I never received information about what happened with my ideas or results," said Thomas Hladish, a University of Florida research scientist whose regular calls with the health department ended June 29. "But I did hear the governor say the models were wrong about everything."  DeSantis, a Republican, this month traveled to Miami to hold a roundtable with South Florida mayors, whose region had emerged as a novel coronavirus hot spot. But the Republican mayor of Hialeah was shut out, weeks after saying the governor "hasn't done much" for a city disproportionately affected by the virus.  As the virus spread out of control in Florida, decision-making became increasingly shaped by politics and divorced from scientific evidence according to interviews with 64 current and former state and administration officials, health administrators, epidemiologists, political operatives and hospital executives. The crisis in Florida, these observers say, has revealed the shortcomings of a response built on shifting metrics, influenced by a small group of advisers and tethered at every stage to the Trump administration, which has no unified plan for addressing the national health emergency but has pushed for states to reopen.  DeSantis relies primarily on the advice of his wife, Casey, a former television reporter and host, and his chief of staff, Shane Strum, a former hospital executive, according to multiple Republican...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Church Defies State Lockdown To Resume In-Person Assembly...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/compliance-would-be-disobedience-prominent-california-church-defies-state-lockdown-to-resume-in-person-assembly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pastor and elders of a prominent evangelical church in California issued a statement on Friday explaining why they will no longer comply with the state&amp;#8217;s mandate ordering them to refrain from in-person gatherings. John F. MacArthur, the 81-year-old senior pastor of Grace Community Church in Sun Valley, California, also claimed that the state had [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gig Economy Compromised Our Immune System...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gig-economy-compromised-immune-system-000048670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- There’s nothing arbitrary about an epidemic.While each disease is the product of a chain of accidental genetic shifts, the process that turns a novel infection into a devastating outbreak is as much social as biological. The vast majority of new conditions will die out before they</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
