<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Stand-up comics still dare to joke about Maduro -- but for how much longer?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article223614560.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan stand-up comedians still dare to joke about Maduro but worry about arrest by the repressive government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest veteran dead at 112; Credited longetivity to God, cigars, whiskey...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox7austin.com/news/local-news/nations-oldest-living-veteran-richard-overton-dies-in-austin-at-age-112</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox7austin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s oldest living veteran, Richard Overton, has died in a rehab facility&amp;nbsp;in Austin, Texas.&amp;nbsp;He was 112 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rough year for 'universal basic income' experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612640/universal-basic-income-had-a-rough-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the biggest and most promising experiments were plagued by delays and shutdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants fed ad dollars to child porn discovery apps...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/27/funding-filth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google has scrambled to remove third-party apps that led users to child porn sharing groups on WhatsApp in the wake of TechCrunch’s report about the problem last week. We contacted Google with the name of one of these apps and evidence that it and others offered links to WhatsApp groups for sharing…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depression, anxiety, withdrawal: The Hell of trying to quit vaping...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/12/27/quitting-vaping-e-cigarette-addiction-nicotine-withdrawal-depression-anxiety-headaches/2388272002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;E-cigarettes were introduced to help smokers quit. But for those trying to quit vaping, nicotine withdrawal can be 'hell'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside FACEBOOK Secret Rulebook for Global Political Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/27/world/facebook-moderators.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under fire for stirring up distrust and violence, the social network has vowed to police its users. But leaked documents raise serious questions about its approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESURRECTED CONTROVERSY MET WITH SKEPTICISM...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/27/michael-cohen-prague-mueller-mcclatchy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But McClatchy story is being met with skepticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Winter Be Cold? Depends Which FARMERS' ALAMANAC You Read...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/will-winter-be-nasty-or-nice-depends-which-farmers-almanac-you-read-11545929300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dueling weather forecasts confound fans of longtime rivals the Old Farmer’s Almanac and the Farmers’ Almanac; ‘I don’t know what to believe’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk argues pedophile accusation made on 'rough and tumble' TWITTER is protected speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musk-says-pedophile-accusation-against-british-man-was-protected-speech-11545938184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk sought to dismiss a defamation lawsuit, with his lawyers arguing that no one could have taken seriously his claim that a British cave diver is a pedophile, especially because the statement was made in the “rough and tumble” forum of Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS standing by misleading story...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2018/12/27/nbc-news-is-standing-by-misleading-story-trumps-visit-troops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the darkness of Christmas night, the president sneaked out of the White House en route to Iraq, undermining the premise of an NBC News story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University official: Asking smaller woman on date violates Title IX...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/mizzou-official-asking-a-smaller-woman-on-a-date-violates-title-ix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Power or authority' provision 'could apply to any situation with any man and any woman,' another says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela murder rate dips -- as violent criminals flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-crime/venezuela-murder-rate-dips-partly-due-to-migration-monitoring-group-idUSKCN1OQ1GJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The murder rate in Venezuela, one of the world's highest-crime countries, d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump's covert Iraq trip was exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/27/politics/donald-trump-secret-trip-iraq/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a crisp winter morning in Sheffield, England, when amateur photographer and plane enthusiast Alan Meloy looked out his kitchen window and noticed a large trail in the sky. He didn't know he was about to accidentally help uncover a highly sensitive, secret presidential trip to a conflict zone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab Spring 2.0? Tunisian journalist calls for revolt, sets self on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/447500-tunisia-journalist-suicide-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A journalist in Tunisia – the first country to face the Arab Spring – has set himself on fire, triggering a protest against unemployment and poverty. The case resembles the start of the 2011 Western-hailed revolt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's College to Admit Some Trans Students...</title>
      <link>https://www.insidehighered.com/quicktakes/2018/12/27/stephens-college-will-admit-some-trans-students</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insidehighered.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many women's colleges, including some of the most prominent ones, started admitting transgender students several years ago. But others have held off. One in the latter group, Stephens College, in Missouri, has now announced that it will admit some transgender women, but will exclude trans men. The college's new policy says, "The college’s undergraduate residential women’s program will continue to admit and enroll students who are women and who live as women, just as it always has. It will also admit and enroll students who were not born female, but who identify and live as women; those students will need to provide legal documentation that they are legally women or that they are transitioning to female. Because the college has expanded its definition of womanhood to include both sex and gender, it is logically consistent that it also acknowledges both sex and gender in its definition of manhood. As a result, the college will stop admitting and enrolling students who were born female but who now identify as men or who are transitioning from female to male." A timeline from the college shows that the policy has been under consideration since 2014.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIDWEST: Blizzard to blast post-Christmas travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/major-snowstorm-to-threaten-travelers-with-whiteout-conditions-from-colorado-to-minnesota-michigan/70006986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone CLONED?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6533445/New-claim-Michael-Cohens-phone-Prague-time-meeting-described-Trump-dossier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unclear whether the murky intelligence sources behind the new revelation are trustworthy, and it's unknown whether someone may have cloned the former Trump lawyer's phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disinformation campaign against Roy Moore may have violated law, Alabama AG says...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/alabama/2018/12/disinformation-campaign-targeting-roy-moores-senate-bid-may-have-violated-law-alabama-ag-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama Attorney General Steve Marshall said Thursday that his office is exploring whether disinformation tactics deployed against Republican Roy Moore during last year's special election violated state campaign laws and said he was worried that the operation could have affected the closely fought Senate race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Husband tosses wife's pets off balcony...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/27/man-charged-with-tossing-wifes-pets-off-balcony-you-love-those-dogs-more-than-you-love-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago-area attorney fed up with his wife’s love for her two Chihuahuas tossed the animals off her second-floor balcony, killing one, during an argument, Chicago police said. Jerald Jeske, 51, f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Chinese officials forced to carry out self-criticisms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/top-chinese-officials-forced-carry-self-criticisms-113232750.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Chinese leaders have been forced to undergo a self-criticism session, state media said Thursday, in a further sign of President Xi Jinping's efforts to enforce party loyalty amid signs of internal dissent over his handling of a trade war with the United States. A tool highly favoured by Mao</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Surgeons Make Significantly More Mistakes When Under Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-surgeons-make-significantly-more-mistakes-when-under-stress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surgeons under stress are far more likely to make mistakes on patients in the operating room, even if the stress is caused by a trivial source and lasts briefly, a Columbia University study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli general, polling closest to Netanyahu, joins election race...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election-gantz/israeli-ex-general-polling-closest-to-netanyahu-joins-2019-election-race-idUSKCN1OQ14E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Israeli armed forces chief who opinion polls show poses the toughest ch...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Bernie supporters won't commit to supporting him...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/27/us/politics/bernie-sanders-president-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Sanders has not yet told advisers he intends to pursue another White House bid. But if he does, he will encounter a vastly different landscape than that of 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6533447/Kevin-Spacey-court-docs-sexual-assault-teen-Nantucket-bar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spacey will appear in court next month to be arraigned on a charge of Indecent Assault &amp; Battery that stems from an incident that allegedly occurred in the early morning hours of July 8 in Nantucket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercer Cuts Political Spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-27/mercer-cuts-political-spending-after-unwelcome-turn-in-spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths of Police Officers on Duty on Rise...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5489190/police-officer-deaths-rise-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The majority of the officers who died were shot or in car crashes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluto explorer ushering in new year at more distant world...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a04d42ffb8724be388759bd8516a1f48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The spacecraft team that brought us close-ups of Pluto will ring in the new year by exploring an even more distant and mysterious world. NASA's New Horizons spacecraft will zip past the scrawny, icy object nicknamed Ultima Thule (TOO-lee) soon after the stroke of midnight. One billion miles beyond Pluto and an astounding 4 billion miles from Earth (1.6 billion kilometers and 6.4 billion kilometers), Ultima Thule will be the farthest world ever explored by humankind. That's what makes this deep-freeze target so enticing; it's a preserved relic dating all the way back to our solar system's origin 4.5 billion years ago. No spacecraft has visited anything so primitive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal marijuana industry had banner year in 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/legal-marijuana-industry-had-banner-2018-060708442--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — The last year was a 12-month champagne toast for the legal marijuana industry as the global market exploded and cannabis pushed its way further into the financial and cultural mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Boxoffice Hits Record $41 Billion as Movie Theaters Bounce Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/2018-global-box-office-projected-to-pass-41-billion-thanks-to-us-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;comScore is projecting that the annual global box office will reach a new milestone next week, passing $41 billion for the first time in industry history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Taliban Video: Intense training for cheer squad competition...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2018/12/26/bring-it-on-new-taliban-video-shows-them-training-for-cheer-squad-competition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban training video documentation is the gift that keeps on giving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq demands U.S. troop withdrawal!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/iraq-legislators-say-surprise-trump-visit-violated-sovereignty-demand-us-troop-withdrawal-2018-12-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both blocs in Iraq’s divided parliament call for a vote on the expulsion of U.S. forces in wake of Trump’s brief, ‘arrogant’ trip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX's 25 seasons of doing NFL has changed the game...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/nfl/story/how-fox-s-25-seasons-of-covering-the-nfl-changed-the-game-122718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox gave football on television a 'new attitude' 25 years ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opens fire on sixth day of govt shutdown... </title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/trump-opens-fire-sixth-day-government-shutdown-doc-1bu7ck1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAT Officer Ends Hours-Long Standoff By Singing 'White Christmas' To Suspect...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/27/swat-officer-ends-hours-long-standoff-by-singing-white-christmas-to-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An hours-long standoff ensued with Lewis firing at police officers from inside the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tweet reveals secretive SEAL team?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/27/trump-accidentally-identifies-secret-navy-seal-team-in-video-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortly after his first visit to US troops stationed in a war zone, President Trump posted a video on Twitter that showed him posing for pictures with service members who appear to be from SEAL Tea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California moves up primary, wants bigger impact...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b58e7841a89b4535bccb122e8c1bcf5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go west, 2020 presidential candidates? Early voting in California's primary will overlap with the traditional early nominating contests in Iowa, New Hampshire, Nevada and South Carolina. That could force the sprawling field of Democrats to navigate those states as well as California's notoriously complex landscape, where campaigning is done through paid political ads. Strategists estimate it could cost at least $5 million for a candidate to compete in California, an amount that could be prohibitive for all but the best-funded contenders. Nascent campaigns are asking themselves if they should gamble on California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS PLANS NEW YEAR'S EVE BLOWOUT TO RIVAL NYC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/74192134bd7549c38ad78d8f201544bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — No other city does New Year's Eve like Las Vegas. Lady Gaga, Bruno Mars and Gwen Stefani are among the superstars who will be ushering in the new year with performances at venues on the Las Vegas Strip, while more than 300,000 people are expected to gather on the world-famous corridor Monday to watch eight minutes of fireworks. At another celebration in the downtown Fremont Street entertainment district, 12 bands will play under a massive video canopy that will show the ball drop in New York's Time Square.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey claims 'sex attack' was consensual...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8066178/kevin-spacey-lawyer-claims-sex-attacker-accuser-allowed-grope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TEENAGE boy who accused Kevin Spacey of sexually assaulting him allowed the actor to grope him during a boozy lunch, the star’s lawyers claim. Spacey’s legal team went to court last w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFIDENCE FALLS</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/americans-confidence-in-the-economy-falls-again-and-is-at-lowest-level-since-summer-2018-12-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The confidence Americans feel in the economy fell for the second month in a row and touched the lowest level since last summer, perhaps a sign that worries about the nine-and-a-half year-old U.S. expansion have spread from Wall Street to main street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Media Stocks Suffer Steep Declines In 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/media-stocks-suffer-declines-2018-1171021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With only a few trading days left this year, 31 of the 50 stocks tracked by THR are down for the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Parliament urges end to words like 'man-made', 'mankind', 'layman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6345409/EU-moves-outlaw-gender-biased-phrases-man-manpower.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new guidelines are aimed at EU translators tasked with converting documents between the different languages spoken and written by the 28 member states in parliament (shown).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg prepared to spend at least $100 million on '20 campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/26/mike-bloomberg-likely-to-spend-over-100-million-on-a-2020-campaign-for-president-if-he-chooses-to-run.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the former New York City Mayor contributes that much to his own campaign, he will have one of the largest 2020 war chests and a stark advantage over the other Democratic presidential nominee hopefuls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American First to Solo Across Antarctica Unaided...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a44f393f98a4b43bacf5034e398d796</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oregon man became the first person to traverse Antarctica alone without any assistance on Wednesday, trekking across the polar continent in an epic 54-day journey that was previously deemed impossible. Colin O'Brady, of Portland, finished the bone-chilling, 930-mile (1,500-kilometer) journey as friends, family and fans tracked the endurance athlete's progress in real time online. "I did it!" a tearful O'Brady said on a call to his family gathered in Portland for the holidays, according to his wife, Jenna Besaw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 10 States Don't Go on Vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/articles/2018-12-27/people-in-these-10-us-states-dont-go-on-vacation </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake moon landings, flat Earth: Why do athletes love conspiracy theories?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/dec/27/stephen-curry-kyrie-irving-conspiracy-theories-nba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sports stars as varied as Stephen Curry and Andrew Flintoff have flirted with conspiracy theories. But they are guided by very human emotions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Parliament urges end to words like 'man-made', 'mankind', 'layman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2018/12/27/politically-correct-european-parliament-urges-end-words-like/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Parliament is attempting to stamp out the use of words such as &amp;ldquo;mankind&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;manpower&amp;rdquo; and have them replaced with more gender neutral terms such as &amp;ldquo;humanity&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;staff&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 60 years of revolution in Cuba, cracks in leadership emerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article223562470.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With minimal economic growth in 2018 and continuing shortages of basic staples like flour at year’s end, experts say the Cuban government is failing under the leadership of Miguel Díaz-Canel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When cops become addicts: Police falling prey to pills and heroin...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/when-cops-become-addicts-police-are-falling-prey-to-pills/article_9e66adf0-8967-5a19-ab6d-e13431e149e6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE — Every mile brought Lt. Dan Gosnell closer to relief. His body ached for the little white pills, though his mind shouted to turn back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi king orders major govt reshuffle...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181227-saudi-king-orders-major-government-reshuffle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi king orders major government reshuffle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled Fed chairman says he'll meet face-to-face with Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6532761/Embattled-Federal-Reserve-chairman-tells-White-House-officials-hell-meet-face-face-Trump.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerome Powell is now telling the White House that he'd be willing to meet with President Trump to discuss his concerns about the independent agency's rate hikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS MORE TODAY?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/el-paso-texas-las-cruces-new-mexico-ice-drops-off-hundres-more-migrants-today-2018-12-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That raises the total number of people released this week to more than 1,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus sending infants to intensive care...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/27/health-officials-warn-of-virus-that-sends-infants-to-intensive-care/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal health officials warned this week of a highly contagious cold-like virus that affects everyone, and leaves the elderly and young kids especially vulnerable — including a 14-month-old …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 Ebola patients break out of treatment center sparking emergency search...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/750139/breaking-ebola-breakout-patients-flee-congo-beni-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN SHAME: Public drug usage, homelessness, disease plague city...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/27/health/drug-use-san-francisco-streets/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public drug usage and homelessness are not new problems for the city of San Francisco, home to Uber, Twitter and Salesforce. But residents say the situation has gotten worse in recent years with 7,500 complaints about discarded needles made in the first 10 months of this year. That's up from 6,363 last year. In 2015, the number was less than 3,000. It's moved some locals -- so-called "video vigilantes" -- to document the mess they see, in an attempt to get the city's attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE WORLD OF 2018: Photographers capture awe and beauty...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e123ebe311c9402593ff14716cb24b33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through the eyes of Associated Press photographers, the world of 2018 was always captivating, sometimes comical, often awe-inspiring — and above all, beautiful. They saw beauty in the disarray of clothing left behind by 450 refugees and migrants, rescued from a boat off the Libyan coast; in the clouds of smoke from a California wildfire, captured from aloft; in the toil of a Mexican farmworker, surrounded by a carpet of cabbage. They found splendor in some of the most unexpected places. At an Israeli bodybuilding exhibition, competitors flex and glisten; at a Brazilian fashion show, sex workers shimmy and strut.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope blind spot on sex abuse threatens legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1d175bccdb364e5387956fc0e0672bf2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — It has been a wretched year for Pope Francis, whose blind spot on clergy sex abuse conspired with events beyond his control to threaten his legacy and throw the Catholic hierarchy into a credibility crisis not seen in modern times. The latest development — a high-profile verdict in a far-away country — cements the impression that Francis simply didn't "get it" when he first became pope in 2013 and began leading the church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  STOCKS HEADED FOR WORST DECEMBER EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.fin24.com/Markets/analysis-whiff-of-extinction-blows-in-bull-market-that-outlived-them-all-20181226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fin24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Itâ€™s been derided as a house of cards, a gift to the one-percent, an experiment in monetary policy taken way too far. Now a bull market that for 10 years has confounded and chastened its detractors - by outlasting all its predecessors - is staggering up to deathâ€™s door. And haters and admirers alike are turning out to pronounce last rites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela rocked by 5.6 mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1063979/Venezuela-earthquake-carabobo-caracas-pacific-ring-of-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA has been rocked by a 5.6 magnitude earthquake, with residents in the region of Carabobo reporting strong shaking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb shark hunter under police investigation after cruelly attacking seabird...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6531499/Celebrity-shark-hunter-investigation-cruel-bird-attack-video-posted-Xmas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Posted on Mark the Shark's Monster Fishing Charter page on Monday, the video shows someone grabbing the seabird by its neck and violently shaking it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman 'aged 65 gives birth to second child'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6530449/Woman-aged-65-gives-birth-second-child-India.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mother, who has not been named, was taken to hospital with labour pains on Boxing Day before giving birth to a baby girl in a remote part of the Indian state of Jammu and Kashmir hours later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK RALLY FIZZLES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/27/futures-on-the-back-of-wednesdays-wall-street-surge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks on Wall Street surged on Wednesday as the three major indexes posted gains of at least 4.9 percent and the Dow Jones Industrial Average saw its largest single-day point gain in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump presidency has changed Washington, defied convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d7239932bb0a42ee91c71bead38c6baa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Mr. Trump went to Washington. And he changed it. In his first two years in office, President Donald Trump has rewritten the rules of the presidency and the norms of the nation's capital, casting aside codes of conduct and traditions that have held for generations. In Trump's Washington, facts are less relevant. Insults and highly personal attacks are increasingly employed by members of both parties. The White House press briefing is all but gone, international summits are optional, the arts are an afterthought and everything — including inherently nonpartisan institutions and investigations — is suddenly political.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O Ends Hillary Run as Most Admired...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/245669/michelle-obama-ends-hillary-clinton-run-admired.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michelle Obama has ended Hillary Clinton's 16-year run as Most Admired Woman. Barack Obama is the Most Admired Man for the 11th straight year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Rourke and Castro on collision course in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/27/orourke-julian-castro-collision-texas-election-1073720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juli&amp;aacute;n Castro was the Democratic up-and-comer from Texas to watch — until Beto came along.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTH ALIVE!  Indonesia hikes danger level for deadly tsunami volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181227-indonesia-hikes-danger-level-deadly-tsunami-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesia hikes danger level for deadly tsunami volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German army 'could recruit EU citizens'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46692176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief of defence says employing EU citizens is an option to fill shortages in expert posts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 ILLEGALS RELEASED IN EL PASO...</title>
      <link>https://kfoxtv.com/news/local/about-500-migrants-released-by-ice-wednesday-over-1000-released-past-few-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kfoxtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 518 migrants are expected to be released by U. S Immigration and Customs Enforcement on Wednesday, according to the Annunciation House. That makes more than 1,000 migrants released in the past three days. The migrants will be dropped off at undisclosed shelters across El Paso. The Annunciation House says they need relatives or sponsor families to buy bus or plane tickets for their migrant relatives as soon as possible to free up space at the shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House considering executive order to bar HUAWEI, ZTE purchases...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181227081104-uicvv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CHINA/HUAWEI TECH (UPDATE 1, EXCLUSIVE):EXCLUSIVE-White House considers new year executive order to bar Huawei, ZTE purchases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb Explosion in Athens Fuels Fear of New Generation of Terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/bomb-explosion-in-athens-fuels-fear-of-new-generation-of-terror-11545907002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were injured after a bomb exploded outside a church in central Athens on Thursday, fueling concerns of a resurgence of urban-guerrilla violence in Greece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Putin setting up nuke bomber base on Caribbean island...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8064941/russia-military-base-caribbean-island-nuclear-bombers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has sent supersonic bombers capable of carrying nuclear missiles to one of Venezuela’s islands in the Caribbean Sea, according to reports. This follows news earlier in the month that the for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLDIER:  'I Came Back into the Military Because of You'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/12/amazing-moment-us-soldier-in-iraq-tells-president-trump-i-came-back-into-the-military-because-of-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer breakthrough means disease may not be threat to future generations..</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/12/26/immune-system-transplants-strangers-horizon-fight-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have discovered a breakthrough treatment to fight cancer, as they claim the disease will no longer be deadly for future generations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego sees surge in salmonella cases..</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/health/sd-no-salmonella-cluster-cheese-20181221-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through mid-December, San Diego County recorded 730 salmonella cases, the highest total observed in at least 25 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy survives 40-minute burial after avalanche in Alps...</title>
      <link>https://www.rte.ie/news/europe/2018/1226/1019154-avalanche-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rte.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 12-year-old boy was found alive today 40 minutes after being swept away and buried by an avalanche while skiing with his parents in the French Alps, rescuers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First year with no violent tornadoes in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/2018-will-be-the-first-year-with-no-violent-13491861.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the whirlwind that is 2018, there has been a notable lack of high-end twisters. We're now days away from this becoming the first year in the modern record with no violent tornadoes touching down in the United States. Violent tornadoes are the strongest on a 0 to 5 scale, or those ranked EF4 or EF5. It was a quiet year for tornadoes overall, with below normal numbers most months. Unless you're a storm chaser, this is not bad news. The low tornado count is undoubtedly a big part of the reason the 10 tornado deaths in 2018 is also vying to be a record low.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOYOTA Wants to Put Robot Friend in Every Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.industryweek.com/technology-and-iiot/toyota-wants-put-robot-every-home-and-make-it-your-pal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.industryweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toyota's Human Support Robot is the machine the automaker sees as closest to making the leap from the lab to the living room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologist haunted by 'cursed dreams' after opening sarcophagus...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1063812/egyptian-curse-archaologiist-haunted-nightmare-opening-sarcophagus-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ARCHAEOLOGIST was left terrified after the mummy he apparently “disturbed” came back to haunt him in his dreams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How dead pig brain was kept alive for 36 hours in shock experiment...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1063896/Life-After-Death-science-news-pig-brain-yale-university</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have found a way extend life after death in a gruesome experiment which saw pig brains brought back for 35 HOURS after death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's interest payments about to skyrocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/u-s-national-debt-interest-costs-are-about-to-skyrocket-does-it-matter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising interest rates and a growing deficit are sending the costs of the U.S.'s "credit card balance" to a 25-year high</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Push Largest Expansion Of Govt Since FDR...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/25/democrats-green-new-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's more aspirational than actual policy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ilhan Omar's influence already expanding in Congress...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/ilhan-omar-influence-already-expanding-in-congress/503484652/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incoming House member takes on leadership role in party's biggest block.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread flu outbreaks reported...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/widespread-flu-activity-across-the-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities are reporting widespread flu activity across the country and two states with especially high levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  How Much of Internet Is Fake?</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2018/12/how-much-of-the-internet-is-fake.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out, a lot of it, actually.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors Fret Over Khashoggi Killing, But  Maintain Saudi Ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/partners-fret-over-khashoggi-killing-but-still-maintain-saudi-ties-11545829201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Western investors scrambled to figure out how to preserve their relations with Saudi Arabia following the Khashoggi killing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Ferrell 'HOLMES &amp; WATSON' Gets Rare 0% On ROTTEN TOMATOES...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/holmes-watson-gets-zero-percent-rotten-tomatoes-score-1171637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The John C. Reilly and Will Ferrell team-up was not screened in advance for critics, so subsequent reviews will likely be added that may affect the score.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is NASA hiding? ISS feed repeatedly cut in 2018 as 'huge objects tower over Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/748003/nasa-cover-up-iss-live-feed-international-space-station-objects-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President and First Lady make secret visit to Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6530903/Donald-Melania-Trump-make-surprise-visit-Iraq.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said in his first-ever visit to Iraq that the terror group had been 'very nearly defeated' altogether and Turkey and other regional powers will finish the job.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
