<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at WALMART in Baton Rouge: 1 injury, no active-shooter situation...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/baton_rouge/news/crime_police/article_cae700c4-b86c-11e9-9f27-dff771536d92.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person was injured in a shooting at the Walmart on Burbank Drive Tuesday afternoon after an altercation between two patrons, prompting dozens of law enforcement and first responders to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant rapper shot at in drive-by shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-7327991/Pregnant-rapper-Yung-Miami-unharmed-shot-drive-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pregnant rapper was the target of a drive-by shooting in Miami, Florida early Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Selling Mass. Mansion For $39.5 Million...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/08/06/tom-brady-gisele-bundchen-put-brookline-house-up-for-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady only has one real year left on his current contract. And the quarterback is apparently planning a move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 7 Dems don't have single supporter...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/857286/7-democrats-didnt-single-supporter-new-hampshire-primary-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reality is knocking for these seven Democratic presidential candidates. The twenty-something strong 2020 primary field has been desperate for a weeding since it hit double-digit territory, though even candidates who didn't make a single debate stage have so far been reluctant to drop out. If they're looking for a reason to do so, this new Boston Globe/Suffolk University poll of likely New Hampshire primary voters might be the answer. Unsurprisingly, former Vice President Joe Biden retains his top spot in this New Hampshire poll, gathering 21.4% support. Next up is Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) with 16.8%, Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) with 13.6%, and Sen. Kamala Harris (D-Calif.) at 8%. Yet down at the other end of the spectrum, seven Democrats didn't get a single survey respondent to declare they were their top primary choice: New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio; former Alaska Sen. Mike Gravel; Washington Gov. Jay Inslee; Miramir, Florida Mayor Wayne Messam; Massachusetts Rep. Seth Moulton; Ohio Rep. Tim Ryan; and former Pennsylvania Rep. Joe Sestak. Inslee, Moulton, and Ryan at least got a few people to say they were their second choice for president. Still, a solid 20.8% of respondents said they're undecided on their top 2020 primary pick so far, and another 15.7% are undecided on their second choice, giving these seemingly hopeless candidates a slim chance to turn things around. The Suffolk University/Boston Globe poll surveyed 500 likely Democratic New Hampshire primary voters from Aug. 1-4, and had a margin of error of 4.4%. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Proof Of Need To Take Left-Wing Violence Seriously...</title>
      <link>https://forward.com/opinion/428960/the-dayton-murderer-is-proof-we-need-to-take-left-wing-violence-seriously/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;forward.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did Betts see himself as a gun-wielding warrior and avenger for the left? It should be clear that we ignore the violent left at our own peril.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARNEYS bankrupt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/868e8a905caa4a51b7cde13028fb443e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego increases use of streetlamp cameras; Surveillance concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/as-san-diego-increases-use-of-streetlamp-cameras-aclu-raises/article_8e9a1b8c-3e31-51df-a7f4-30dbcdfe9b7c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — When police stopped a taxicab early one morning last summer to find Jonathan Hernandez armed with a handgun and fleeing the scene of a fatal Gaslamp Quarter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos dumps more shares...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/angelauyeung/2019/08/05/jeff-bezos-unloads-another-990-million-worth-of-amazon-shares-in-early-august/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the course of five days between July 29 and August 2, Bezos has sold $2.8 billion worth of shares -- before taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke-filled cabin on BRITISH AIRWAYS flight leads to mass evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/06/europe/british-airways-flight-smoke-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British Airways flight from London to Spain was evacuated after smoke filled the cabin moments before the flight was due to land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders, Warren gain on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/456317-sanders-warren-gain-on-biden-in-new-hampshire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Demand for bulletproof backpacks surging in wake of shootings...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/456318-demand-for-bulletproof-backpacks-surging-in-the-wake-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bulletproof backpacks are reportedly rising in popularity as shootings increase across the nation and in the wake of two weekend massacres that left more than 30 people dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin Wins Appeal Reviving Defamation Lawsuit Against NYT...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/sarah-palin-wins-appeal-reviving-defamation-lawsuit-against-new-york-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot tail to balance human body, stop from falling over...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/robot-tail-developed-balance-out-18838128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The robotic tail is designed to help the wearer to stay balanced when moving quickly or carrying heavy objects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS SWARM MCCONNELL HOME; THREATEN TO 'STAB MOTHERF*CKER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/far-left-protesters-descend-on-mitch-mcconnells-home-threaten-to-stab-the-motherfker-in-the-heart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgusting harassment caught on camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The Cold, Hard Math Tells NETFLIX Could Crash 70%...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenmcbride1/2019/08/06/the-cold-hard-math-tells-netflix-could-crash-70/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s official... it’s the beginning of the end for Netflix (NFLX). As you may have heard, the online video company made a troubling announcement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug lord who tried to escape prison disguised as daughter found 'HANGED' in cell...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7327323/Brazilian-inmate-nearly-escaped-jail-dressed-woman-hanged.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian drug dealer Clauvino da Silva, 42, who tried to escape from a decade-long drugs sentence by disguising himself as his own daughter, has been found dead in his cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINK crew in miracle escape after private jet crash-lands, bursts into flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7326301/Private-jet-carrying-Pinks-manager-crew-crash-lands-bursts-flames-Denmark.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The manager and other staff of the US artist Pink, who had given a concert in Oslo the night before, were among the 10 passengers and crew who all escaped without injuries at Aarhus airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside documentary that's inspiring militant vegan movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7325015/Vegan-documentary-Dominion-horrific-viewers-sit-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominion, a documentary released in 2018, uses drone footage and hidden cameras to film farms in Australia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT SELL-OFF 'LEHMAN-LIKE'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/06/nomura-a-second-market-sell-off-could-be-lehman-like.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buckle up because the next sell-off could be even more violent, according to Nomura.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel laureate Toni Morrison dead at 88...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/11910324b8c848af823a4b19a3e1bc7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS TIPPING POINT?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/456277-texas-faces-turbulent-political-moment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a quarter century, Texas Republicans have run a ruby-red state, building a conservative bastion where government is limited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro says criminals will 'die like cockroaches' under new laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/06/jair-bolosonaro-says-criminals-will-die-like-cockroaches-under-proposed-new-laws </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil’s president calls for security forces and citizens who shoot alleged offenders to be shielded from prosecution</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-stakes dispute turns nasty, pits 5G technology against weather forecasting...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/will-5g-satellite-deployment-undermine-noaa-weather-forecasting/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dispute within the federal government has FCC officials saying 5G technology can be safely developed, while NASA and National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration officials contend that could threaten the work of polar-orbiting satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH SEA: US carrier sails into disputed waters amid new flare-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2019/08/06/us-carrier-sails-into-disputed-waters-amid-new-flare-ups/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy flew a small group of Philippine generals, officials and journalists Tuesday to the USS Ronald Reagan, where fighter jets landed and took off by catapult with thunderous blasts. The nuclear-powered carrier, which was brimming with about 70 supersonic F18 jets, spy planes and helicopters, was en route to Manila.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At time of transformation and tumult, film academy prepares to elect new president...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/movies/story/2019-08-05/motion-picture-academy-president-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscars: On Tuesday, the academy's board of governors will elect a new president to replace John Bailey. Who might they choose?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLD SOARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.kitco.com/news/2019-08-06/Gold-Prices-Pause-Bulls-Remain-Strong.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kitco.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Technical Analyst Jim Wyckoff prepares investors with an overview of how the markets opened and closed. What moved metal prices? How do the technicals look? By looking at important developments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed thugs return to streets to attack demonstrators...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1681557/armed-thugs-in-white-attack-protesters-in-hong-kong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incidents are eerily similar to the violent gang attack against anti-government protesters last month in the suburb of Yuen Long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strip club empire pledges to send erotic dancers to Area 51...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/06/strip-club-empire-pledges-to-send-erotic-dancers-to-area-51/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top adult entertainment company in Nevada is reportedly set to storm Area 51 next month — with strippers. “Come September 20, we’ll be there,” Ryan Carlson, director of operations at Déjà…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez rips McConnell over pic of men in 'Team Mitch' shirts 'groping &amp; choking' her cutout...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/05/aoc-rips-mcconnell-over-pic-of-young-men-in-team-mitch-shirts-groping-choking-cutout-of-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez called out Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell on Monday night after a photo surfaced on social media, showing a group of young men “groping and choking&amp;#8221…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog Falls From 6-Story Building, Crashes Through Car Sunroof -- Survives!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/05/dog-jumps-off-building-crashes-through-sunroof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dog's owner says they were returning from a walk when the dog ran up a flight of stairs and got onto the roof through a door that had been left open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Tut 'cursed' golden sarcophagus pictured outside tomb first time ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9662770/tutankhamuns-sarcophagus-curse-coffin-restoration-egypt/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KING Tutankhamun’s sarcophagus has been pictured outside his tomb for the first time since its discovery 100 years ago. The Egyptian boy king’s gold-plated coffin – believed by some to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing warns of financial chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china/china-says-u-s-currency-manipulator-labeling-could-cause-chaos-in-financial-markets-idUSKCN1UW04S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's central bank said on Tuesday that Washington's decision to lab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA LABELS CHINA 'CURRENCY MANIPULATOR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/05/trump-blasts-china-yuan-drop-as-currency-manipulation-1634502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time Treasury designated any country as a currency manipulator was in the early 1990s, when China was named.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 89% young feel lives meaningless...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/poll-89-per-cent-of-uk-gen-zers-say-their-lives-are-meaningless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Societal malaise of nihilism evident in survey results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Bites Back at Anti-Graft Leader Who Taunted Putin Allies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kremlin-bites-back-anti-graft-104224967.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For years, opposition leader Alexey Navalny embarrassed Russia‘s leadership with YouTube videos exposing their lavish lifestyles and dubious wealth, and the Kremlin put up with it. Now President Vladimir Putin’s patience appears to have run out.With Navalny in prison and riot police brutally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECESSION WARNING</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yield-curve-blares-loudest-u-153828113.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The latest eruption in the U.S.-China trade dispute pushed a widely watched Treasury-market recession indicator to the highest alert since 2007.Rates on 10-year notes sank to 1.714% on Monday, completely erasing the surge that followed President Donald Trump’s 2016 election. At one point</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey Responds to Mass Shootings in 'Looking for America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/lana-del-rey-looking-for-america-867851/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer previews a brand new song she wrote with Jack Antonoff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most would rather lose job to robot than human...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2212417-most-people-would-rather-lose-their-job-to-a-robot-than-another-human/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people would prefer a robot to take their job if they had to lose it, but they would prefer to see another human step in if a co-worker was going to lose theirs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cord-Cutting Speeds Up As TV Providers Scramble to Boost Profits...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/tv-cord-cutters-us-accelerating-study-emarketer-1229346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of households without a traditional pay-television subscription could soon equal those that have one, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran unveils new missiles; Warns of 'mother of all wars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7325835/Iran-warns-mother-wars-Britain-joins-task-force-Strait-Hormuz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's defence ministry unveiled what it described as three precision guided air-to-air missiles on Tuesday, after President Hassan Rouhani warned of the 'mother of all wars' if the country is attacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Fear 'Extinction in Suburbs' Over Gun Control...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/republicans-fear-extinction-in-the-suburbs-over-gun-control-1.1297594</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder, 'gay-hunters' strike terror in Russia's LGBT community...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/murder-gay-hunters-strike-terror-russias-lgbt-community-023743858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When LGBT activist Yelena Grigoryeva found her name on a hit list of a "gay-hunting" group, she did not appear to take the threat seriously. The group called itself "Pila", meaning "saw", after the series of Hollywood horror films of the same name, in which a serial killer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galveston officers on horseback seen leading handcuffed man with rope...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/5445603/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the officers led him around the corner to 21st and Market, where the mounted patrol unit was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge study explores genetics of PTSD in more than 165,000 veterans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/huge-study-explores-genetics-of-ptsd-in-more-than-165000-us-veterans/ar-AAFnOZY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged for midair meltdown challenges law, saying it was just rudeness...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/08/05/texas-man-charged-mid-air-meltdown-challenges-law-saying-just-rudeness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When does being a jerk rise to the level of becoming a felony when you're 30,000 feet in the air? A federal judge intends to decide the matter....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dayton killer drove to slaughter with best friend...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7324839/Connor-Betts-shot-best-friend-mass-shooting-driving-Dayton.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chance Betts, 24, was the man in the car with Betts and his sister Megan before the gunman killed nine outside Ned Peppers Bar, DailyMail.com can reveal. He is critically ill but is cops' key witness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUTURES DOWN MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/dow-futures-fall-implying-a-200-point-drop-on-tuesday-as-trade-war-fears-batter-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stock futures fell on Monday night, adding to Wall Street's losses from its worst day of 2019 amid intensifying trade-war fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godson of 'El Chapo' testifies about 'hit' put on him in Chicago jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/criminal-justice/ct-sinaloa-cartel-lieutenent-sentencing-chicago-20190805-m4viapclzjauxoodzm7weklcge-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesus Beltran Leon, who prosecutors say worked directly with the sons of Sinaloa boss Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman, is scheduled to be sentenced Monday in federal court in Chicago to importing thousands of pounds of narcotics into the U.S. on behalf of the cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech vows to fight white nationalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tech-companies-say-theyre-ready-to-fight-white-nationalist-terror-2d221935-3d78-4091-bece-cb216294a874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The companies believe concerted action could work, but doubt the White House is serious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio lawmaker blames 'drag queen advocates' in rant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/05/ohio-lawmaker-candice-keller-blames-gay-marriage-drag-queen-advocates-for-dayton-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawmaker in Ohio blamed the breakdown of the “traditional American family,” gay marriage and “drag queen advocates” for the Dayton massacre in a since-deleted Facebook rant. Sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS IN 'PORNOGRIND' BAND THAT RELEASED SONGS ABOUT RAPING AND KILLING WOMEN...</title>
      <link>https://news.vice.com/en_us/article/j5yekp/exclusive-dayton-shooter-was-in-a-pornogrind-band-that-released-songs-about-raping-and-killing-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Menstrual Munchies released albums like "6 Ways of Female Butchery" with cover art showing the rape and mutilation of female bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake ride-share driver cleans out bank accounts of victims...</title>
      <link>https://herald-review.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/fake-ride-share-driver-cleans-out-bank-accounts-of-victims/article_983d4539-0ba2-5b7f-9f4f-dd997ac8356f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;herald-review.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Authorities said a parolee with a long history of identity theft and credit card scams masqueraded as a ride-share driver downtown and cleaned out the bank accounts of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retaliation '11' on Scale of 1 to 10...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-retaliation-11-scale-1-123135905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. Analysts continued to warn about the dangers of an escalating trade war on Monday, as China moved to strike back at the U.S., hitting U.S. stocks and boosting Treasuries. Semiconductors,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurls devaluation back in Trump's face...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-hits-back-trump-weaker-041855645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Terms of Trade is a daily newsletter that untangles a world embroiled in trade wars. Sign up here. China responded to President Donald Trump’s tariff threat with another escalation of the trade war on Monday, letting the yuan tumble to the weakest level in more than a decade and asking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -767</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ba7d32105b6c4b0a932f6e44f3c54e48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA:  Must not let racist views become normalized...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/873dcdec893c43d2b22f6aaa0e574dca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Republican retirement highlights party's growing peril in TX...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7def26496545425a9bc83453f9147b00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds face challenges in stopping domestic terror attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/05a358527d994a47b40950dacb37cba9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TO VISIT EL PASO...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190805223505-y7gd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEXAS-SHOOTING/ (UPDATE 7, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 7-Two more Texas shooting victims die in attack, Trump to visit El Paso</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil deforestation climbs 67% through July as gov't attacks data...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190805200950-3ic5u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-ENVIRONMENT/ (PIX, GRAPHICS):Brazil deforestation climbs 67% through July as gov't attacks data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halts new agricultural purchases......</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190805172900-mc8jo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA-AGRICULTURE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China halts purchase of U.S. farm products</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN COMPARES TRUMP TO THE KKK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7324427/Biden-compares-Trump-Ku-Klux-Klan-claims-president-abandoned-national-unity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden claimed Monday that Donald Trump's use of a 'dog whistle' to subtly support racists makes him an heir to the Ku Klux Klan, the infamous white supremacist hate group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Anxious, Fearful Of Violence In Public Places 'The New Normal'...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/08/05/feeling-anxious-nervous-in-public-places-following-mass-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you find yourself looking for the nearest exits, or scouting out hiding places in public, you're not alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market's 'everything bubble' finally popping?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/is-the-stock-markets-everything-bubble-finally-popping-this-chart-might-have-the-answer-2019-08-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stock market is in shambles to start the week, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average dropping more than 700 points after China retaliated against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH LOSES $162B IN VALUE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/big-tech-plunges-in-market-rout-led-by-slump-in-apple-microsoft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the stock market's worst day of 2019, the biggest tech companies got hammered, losing more than $160 billion in combined market cap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MAGA bomber' sentenced to 20 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/05/maga-bomber-cesar-sayoc-sentenced-to-20-years-in-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Manhattan federal judge has sentenced “MAGA bomber” Cesar Sayoc to 20 years in prison, with five years’ supervised release. Judge Jed Rakoff said Monday the sentence was “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US prosecutors accuse Honduran president of drug conspiracy...</title>
      <link>https://cbs2iowa.com/news/nation-world/us-prosecutors-accuse-honduran-president-of-drug-conspiracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbs2iowa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) &amp;mdash; U. S. federal prosecutors have accused the Honduran government of essentially functioning as a narco-state, with the current and former presidents having received campaign contributions from cocaine traffickers in exchange for protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama attacks Trump's rhetoric in wake of El Paso, Dayton...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7324085/Obama-slaps-Trump-rhetoric-normalizes-racist-anti-immigration-sentiments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama forcefully denounced the rhetoric that Donald Trump has employed while in office to describe immigrants and minorities on Monday in a rare public rebuke of his successor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE sheds $45.7 BILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7321465/Asian-stock-tumble-3rd-day-China-lets-yuan-sink.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global shares fell sharply Monday after China let its currency to sink to an 11-year low against the dollar, fueling concern that Beijing is using the yuan as a weapon in an escalating tariff war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Deep Space Signals Can Now Be Picked Up In Real Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/mysterious-deep-space-signals-can-now-be-picked-up-in-real-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence has been able to tune in to the odd energy known as Fast Radio Bursts and observe them as they reach Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague-Infested Fleas Spark Warnings In CO...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/08/02/plague-fireworks-dicks-sporting-goods-park-commerce-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tri-County Health Department confirms plague-infected fleas have been infecting and killing prairie dogs at numerous areas in Commerce City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult Film Use of Copyright Suits Has Judges Seeing Red...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/porn-purveyors-use-of-copyright-lawsuits-has-judges-seeing-red</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porn producers, sellers account for lionâ€™s share of copyright-infringement lawsuits in U.S. -- and judges may have seen enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER PAN bus driver locked passenger in luggage compartment...</title>
      <link>https://wxow.com/news/national-news-from-the-associated-press/2019/08/05/bus-driver-arrested-for-locking-woman-in-luggage-compartment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wxow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — A bus driver has been charged with locking a passenger in the vehicle's luggage compartment. Connecticut State Police got a 911 call at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6-year-old thrown from 10th floor of London's Tate Modern gallery...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190805-boy-thrown-londons-tate-modern-french-tourist-visiting-uk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boy thrown from London's Tate Modern is French tourist visiting UK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline monitoring passengers via onboard cameras...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/cathay-pacific-onboard-camera/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong airline Cathay Pacific has revealed it is monitoring passengers via cameras on its aircraft, re-opening an uncomfortable debate over surveillance aboard airplanes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compostable bowls contain cancer-linked 'forever chemicals'...</title>
      <link>https://newfoodeconomy.org/pfas-forever-chemicals-sweetgreen-chipotle-compostable-biodegradable-bowls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newfoodeconomy.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
