<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BARNEYS sold for scraps, ending an era...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/barneys-new-york-is-sold-for-scraps-ending-an-era/ar-AAJHDUC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala abandons New Hampshire...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/01/kamala-harris-new-hampshire-offices-063902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: How 1 Company Surveils Everything Kids Do, Say In School...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/carolinehaskins1/gaggle-school-surveillance-technology-education</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaggle monitors the work and communications of almost 5 million students in the US, and schools are paying big money for its services. Hundreds of company documents unveil a sprawling surveillance industrial complex that targets kids who can’t opt out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mouth cancer rates reach record high...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/01/mouth-cancer-rates-reach-record-high-is-oral-sex-to-blame/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, this sucks. Mouth cancer rates “have more than doubled in a generation,” according to a new awareness campaign by the Brit-based nonprofit Oral Health Foundation. Over the past 20…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian president's son suggests using dictatorship-era tactics on leftist foes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/01/brazili-president-son-jair-eduardo-bolsonaro-dictatorship-era-tactics-leftist-foes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eduardo Bolsonaro’s incendiary remarks prompted many across the political spectrum to condemn him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA opens national security investigation into TIKTOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tiktok-cfius-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-opens-national-security-investigation-into-tiktok-sources-idUSKBN1XB4IL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government has launched a national security review of TikTok owner Beij...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most profitable company pays surprisingly little...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/business/article/The-world-s-most-profitable-company-pays-14791896.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They run the world's most profitable company, oversee one-tenth of global oil output and their decisions help shape the fate of a nation. Their paychecks, however, are a little less grandiose. Saudi oil giant Aramco is a cash cow for the kingdom, allowing the royal family to wield power with a drip-feed of petrodollars. For executives, it's a relatively modest life compared with some of their peers elsewhere. Last year, top management and board members-about 17 people in total-split roughly $30 million worth of compensation and benefits. That was half of what rivals Exxon Mobil Corp. and Chevron Corp. handed their executives and directors, though they would have been subject to income tax whereas Saudi nationals aren't. Chief Executive Officer Amin Nasser collected no more than a $5 million package in 2016 as the company began preparing its protracted initial public offering, people familiar with the matter said. That was less than a fifth of what Exxon's then-CEO Rex Tillerson received at the time. Even when taking into account the tax regime and other perks like secluded housing with private pools, the numbers are hardly staggering compared with the grand plan for the company. Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman wants Aramco valued at a spectacular $2 trillion when the government eventually sells shares in it, the centrepiece of the biggest economic transformation since the firm was brought under state control in the 1970s. Inside the C-suite, senior executives for decades have been schooled in the mantra that long-term success trumps all other priorities. It's about the future of the kingdom, not personal enrichment. "This is the lifeblood of Saudi Arabia," said Ellen Wald, who runs her own energy and political consulting firm and is author of the 2018 book...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>56 PERCENT OF WOMEN WANT REMOVED FROM OFFICE?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/01/18-percent-republicans-impeach-remove-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll indicates that 18 percent of Republicans now favor impeaching and removing President Donald Trump from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horse racing: 'Conveyor belt for slaughter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/horseracing/2019/10/31/breeders-cup-horses-go-racetracks-slaughterhouses/2485345001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science Of Scary: Why It's So Fun To Be Freaked Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/11/01/775198994/the-science-of-scary-why-its-so-fun-to-be-freaked-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to hair-raising experiences, why do some of us cower while others can't get enough? Ken Carter, an expert on adrenaline junkies reveals what makes them tick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside CA's black-market nightmare spawned by law gutting shoplifting penalties...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/california-prop-47-shoplifting-theft-crime-statewide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a lighted garage on one of San Francisco's busiest streets, a young man in baggy trousers and messy brown hair pulled down his pants. He had been hiding two pairs of stolen jeans with the tags still on them. He handed them to another man waiting nearby, took some money, pulled up his pants and headed back into another store on Market Street - home to the city's high-end designers and big-chain retail shops. The incident wasn't a one-off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who advocated caning for adultery gets caned for adultery...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/01/asia/indonesia-adultery-caning-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indonesian man has been publicly flogged for adultery, under a draconian law he helped create.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Expects Public Hearings This Month...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pelosi-expects-public-impeachment-hearings-to-begin-this-month/ar-AAJGRzn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private group seeks armed volunteers to protect Trump rally attendees...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/1/private-group-seeks-volunteers-conceal-carry-permi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A private association is putting out a call for volunteers, armed or unarmed, to provide outdoor security for Trump supporters traveling to the president’s campaign rally Friday night in Tupelo, Mississippi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to build a mega-church?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/revealed-trump-wanted-to-build-a-mega-church</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of all the projects real estate mogul Donald Trump wanted to build, here’s one that nobody saw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary laughs when asked how she killed Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/hillary-clinton-laughs-when-asked-how-she-killed-jeffrey-epstein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trevor Noah, the host of the Daily Show, asked Hillary Clinton in an interview about conspiracies that suggest the Clintons have murdered people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  18%  of Republican Voters Now Favor Impeachment?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trumps-republican-support-drops-13-points-18-percent-of-gop-voters-now-favor-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While support for and against impeachment have stayed relatively level, with 49 percent of respondents saying a new ABC News/Washington Post poll that they believe Donald Trump should be removed from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent and drunk monkeys attack tourists in paradise beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/violent-angry-monkeys-attack-tourists-20788002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: It's supposed to be a place of relaxation but has become a nightmare with primates stealing booze from holidaymakers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People entering US screened for Ebola at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/people-entering-united-states-screened-20789128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travellers coming from "Ebola-affected nations" will have to undergo screening by specialists at Washington Dulles International Airport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelike sex robots walk, talk and 'breathe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-breathe-using-ai-20722897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Cloud Climax are working on the human-like upgrade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Nearly 40% of farm income coming from aid, insurance...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/farmers-income-insurance-federal-aid-bankruptcies-5a05b8cb-3348-447b-8bac-ee718fd409fd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farm bankruptcies are also up 24% from 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DECLARES RUPAUL PARTY!</title>
      <link>https://worldofwonder.net/trumps-tweet-mistake-just-accidentally-created-mamas-rupublican-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;worldofwonder.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos would pay  $7 BILLION in tax with Warren's Medicare-for-all!</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/875830/jeff-bezos-pay-nearly-7-billion-elizabeth-warrens-medicareforall-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) has a plan for taking Jeff Bezos' money. The 2020 candidate unveiled her proposal Friday to pay for her estimated $34 trillion Medicare-for-all plan without upping taxes on the middle class. It relies on a big chunk of change from the country's biggest earners, and would end up costing the Amazon founder nearly $7 billion. To raise the tremendous sum needed to provide universal health care, Warren laid out a $20.5 trillion tax package that she says targets "the financial sector, large corporations, and the top 1 percent." Bezos squarely falls under that last category, and he'd be subject to Warren's wealth tax that was upped in this plan from two percent to six percent. And six percent of Bezos' $111.7 billion net worth? That's about $6.7 billion. Joining Bezos at the top of the pile is Bill Gates, who would put in around $6.4 billion, and Warren Buffett, who'd contribute closer to $5 billion. Bezos' company would also end up paying heftier taxes, though it won't have to worry about providing them with health care anymore. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is tight Kentucky gov race sign of trouble awaiting McConnell in 2020?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/tight-kentucky-governors-race-sign-trouble-awaiting-mitch-mcconnell-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Competitive race in red state excites Democrats, but Republicans say there's no comparison between GOP Gov. Matt Bevin and the Senate majority leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire in Ventura County erupts to more than 8,000 acres...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-10-31/maria-fire-south-mountain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maria fire erupted Thursday evening atop South Mountain, just south of Santa Paula, and spurred evacuations. The blaze is moving to the west.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IRISHMAN' Short Window From Big Screen to Small Has Theaters Fuming...</title>
      <link>https://skystatement.com/irishmans-short-window-from-big-screen-to-small-has-theaters-fuming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;skystatement.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix, the company that financed and produced the $159 million movie starring Robert De Niro and Al Pacino.After negotiations between major chains and Netflix ended in a stalemate last month, “The Irishman,” opening Friday, will have a 26-day run in a limited number of theaters before it starts streaming on Nov. 27. A sticking point…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY HE'S LEAVING...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/31/this-is-president-trumps-why-im-leaving-new-york-essay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is leaving New York. President Trump on Thursday night explained his decision to ditch the glitzy world of Midtown skyscrapers and — eventually — flee to his Mar-a-Lago resort at the c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue elephant named after Bin Laden kills five Indian villagers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rogue-elephant-named-bin-laden-kills-five-indian-141755252.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forest officials in northeast India on Friday conducted a major operation to contain a rogue elephant that killed five villagers earlier this week. The male elephant, dubbed "Laden" by locals after the late Al-Qaeda chief Osama bin Laden, killed the people on Tuesday night in Assam state,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How Mayor Pete Becomes President Pete...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/11/pete-buttigieg-2020-next-phase/601237/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year, the Millennial mayor became a household name. Now, how does he translate that into votes?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil federal police investigate Greek ship in connection with oil spill...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-oil-spill/brazil-federal-police-investigate-greek-ship-in-connection-with-oil-spill-idUSKBN1XB47T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's federal police on Friday announced a potential breakthrough in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IRISHMAN' Short Window From Big Screen to Small Has Theaters Fuming...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/01/business/irishman-netflix-theaters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scorsese’s Netflix gangster epic will play in select theaters before it streams. “It’s a disgrace,” says John Fithian, the head of the theater owners organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelike sex robots walk, talk and 'breathe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/lifelike-sex-robots-walk-talk-20787524</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cloud Climax, UK agent for AI-AITech, says that it’s adapting its ‘Emma’ sex robot, so she’s even more human-like</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman found dead with 8ft python wrapped around neck in house of snakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/woman-found-dead-8ft-python-20788083</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benton County Sheriff Don Munson walked in to the house in Battle Ground, Indiana to find the snake wrapped around Laura Hurst's neck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rep Headbutts Camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-gop-rep-headbutts-camera-when-chased-down-by-activists-asking-about-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evasive tactics from members of Congress when ducking questions from constituents, journalists, and activists are nothing new. But this rather painful maneuver, we suspect, has never been tried before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLBOARD IN LONDON ENCOURAGES WHITE PEOPLE TO STERILIZE SELVES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/billboard-in-london-encourages-white-people-to-sterilize-themselves-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advertisement betrays a noticeable lack of diversity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: How the Internet lost its soul...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/How-the-Internet-lost-its-soul-14775213.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, we celebrate what many consider the 50th birthday of the Internet. The underpinnings of the World Wide Web originated in an American communications network built for national defense and the pursuit of knowledge: ARPANET. Funded by the Defense Department's Advanced Research Projects Agency, the network was designed so that scientists could share computer hardware, software and data.  It worked. In the ensuing decades, the ARPANET, and after the 1980s, the National Science Foundation Network (NSFNET), did indeed allow scientists to collaboratively build knowledge around networked tools and information. But expanding access to the Internet, combined with looser government regulations, ultimately produced a situation no one foresaw or intended. On today's Internet, conspiracy theories run rampant, identities can be faked and our real-life elections are vulnerable to manipulation. A network designed for spreading truth became a profit-driven industry, a public sphere that threatens to undermine the public good.  The original ARPANET was designed for a relatively small community of people united by a technical challenge. At the time, computers from different manufacturers ran incompatible software, and long-distance data communications links were costly and unreliable. Networks connected only a few identical computers within a small region.  But ARPANET had an audacious proposal: It would span the continental United States to connect 15 research sites encompassing a diverse array of computers.  "Almost every conceivable item of computer hardware and software will be in the network," project leader Larry Roberts pointed out. "This is the greatest challenge of the system, as well as its greatest ultimate value." As a leading funder of computer science research, ARPA was able to mobilize a talented group of faculty...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBS BEAT BIG!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/01/jobs-report-october-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with a decline of 42,000 in the motor vehicles and parts industry, the pace of new jobs well exceeded the estimate of 75,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treatment of Assange putting his life 'at risk': UN expert...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/treatment-of-assange-putting-his-life-at-risk-un-expert-12055824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planeloads of Cash From Russia Shipped to Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/planeloads-of-cash-from-russia-have-been-shipped-to-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Planeloads of Cash From Russia Have Been Shipped to Venezuela</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden slips to fourth in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/468472-warren-holds-slim-iowa-lead-biden-in-fourth-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll shows a tight race in Iowa, with Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) leading the early voting state while Vice President Joe Biden has slipped to fourth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK UNEMPLOYMENT RECORD LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/huge-october-payrolls-beat-128k-jobs-added-black-unemployment-rate-hits-all-time-low</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The land of 'El Chapo' was once at peace. Then it was in flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-11-01/the-land-of-el-chapo-was-once-at-a-kind-of-peace-now-it-is-in-flames</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sinaloa cartel shattered the social contract in Culiacan last month when it took the city hostage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot brothel using teledildonics to give customers virtual hookers at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/sex-robot-brothel-using-teledildonics-20765805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Alien Cathouse in Nevada is set to become the most technologically advanced house of pleasure on Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>158,510,000 WORKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/national/susan-jones/23rd-record-trump-158510000-americans-working-october</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following September's blockbuster report, the Bureau of Labor Statistics today released its October jobs and unemployment report, another record setter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren unveils $52 trillion health care plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/01/elizabeth-warren-releases-plan-to-pay-for-medicare-for-all.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As she became one of the frontrunners in the Democratic presidential race, Elizabeth Warren faced more pressure about funding Medicare for All.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil: Oil Spill Likely from Venezuela Could Be Worst 'Environmental Attack' in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/11/01/brazil-oil-spill-likely-from-venezuela-could-be-worst-environmental-attack-in-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEO of Petrobras warned the oil spills in Brazil’s northeast may be the worst environmental incident in the country’s history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA BREAKDOWN: Flyers Report 'Mayhem' at Newark Airport Security Check...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Flyers-Report-Mayhem-at-Newark-Airport-Security-Check-564214561.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flyers at Newark Liberty International Airport are reporting unprecedented lines at the TSA security check Friday morning, though the agency could not immediately be reached for comment on what prompted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration's obsession with ancient Persian emperor...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/The-Trump-administration-s-obsession-with-an-14756082.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump and his lieutenants have a penchant for Middle Eastern monarchs. In close to three years in power, the administration has courted or hosted virtually all the region's unelected potentates, yoking its anti-Iranian agenda in part to the concerns of a clutch of Arab sheikhs and princes. But looming above them all is a royal ghost from the past.  On Tuesday, Secretary of State Mike Pompeo commemorated a moment more than 2,500 years ago. "Today in 539 BC, Cyrus the Great entered Babylon and freed the Jewish people from captivity," Pompeo tweeted. "His respect for human rights and religious freedom inspired America's founding fathers. The U.S. stands with the Iranian people, who are blocked by the regime from celebrating his legacy."  Pompeo was referring to a rather famous event in history. According to sources including biblical scripture, Cyrus allowed the Judeans deported and exiled following the ravages of Babylonian King Nebuchadnezzar II to return to their homeland. His conquest of Babylon cemented his dominion over much of the lands we now consider to be the Middle East, an empire that stretched from the Indus River basin to the Mediterranean Sea. Like any other ancient warrior king, he presided over massacres and pillage, including a notorious incident immortalized by the ancient Greek chronicler Herodotus where Cyrus burned a vanquished foe and 14 young boys alive on a funeral pyre.  But Cyrus is memorialized by Iranians (and non-Iranians) as a unifying proto-national hero, an all-powerful emperor who still allowed for toleration and coexistence among different peoples, sects and religions. The Cyrus Cylinder, a barrel-shaped tablet etched in Babylonian cuneiform that was unearthed by archaeologists in the late 19th century, announced his victory and his desire to let his new subjects retain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garoppolo heats up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/49ers-hold-off-late-cardinals-push-jimmy-garoppolo-heats-up-raises-super-bowl-ceiling/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're bringing you our biggest takeaways of the 49ers' big win over Arizona</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The science of zombies: Will the undead rise?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/science-zombies-undead-rise-004009241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are in fact a growing number of documented examples in the animal kingdom of parasites that change their hosts' behavior -- and increasing evidence that humans are not immune to zombie-like manipulations. It's a subject that fascinates theoretical evolutionary biologist Athena Aktipis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Not on my list': Private firms battle flames, raise concerns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/not-list-private-california-firms-fight-fires-raise-055332946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kris Brandini and his crew had just returned from four intense, non-stop days battling fires in western Los Angeles. "I don't just go there randomly -- that's the difference between me and the state firefighters. Firms like Brandini's Firebreak Protection Systems hit the headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Detroit, elusive black voters could upend 2020 Democrats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/detroit-elusive-black-voters-could-upend-2020-democrats-014611501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside the dilapidated Michigan home where civil rights icon Malcolm X once lived, Aaron Sims hesitated before confiding that he voted for Donald Trump. In majority-black Detroit and across the nation, African Americans overwhelmingly support Democrats. "I know I'll probably get a lot of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Russian law to control internet enters force...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/controversial-russian-law-control-internet-enters-force-112840110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A controversial law that would allow Russia to cut internet traffic from international servers came into force Friday, prompting fears from rights activists of online isolation. The law, which President Vladimir Putin signed in May, requires Russian internet providers to install technical devices provided</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pig Plague Starts Rippling Through American Meat Markets...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/pig-plague-starts-rippling-american-192503598.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. meat markets had so far been shielded from the effects of a deadly pig disease wiping out Asian herds. That’s starting to change.As pork supplies plummet in China, the world’s top consumer is desperate for meat and is ramping up imports. As a result, it’s becoming harder to set longer-term</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inquiry focuses on 2 White House lawyers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/01f2000ce18f44e89a8079ba6af2b546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House impeachment inquiry is zeroing in on two White House lawyers privy to a discussion about moving a memo recounting President Donald Trump's phone call with the leader of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile's fiery anger fueled by fears of poverty in old age...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191101093303-inbqw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILE-PROTESTS/PENSIONS (PIX, TV):Chile's fiery anger fueled by fears of poverty in old age</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third Of Americans Battle Burnout Every Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/the-new-normal-over-a-third-of-americans-battle-job-burnout-every-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shocking 36% of 2,000 working Americans surveyed reported dealing with feelings of on-the-job burnout every single week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BLADE RUNNER' was set in November 2019. What did movie get right?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/entertainment/films/1198613/Blade-Runner-setting-predictions-November-2019-Los-Angeles-Harrison-Ford-Rick-Deckard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLADE RUNNER is set in November 2019, so what predictions did Harrison Ford’s movie get correct?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He came out of straps, flipped on his back like it was nothing.' Exorcisms soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.10tv.com/article/vatican-training-more-priests-while-exorcism-requests-are-rise-2019-nov</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican is training more priests to be exorcists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China warns it won't tolerate dissent in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-warns-wont-tolerate-dissent-hong-kong-074613842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China warned Friday it would not tolerate any challenge to Hong Kong's governing system, as it laid out plans to boost patriotism in the city and change how its leader is chosen or removed after months of pro-democracy protests. Beijing also said it would brook no foreign interference in Hong Kong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to read Ukraine call transcript to American people...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/fireside-chat-on-live-television-trump-says-he-wants-to-read-transcript-of-ukraine-call-to-american-people  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A defiant President Trump signaled he will not cooperate with the Democratic Party's impeachment proceedings, insisting his telephone conversation with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky was "a good call" and that he might read it aloud to Americans so they can see his point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Days of terrifying darkness, cold and hunger amid PG&amp;E's sweeping power blackouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.omaha.com/news/national/days-of-terrifying-darkness-cold-and-hunger-amid-pg-e/article_2bf8fd0b-94a0-52e4-9b9a-087e98dc0541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEARLAKE, Calif. — For four nights, Eliana Rubin cared for her newborn son, James, by candlelight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER NO MORE!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-lifelong-new-yorker-declares-himself-a-resident-of-florida/ar-AAJFly0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  DEADSPIN Revolt Is Latest Clash as Private Equity Swallows Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/deadspin-revolt-is-latest-clash-as-private-equity-swallows-media/ar-AAJEWDC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake firefighters entering evacuated areas to loot homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7635979/California-police-warn-FAKE-firefighters-trying-loot-wildfire-devastated-areas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sonoma County Sheriff's Office announced they're investigating reports of fake firefighters in the area of the Kincade Fire in Northern California on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watchdog sues FBI over facial recognition secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/watchdog-sues-fbi-over-facial-recognition-secrecy-185123202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A civil liberties watchdog Thursday sued the FBI and other federal agencies claiming the government is improperly withholding information on how it uses a facial recognition database of millions of Americans. "Because of the FBI's secrecy, little is known about how the agency is supercharging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidency on Treacherous New Ground...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-presidency-treacherous-ground-house-182244439.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s presidency stands on its most treacherous ground after the House voted Thursday to approve and proceed with its impeachment inquiry.The resolution, passed on a largely party-line 232-196 vote, does not just lay out a road map for the public phase of the inquiry. It sends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inquiry Faces Critical Test...</title>
      <link>https://justrealnews.ca/2019/10/28/moving-closer-to-trump-impeachment-inquiry-faces-critical-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justrealnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYT &gt; U.S. &gt; Politics WASHINGTON — House impeachment investigators are speeding toward new White House barriers meant to block crucial testimony and evidence from the people who are closest to President Trump — obstacles that could soon test the limits of Democrats’ fact finding a month into their inquiry. What has been a rapidly …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt officials around globe targeted for hacking through WHATSAPP...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191031220251-c0v3i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK-CYBER/WHATSAPP-NSOGROUP (UPDATE 3, EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Government officials around the globe targeted for hacking through WhatsApp -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president dismisses report alleging military discontent...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191031205645-okprt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-MILITARY/:Mexican president dismisses report alleging military discontent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keystone pipeline shut after spilling 9,000 barrels of oil in NDakota...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191031180757-6lurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIPELINE SPILL/NDAKOTA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Keystone pipeline shut after spilling 9,000 barrels of oil in N. Dakota</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Trump aide confirms Biden probe linked to Ukraine aid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6b5c1b4adbc40dda0bb4f7fba8bae1d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A former top White House official confirmed Thursday that military aid to Ukraine was held up by President Donald Trump's demand for the ally to investigate Democrats and Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINDS CALM IN CA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96b6eaacf3fa49d3be2575fdfc3c2caf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDSOR, Calif. (AP) — Lynn Darst and her husband were camped out in their motor home on the edge of their seats for four days wondering if their house would survive yet another wildfire menacing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists working on pill to edit memories...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/eternal-sunshine-of-the-spotless-mind</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are working on ways to edit memories — to make the intolerable bearable — by, say, blocking the synaptic changes needed for a memory to solidify</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING grounds 50 planes over cracks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boeing-says-50-planes-grounded-052100893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
