<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>THE NOCTURNALS: Ultra-introverts reveling in quiet and solitude...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2022/02/ultra-introverts-nocturnal-lives/622856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most people are fast asleep, some ultra-introverts are going about their lives, reveling in the quiet and solitude. They challenge a core assumption of psychology: that all humans need social connection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court formally ends Trump's fight over Capitol attack records...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/government/us-supreme-court-formally-ends-trumps-fight-over-capitol-attack-records-2022-02-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court on Tuesday brought a formal end to former President Donald Trump's request to block the release of White House records sought by the Democratic-led congressional panel investigating last year's deadly attack on the Capitol by a mob of his supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convoy organizer eyes Beltway shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/595277-truck-convoy-organizer-eyes-dc-beltway-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A truck convoy organizer says that his group has plans to shut down the Capital Beltway in the D.C. region this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Beckel dies at 73...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/595276-bob-beckel-dies-at-73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime cable news pundit and political analyst Bob Beckel died on Monday. He was 73.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices skyrocket 19%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/22/homes/us-home-prices-case-shiller-december-2021/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland's new Forest Lagoon spa immerses visitors among trees...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/forest-lagoon-spa-iceland/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucked away in the northern woodlands of Iceland lies a cozy new spa set to soothe visitors who are looking to enjoy natural hot springs and greenery in equal measure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: The Long Crusade of Clarence and Ginni Thomas...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/02/22/magazine/clarence-thomas-ginni-thomas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court justice and his wife battled for years for a more conservative America. New reporting shows how far she was willing to go after Donald Trump’s 2020 election loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNER BROS. 'MATRIX' legal slugfest exposes Hollywood's shifting priorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/warner-bros-matrix-legal-slugfest-exposes-hollywoods-shifting-priorities/ar-AAU80uC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIAGRA Emerges As 'Life-Changing, Life-Saving' Drug For Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/viagra-dogs-eating-disorder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megaesophagus is a condition which affects the esophagus of many dog breeds. The organ enlarges and loses its ability to move food to the stomach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. spy plane takes spotlight in empty airspace...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-drone/u-s-air-force-spy-plane-takes-spotlight-in-empty-ukraine-airspace-idUSKBN2KR19F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Ukraine's airspace has been largely empty amid the crisis with Russia, a remotely piloted U.S. military vehicle called the RQ-4 Global Hawk has flown over the country in circles for hours at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Kitchen Sponge Crawling With More Bacteria Than Lab Petri Dish!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/kitchen-sponges-more-bacteria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact, no matter how much you replace your sponge, you’ll always run into the same issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORSCHEs, LAMBORGHINIs Lost at Sea May Cost VW $155 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/porsches-lamborghinis-lost-at-sea-may-cost-vw-155-million/ar-AAU7UdI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Successfully Map Out Entire Human Gut For First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/first-map-human-gut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have successfully mapped out the entire human GI tract, including how different cells living in the gut are important to daily life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Crackdown Risk Roars Back With Probe of Jack Ma Empire...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-crackdown-risk-roars-back-103142902.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- From Alibaba to Tencent, China’s largest companies are once again at the center of a market storm, spurred by speculation that Beijing is readying another assault on the world’s biggest internet arena.Most Read from BloombergU.S. Condemns Russian Move at UN, Reassures Kyiv: Ukraine UpdatePorsches, Lamborghinis Lost at Sea May Cost VW $155 MillionStocks Retreat, Ruble Weakens on Ukraine Tension: Markets WrapKremlin Cautious on Prospect of Biden-Putin Summit Amid TensionsTrump Holds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China walking tightrope between Russia and West...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-keeps-walking-its-tightrope-between-russia-and-the-west-as-tensions-flare-in-ukraine/ar-AAU9oTf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four in 10 people 'not confident using numbers in everyday lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishnews.com/business/2022/02/22/news/four-in-10-people-not-confident-using-numbers-in-their-everyday-lives--2594773/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR in 10 (40 per cent) people do not feel confident about using numbers in their everyday lives, a survey has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen cancels virtual engagements over Covid symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/22/uk/queen-elizabeth-ii-covid-update-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Queen Elizabeth II canceled her planned virtual engagements on Tuesday as she continues to suffer from mild Covid-19 symptoms, Buckingham Palace has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Peacekeeping' forces in tanks roll into Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4742020/russian-tanks-ukraine-putin-doctors-bloodshed/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s tanks have rolled into Ukraine creating the most “dangerous situation since the Cuban Missile Crisis”. Around 10,000 troops moved into two Russian speaking breaka…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany halts pipeline project...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/germanys-scholz-halts-nord-stream-2-certification-2022-02-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Olaf Scholz put on ice the certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline designed to bring Russian gas to Germany on Tuesday after Russia formally recognised two breakaway regions in eastern Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icahn launches proxy fight with MCDONALD'S over treatment of pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/20/carl-icahn-launches-proxy-fight-with-mcdonalds-over-treatment-of-pigs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carl Icahn, the famed billionaire corporate raider, has pushed McDonald's for better treatment of pigs in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astrologers explain 'power shift' significance of 2/22/22 for USA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/21/astrologers-explain-power-shift-significance-of-2-22-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little more than two hours after midnight, the deuces will be too wild to ignore: 2:22:22 on 2/22/22, a Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Wendy Williams Show Ends...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/wendy-williams-producers-to-announce-sherri-shepherd-as-permanent-replacement-this-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary talk show host is officially out after 13 seasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Immense fraud' found after $6 TRILLION in virus spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/immense-fraud-creates-immense-task-for-washington-as-it-tries-to-tighten-scrutiny-of-6-trillion-in-emergency-coronavirus-spending/ar-AATZ0cF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/defying-west-putin-orders-troops-to-ukraine-rebel-regions/ar-AAU8rKm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin ordered Russian troops into two Moscow-backed rebel regions of Ukraine on Monday, defying Western threats of sanctions in a move that could set off a potentially catastrophic war with Kyiv. Earlier, the Kremlin leader recognised the independence of two rebel-held areas of the Donetsk and Lugansk regions of Ukraine, paving the way for an operation to deploy part of the potential invasion force he has massed around the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia court decriminalizes abortion, adding to Latin America momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Colombia-court-decriminalizes-abortion-adding-to-16936452.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTÁ, Colombia - Colombia's constitutional court voted Monday to decriminalize...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN EMERGENCY MEETING</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-agrees-biden-putin-summit-071704190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russian President Vladimir Putin officially recognized two self-proclaimed separatist republics in eastern Ukraine, a move that torpedoes European-mediated peace talks and further escalates tensions with the West. Most Read from BloombergUNSC to Hold Emergency Meeting On Russia’s Move: Ukraine UpdateStocks Retreat, Ruble Weakens on Ukraine Tension: Markets WrapKremlin Cautious on Prospect of Biden-Putin Summit Amid TensionsTrump Holds Onto Piles of Cash, Gives None to GOP Candidat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS MILITARY BASES</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-russia-now-build-military-004809042.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has acquired the right to build military bases in Ukraine's two breakaway regions under treaties signed by President Vladimir Putin with their separatist leaders. Putin on Monday officially recognised the two breakaway regions - the self-proclaimed Donetsk People's Republic and the Lugansk People's Republic - as independent statelets, defying Western warnings that such a step would be illegal and kill peace negotiations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL NEARS $100</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/oil-price-charts/#Brent-Crude</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oilprices from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-boris-johnson-europe-emmanuel-macron-2b7c2949ae3168effce9d0cb2584bb32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A long-feared Russian invasion of Ukraine appeared to be imminent Monday, if not already underway, with Russian President Vladimir Putin ordering forces into separatist regions of eastern Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  'Peacekeeping forces' to cross border...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10536311/Biden-phones-Zelensky-gathers-National-Security-team-Putin-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin ordered a 'peacekeeping mission' in Ukraine breakaways of Donetsk and Luhansk after iden hit the two regions with sanctions following Russia declaring them 'independent republics'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For most Americans, owning home now distant dream...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/real-estate-home-prices-middle-class-affordability/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As housing prices soar, owning a home in the U.S. "is a signifier of the upper class now," one real estate economist says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spears set to pen tell-all book in bombshell $15M deal...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/02/21/britney-spears-set-to-write-tell-all-in-15-million-book-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deal comes after a bidding war from multiple publishers, according to one insider, who claimed, “the deal is one of the biggest of all time, behind the Obamas.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk accuses SEC of leaking information from federal probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/21/tesla-ceo-elon-musk-accuses-sec-of-leaking-information.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk's attorney did not specify which investigation or what type of information may have been leaked by the SEC, and to whom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Orders Sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/21/biden-set-to-order-sanctions-on-separatist-regions-of-ukraine-after-putin-decree.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said it was ready to respond immediately to Russian President Vladimir Putin's decision to recognize the independence of two Ukrainian regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodeo industry bucks LA bid to bust up sport...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/feb/21/rodeo-industry-bucks-los-angeles-city-council-bid-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodeo organizers are calling bull on a Los Angeles City Council proposal to hog-tie the sport in the name of animal rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Airspace over Sea of Azov closing at midnight...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-698088</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Independent trackers reported that a number of Russian naval vessels entered the Sea of Azov as well on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rape in Atlanta soars by 236%; Murder up 43%...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10536017/Atlantas-crime-wave-spirals-control-rapes-increase-236-murders-spike-43.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Statistics released by the Atlanta Police Department show homicides are up 43% compared to the same time period in 2021, when the city recorded a 30-year high murder rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY assess local cyber threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/as-the-prospect-of-war-looms-over-europe-n-y-officials-assess-local-cyber-threat/ar-AAU8mhv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot police clash with New Zealand anti-vax protesters...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/riot-police-clash-zealand-anti-200049979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police with riot shields clashed with anti-vaccine demonstrators outside New Zealand's parliament early Tuesday, with one protester unsuccessfully attempting to drive a car into a group of officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists 'dismayed' by treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2022/feb/21/journalist-beijing-winter-olympics-foreign-correspondents-club</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign Correspondents’ Club of China says reporters tailed and manhandled by security despite assurances from Games officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King of Jordan hoarded massive wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2022/feb/21/revealed-king-jordan-used-swiss-accounts-hoard-massive-wealth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leak shows King Abdullah was beneficial owner of at least six Credit Suisse accounts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convoy of protesters begin trip to DC area this week...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2022/02/group-of-protesting-truckers-begin-trip-to-dc-area-this-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inspired by the trucker convoy in Canada, a group from California says they will now head to Washington D.C. to protest COVID-19 restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reef ball burials: New trend for becoming 'coral' when you die...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2022/feb/21/reef-ball-burials-the-new-trend-for-becoming-coral-when-you-die</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do underwater cremation memorials help people regenerate marine habitats in death or are they a ‘greenwashing’ gimmick?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange reason birds flocking to cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20220217-the-strange-reason-migrating-birds-are-flocking-to-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some species of migrating birds are increasingly attracted to life in the big city – but these unnatural environments can be deadly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN RECOGNIZES BREAKAWAY REGIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/talk-biden-putin-summit-ukraine-shelling-rcna17033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such a move will be seen as a huge provocation by Ukraine, the U.S. and its European allies, and it could trigger further violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Employees Use Android Phones to Avoid Tim Cook Snooping...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2022/02/21/report-apple-store-employees-want-to-unionize-use-android-phones-to-avoid-tim-cooks-snooping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Store employees around the United States are reportedly attempting to unionize as hourly workers grow frustrated with wages and working conditions. According to the Washington Post, Apple employees are using Android smartphones to discuss unionization to avoid potential snooping efforts by their employer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bags packed, frontline braces for invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220221-bags-packed-ukrainians-at-frontline-brace-for-russian-invasion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a fraction of the apartments in Anna Velichko's shell-scarred high-rise are fit for habitation after years of a war in Ukraine that could yet turn more brutal still should Russia invade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN TO SIGN SEPARATIST RECOGNITION</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/europe/russia-ukraine-crisis-updates-putin-to-recognise-ukraine-rebels-as-independent-says-kremlin-1.85903123</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow the latest updates on the developments between Ukraine and Russia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cavuto confirms he was in ICU with covid pneumonia...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-news-anchor-neil-cavuto-returns-from-5-week-covid-pneumonia-battle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cavuto returned on-air to say he was in the ICU and that it was “touch-and-go” at times. He once again urged Fox viewers to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman stabs husband 140 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/florida-woman-allegedly-stabbed-husband-140-times-fractured-skull-with-meat-cleaver-police-said</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of Melvin Weller, 62, was found by the woman's son, who reported it to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA, IS THAT YOU?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4734607/madonna-shocks-fans-teenager-pic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADONNA’S latest snap has shocked fans who are convinced she “looks 16 years old”. The provocative singer, 63, is continuing to share racy pictures on Instagram – and the la…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK scraps all restrictions... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/breaking-boris-johnson-axes-covid-26291716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson has unveiled plans to repeal the last remaining pandemic restrictions as part of his new 'living with Covid' blueprint</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER Shooting in Tulum Leaves Two Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10535077/Two-men-shot-dead-rival-Mexican-gangs-opened-fire-restaurant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men have been shot dead and a third injured after a group of gunmen opened fire at Art Beach restaurant, which sits in the Mayan Riviera resort of Tulum, on Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logo Legal Issues?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumps-twitter-ripoff-truth-social-suffers-botched-launch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would-be users of Trump’s new app merely struggled to create an account after Sunday night’s launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo's sons take entire town hostage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/town-held-hostage-hitmen-loyal-26290146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty trucks of armed men loyal to the sons of gangster El Chapo held the town of Caborca hostage for 24 hours last week and killed two men, before kidnapping many more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES pilot's UFO report to FBI so detailed it shook experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/american-airlines-pilots-harrowing-ufo-26284737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pilot onboard the American Airlines Flight 2292 reportedly saw a UFO flying over New Mexico in February 2021 – and the FBI has since confirmed they knew about the incident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPAC counterprogramming:  Trump's GOP critics to gather in DC with eye on '24...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trumps-republican-critics-gather-2024-presidential-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the same weekend as the CPAC gathering, Trump critics will cheer on the two Republicans on the select committee probing January 6, Liz Cheney and Adam Kinzinger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump New Social Media App Shows Error Message on Launch Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/trump-s-new-social-media-app-shows-error-message-on-launch-day/ar-AAU8cJ5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems engaged in 'new politics of evasion' that could cost them in '24...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Democrats-are-engaged-in-a-new-politics-of-16935734.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three decades ago, Democratic policy analysts William A. Galston and Elaine Kamarck...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Gabbard to speak at CPAC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/595145-tulsi-gabbard-to-speak-at-cpac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Tulsi Gabbard (D-Hawaii) is set to speak at the Conservative Political Action Conference (CPAC) this week, the chair of the group that organizes the gathering announced on Monday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
