<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Horrors Push Europe Toward New Sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://nz.news.yahoo.com/eu-says-holds-russia-responsible-081840499.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nz.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The European Union said that work is under way on additional sanctions to penalize Russia for what appear to be war crimes in Ukraine, as it condemned the alleged atrocities committed against civilians.Most Read from BloombergA 30-Year-Old Crypto Billionaire Wants to Give His Fortune AwayChina Finds New Virus Subtype as Daily Cases Exceed 13,000Ukraine Update: Kyiv Warns Russia Is Adding Troops in MoldovaUkraine Update: More Talks Possible Even as Bucha Outrage GrowsWhat If Fox Ne</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Election Opens Up as Le Pen Surges...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/04/french-election-opens-up-as-marine-le-pen-surges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — At last, Emmanuel Macron stepped forth. The French president entered a vast arena this weekend, plunged into darkness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flurry of New Laws Move Blue and Red States Further Apart...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/03/flurry-of-new-laws-move-blue-and-red-states-further-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — After the governor of Texas ordered state agencies to investigate parents for child abuse if they provide certain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service paying $30K per month for Malibu mansion to protect Hunter Biden...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/secret-service-paying-30k-month-malibu-mansion-protect/story?id=83821498</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Secret Service detail protecting Hunter Biden has been paying more than $30,000 a month for a swanky Malibu mansion close to Biden's home, sources tell ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Covid Crisis Grows With Cases Surging, New Sub-Variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-covid-crisis-grows-with-cases-surging-new-sub-strains/ar-AAVOX0W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem anxiety grows over Biden's dismal polls...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/3256844-democratic-anxiety-grows-over-bidens-dismal-polls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are growing increasingly worried about President Biden’s standing in the polls seven months out from the midterm elections.   Biden hasn’t seen a boost in his approval ratings a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Claims He's Being  Censored on Trump 'Free-Speech' App...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/roger-stone-claims-hes-being-censored-on-trumps-truth-social</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stone is the most high-profile MAGA character to claim he’s being silenced on the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama set for White House return...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/obama-return-white-house-celebrate-health-care-reform-rcna22762</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first visit since he left office, the former president will appear alongside Biden and Harris to promote the success of the Affordable Care Act, a White House official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Covid Crisis Grows With Cases Surging, New Sub-Variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-covid-crisis-grows-with-cases-surging-new-sub-strains/ar-AAVOX0W?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence of War Crimes as Russians Retreat From Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/horror-mass-killings-ukraine-men-26621558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC IMAGES: As Russian forces withdraw from the areas around the Ukrainian capital of Kyiv, some of the horrors of what they have done are being revealed with bodies being discovered littering the streets of towns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ:  Zelensky  makes surprise Grammys appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10682607/Were-going-keeping-peoples-names-mouths-Trevor-Noah-mocks-Smith-Grammys.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zelensky made a surprise appearance, saying: 'Our musicians wear body armor instead of tuxedos.' He added: 'Fill the silence with your music. Fill it today to tell our story.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Bodies of four people killed in Sacramento bar-fight shooting still lying on street 15 hours later...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10682399/PICTURED-Married-dad-38-man-29-six-killed-Sacramento-bar-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A married father-of-three and much-loved son have been named as two of the six people killed in a mass-shooting outside a Sacramento bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORBAN LANDSLIDE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-viktor-orban-europe-nato-budapest-e29b5d42a86086bb65b413e2b6d1c2bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUDAPEST, Hungary (AP) — Prime Minister Viktor Orban declared victory in Sunday's national elections, claiming a mandate for a fourth term as a partial vote count predicted a strong lead for his right-wing party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 3 In 5 Wake Up Thinking About Finances...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/money-matters-waking-up-finances/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than half of Americans feel embarrassed talking to others about their finances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Gas Prices Soar, Biden's Climate Ambitions Sputter...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/01/as-gas-prices-soar-bidens-climate-ambitions-sputter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A year after he entered the White House with a vow that fighting global warming would be a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children used as 'human shields'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/apr/02/ukrainian-children-used-as-human-shields-near-kyiv-say-witness-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horrifying accounts tell of Russian soldiers placing children on tanks to protect their vehicles when moving</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adams' order to clear homeless camps ignites fury in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/02/adams-nypd-homeless-camps-00022473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elected officials and advocates say there's no safe place for homeless New Yorkers to go after Adams already cleared out the subways and transit hubs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break West Coast-Style: Santa Barbara 'overwhelmed' by mayhem...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10680399/Santa-Barbara-EMS-overwhelmed-Deltopia-Spring-Break-mayhem-thousands-pack-streets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Santa Barbara declared a 'multi casualty incident' in Isla Vista where a raucous college Spring Break party Deltopia is underway. Santa Barbara County Sheriff's office made three arrests Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite drone unit on quad bikes ambushed forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-elite-ukrainian-drone-unit-on-quad-bikes-ambushed-russian-forces-helping-to-defeat-putin-s-plan-to-capture-kyiv-report-says/ar-AAVOj4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streets 'littered' with bodies, 280 buried in mass grave...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/02/ukrainian-town-littered-with-civilians-bodies-mayor-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 300 people were buried in a mass grave in Bucha, a commuter town northwest of Ukraine’s capital Kyiv, its mayor said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 killed, 9 injured in downtown Sacramento shooting... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article260065985.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news: Extremely large police presence downtown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets 90 shots to sell forged passes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-germany-europe-document-forgery-120b2c4db8aa71ffeadf766a9829910b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A 60-year-old man allegedly had himself vaccinated against COVID-19 dozens of times in Germany in order to sell forged vaccination cards with real vaccine batch numbers to people not wanting to get vaccinated themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Multiple victims,' chaos on Sacramento street after shooting rampage... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2022/04/03/sacramento-downtown-shooting/7261794001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least six people are dead and nine injured following a shooting rampage Sunday in downtown Sacramento, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The curious doctor who moved to Hawaii, became a hermit...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/hawaii/article/The-tale-of-the-doctor-hermit-Hawaii-17051298.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People may think I am a fool but I have found real happiness and above all real peace...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's next move revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/europe/vladimir-putins-next-move-revealed-amid-russian-retreat-from-kyiv/news-story/7de4b1f0402ba55a514067948c917be3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin’s next move is finally becoming clearer following his surprising decision to pull Russian troops away from the Kyiv area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilians Poison Soldiers With Buns, Booze...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10680875/Two-Russian-troops-dead-28-hospital-POISONED-laced-Ukrainian-buns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Russian soldiers are dead after Ukrainians in Izium laced stuffed buns laced with poison - with 28 others now in intensive care as the citizens ramp up their defiance of Vladimir Putin's troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine regains control...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10679301/Pictured-Columns-Russian-vehicles-line-highways-Kyiv-tank-graveyards.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine has taken back the 'whole Kyiv region', the country's deputy defence minister Hanna Maliar said today. Maliar said: 'Irpin, Bucha, Gostomel and the whole Kyiv region were liberated from the invader.'</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
