<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Meet the People Still Planning Cruise Vacations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/meet-the-insane-people-still-planning-cruise-ship-vacations-despite-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people see the prospect of a deadly virus and a 14-day quarantine and run far, far away. Others see the deal of a lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA halts inspections of foreign plants...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/pharmalot/2020/03/10/fda-coronavirus-foreign-inspections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By postponing inspections, the FDA will not be in a position to visit facilities that would be reviewed as part of product applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEATTLE READIES CRACKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/seattle-area-official-outlines-potential-next-steps-in-coronavirus-response-including-cancellation-of-events/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle area public-health officials are "at the ready" to start ordering involuntary isolation and quarantines and are considering cancellation of major public events, with information coming soon, a top official said Monday. Patty Hayes, director of Public Health — Seattle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel slump worsens as airlines blame media...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/10/airlines-travel-slump-coronavirus-125016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials have warned, though, that it may not be safe for everyone to fly everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Olympic Torch Lighting Ceremony in Greece Closed to Public...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/olympics/news/coronavirus-update-tokyo-olympic-torch-lighting-ceremony-in-greece-will-be-closed-to-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No fans will be present for the event</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ban short-haul flights for climate? In EU poll 62% say yes...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200310175356-sjq0o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-CHANGE-EU/FLIGHTS (PIX):Ban short-haul flights for climate? In EU poll 62% say yes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis Proclaims 'Abortion Provider Appreciation Day'...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2020/03/10/minneapolis-mayor-jacob-frey-proclaims-march-10-abortion-provider-appreciation-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey has proclaimed March 10 as Abortion Provider Appreciation Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie: Real Socialism Has Never Been Tried...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/bernie-real-socialism-has-never-been-tried/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After being hammered for his long history of defending Communists, Bernie Sanders is now employing the other age-old, and equally deceptive, defense of socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Patient Zero Spread Despite Ebola-Style Lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/seattles-patient-zero-spread-coronavirus-despite-ebola-style-lockdown/ar-BB10XnUo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART employee tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/10/walmart-deploys-new-emergency-leave-policy-kentucky-associate-has-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart is deploying an emergency employee leave program as the retailer confirms one of its store associates in Cynthiana, Kentucky has tested positive for the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi rejects calls to shutter Capitol: 'We're the captains of this ship'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/486834-pelosi-rejects-calls-to-shutter-capitol-were-the-captains-of-this-ship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Capitol consumed by anxiety over the coronavirus, Judiciary Chairman Jerrold Nadler (D-N.Y.) rose in a closed-door caucus meeting Tuesday and told his Democratic colleagues they should leave Washington and return home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel seals itself off from international travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Israel-seals-itself-off-from-international-travel-15120089.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV - The arrival hall of Ben Gurion Airport's Terminal 3 is Israel's front door. On Tuesday, one day after the government instituted some of the most sweeping quarantine requirements in the global fight against coronavirus, it was a door swinging shut.  Daily arrivals had collapsed by two-thirds, according to airport authorities, falling from 65,000 to 22,000. The silence of the normally bustling hall was the harbinger of a building economic hit; Israel's finance minister estimated Monday that the new quarantine restrictions, scheduled to last two weeks, could cost $1.4 billion.  Those few passengers who did trickle through, passing under a flight board riddled with "CANCELED" notices, found themselves subject to a baffling triage, as help-desk staffers and tour guides tried to sort the emergency procedures.  Most passengers were directed straight to their homes for two weeks of self-isolation. A few foreign tourists, delighted to learn they had just made it in under the wire, were allowed to set off sightseeing, still hoping for a normal vacation. Others remained unsure of their fate even as they walked out into the Israeli sun.  "We don't know what's going to happen," said Rhonda Schmidt, arriving with a Canadian church group, aware that their plans to tour the Holy Land could yet land them in two weeks of hotel-room confinement. "They might still shut us down on Thursday."  Benito Linde of Madrid looked up from his cellphone with a harried expression. He had been told one thing by a passport officer and another by his airline.  "I think I have to leave by Thursday," said Linde, a musician who had just arrived on a flight from Madrid to visit friends in Tel Aviv. "They are friends, but I don't think they want me here for two weeks."  The quarantine requirements...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to Propose Changes to Legal Shield for Tech Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/doj-to-propose-changes-to-legal-shield-for-tech-companies/ar-BB10Zse6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service faces unique challenge of protecting president from exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Secret-Service-faces-unique-challenge-of-15118700.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air Force One touched down near Orlando, Florida, on Monday, and President Donald Trump disembarked, shaking hands with local politicians on the tarmac before heading directly to a rope line where he grasped the outstretched hands of supporters.  It was a routine photo op - but one that has some former Secret Service agents flagging as unsafe and worth scaling back or ending entirely amid the threat of the highly contagious novel coronavirus.  "Forget about rope lines - it's the ultimate threat," said one former agent now serving as a private security consultant who spoke on the condition of anonymity because he was concerned about his business. He cited handshaking and airborne particles as the prime ways the illness is transmitted.  The scene on the tarmac illustrated the challenge for the elite federal agency charged with ensuring the safety of Trump, Vice President Mike Pence and other U.S. dignitaries as it assesses the unpredictable risk associated with an illness that has infected more than 100,000 people worldwide - including more than 650 confirmed cases in the United States - and killed more than 3,000. The Secret Service is expected to soon begin providing protection for former vice president Joe Biden and Sen. Bernie Sanders, I-Vt., the leading candidates for the Democratic presidential nomination.  As Trump mingled with the supporters, his protective detail, dressed in suits and earpieces, clustered tightly around him, with one holding open the door of the presidential limousine nearby in case of an attack. Yet the coronavirus presents a silent, unseen enemy, one whose dangers can be unleashed without ill intent and spread without warning.  In recent days, reports that an attendee of the Conservative Political Action Conference at National Harbor in Maryland tested positive for the virus has led to questions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Common artificial sweetener might be making you fatter and sicker...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/A-common-artificial-sweetener-might-be-making-you-15119900.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study published in the journal Cell Metabolism by a group of Yale researchers found that the consumption of the common artificial sweetener sucralose (which is found in Splenda, Zerocal, Sukrana, SucraPlus and other brands) in combination with carbohydrates can swiftly turn a healthy person into one with high blood sugar.  From whole grain English muffins to reduced-sugar ketchup, sucralose is found in thousands of baked goods, condiments, syrups and other consumer packaged goods - almost all of them containing carbs.  The finding, which researchers noted has yet to be replicated in other studies, raises new questions about the use of artificial sweeteners and their effects on weight gain and overall health.  In the Yale study, researchers took 60 healthy-weight individuals and separated them into three groups: A group that consumed a regular-size beverage containing the equivalent of two packets of sucralose sweetener, a second group that consumed a beverage sweetened with table sugar at the equivalent sweetness, and a third control group that had a beverage with the artificial sweetener as well as a carbohydrate called maltodextrin.  The molecules of maltodextrin don't bind to taste receptors in the mouth and are impossible to detect. While the sensation of the third group's beverage was identical to the Splenda-only group, only this group exhibited significant adverse health effects.  The artificial sweetener by itself seemed to be fine, the researchers discovered, but that changed when combined with a carbohydrate. Seven beverages over two weeks and the previously healthy people in this group became glucose intolerant, a metabolic condition that results in elevated blood glucose levels and puts people at an increased risk for diabetes.  The finding follows a study in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Sanders face off in 6 primaries that could finish race...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/biden-and-sanders-to-face-off-in-tuesday-in-primaries/article_f726df5e-8750-589c-9f97-adea5e143c3c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden and Bernie Sanders, the last two White House hopefuls with a realistic shot at claiming the nomination, will face off in Michigan, Mississippi, Missouri, Washington, Idaho and North</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRUGGLES TO CALM NATION</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-struggles-to-calm-nation-after-days-of-15118445.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump confronted one of the most perilous days of his presidency Monday by first erupting in a barrage of commentary that failed to calm the cratering financial markets, struggling to inspire confidence that his administration could stop the spread of the novel coronavirus.  But by the time the sun set in Washington, Trump sounded momentarily chastened by the turbulence and previewed a raft of emergency measures to shore up the economy.  "We have a very strong economy," the president told reporters, "but this blindsided the world."  Responding to days of mounting pressure from Wall Street executives and congressional allies, Trump said he plans to visit the Capitol on Tuesday to advocate for a payroll tax cut and other proposals to provide relief for hourly workers and others affected by the fallout.  Trump, who for weeks has resisted such steps, described the policies at a White House news conference as "very dramatic," before ceding the lectern to Vice President Mike Pence and top public health experts to deliver a coronavirus update.  Trump's overall handling of the converging crises - while spreading misinformation and blaming others - has unsettled many of his Republican allies on Capitol Hill and even inside the White House, where some aides acknowledged that the president is compounding problems with his grievances and conspiratorial mind-set.  The coronavirus and market meltdown present Trump with a challenge unlike any he has faced as president, and one for which he has no ready solution. At a moment when anxious citizens are turning to the government for facts and assurance, Trump is playing down risks and immersing himself in feuds with Democrats, the media and other perceived enemies.  While Pence and other top administration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTHQUAKE SHAKES</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8096163/Earthquake-rocks-Italy-amid-coronavirus-outbreak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2.6-magnitude quake, which struck around a mile north of Camaiore, was recorded by the Italian Institute of Geophysics and Volcanology at 2.17pm this afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French defend Smurf rally after outcry over virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-mayor-defends-smurf-rally-outcry-over-virus-001955753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor of a small French town on Tuesday defended hosting a record-breaking gathering of 3,500 people dressed as Smurfs at the weekend, after accusations that the event increased the risks of spreading the coronavirus. "We must not stop living... it was the chance to say that we are alive,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surging health care worker quarantines raise concerns... </title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/surging-health-care-worker-quarantines-raise-concerns-as-coronavirus-spreads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of U.S. health care workers who have been ordered to self-quarantine because of potential exposure to the new coronavirus is rising at an exponential pace. Many experts say something has…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP PHOTOS: Life in the time of coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/07b540c6c7e41c45cf72a8e650cfb268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As cases of the coronavirus increase in Italy, Iran, South Korea, the United States and elsewhere, AP photographers around the world are capturing the impact on daily life. Fear of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer, bear and everywhere: Animals move into the city...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2020/03/09/deer-bear-and-everywhere-animals-move-into-the-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley bans mass gatherings of 1,000 or more...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-10/coronavirus-economy-grand-princess-cruise-ship-oakland-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Markets plummeted, Italy took the extraordinary step of limiting personal movement for the entire country, and new cases of coronavirus crept across California and the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EL-ERIAN: Stock market bottom not in yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/10/mohamed-el-erian-market-bottom-not-in-yet-despite-bounce-off-big-drop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's going to be very volatile, but around, unfortunately, a downward trend for now," Allianz's Mohamed El-Erian told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS secretary unsure of how many Americans have been tested...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/486752-hhs-secretary-unsure-of-how-many-americans-have-been-tested-for-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Alex Azar said early Tuesday that U.S. health officials do not know how many Americans have been tested for coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest Nordic Economy Now Faces First Downturn Since '08...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/richest-nordic-economy-now-faces-142932926.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Norway risks sinking into a recession for the first time since the financial crisis of 2008, after a collapse in oil prices added to the threat of an export slump.The government of western Europe’s biggest petroleum producer, which is also the richest Nordic economy, is already looking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Iger's Sudden DISNEY Departure as CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hollywood-still-reeling-from-bob-iger-disney-departure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studio executives and Hollywood power players are still questioning the timing and suddenness of Iger's exit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUCKER: People You Probably Voted For Are Minimizing Danger...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fox-news-tucker-carlson-warns-people-you-probably-voted-for-are-minimizing-coronavirus-danger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlson's comments came after the President was dismissive of the outbreak on the same network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Mayor Switches To Joe: President 'Deranged'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/michigan-republican-mayor-who-voted-for-trump-switches-to-biden-even-more-deranged-now-than-i-thought-then/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michigan mayor and longtime Republican has decided to renounce President Donald Trump in favor of Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of corporate debt bomb grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Fears-of-corporate-debt-bomb-grow-as-coronavirus-15119381.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus panic could threaten a $10 trillion mountain of corporate debt, unleashing a cycle of layoffs and business spending cuts that would hit the economy just as some analysts are warning of a recession.  Financial markets already are showing major signs of stress. Investors are demanding higher interest payments in return for lending to less creditworthy companies; some businesses are delaying their planned bond sales while they wait for Wall Street to settle down; and ratings agencies are moving toward downgrading some corporate borrowers.  The mammoth debt bulge includes a dramatic increase in borrowing by the lowest quality investment grade firms -- those rated just one level above "junk." More than $1 trillion in "leveraged loans," a type of risky bank lending to debt-laden companies, is a second potential flash point.  Watchdogs including the Federal Reserve have warned for years that excessive borrowing by corporations, including some with subpar credit ratings, might eventually blow a hole in the U.S. economy. Now, as Wall Street wrestles with a global epidemic, the debt alarms show how investors are reassessing risks they overlooked during the long economic expansion.  "It is a big concern," said Ruchir Sharma, chief global strategist for Morgan Stanley. "We're dealing with the unknown. But given the enormous increase in leverage, the system is fragile and vulnerable."  Energy companies that have borrowed heavily in recent years may be the first to suffer, due to the oil price war between Saudi Arabia and Russia. Falling oil prices, while good news for consumers, may reach levels that will make it impossible for companies in the U.S. shale industry to cover their costs.  On Monday, investors battered some energy companies that have big outstanding obligations. Shares of Halliburton, which has more than...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS CLAW BACK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/09/dow-futures-fall-200-points-following-markets-worst-day-since-financial-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rallied on Tuesday as Wall Street clawed back some of the massive losses suffered in the previous session.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprised Staff With Vow to Detail Aid Package...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-virus-aid-package-leave-032208157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. stocks rebounded from the worst drop since the global financial crisis after President Donald Trump said he would announce “substantial” economic measures on Tuesday to combat the fallout from the coronavirus.Trump’s economic plan -- which he said could include a payroll tax cut and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein lawyers seek mercy after his 'historic' fall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9c96c04af044201538c2947c3c56161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — With prosecutors seeking a severe punishment for Harvey Weinstein in his landmark #MeToo case, his lawyers argued on Monday that he deserves mercy for his already “historic fall...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin backs amendment allowing him to remain in power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/89c16e0f87b08ed022122194feb13cda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin on Tuesday backed a proposed constitutional amendment that would allow him to seek re-election after his current term ends in 2024, ending...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Trump lose Florida because of hurricane refugees?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/mar/10/donald-trump-lose-florida-hurricane-maria-refugees-us-elections-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Puerto Ricans fleeing to Florida felt sidelined by Trump after the federal government’s insufficient response to Hurricane Maria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant piglet born with 'human face and hair'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mutant-piglet-born-human-face-21666664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A malformed piglet with a squashed "human" face and giant eyes was filmed wriggling in a man's arms several hours after its birth in Venezuela</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD Tells Students Not To Return From Spring Break...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/03/10/coronavirus-harvard-classes-online-spring-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard University told students Tuesday not to return from their upcoming spring break due to coronavirus fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITALY QUARANTINES ENTIRE COUNTRY</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-italy-idUSKBN20X11D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy woke up on to deserted streets in an unprecedented lockdown on Tuesday aft...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payments on mortgages suspended across Italy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-health-coronavirus-italy-mortgages-idUKKBN20X0XN?taid=5e6769ea05296a0001046629</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Payments on mortgages will be suspended across the whole of Italy after the coro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As recession fears mount, eyes turn to American consumer...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-03-09/as-recession-fears-mount-eyes-turn-to-the-american-consumer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As political leaders grapple with how to address the economic fallout, success may ultimately come down to one factor: the American consumer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Xi says outbreak 'basically curbed' at epicenter...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/chinas-xi-pays-first-visit-virus-epicentre-wuhan-055240815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping said Tuesday that Wuhan has turned the tide against the deadly coronavirus outbreak, as he paid his first visit to the city at the heart of the global epidemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerless Weinstein Faces Hard Time: Best Not to Fight Over TV...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/powerless-weinstein-faces-hard-time-100000715.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- On Wednesday, fallen Hollywood power broker Harvey Weinstein will learn his fate from a New York state judge who could send the 67-year-old rapist to prison for almost three decades.Here, legal experts sketch out Weinstein’s likely future.What kind of time is Weinstein looking at?The former</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEARL JAM Delays Tour: 'No Clear Message Regarding Safety'...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/03/09/coronavirus-event-cancellations-pearl-jam-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group announced its decision to reschedule its shows Monday on its website. They had been scheduled to perform at Royal Farms Arena on March 28.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS: Tentacles of Olympic cancellation would reach around globe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ac7b4fa3f336f77a61303940af4d4b7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The tentacles of canceling the Tokyo Olympics — or postponing or staging it in empty venues — would reach into every corner of the globe, much like the spreading virus that now...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands on virus-hit cruise ship await disembarkation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96e87b81f05f7ec54fc3e0ad152bd25c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — Thousands of passengers aboard a cruise ship struck by the novel coronavirus waited anxiously Tuesday for their chance to leave the vessel, even if it meant being shipped to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire bids anxious farewell to Picasso...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8b9bfbc3670b7e1f97c28ab1e27fdc99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONACO (AP) — Billionaire art collector David Nahmad can't fully recall why he bought “Nature Morte,” a charmingly simple oil on canvas that Pablo Picasso painted in 1921. Given that Nahmad...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coachella to Postpone...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/coachella-music-festival-postpone-coronavirus-964858/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music festival’s organizers are in talks to delay the festival until October, as the U.S. reports new coronavirus cases, sources tell Rolling Stone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope tells priests to go out and meet sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8095021/The-Pope-urges-priests-visit-coronavirus-sufferers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis (pictured today) prayed that clergymen would 'have the courage to go out and go to the sick people' as he celebrated Mass by himself at the Vatican this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex club orgies thrusting onwards...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/09/snctms-la-nyc-orgies-thrusting-onwards-in-face-of-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extra soap and sanitizer will be provided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS STEADY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e451508630c852f4ee9082c574ce31aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Global stock markets rebounded Tuesday from record-setting declines after President Donald Trump said he would ask Congress for a tax cut and other measures to ease the pain of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Odd' quirk raises delegate stakes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8d90a37e5e5b177d08424fd14a24ffe6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A quirk in how delegates are won under Democratic Party rules is raising the stakes for Tuesday's elections, allowing a candidate to make up ground in the race quickly — or fall...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan primary could make or break Sanders' campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5b4fa2256d232ca24b2f93fff3131e99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Bernie Sanders proved his 2016 presidential bid was serious with an upset victory in Michigan powered by his opposition to free trade and appeal among working-class voters. Four...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO KITS! Nursing home unable to test 65 workers with symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200309234801-s0bah</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-NURSINGHOME (PIX):Seattle-area nursing home unable to test 65 workers with COVID-19 symptoms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's Good For People'...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/03/09/tustin-coronavirus-sichuan-impression-restaurant-checking-temperatures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before customers are allowed to sit down for a meal at Sichuan Impression, a member of the waitstaff takes their temperature using an infrared thermometer. Anyone without a fever is then taken inside to their table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented challenges loom over 2020 elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Unprecedented-challenges-loom-over-2020-elections-15118406.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When asked what kept him up at night, Ben Wikler, who is responsible for delivering a must-win state in November as chairman of the Wisconsin Democratic Party, used to answer, "unknown unknowns." He no longer has to wonder what such a risk might look like.  Presidential campaigns, parties and state election officials are scrambling to heed health warnings while safeguarding the democratic process against a growing coronavirus epidemic whose scope is difficult to predict.  Their planning has included advising voters not to lick their mail-in ballots, relocating polling places away from senior living communities, and weighing whether to move forward with plans to bring tens of thousands of visitors from around the world to Milwaukee and Charlotte, North Carolina, for the planned Democratic and Republican summer conventions, respectively.  Former vice president Joe Biden's digital staff was envisioning options for virtual campaigning if sweeping changes were necessary. Sen. Bernie Sanders' campaign already has an elaborate streaming operation, which it said it could tap in the event that campaigning is curtailed. Both campaigns have been providing hand sanitizer at events.  Over the weekend, the AFL-CIO, the nation's largest federation of unions, canceled a presidential forum scheduled for Thursday in Orlando, where Biden and Sanders, I-Vt., the leading contenders for the Democratic nomination, had been scheduled to appear. It was the first such cancellation to have been attributed to the coronavirus's spread.  Asked about the wisdom of holding campaign events, Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, said it "really depends."  "If you want to talk about large gatherings in a place where you have community spread, I think that's a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu's self-declared victory looking less certain as his rival reaches out to unlikely coalition partners... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahus-self-declared-victory-looking-less-certain-as-his-rival-reaches-out-to-unlikely-coalition-partners/ar-BB10Xuul?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk worries SPACEX won't get to Mars before he dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/elon-musk-worries-spacex-won-e2-80-99t-get-to-mars-before-he-dies/ar-BB10XMVm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Americans over 60 should 'stock up' on supplies, avoid crowds...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/486645-cdc-americans-over-60-should-stock-up-on-supplies-avoid-crowds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older Americans, especially those with underlying health conditions, should stockpile supplies and avoid unnecessary travel, a top official at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FEELS HEAT</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-feels-heat-coronavirus-stalks-us-215617212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concern that President Donald Trump himself could be exposed to the coronavirus through contact with two Republican lawmakers loomed Monday as US stocks plummeted, feeding growing national anxiety. Trump, who flew back to Washington after a weekend golfing at his Florida resort and having dinner with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS grounds planes, CEO forgoes pay...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/qantas-grounds-planes-ceo-forgoes-pay-virus-spreads-235842434.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qantas announced Tuesday it was grounding most of its Airbus A380 fleet and its CEO would forgo his salary as the airline slashed international flights in response to the coronavirus epidemic. The Australian flag carrier and its budget offshoot Jetstar will cut international flights by nearly 25 percent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Chief Of Staff Self-Quarantines...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/03/09/trumps-new-chief-of-staff-mark-meadows-self-quarantines-possible-meeting-individual-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's new chief of staff Mark Meadows on Monday said that he will be self-quarantining after possibly meeting the individual who attended CPAC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA, MLB, NHL, MLS closing locker rooms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/34008514b51705ce53ce00b6d47ead89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The NBA, NHL, Major League Baseball and Major League Soccer are closing access to locker rooms and clubhouses to all non-essential personnel in response to the coronavirus crisis, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPAC Attendees Want to Know Who Mystery Patient Is...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cpac-attendees-want-to-know-who-the-mystery-coronavirus-patient-is</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservatives have been desperately trying to find out if they interacted with the CPAC attendee who later tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN: Homeless man sits with decaying raccoon inside MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020/03/shock-video-man-sits-with-decaying-raccoon-in-san-fran-mcdonalds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is happening in San Francisco? New video shows a man sitting with a dead, decaying raccoon inside a San Francisco McDonald's. Warning, language:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistrust, rumor and conspiracy theories hinder fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/mistrust-rumor-and-conspiracy-theories-hinder-us-virus-fight/ar-BB10Xemg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Republican goes into quarantine AFTER flying on Air Force One...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8093227/Florida-Republican-Matt-Gaetz-goes-quarantine-flying-Air-Force-One-Donald-Trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump refused to answer questions on whether he's been tested for the coronavirus after traveling with Congressman Matt Gaetz, who is voluntarily self-quarantining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUDLOW ON HOT SEAT...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coronavirus-larrykudlow-stocks-americas-worst-financial-advisor-215108082.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House economic adviser Larry Kudlow has some terrible financial advice to explain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average of 5 days for symptoms to show...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/09/it-takes-an-average-of-5-days-for-coronavirus-symptoms-to-show-new-study-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Johns Hopkins found that 97.5% of people infected with the new coronavirus will show symptoms within 12 days of catching the virus. That's in line with current CDC recommendations that call for patients to remain in isolation for 14 days after potential exposure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French minister catches after parliament visit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200309205743-rvt4v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-French minister caught coronavirus after parliament visit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Software pushed BOEING jet down before crash...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/report-software-pushed-jets-nose-times-crash-69484629</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desperate pilots of an Ethiopian Airlines Boeing 737 Max reactivated the jet's flight control software that prevents aerodynamic stalls when nothing else worked to stop their descent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Catch From Handling Cash?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-cash-handling-money-from-asia-aside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed is setting aside greenbacks from Asia for 7 to 10 days before processing them, citing coronavirus concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Cruise Ship Arrives At Port Of Oakland...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/09/coronavirus-stricken-grand-princess-golden-gate-bridge-sick-passengers-oakland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus-stricken Grand Princess made its way under the famed Golden Gate Bridge Monday, heading toward the Port of Oakland where the more than 2,000 passengers will disembark under heavy military security, undergo medical examinations and then be transported to 14-day quarantine sites at four bases across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHPOST, POLITICO, DAILY BEAST reporters quarantined...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2020/03/09/politico-reporters-who-covered-cpac-have-self-quarantined-due-to-coronavirus-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publications say they're taking measures out of an abundance of caution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Prison Labor Prepares to Dig Graves...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rikers-inmates-will-dig-graves-if-coronavirus-batters-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the city’s epidemic plan shows, prisoners are always the first in line to be sacrificed in times of crisis or plague.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA restaurant takes temperatures before serving customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article241032031.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reassures donors response is under control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/09/trump-pence-try-to-reassure-gop-donors-coronavirus-response-under-control.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's and Pence's words of assurance to donors come as the president is facing political backlash for what his critics describe as a sluggish coronavirus response from the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All travelers to Israel to be isolated...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Israeli-diagnosis-two-more-people-with-coronavirus-patients-40-and-41-620347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is an uneven epidemic at the global level, " said WHO director general Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus during a virtual press conference on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna cancels remaining Paris gigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200309-madonna-cancels-remaining-paris-gigs-over-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna cancels remaining Paris gigs over coronavirus</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
