<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>24 dying industries...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/12/18/americas-dying-industries-businesses-losing-most-workers/38693221/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall St. reviewed annual employment data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics from 2008 to 2017 to identify the fastest dying industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery delivery, with no humans drivers, underway...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/256e18799e7a4959bed312ead8a60683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. (AP) — Deliveries from an Arizona grocery store will soon be arriving with no one behind the wheel. A fully autonomous vehicle is about to pilot public roads Tuesday with no back up driver, though it will be monitored by humans in another automobile. After almost a thousand test runs with humans aboard modified Prius vehicles, deliveries will be made Tuesday in Scottsdale, Arizona, using the R1, an automobile with no steering wheel and no seats for humans. The R1, when summoned, will travel within a one-mile radius of the Fry's Food grocery store just east of the Phoenix Zoo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XI DEFENDS COMMUNISM...</title>
      <link>https://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/world/chinas-economy-open-but-party-will-remain-in-control/news-story/ab92349ebe831245f17b3316410cc5b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theaustralian.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have cookies turned off To use this website, cookies must be enabled in your browser. To enable cookies, follow the instructions for your browser below. Facebook App: Open links in External Bro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's secret detention camps...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/central-asians-cry-over-chinas-secret-detention-camps-101732645.html;_ylt=Awr9CW3WJBlcV.IA8ntXNyoA;_ylu=X3oDMTByM3V1YTVuBGNvbG8DZ3ExBHBvcwMzBHZ0aWQDBHNlYwNzcg--</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asyla Alymkulova fights back tears in her home in Kyrgyzstan as she recalls the first time she heard her husband was whisked away to one of the notorious internment camps in neighbouring China's troubled Xinjiang region. Shairbek Doolotkhan, a Chinese-born Muslim and mining executive, had told his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab refugees in sights of Berlin's crime 'clans'...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/arab-refugees-sights-berlins-crime-clans-034423567--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berlin crime gangs of Arab origin have long earned infamy with violence and brazen robberies but now, police warn, they have targeted a new generation of refugees for recruitment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians 'Standing in the Way' of Totalitarian Rule...</title>
      <link>http://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/world/2018/december/christians-standing-in-the-way-of-chinas-xi-jinpings-totalitarian-rule</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since coming to power in 2012, China's leader Xi Jinping has severely cracked down on human rights, religious freedom and freedom of expression. Christians are experiencing some of the worst persecution in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie top choice of progressives in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/bernie-sanders-top-choice-of-progressives-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The progressive wing of the Democratic Party, vying to control the 2020 presidential primaries, wants Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders — by a country mile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited farm animals coming. Will public eat?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Gene-edited-farm-animals-are-coming-Will-the-13472924.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVIS, Calif. - Three cows clomped, single-file, through a chute to line up for sonograms - ultrasound "preg checks" - to reveal if they were expecting calves next summer. "Right now. This is exciting, right this minute," animal geneticist Alison Van Eenennaam said as she waited for a tiny blob of a fetus to materialize on a laptop screen on a recent afternoon at the Beef Barn, part of the University of California at Davis's sprawling agricultural facilities for teaching and research. The cows had been implanted a month and a half earlier with embryos genetically edited to grow and look like males, regardless of their biological gender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves to ban bump stocks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6c1af80fb290472c89fb930e223505af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration moved Tuesday to officially ban bump stocks, which allow semi-automatic weapons to fire rapidly like automatic firearms, and has made them illegal to possess beginning in late March. The devices will be banned under a federal law that prohibits machine guns, according to a senior Justice Department official. Bump stocks became a focal point of the national gun control debate after they were used in October 2017 when a man opened fired from his Las Vegas hotel suite into a crowd at a country music concert below, killing 58 people and injuring hundreds more in the deadliest mass shooting in modern U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Women abused every 30 seconds on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/18/women-are-abused-every-30-seconds-on-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black women are 84 percent more likely to experience abuse than white women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal With New York Attorney General...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/18/politics/trump-foundation-dissolve/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Donald J. Trump Foundation has agreed to dissolve under judicial supervision amid an ongoing lawsuit concerning its finances, according to a document filed Tuesday in Manhattan Supreme Court by the New York state Attorney General's office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY IN DECLINE?</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/17/decline-of-tom-brady-patriots-film-breakdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady and the Patriots have lost two straight games. How much is the quarterback to blame, and is this a sign that the end is near?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Government, Immigration America's 'top problems'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/michael-w-chapman/survey-americas-no-1-problem-government-no-2-problem-immigration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled Trump Foundation agrees to dissolve...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/beta-story-container/Politics/embattled-trump-foundation-agrees-dissolve-agreement-york-ag/story?id=59884847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL FUNDING OFF TABLE</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/white-house-signals-its-backing-down-in-shutdown-dispute-will-find-other-ways-to-fund-border-wall/2018/12/18/159994dc-02d9-11e9-9122-82e98f91ee6f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Sanders: “At the end of the day we don’t want to shut down the government.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Has Third-Highest Suicide Rate...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/media-has-third-highest-suicide-rate-in-the-u-s-cdc-report-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicide rates should concern us all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President orders space command...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/military/trump-plans-to-create-us-space-command-sources-say-20181218/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is expected to sign an executive order, possibly today, creating a U.S. Space Command that will better organize and advance the military's vast operations in space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On TWITTER, Trump comes out swinging in many directions...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/On-Twitter-Trump-comes-out-swinging-in-many-13474522.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump lashed out Tuesday morning at threats from many directions, taking aim at the special counsel's Russia inquiry, the Federal Reserve, social media companies and undocumented immigrants in tweets that spanned more than two hours. Trump's Twitter tirade - which included some false and questionable claims - comes as he faces increasing peril from the investigation of special counsel Robert Mueller and remains in a standoff with Democrats in Congress over funding for his long-promised southern border wall that could prompt a partial government shutdown at midnight Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Final Act as Speaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/ryan-on-track-for-his-final-act-as-speaker-government-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such an exit by Ryan would stand in stark contrast to his predecessor, John Boehner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Space-Launch Day Fizzles as 3 of 4 Missions Scrubbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-18/big-space-launch-day-fizzles-as-three-of-four-missions-scrubbed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk to unveil underground tunnel, transport cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6d24c149b46d4a1da97e3412e60ca93e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Tech entrepreneur Elon Musk is set to unveil an underground transportation tunnel on Tuesday that could move people faster than subways. Musk also plans to show off the autonomous cars that will carry people through the test tunnel, which runs about 2 miles (3.2 kilometers) under the streets of Hawthorne, California, Musk's SpaceX headquarters. He's also planning to unveil elevators he says will bring users' own cars from street level to the tunnel. Tuesday's reveal comes almost two years to the day since Musk announced on Twitter that "traffic is driving me nuts" and he was "going to build a tunnel boring machine and just start digging."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Man-free' feminist music festival found guilty of discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6508263/Swedens-man-free-feminist-music-festival-guilty-discrimination-authorities.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The event, called Statement, was held in Gothenburg, Sweden, in August this year having been billed as 'the world's first major music festival for women, non-binary and transgender only'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Leopard decapitates 3-year-old...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/leopard-kills-decapitates-3-old-india-111014305.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The headless body of a three-year-old boy snatched from his home by a leopard in India was handed over to his parents on Tuesday, wildlife officials said. Wasim Akram was in the kitchen with his mother when the animal snuck inside, pounced on the child and took him deep into the woods, officials said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos on French highways as 'yellow vests' torch toll booths...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181218145115-px79z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PROTESTS/ROADS (PIX):Chaos on French highways as 'yellow vests' torch toll booths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos on French highways as 'yellow vests' torch toll booths...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181218144844-kadx4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE-SPACEX/LAUNCH (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-SpaceX halts U.S. satellite launch for national security mission</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebound?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/18/us-futures-on-tuesday-after-wall-street-rout-a-day-earlier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rebounded Tuesday, recovering some of the steep losses of the prior trading session that sent both the Dow and the S&amp;P 500 tumbling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Tarantino 'scares off' burglars from Hollywood home...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/quentin-tarantino-burglars-home-la-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-film-a8688351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Criminal Case May Be Crumbling, Experts Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/harvey-weinstein-criminal-case-may-be-crumbling-experts-say-1170260 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a key hearing approaches, the disgraced mogul's defense hinges on discrediting accusers with emails and preventing "prior bad act" witnesses — which helped convict Cosby — from speaking: "This is the prosecutor's worst-case scenario."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit Revote? Calls for Second Referendum Grow Louder...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/brexit-revote-calls-for-a-second-referendum-grow-louder-11545139544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two years after Britons voted to leave the European Union, the U.K.’s politicians still can’t agree on what kind of Brexit they want. Now more lawmakers are calling for a do-over, a second referendum that could potentially reverse the results of the first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN NAMED 'JESUS' SMASHES UP CHURCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/748761/jesus-church-window-luke-ripley-monk-st-patricks-roman-catholic-hayling-islands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four back-to-back satellite launches in historic space day...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/18/four-back-to-back-satellite-launches-expected-today-huge-step/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's SpaceX will send a new US spy satellite into orbit today in one of four launches expected to take place within 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police scan faces of London shoppers in controversial trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/uk/446774-facial-recognition-camera-christmas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London’s Metropolitan Police have begun testing facial recognition technology on the capital’s Christmas shoppers, in a move that was attacked by a civil liberties campaigner as an “authoritarian surveillance tool.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mysterious explosions put Phoenix on edge...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/arizona-news/new-mysterious-explosions-puts-north-phoenix-neighborhood-on-edge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More mysterious explosions are putting a north Phoenix neighborhood on edge.&amp;nbsp;FOX 10&amp;#39;s Nicole Garcia reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-Controlled Bionic Limbs...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/12/17/mind-controlled-bionic-limbs-developed-at-mit-brigham-womens-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "smart limbs" being developed at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology are possible because of the Ewing Amputation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big-screen TV rolls up like poster...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-roll-up-tv-20181218-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 65-inch TVs will retract automatically at the touch of a button like a garage door, a source told Bloomberg. They will sport organic light-emitting diode, or OLED screens that produce crisper images and fold more easily than traditional LCD, or liquid-crystal displays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear that recovered from wildfire burns killed by hunter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cinder-the-bear-wildfire-killed-by-hunter-washington-california-idaho-rich-beausoleil/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cinder the bear, whose recovery received national attention, was found shot to death with her tracking collar cut, a wildlife official said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing: Fiscal sanity...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/421737-missing-fiscal-sanity-in-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modern history shows few examples of deficits this high outside of recession, war or the immediate aftermath of either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin claims Russia's new weapons have no foreign equivalent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0647e2d000964f9f8956d05a570953cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — President Vladimir Putin says Russia's new weapons have no foreign equivalents and will help ensure the country's security for decades to come. Putin, speaking during Tuesday's meeting with the top military brass in Moscow, specifically mentioned the new Kinzhal hypersonic missile and the Avangard hypersonic glide vehicle, saying they have significantly bolstered Russia's military capability. Kinzhal has already been commissioned by the military. Russian Defense Minister Sergei Shoigu said the aircraft carrying missiles have flown 89 patrol missions this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRACLE: Girl's inoperable brain tumor disappears; Doctors can't explain it...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/12/18/miracle-texas-girls-inoperable-brain-cancer-disappears/2346822002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roxli Doss was diagnosed with a deadly brain cancer in June. Now, doctors can't find any trace of it on her MRI scans. Her family calls it a miracle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chance of recession rises to highest level of Trump presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/18/cnbc-fed-survey-chance-of-recession-rises-to-23percent.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Respondents boosted the chance of recession, reduced their support for the president's handling of the economy and lowered their outlook for economic growth and Fed rate hikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As life expectancy falls, West Virginia offers lessons...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f1915b8dafdb462986883142ed2ccac6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, W.Va. (AP) — If you want to understand why U.S. life expectancy is declining, West Virginia is a good place to start. The state is a bellwether of bad health, portending major problems years before they became severe nationally. "It seems that the worst outcomes happen here first," said Dr. Michael Brumage, a West Virginia University public health expert who formerly ran the health department in Charleston. "We're the canary in the coal mine." The drug overdose death rate for all Americans today is where West Virginia's rate was 10 years ago. The nation's suicide rate is where West Virginia's was nearly 20 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good boy! Service dog gets honorary diploma...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7d77b8be4e484c8cb456ef42173c00e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — Whenever Brittany Hawley went to class, her loyal service dog Griffin was there. If she needed her cell phone, Griffin would fetch it. Even when she assisted patients as part of an internship, Griffin was there helping out as well. So it's only fitting that when Hawley was honored for receiving her master's degree in occupational therapy from Clarkson University over the weekend, Griffin was once again at her side — with an honorary diploma of his own. "I pushed for him to graduate from Day One," Hawley said Monday. "He did everything I did."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 2,000 jailed for life since 2016 coup: Turkey state media...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181218-nearly-2000-jailed-life-2016-coup-turkey-state-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 2,000 jailed for life since 2016 coup: Turkey state media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90.5% of plastic not recycled...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/scary-stat-90-5-percent-of-plastic-is-not-recycled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The burgeoning crisis in plastic waste has won the attention of Britain's Royal Statistical Society, which chose 90.5 percent — the proportion of plastic waste that has never been recycled — as its international statistic of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man set for world's first head transplant cancels after falling in love...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/man-set-worlds-first-head-13748350</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disabled Valery Spiridonov, 33, was ready to have his neck severed by Professor Sergio Canavero - dubbed 'Dr Frankenstein' - and his head reattached to a new, healthy body</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic Space Launch Day: Bezos, Musk, GPS Satellite...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/historic-space-launch-day-includes-troubled-lockheed-satellite#gs.9mu3Pz4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Historic Space Launch Day Includes Troubled Lockheed GPS Satellite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Get Used to It America: We're No Longer No. 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/china-as-no-1-economy-to-reap-benefits-that-once-flowed-to-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get Used to It America: Weâ€™re No Longer No. 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn sentencing keystone moment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/421774-flynn-sentencing-marks-keystone-moment-in-mueller-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Flynn, President Trump’s first national security adviser who began cooperating with special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation about a year ago, will be sentenced Tuesday for lying to the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba's Ma, NBA star Yao among 110 honored by Communist Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181218-alibabas-ma-nba-star-yao-among-110-honoured-communist-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alibaba's Ma, NBA star Yao among 110 honoured by Communist Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey still lashing out...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/former-fbi-chief-lashes-trump-republicans-225706154.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI director James Comey lashed out at Donald Trump on Monday for telling "lies" and undermining the rule of law, and urged Republicans to stand up to the president. "The FBI's reputation has as taken a big hit because the president of the United States, with his acolytes,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unauthorized...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/black-list-2018-matt-drudge-kobe-bryant-evan-spiegel-best-unproduced-scripts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Black List 2018 is here -- a survey of the best screenplays that have not yet gone into production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE:  THE MOVIE?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/2018-black-list-unproduced-screenplays-drudge-richard-williams-projects-1170129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year's annual list of favorite unproduced screenplays was announced live via Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best unproduced screenplay...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/black-list-2018-evan-spiegel-matt-drudge-1203091407/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elissa Karasik’s Snapchat drama “Frat Boy Genius,” and scripts about Matt Drudge and the father of the Williams sisters are at the top of the 2018 version of the Black List. &amp;#822…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate 'Russia Report' Done By Anti-Conservative Academics...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/techwatch/corinne-weaver/2018/12/17/google-funded-liberal-study-saying-russia-aided-gop-online</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has claimed Russia’s online interference tried to aid the conservative movement and Donald Trump. There’s a big problem with that assessment. It comes from a left-wing operation that previously classified more than 11 different conservative outlets as “junk news.” And two of those authors were also involved in this report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA estimates record 46 million holiday fliers... </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/TSA-estimates-record-46-million-holiday-iers-13473492.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are hankering to be one among millions this holiday, do not bother with the shopping malls, just head to the airport, where nearly 46 million people will mix travel anxiety with Christmas anxiety and a tad of family-get-together anxiety to create a merry little stew of emotions. The projected number of people who plan to fly between Thursday and Jan. 6 is up more than 5 percent from last year. "That's an increase of about 126,000 passengers a day," said Nick Calio, CEO of the trade group Airlines for America. With a daily average of more than 2.5 million people flying, those with the very most holiday spirit may enjoy travel on Thursday, Friday and Dec. 26, which figure to be the busiest days during the holiday period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Russian influence efforts ongoing'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8890210ce2ce4256a7df6e4ab65c33d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Russia's sweeping political disinformation campaign on U.S. social media was more far-reaching than originally thought, with troll farms working to discourage black voters and "blur the lines between reality and fiction" to help elect Donald Trump in 2016, according to reports released Monday by the Senate intelligence committee. And the campaign didn't end with Trump's ascent to the White House. Troll farms are still working to stoke racial and political passions in America at a time of high political discord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burglar Breaks Into Home, Steals Dog, Christmas Presents...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcdfw.com/news/local/Burglar-Breaks-Into-Home-Steals-Dog-Christmas-Presents-502860251.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcdfw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A burglar broke into a home through a bedroom window in Dallas Friday and stole jewelry, Christmas presents and the homeowner's dog, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US sportswear traced to factory in China's internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/99016849cddb4b99a048b863b52c28cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOTAN, China (AP) — Barbed wire and hundreds of cameras ring a massive compound of more than 30 dormitories, schools, warehouses and workshops in China's far west. Dozens of armed officers and a growling Doberman stand guard outside. Behind locked gates, men and women are sewing sportswear that can end up on U.S. college campuses and sports teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOONVES DOESN'T GET A PENNY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7858ff2dc8044b139c99a20aed18c502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — CBS announced Monday that former CEO Les Moonves will not receive his $120 million severance package after the board of directors concluded he violated company policy and was uncooperative with an investigation into sexual misconduct allegations. The decision, which came after a five-month outside investigation, capped the downfall of one of television's most influential figures, the biggest entertainment powerbroker to see his career derailed amid the #MeToo movement against sexual misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreigners Dump Treasuries, Liquidate Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-17/foreigners-dump-us-treasuries-they-liquidate-record-amount-us-stocks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Thousands Of Vegas Homes Get ZERO Offers...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-16/residents-should-not-panic-thousands-las-vegas-homes-get-zero-offers-november</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Generates Humans That Look 100% Real...</title>
      <link>https://www.tomsguide.com/us/nvidia-ai-faces-generative-adversarial-network,news-28869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tomsguide.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Nvidia AI technology defies belief by creating 100% realistic synthetic humans, cats, and even cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media 'turning generation into liars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/12/18/social-media-turning-generation-children-liars-leading-headmistress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media is turning a generation of children into liars, a leading headmistress has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited farm animals coming. Will public eat?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Gene-edited-farm-animals-are-coming-Will-the-13472924.php  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVIS, Calif. - Three cows clomped, single-file, through a chute to line up for sonograms - ultrasound "preg checks" - to reveal if they were expecting calves next summer. "Right now. This is exciting, right this minute," animal geneticist Alison Van Eenennaam said as she waited for a tiny blob of a fetus to materialize on a laptop screen on a recent afternoon at the Beef Barn, part of the University of California at Davis's sprawling agricultural facilities for teaching and research. The cows had been implanted a month and a half earlier with embryos genetically edited to grow and look like males, regardless of their biological gender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Do more with less:' Mexico president defends budget cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-budget/do-more-with-less-mexico-president-defends-budget-cuts-idUSKBN1OG26C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador on Monday defended deep cuts to se...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Events that marked 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181217-events-marked-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Events that marked 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market on pace for worst December since Great Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/17/worst-start-to-december-for-the-stock-market-since-great-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two benchmark U.S. stock indexes are careening toward a historically bad December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal court says ban on nunchucks unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://13wham.com/news/state/federal-court-says-ny-ban-on-nunchucks-unconstitutional</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;13wham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) -- A federal court says New York's ban on nunchucks, the martial arts weapon made famous by Bruce Lee but prohibited in the state for decades, is unconstitutional under the Second Amendment. Judge Pamela Chen issued her ruling Friday in federal court in Brooklyn. The plaintiff, James Maloney, started his legal quest after being charged with possession of nunchucks in his home in 2000. Maloney wants to teach a form of martial art using nunchucks that he created to his sons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Under Fire For Allowing 'Anti-Semitic' Book Touting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ny-times-alice-walker-anti-semitic-book-under-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The book is an unhinged anti-Semitic conspiracy tract written by one of Britain’s most notorious anti-Semites," Yair Rosenberg says in Tablet Magazine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge barrier sent to corral plastic in ocean -- isn't trapping any...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/716ebcce87a2415c9047156ac84e2c79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A floating device sent to corral a swirling island of trash between California and Hawaii has not swept up any plastic waste — but the young innovator behind the project said Monday that a fix was in the works. Boyan Slat, 24, who launched the Pacific Ocean cleanup project, said the speed of the solar-powered barrier isn't allowing it to hold on to the plastic it catches. "Sometimes the system actually moves slightly slower than the plastic, which of course you don't want because then you have a chance of losing the plastic again," Slat said in an interview with The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIKOFF: Sensational Dossier Claims 'Likely False'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/17/michael-isikoff-steele-dossier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Sensational allegations will never be proven and are likely false'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29-year-old announces 'self-care' break before congress even begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-pol-alexandria-cortez-self-care-break-20181217-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bronx-bred democratic socialist announced Monday she’s taking some time off to take care of herself before she officially starts her new job — and she’s taking her supporters along for the ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro says civil militia grows to 1.6 million, mission to stop 'invaders'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-militia/maduro-says-venezuelas-civil-militia-grows-to-1-6-million-members-idUSKBN1OH01P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro said on Monday the country's civil mili...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAACP pushes #LogOutFACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/17/naacp-logoutfacebook-senate-report-facebook-2016-election-interference-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia tried to suppress African-American turnout in the 2016 election, the report says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller releases [redacted] Flynn FBI memo...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/17/politics/mueller-memo-michael-flynn-interview/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller has released a January 2017 FBI memo detailing the interview by agent Peter Strzok and another FBI agent with President Donald Trump's then-national security adviser, Michael Flynn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware pulls instructions from code hidden in TWITTER memes...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/17/malware-commands-code-twitter-hidden-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security researchers said they’ve found a new kind of malware that takes its instructions from code hidden in memes posted to Twitter. The malware itself is relatively underwhelming: like most primitive remote access trojans (RATs), the malware quietly infects a vulnerable computer, takes scr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey Dodges Questions About Leaking Classified Info...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/katiepavlich/2018/12/17/comey-asked-if-he-leaked-classified-info-in-his-memos-wont-say-that-he-didnt-n2537637</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commuters dumbfounded as bus passenger strips, pole dances...</title>
      <link>https://www.perthnow.com.au/news/australia/sydney-bus-stripper-puts-on-show-for-bemused-passengers-ng-b881053446z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.perthnow.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocked bus passengers in Sydney watched on as a woman stripped naked and performed a pole dance during a trip to Bondi Junction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second straight 2% plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bd739b64af9e4e6fa1653842d7f38f98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Another day of big losses knocked U.S. stocks to their lowest levels in more than a year Monday. Selling was widespread. Investors dumped high-growth technology and retail companies as well as steadier, high-dividend companies. Hospitals and health insurers slumped after a federal judge in Texas ruled that the 2010 Affordable Care Act is unconstitutional. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 507 points after a 496-point drop Friday, and all the major stock indexes fell at least 2 percent. Oil closed below $50 a barrel for the first time since October 2017. Bonds rose and their yields fell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex toys on INSTA to sow discord...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1498265/instagram-was-a-massively-important-tool-for-russian-operatives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin-sponsored influencers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Develop Way to SHRINK Objects to Nanoscale...</title>
      <link>https://www.geek.com/news/mit-researchers-can-shrink-objects-to-nanoscale-1766243/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIT researchers invented a method of shrinking objects to the nanoscale. The team can generate structures one-thousandth the volume of the original using a variety of materials, including metals, quantum dots, and DNA. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CASH COMP FOR LES</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/les-mooves-no-severance-cbc-sexual-assault-harassment-allegations-shari-redstone-1202521696/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once powerful CEO of CBS Les Moonves will not be getting a single dime of the $120 million in severance he expected after stepping down under allegations of misconduct this fall, the company’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI crafts 'perfect' Xmas jingles: 'Peaches Twinkleleaves', 'Cocoa Jollyfluff'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6504887/Listen-perfect-Christmas-song-created-AI.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Made by AI trained a neural network by inputting one hundred Christmas tunes in the form of Musical Instrument Digital Interface (MIDI) files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers find 'Farout': Most-distant object in Solar System...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/42755-farout-farthest-solar-system-object-discovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have identified a new solar system body, designated 2018 VG18 and nicknamed Farout, that is the farthest solar system object ever observed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannibal, wife, mistress jailed for serving neighbors human-flesh pastries...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/brazilian-cannibal-wife-and-mistress-who-killed-women-stuffed-flesh-into-pastries-sentenced-to-71-years-in-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian man, dubbed the “Sweeney Todd” cannibal, his wife and mistress were sentenced to 71 years in prison after they killed women and mixed their flesh into pastries that they ate and handed out to neighbors, reports said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams tops Beto, Ocasio-Cortez to be most GOOGLED politician...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/421699-googles-most-searched-politician-of-2018-is-stacey-abrams</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Georgia gubernatorial candidate Stacey Abrams was the top trending politician in searches in 2018, Google announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin calendar sales surpassing those of celebs in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/national/putin-calendar-sales-surpassing-those-of-japanese-stars-in-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current leader in 2019 calendar sales at a popular chain store in Japan is not a fresh-faced young idol, nor is it a sexy heart-throb actor. Rather, Vladimir Putin, the 66-year-old president of Russia, takes the cake in that category. That’s right, the very same exercise buff that also has claim to a fragrance in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45 states to pursue Catholic priest abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/12/17/josh-shapiro-more-horrors-coming-catholic-clergy-abuse-scandal/2329159002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pennsylvania authorities have joined with their counterparts across the U.S., helping craftÂ search warrant applications and grand jury subpoenas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER:  Most treacherous market in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/17/cramer-says-not-a-safe-stock-market-most-treacherous-market-in-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think that there's a lot of people who say, 'I got to get out. I got to get out, because everyone else is getting out,'" says the "Mad Money" host.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  AIRBNB Hebrew statement contradicts anti-Israel policy released in English...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/airbnb-suspends-ban-on-west-bank-settlement-homes-expresses-unequivocal-rejection-of-bds-movement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airbnb announced Monday it would not implement a recently announced policy to exclude homes in Israeli settlements from its listings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran tech columnist quits FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2018/12/17/veteran-tech-columnist-walt-mossberg-quits-facebook/2336828002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social network has come under fire all year for security breaches and data collection on users. Mossberg says he's "no longer comfortable" with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France to intro tax on large internet, tech firms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181217-france-tax-large-internet-tech-gafa-company-usa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France will introduce its own tax on large internet and technology companies from January 1, Finance Minister Bruno Le Maire said Monday amid difficulties in finalising a new EU-wide levy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -500</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/17/us-stock-futures-fall-slightly-in-early-trading-after-fridays-big-losses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks sank Monday as investors grew worried that the Fed's plan to raise rates could be too much for the economy and stocks to handle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest diamond in North America found: 187.7 carats...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46562131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 552-carat yellow gemstone was found in a Canadian mine and is more than two inches long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals slash an inflatable black Santa...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article223200495.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vandals slashed an inflatable black Santa Claus in a Bethany, Oregon, family’s yard, but neighbors say they’ll put up their own black Santas in solidarity with the family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking at funeral, priest criticizes teen who killed himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/maison-hullibarger-funeral-priest-don-lacuesta-criticizes-teen-who-killed-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The archdiocese released a statement saying it's sorry that an "unbearable situation was made even more difficult"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumner Redstone declared incapacitated...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-sumner-redstone-incapacitated-20181217-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media mogul Sumner Redstone is incapacitated and needs a guardian ad litem to protect his interests in a current legal case, a judge determined Monday during a hearing in a long-running court dispute about the health of the controlling shareholder of CBS and Viacom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blast smashes windows, wrecks offices at Greece TV station...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-greece-blast-skai/blast-smashes-windows-wrecks-offices-at-greeces-skai-tv-in-attack-on-democracy-idUSKBN1OG0CD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful blast smashed windows and wrecked offices at Greece's SKAI TV in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If Feds Went After WASH POST as They're Going After NATIONAL ENQUIRER?</title>
      <link>https://www.nysun.com/national/what-if-g-men-went-after-washington-post-as-they/90499/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nysun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine that a federal prosecutor had gone after The Washington Post Company back in the 1990s on the theory that the reluctance of its magazine, Newsweek, to publish an article about a sex scandal involving Bill Clinton constituted an illegal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops find 3 kids home alone after girl calls 911 for 'help watching YOUTUBE'...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/home-alone-youtube-859231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 17--An Iowa woman who left her three small children home alone late Thursday night was arrested on endangerment charges after one of the children called 911 to report that “her mom and dad le</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First private Israeli lunar mission to launch...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af0168ec78cc4144b8c1bd23327ef75a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEHUD, Israel (AP) — An Israeli nonprofit on Monday said it has pushed back the launch of what it hopes will be the first private spacecraft to land on the moon until February. Officials from SpaceIL and its project partner, the state-owned Israel Aerospace Industries, announced that the landing craft, dubbed "Beresheet," or Genesis, will ship in February to Florida. Propelled by a SpaceX Falcon rocket launch, the robotic lander will then commence its months-long voyage to the moon. It had been slated to launch this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNAL CONFRONTATION...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/12/17/google-china-censored-search-engine-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google reassigned several groups of engineers away from a planned censored search engine after a rift over its use of real internet queries in China for testing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
