<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Judge Denies Request to Delay NYC Trial After L.A. Indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/weinstein-judge-denies-request-delay-new-york-trial-la-indictment-1267523</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Burke denied the motion, arguing that the new charges are "next to meaningless" as far as Weinstein's criminal case in New York is concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE ON PELOSI...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/07/politics/nancy-pelosi-impeachment-strategy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is once again awaiting House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's next chess move as she returns to Capitol Hill on Tuesday, continuing to withhold the articles of impeachment from the US Senate while attempting to place another check on President Donald Trump to address his actions on Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australians scoop up koalas, kangaroos to save them from bushfires...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/07/australians-scoop-up-koalas-kangaroos-to-save-them-from-bushfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australians are doing their best to save local animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE THREATENS WEINSTEIN WITH JAIL FOR USING PHONE AT TRIAL</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-jail-threat-new-charges-adjournment-request-1202823277/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Events over on the West Coast and cell phones dominated the early part of the second day of Harvey Weinstein’s rape trial in New York City this morning – and almost landed the disgraced producer be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Track Repeating Radio Signal Across Space to Unexpected Origin...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/that-newly-discovered-repeating-frb-has-been-tracked-to-a-really-puzzling-origin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious repeating radio signal from space revealed last year is now the fifth fast radio burst to be tracked back to its source galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 50 killed in stampede at Iranian general's funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iraq-security/at-least-50-killed-in-stampede-at-iranian-generals-funeral-tehran-weighs-response-to-u-s-attack-idUSKBN1Z60NL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 50 people were killed in a stampede as mourners packed streets for the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin lands in Damascus on unannounced visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/putin-syria-damascus-assad-russia-a9273781.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigantic triangular craft spotted above Texas days after New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/gigantic-triangular-ufo-spotted-above-21231036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The huge object slowly moved across the night-time sky on New Year's Day and it bears a startling similarity to a so-called UFO seen above the US state of New York just days before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos of grinning 'poachers' with gorilla 'shot dead' spark outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/disturbing-photos-grinning-poachers-gorilla-21229775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The primate was “shot dead illegally” in a “crime against nature” in Brazzaville, Democratic Republic of Congo, animal rights campaigners fear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds to Hand Over Roger Stone Records to Media Outlets...</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/feds-to-hand-over-roger-stone-records-to-media-outlets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors told a judge Monday they are prepared to release sealed materials in search and seizure warrants against Roger Stone issued during the FBI probe into the Trump campaign’s ties to Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone attacks?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/07/politics/us-iran-high-alert-drone-attacks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US forces and air-defense missile batteries across the Middle East were placed on high alert overnight Monday to possibly shoot down Iranian drones as intelligence mounted about a threat of an imminent attack against US targets, two US officials tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORM OF GOVT CENSORSHIP...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2020/01/06/monopoly-is-speech-policy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In my latest Locus column, Inaction is a Form of Action, I discuss how the US government’s unwillingness to enforce its own anti-monopoly laws has resulted in the dominance of a handful of gi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER PUMP: Repo Panic Returns As Fed Injects $99 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/repo-remains-paralyzed-fed-announces-first-oversubscribed-term-repo-mid-december</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL: Worsening conditions threaten to intensify Australia blazes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/australia-fires-worsening-conditions-threaten-to-intensify-blazes-california-firefighters-join-effort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insurers report the Australian bushfires have caused nearly half a billion U.S. dollars in damage and that estimate is expected to rise. Strong gusts and sweltering heat could intensify the fires later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's stock market gamble...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/476955-president-trumps-stock-market-gamble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the 2020 presidential election campaign gets into full swing, President Trump might want to reflect on a 1929 cautionary tale involving Irving Fishe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural wonder Punta Ventana collapses... </title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/article238996843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to ban deepfakes, but new policy may not cover controversial Pelosi video...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facebook-to-ban-deepfakes-sources-say-but-new-14954730.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook plans to issue new rules as soon as Tuesday that would ban users from posting computer-generated, highly manipulated videos, known as deepfakes, seeking to stop the spread of a novel form of misinformation months before the 2020 presidential election.  But the policy - described by three people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss the yet-unannounced rules - does not ban all doctored videos. It appears, for example, that Facebook's new guidelines would not have prohibited a deceptively edited clip of House Speaker Nancy Pelosi that went viral on the social network last year.  Facebook did not immediately respond to a request for comment late Monday. The change in policy comes as a company executive prepares to testify at a congressional hearing later this week on "manipulation and deception in the digital age."  Going forward, Facebook intends to ban videos that are "edited or synthesized" by technologies such as artificial intelligence in a way that average users would not easily spot, the people said, including attempts to make the subject of a video say words that they never did.  Facebook, however, will not ban videos manipulated for the point of parody or satire. And it signaled that other lesser forms of manipulation would not be outlawed, either, though they could be fact-checked and limited in their spread on the social networking site, the people said.  The policy does not appear to cover the infamously altered "drunk" video of Pelosi that was viewed millions of times on Facebook last year. Though her speech was slowed and distorted in the video to make her sound inebriated, the effect was accomplished with relatively simple video-editing software. To contrast with more sophisticated computer-generated "deepfakes," disinformation researchers have referred to these...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 'revenge scenarios'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7860045/Iran-considering-13-revenge-scenarios-death-General-Soleimani.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ali Shamkhani, secretary of Iran's Supreme National Security Council, revealed the regime is considering 13 'revenge scenarios', expected to ramp up Tuesday as a three-day period of mourning ends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us70006vll/map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victim's Account Fuels Reckoning Over Sex With Children in France...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/01/07/a-victims-account-fuels-a-reckoning-over-sex-with-children-in-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — The French writer Gabriel Matzneff never hid the fact that he engaged in sex with girls and boys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're going to war, bro'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200107102718-0wstz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/USA-FORT BRAGG (PIX):'We're going to war, bro': Fort Bragg's 82nd Airborne deploys to the Middle East</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too old? Too slow? No! Debut marathoners may add years to life...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200106182713-v6r6l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-MARATHON/ (PIX):Too old? Too slow? No! Debut marathoners may add years to life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI seeks APPLE help unlocking phones of suspected Pensacola naval station gunman...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/fbi-seeks-apple-s-help-unlocking-phones-suspected-pensacola-naval-n1111636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phones thought to belong to the Saudi air force member accused in the deadly attack are password-protected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Island in the dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/puerto-rico-earthquake-strong-quake-knocks-out-power-island-wide-today-2020-01-07-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They were the largest in series of quakes to hit the U.S. territory in the last few days and came a day after a powerful one collapsed five houses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety over fate of American hostages...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/death-iran-general-spurs-anxiety-052022548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The killing of a top Iranian general has ratcheted up the anxiety of families of Americans held in Iran, one month after the release of a New Jersey student had given them hope. The Trump administration has made a priority of bringing home hostages held abroad, but the prospect of a resolution for the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.4 quake rocks Puerto Rico amid heavy seismic activity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e2ec8e9bd12aea8aff6b240976897389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — A 6.4-magnitude earthquake struck Puerto Rico before dawn on Tuesday, and was followed three hours later by an aftershock measuring 6.0. They are the largest in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stampede kills 32 at funeral for Iran general...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/add7a702258b4419d796aa5f48e577fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — A stampede erupted on Tuesday at a funeral procession for a top Iranian general killed in a U.S. airstrike last week, killing 32 people and injuring 190 others, Iran's state...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New drone task force investigating mysterious sightings across Colorado, Nebraska...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/drone-task-force-investigating-mysterious-sightings-colorado-nebraska/story?id=68102066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drone sightings in Colorado and Nebraska have so far been unexplained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein To Seek Delay In NYC Rape Trial After Being Charged  In L.A...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-delay-request-la-charges-1202822880/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The second official day of Harvey Weinstein’s criminal trial for rape in New York City may be the last – at for a while, if the producer gets his way. Following Weinstein being cha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE FIGHT</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/analysis-behind-boltons-decision</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former national security adviser John Bolton shook up the Trump impeachment standoff Monday with his announcement that, if subpoenaed, he is "prepared to testify" before a Senate trial. It's still not clear, of course, when or even if a trial might occur, since House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Iran Leader Wants Retaliation to Be Carried Out Directly...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/khamenei-wants-to-put-irans-stamp-on-reprisal-for-us-killing-of-top-general/ar-BBYGcIB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAKER:  High-risk gambles with much at stake...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-trump-the-burden-may-be-proving-this-is-not-the-moment-his-critics-predicted/ar-BBYDYRk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON READY</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Bolton-says-he-is-prepared-to-testify-in-Senate-14953296.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - John Bolton complicated Senate Republicans' impeachment strategy on Monday, declaring his willingness to testify and upping the pressure on Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell and his party to summon the former national security adviser as a witness in President Donald Trump's trial. Bolton last fall rebuffed House impeachment investigators' entreaties to testify about his concerns about Trump's demands that Ukraine investigate his political rivals as the administration delayed military aid. Bolton's surprise announcement changed the political calculus for McConnell's no-witness strategy and appeared to increase the likelihood of additional testimony that could embarrass the president. "Since my testimony is once again at issue, I have had to resolve the serious competing issues as best I could, based on careful consideration and study," Bolton said. "I have concluded that, if the Senate issues a subpoena for my testimony, I am prepared to testify." The announcement was a major boost for congressional Democrats, who have delayed transmission of the articles of impeachment for more than two weeks while seeking guarantees about the scope of the trial, including witnesses. Democrats have pressed for testimony from Bolton, as well as acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney and several other of the president's men. At least one Senate Republican, Mitt Romney of Utah, agreed Monday that it was imperative that Bolton testify, while Democrats insisted that Republicans' refusal to allow him to tell his story would be tantamount to a "coverup." Bolton has firsthand knowledge of internal White House deliberations, and according to testimony in the House probe, reacted angrily to Trump's pressure on Ukraine to investigate former vice president Joe Biden, now a 2020 candidate, and a debunked theory about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE BEST BET?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/476995-why-trump-should-fear-sanders-much-more-than-warren-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is conventional political wisdom that President Trump stands his best chance in 2020 if Democrats nominate a far left candidate like Bernie Sanders or Elizabeth Warren. That is half right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TOUTS ZUCKERBERG...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-zuckerberg-told-him-hes-facebooks-number-212100210.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump boasted Monday that Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg told him at dinner he is "number one" on the global social media platform. "I had dinner with Mark Zuckerberg the other day and he said 'I'd like to congratulate you... you are number one on Facebook,'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next 28 days could reset  Dem primary...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-ways-the-next-28-days-could-reset-the-democratic-primary-204525248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reminder: There are 28 days until the Iowa caucuses and 302 days until the 2020 election. Fourteen Democrats have dropped out. Exactly one year ago, Joe Biden led the field with 27.7 percent support, according to the RealClear Politics national polling average; Bernie Sanders was second with 17.3 percent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRACKS IN REPUBLICAN UNITY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fea570b6eb3da882b3f7c1618ca9c71a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate seems certain to keep President Donald Trump in office thanks to the overwhelming GOP support expected in his impeachment trial. But how that trial will proceed — and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Completely coincidental': Air Force launches 52 fighter jets in training exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/6/air-force-launches-52-fighter-jets-training-exerci/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force conducted an exercise involving the launch of 52 fighter jets from a Utah air base, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP GIVES RADIO KING EXCLUSIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.rushlimbaugh.com/daily/2020/01/06/americas-anchorman-interviews-president-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rushlimbaugh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PRESIDENT: He should have been taken out a long time ago. And we had a shot at it, and we took him out. And we're a lot safer now because of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House awaits Iranian retaliation...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/06/trump-iran-soleimani-security-095126</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the president’s first day back from his Mar-a-Lago resort, his White House team was waiting in suspense for the backlash to the U.S. killing of a top Iranian official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIMBAUGH GETS 4 MORE YEARS!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/05/media/rush-limbaugh-show-contract/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The Rush Limbaugh Show" will continue well into the new decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020:  BIG TECH BIGGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/06/google-and-facebook-hit-all-time-highs-despite-antitrust-probes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook also hit a 52-week high. The records come even as both companies face ongoing antitrust investigations by coalitions of state attorneys general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College students panic over fine print about registering for the draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/military-draft-united-states-college-students-loan-fafsa-selective-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerns over an active draft and FAFSA's role in the service even shut down the Selective Service System's website because of the sudden surge in traffic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: WE THOUGHT TRUMP WOULD BE DIFFERENT...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/06/ann-coulter-trump-different-iran-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ann Coulter bemoaned President Donald Trump's increase in escalations with Iran in a tweet Monday, saying that his supporters thought he would be &amp;quot;different.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEILLANCE EXPANDS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb29de015e3d454ca24025777a8784ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the face scanner that will check in some attendees to the cameras-everywhere array of digital products, the CES gadget show is all-in on surveillance technology — whether it calls it that or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta's police chief orders halt to all police car chases...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/atlanta-police-chief-halts-car-215513226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta&amp;#39;s police chief has ordered a halt to all police car chases after crashes that killed or injured people. Two men were killed last month in Atlanta when their car was hit by a stolen car evading police, police said. Changes might include allowing only highly trained officers to take part</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney wants it...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/477010-romney-wants-to-hear-from-john-bolton-in-impeachment-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Mitt Romney (R-Utah) said on Monday that he wants to hear from John Bolton after the former White House national security adviser offered to testify in President Trump’s impeachment trial if subpoenaed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delayed Zika effects seen in babies who appeared healthy at birth...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/delayed-zika-effects-seen-babies-appeared-healthy-birth-183215111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infants in Colombia who were exposed to the Zika virus in the womb showed motor and cognitive development delays in their first 18 months of life, despite having a normal head circumference at birth, scientists reported Monday. The Zika virus is spread by mosquitoes, and can cause pregnant mothers to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds seek answers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/58a4ee8fa66dbb2e82be31fdba479d9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT MORGAN, Colo. (AP) — Groups of drones have been spotted buzzing over rural parts of northeastern Colorado and western Nebraska for weeks, unnerving residents. Now, U.S. officials are working...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIER 1 closing 450 stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/retail/pier-1-imports-bankruptcy-layoffs-store-closures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The embattled home goods retailer is also canceling orders as it reworks its business structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B-52s Getting Ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/us-iran-soleimani-tensions-intl-01-06-20/h_722dbe977eb7b811274e4d458c5e72eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US is sending thousands of additional troops to the Middle East as tensions grow following the killing of Iran's top general. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HONEST MISTAKE'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/06/politics/us-troops-iraq/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top US general said Monday a letter suggesting the US would withdraw troops from Iraq was released by mistake and poorly worded, telling reporters "that's not what's happening."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFENSE SECRETARY: 'NO DECISION'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e384b6e3d230b63d3f69092ef53b5bd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Top Pentagon leaders said Monday that the United States has no plans to withdraw troops from Iraq, despite a draft letter from a senior military officer that appeared to suggest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workaholism Epidemic: 4 In 10 Adults 'Can't Stop'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/workaholic-epidemic-4-in-10-adults-cant-stop-working-no-matter-where-they-are/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, many modern workers just don't know when to take a break -- even if they're home and the workday, for all intents and purposes, is over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LETTER: USA TO WITHDRAW FROM IRAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7858201/US-led-military-coalition-says-WITHDRAW-Iraq-parliament-voted-troops-leave.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the U.S. military's Task Force Iraq, Brigadier General William Seely, sent a letter to the head of Iraq's joint operations command, saying the coalition is pulling up stakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another big milk producer files for bankruptcy
...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/borden-becomes-second-big-us-milk-producer-to-file-for-bankruptcy/ar-BBYEvp7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden linked to 2016 identity theft involving deceased brother...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/hunter-biden-linked-identity-theft-case-involving-deceased-brother</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly submitted court documents links Hunter Biden to a 2016 identity theft case when he was being checked into an Arizona “facility”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT GEN: Decorated Alabama QB Entering NFL Draft...</title>
      <link>https://247sports.com/college/alabama/Article/Alabama-Football-QB-Tua-Tagovailoa-declares-for-2020-NFL-Draft-141728463/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;247sports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside secretive Silicon Valley group funneling cash to Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/1/6/21046631/mind-the-gap-silicon-valley-democratic-donors-stanford</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a reason you haven’t heard of Mind the Gap: Its "raison d’être is stealth."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arlington National Cemetery on alert after 'hit list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10682307/security-ramps-up-across-major-us-cities-hotspots-strike-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US cities and tourist hotspots are on high alert after Iran threatened revenge for the US strike that killed General Qasem Soleimani. Chad Wolf, acting secretary of the US Department of Homeland Se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamaworld hates Bernie -- and has no idea how to stop him...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/obamaworld-hates-bernie-sandersand-has-no-idea-how-to-stop-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most striking response to an ascendant Sanders is the lack of one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bed Bugs Released In WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/01/05/police-investigating-after-bed-bugs-found-at-local-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Walmart in Pennsylvania is facing a bedbug infestation after someone released the parasitic insects in a men's changing room, state police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused cannibal eats testicles of his GRINDR date...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article238998043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi Consulate in Detroit to open for condolences in Soleimani death...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/01/06/condolences-qassem-soleimani-iraqi-consulate-southfield/2822725001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The consulate said it'sÂ open to people who want to offer their sympathy on Tuesday and Wednesday from 2-5 p.m.Â at the consulate building in Southfield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dentist accused of setting girl's mouth on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/lawsuit-nevada-dentist-set-5-year-old-girls-mouth-on-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parents of a 5-year-old girl say a Las Vegas dentist set their daughter's mouth on fire as she underwent a routine dental procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors Fed Up With MCDONALD'S Blasting Bagpipe Sounds To Keep Homeless Away...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/03/bagpipes-blasting-broadway-mcdonalds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People living in Midtown Sacramento are getting an earful from a nearby McDonald's that's reportedly blasting bagpipe music nonstop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEINSTEIN INDICTED IN LA</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/01/06/harvey-weinstein-indicted-in-los-angeles-on-sex-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA prosecutors are planning a Monday news conference to announce the charges at 2 p.m. New York time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will he be subpoenaed?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bolton-prepared-testify-trump-impeachment-trial-subpoenaed/story?id=68097771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's former national security adviser, John Bolton, said Monday he was willing to testify in a Senate impeachment trial if subpoenaed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Tells Defense to 'Leave the Witnesses Alone' in Public Statements...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/harvey-weinstein-trial-judge-tells-defense-to-leave-the-witnesses-alone-in-public-statements/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's going to be hard enough to get a fair and impartial jury," Judge James Burke says in courtroom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural wonder Punta Ventana collapses... </title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/article238996843.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIAL STARTS WITH FIREWORKS</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-fireworks-rosanna-arquette-rose-mcgowan-1202822314/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even before a jury has been selected, the first day of Harvey Weinstein’s criminal trial for rape saw legal and cultural explosions going off inside and outside a Manhattan courtroom this morning. …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
