<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Crystal Ball Sitting In Window Reflects Sunlight Onto Couch, Causes Major House Fire...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/crystal-ball-causes-house-fire-near-wisconsin-dells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crystal ball didn't predict a fire in Wisconsin -- but it did start one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burglar caught over bite from German's sausage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/statutes-france-germany-burglary-crime-9d1386976208e91b98913bcc2c02d97a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German police say they have solved a nine-year-old burglary after DNA found on a half-eaten piece of sausage matched that of a man detained in France over an unrelated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving Joel Silver: The Twisted Saga That Entangled Ari Emanuel, Ron Meyer, Anthony Pellicano, MBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/saving-joel-silver-the-twisted-saga-that-entangled-ari-emanuel-ron-meyer-anthony-pellicano-and-even-mohammed-bin-salman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the former power producer couldn't settle his beef with Canadian billionaire Daryl Katz, a who's who of industry players became embroiled in the feud. The question is, why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14-hour days and no bathroom breaks: AMAZON's overworked delivery drivers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/14-hour-days-no-bathroom-100050909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers report being underpaid and having to urinate in bottles in their vehicles to keep up with delivery rates An Amazon delivery driver loads a van outside of a distribution facility on 2 February 2021 in Hawthorne, California. Photograph: Patrick T Fallon/AFP/Getty Images Sign up for the Guardian Today US newsletter James Meyers worked as a driver for several Amazon delivery service providers in Austin, Texas, for about one year until he quit in October 2020 citing the immense workloads and poor working conditions. Fourteen-hour shifts were common because delivery service providers wouldn’t allow drivers to return any packages from their routes and the pressure to meet delivery rates meant Meyers used a plastic bottle to go to the bathroom on a daily basis. “I saw no effort on Amazon’s part to push delivery service providers to allow their drivers to use the restroom on a normal human basis, leading many, myself included, to urinate inside bottles for fear of slowing down our delivery rates,” Meyers said. “Any time a van is off route or stops for longer than three minutes, it notifies the delivery service provider. Amazon encourages the delivery service owners to cut down on said stops. I would personally get called by a dispatcher every time I stopped to go to the bathroom. Sitting on the phone with them made the stop take longer. It just wasn’t worth the angry looks in the morning or the worry I’d get fired.” Amazon uses contractors for delivery services, a move Meyers said makes it exceedingly difficult for workers to organize, and he said, contributes to drivers being overworked and underpaid by the delivery service providers who are paid bonuses on metrics such as route completion percentages. Amazon has been publicly opposed to unionization and organizing among their employees, most recently through an anti-union campaign launched ahead of a union election vote at a warehouse in Bessemer, Alabama, which has included anti-union captive audience meetings and sending mass texts and ads to workers encouraging them to vote against the union. The Teamsters Union is now working to organize drivers at Amazon delivery service providers around the US over concerns about the retail giant’s impact on the transportation industry and use of subcontractors. An Amazon delivery driver pushes a cart of groceries to load into a vehicle outside of a distribution facility on 2 February 2021 in Redondo Beach, California Photograph: Patrick T Fallon/AFP/Getty Images “This sort of model is problematic for the entire industry,” said Randy Korgan, the director of the Teamster’s Amazon Project. “They’re willing to loan these small subcontractors money, get them access to their vans and help them advertise for employees to offload all the responsibility that would normally fall on Amazon.” The Teamsters currently represent pilots at two Amazon air transport contractors. Korgan said the wages Amazon delivery drivers receive, starting at $15 an hour, are far below the average wages for drivers at companies like UPS, where Teamsters represent about 240,000 workers. Based on the union’s current contract, UPS drivers start at $21 an hour and can make up to $40 an hour or more. “If Amazon decides to take millions of jobs and essentially cut their labor costs in half, that only comes out of workers’ pockets,” added Korgan. “That creates a major economic problem in an industry that for the last 50 years has done a good job of supporting millions of middle-class jobs.” In Iowa, the Des Moines Register reported the Teamsters are organizing drivers and warehouse workers at Amazon for higher pay and less stringent rates, utilizing strikes rather than focusing on union elections through the National Labor Relations Board. Drivers for Amazon contractors have complained of the surveillance and pressure they receive through cameras and a tracking app, Mentor. A driver for an Amazon delivery service provider in the Portland, Oregon area, who requested to remain anonymous for fear of retaliation, expressed concerns over the surveillance cameras being installed in delivery vehicles, as she often has to use the bathroom in the van due to the lack of available public restrooms and pressure against taking time off of routes to use them. “In order to take a bathroom break, especially being a woman, we would have to be in an area that has a grocery store. That isn’t always the case and even if it were, that would take at least 10 minutes off our drive time, in which our dispatch would wonder why we’re falling behind,” she said. “So instead, I keep a cup with me and wipes and I go to the bathroom in the back of my van. I’m very concerned about the AI technology being installed in the vans, and being seen while I am urinating is just one of my concerns.” Drivers for Amazon delivery service providers also face fear of retaliation for trying to organize in their workplaces. Derrick Flournoy worked as a driver for an Amazon Delivery Service Provider in Downers Grove, Illinois, for more than one year before he quit after experiencing retaliation from management for organizing an online chat for workers to discuss grievances on the job such as the lack of pay increases. Jeff Bezos and Elon Musk have gone back and forth every week about who is the wealthiest person in the world and I can’t even pay my rent Derrick Flournoy “I started the chat group on a Friday morning, and about an hour after the chat group was put up the manager took it down, which we didn’t even know that he had the power to do if he wasn’t included in the chat, and then he also disabled my ability within the entire app to even communicate with anybody, unless it was directly with management,” said Flournoy, who filed an unfair labor practice charge through the Amazon Delivery Drivers Coalition against Amazon after he was removed from his work shift immediately after the incident. “To me, it was obvious retaliation, and it was his way of showing that he had power and if we didn’t basically form a model of who he wanted, that he could take our hours.” Flournoy made $16 an hour, which remained unchanged from when he started in December 2019 to when he left in February 2021, even as a 40-hour full-time work week wasn’t guaranteed. “Sixteen dollars an hour isn’t enough for the amount of work that we have to do. We’re a representation of the wealthiest company in the world and we’re barely making enough money to live,” Flournoy added. “I just think that it’s crazy to me that Jeff Bezos and Elon Musk have gone back and forth every week about who is the wealthiest person in the world and I can’t even pay my rent. I’m breaking my back to deliver packages every day and there’s no compassion from upper management to understand or to listen to drivers’ concerns.” An Amazon spokesperson claimed drivers have built-in time through their routes for breaks and provide a list of nearby restrooms in the delivery app. They did not comment on the unfair labor practice charge or on organizing efforts by drivers. “We’re proud to empower more than 2,000 delivery service partners around the country – small businesses that create thousands more jobs and offer a great work environment with pay of at least $15/hour, healthcare benefits, and paid time off,” the spokesperson said in an email.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Keeping Vaccines Secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2021/03/covid-vaccine-secrecy/618253/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 vaccinations have become a public spectacle, but they touch intensely private questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince William defends royal family against racism claims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-prince-harry-london-oprah-winfrey-prince-william-52698fca3307c802d7d8f6a4be60a074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Prince William defended Britain's monarchy Thursday against accusations of bigotry made by his brother, Prince Harry, and sister-in-law, Meghan, insisting the family is not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious shaking again rattles San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2021-03-10/mysterious-shaking-again-rattles-san-diego-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents from Rancho Bernardo to Chula Vista to El Cajon reported feeling and hearing a shaking and boom in an event similar to one from Feb. 16</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PREPS VICTORY LAP</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-prepares-nationwide-victory-lap-to-promote-his-rescue-plan/ar-BB1etfVS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden got his giant coronavirus stimulus bill. Now, he wants to make sure he gets credit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans leaving home more than before pandemic, cellphone data shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Americans-have-started-leaving-home-even-more-16017279.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have begun leaving home more often than before the coronavirus pandemic took...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will coronavirus ever go away?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-98ae7fbfdc457425dae47efb38139db2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Will the coronavirus ever go away? No one knows for sure. Scientists think the virus that causes COVID-19 may be with us for decades or longer, but that doesn’t mean it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO still struggling to manage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-pandemics-geneva-coronavirus-pandemic-china-2c173926c95ed3769107c7eaa043fa86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — When the World Health Organization declared the coronavirus a pandemic one year ago Thursday, it did so only after weeks of resisting the term and maintaining that the highly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals buckle in absence of plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brazil-rio-de-janeiro-health-coronavirus-pandemic-jair-bolsonaro-04931a387c7fb128266235635a1422a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Brazil’s hospitals are faltering as a highly contagious coronavirus variant tears through the country, the president insists on unproven treatments and the only attempt to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're going to lose fast': Air Force war game with Chinese biological attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/were-going-to-lose-fast-us-air-force-held-a-war-game-that-started-with-a-chinese-biological-attack-170003936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many foreign affairs and national security experts believe the global pandemic has accelerated trends that were already pushing the U.S. and China toward a potential confrontation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden seeks his moment with pandemic address...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/542648-biden-seeks-his-moment-with-pandemic-address</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is being urged to combine his well-known empathy with some positivity Thursday night when he makes a primetime address on the anniversary of when much of the country went into lockdown because of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron urged to rethink 'private' vaccine stance...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/lebron-urged-rethink-private-vaccine-204653996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James has been urged to reconsider his refusal to confirm whether or not he will take the Covid-19 vaccine after comments which underscored apprehension amongst NBA players over the new coronavirus drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil posts new record of 2,000 deaths in day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-covid-deaths-top-2-213419542.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil registered a record 2,286 deaths from Covid-19 in the past 24 hours, the health ministry said Wednesday, as a worrying surge pushed the figure past 2,000 for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula blasts 'imbecile' Bolsonaro for mishandling pandemic, economy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210310205605-pf6um</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/LULA (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Brazil's Lula, Bolsonaro fire starting gun on 2022 presidential race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of websites offline after fire at French cloud services firm...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210310183756-alpef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-OVH/FIRE (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Millions of websites offline after fire at French cloud services firm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffett Becomes Sixth Member of $100 Billion Club...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-becomes-sixth-member-214145924.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Warren Buffett has been a fixture at the top of the world’s wealth rankings for decades, but in recent years he’s slipped down the list as tech fortunes soared and his hot hand cooled.Now, at 90, his net worth has blown past $100 billion.The Berkshire Hathaway Inc. chairman’s wealth jumped on Wednesday to $100.4 billion, according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, making Buffett the sixth member of the $100 billion club, a group that includes Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk and his friend Bill Gates.The group’s combined wealth has grown rapidly, fueled by government stimulus, central bank policy and the surging equity market. On Wednesday, President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion Covid-19 relief bill cleared its final congressional hurdle as the House voted to approve the legislation, adding to the $3 trillion or so in stimulus Washington has already disbursed in the past year.Berkshire Hathaway, the source of virtually all of Buffett’s wealth, has had a good start to 2021. The firm’s A shares are up 15% this year, outpacing the 3.8% gain of the S&amp;P 500 Index. That’s been helped by Buffett’s recent push to spend record amounts buying back Berkshire’s own stock, a notable shift for an investor who previously preferred to use the $138 billion cash pile to buy other businesses or common stocks.Share BuybacksBuffett’s been struggling in recent years to find sizable deals to spark Berkshire’s growth, partially due to the sheer size of the conglomerate. That’s caused the business to underperform the S&amp;P 500 over the past five years. But last year, Buffett spent a record $24.7 billion on buybacks and filings indicate he’s already bought at least $4.2 billion worth of stock through mid-February.Read more: Berkshire’s Busy 2020 Broke a Record Despite No Major Deals Surpassing $100 billion is all the more notable considering how much the Omaha billionaire has given away. A co-founder of the Giving Pledge, a campaign to encourage billionaire philanthropy, Buffett has donated more than $37 billion in Berkshire stock since 2006. Without those gifts, which have cut his holdings of Berkshire Class A shares nearly in half, he’d be worth more than $192 billion.The staggering amount of wealth accumulated by the ultra-wealthy -- $1.8 trillion by the world’s 500 richest in 2020 alone -- highlights the K-shaped recovery that’s taking shape as the U.S. emerges from the pandemic. While millions of disproportionately poor, working-class and minority people remain unemployed, wealthy Americans have seen incomes and net worth levels rise thanks to a buoyant stock market and rising home prices.Meanwhile more than 8 million Americans -- including many children -- fell into poverty in the second half of last year, according to an analysis by University of Chicago economist Bruce Meyer, University of Notre Dame’s James Sullivan and Zhejiang University’s Jeehoon Han.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marks end to four decades of Reaganism?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/mar/10/joe-biden-covid-relief-bill-passed-analysis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: Reagan’s presidency undermined faith in government. The stimulus package helps restore FDR’s legacy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive camera hack exposes growing reach and intimacy of surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Massive-camera-hack-exposes-the-growing-reach-and-16016067.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one video, a woman in a hospital room watches over someone sleeping in an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entertainers discuss disbelief and despair that took over when covid shut down their world...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/entertainment/article/Entertainers-discuss-disbelief-and-despair-that-16015711.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe you were at the Metropolitan Opera House in New York, taking in a matinee of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT criticizes Tucker Carlson for attacking journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/new-york-times-issues-rare-statement-slamming-tucker-carlson-for-calculated-and-cruel-criticism-of-taylor-lorenz/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times responded Wednesday to Fox News host Tucker Carlson's comments about one of its reporters, Taylor Lorenz, who had issued a plea to support women facing online harassment late Tuesday, in connection with International Women's Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARLER denied by App Store again...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/parler-blocked-apples-app-store-211138243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Parler, the controversial conservative social media app, was denied re-entry to Apple Inc.’s App Store recently after it was kicked off the platform in the wake of the Jan. 6 Capitol riot, documents obtained by Bloomberg show.On Wednesday, Parler LLC cut its three remaining iOS developers, according to a person familiar with the matter. The company eliminated seven workers in total, most of whom were contractors. The other staff worked on Parler TV and quality assurance, said the person, who asked not to be identified discussing private matters.When it initially removed Parler from the App Store in January, Apple asked the social network to change its moderation practices. Apple said that Parler’s new community guidelines, released when the service came back online Feb. 15, were insufficient to comply with the App Store rules.“After having reviewed the new information, we do not believe these changes are sufficient to comply with App Store Review guidelines” Apple wrote to Parler’s chief policy officer on Feb. 25. “There is no place for hateful, racist, discriminatory content on the App Store.”Apple included several screenshots to support the rejection. Some screenshots, reviewed by Bloomberg, show user profile pictures with swastikas and other white nationalist imagery, and user names and posts that are misogynistic, homophobic and racist.“As you know, developers are required to implement robust moderation capabilities to proactively identify, prevent and filter this objectionable content to protect the health and safety of users,” Apple added in its letter to Parler, a copy of which was obtained by Bloomberg.“In fact, simple searches reveal highly objectionable content, including easily identified offensive uses of derogatory terms regarding race, religion and sexual orientation, as well as Nazi symbols,” Apple wrote “For these reasons your app cannot be returned to the App Store for distribution until it complies with the guidelines.”Parler’s community guidelines were written by Chief Policy Officer Amy Peikoff, according to two people familiar with the matter. Parler did not immediately respond to a request for comment on Wednesday.Read more: Parler Reboot Is Driven by Ayn Rand Devotee and Never TrumperParler went offline following the riot at the U.S. Capitol. Amazon Web Services cut ties with Parler, and Google and Apple removed Parler from their mobile app stores. The Parler website relaunched in February with support from cloud hosting company SkySilk Inc.(Updates with description of screenshots in fifth paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megayacht-Racing Billionaires Invading NZ in Guise of 'Essential Workers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-megayacht-racing-billionaires-invading-new-zealand-in-the-guise-of-essential-workers/ar-BB1esCrj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In case you weren’t aware, a select club of billionaires from around the world—with their superyachts in tow—have descended upon Waitematā Harbour in Auckland, New Zealand to resume one of their favorite activities: watching a bunch of guys race big, fast boats back and forth across an invisible line. It’s a bit like NASCAR for rich people. These billionaire owners were lucky enough to receive special “essential service worker exemptions” to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia China moon base plan sparks fears of space race...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/russia-chinas-joint-moon-base-23668748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Russia China moon-pact 'could lead to all kinds of security threats' with British and American forces playing catch up by boosting military forces capable of fighting battles against future enemies in space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record taxes, record spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/trifecta-federal-taxes-spending-and-deficit-all-set-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal taxes, federal spending and the federal deficit all set records in the first five months of fiscal 2021 (October through February), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement released today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geraldo Considering Ohio Senate Run...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-geraldo-rivera-says-hes-considering-a-senate-run-in-ohio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would Geraldo Rivera run for Senate?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican leader fears 'Migrant President' Biden will spark boom time for cartels...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9347257/Migrant-president-Joe-Biden-stirs-angst-boom-time-gangs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's government is worried the new U.S. administration's asylum policies are stoking illegal immigration and creating business for organized crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run for TX gov now 'real consideration,' Matthew McConaughey says...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/politics/run-for-tx-gov-a-real-consideration-mcconaughey-says/10403383/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The star actor and proud Texan didn't give a hard no late last year, but that was before criticism with current lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ man who disappeared during Jan. storm found dead under pile of melting snow...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/nj-man-missing-dead-snow-storm-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey man who went missing during a major snowstorm in January has been found dead under a pile of melting snow, authorities said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  Nursing home residents can get hugs again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-coronavirus-pandemic-medicaid-nursing-homes-medicare-6095d595d51ff44e86f17300858c9516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nursing home residents vaccinated against COVID-19 can get hugs again from their loved ones, and indoor visits may be allowed for all residents, the government said Wednesday in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record $1.05 trillion -- after 5 months...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-financial-markets-financial-crisis-coronavirus-pandemic-fbfc9afd97ec48a8f7a7db43c10d278d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. government's budget deficit through February hit an all-time high of $l.05 trillion for the first five months of this budget year, as spending to deal with the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St A-Listers Fled to Sunshine State. Many Now Eye Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/wall-street-a-listers-fled-to-florida-many-now-eye-a-return/ar-BB1erwTQ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “Upper East Side” cocktail at Sant Ambroeus is just the same as in Manhattan, the carpaccio at Cipriani as meaty red as on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College offers students $75 to stay put for spring break...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/nationworld/uc-davis-offers-students-75-gift-cards-to-stay-put-for-spring-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No caravans of college students in Miami or beach parties in Malibu during a pandemic, please. UC Davis is offering a sure-fire incentive to keep students from traveling during spring break an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Drove Dealer Loaner To Rob Bank -- Then Tried Using Loot To Buy BMW...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/texas-man-rob-bank-dealership-loaner-loot-buy-bmw/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors said he drove a vehicle loaned to him by a car dealership to rob a bank in Texas and brought the money back to try and use for a down payment on a BMW, now Eric Dion Warren is headed to prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust in US military tanks...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2021/03/10/trust-in-the-military-is-dropping-significantly-new-survey-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 56 percent of Americans said they have great trust in the military, down significantly in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O Opens Up About Her Depression...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/michelle-obama-gets-real-about-her-covid-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former First Lady Michelle Obama is back to her eat-your-vegetables roots, starring in the new Netflix children’s series Waffles + Mochi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB RANGERS to be first team back to full capacity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mlb-baseball-coronavirus-pandemic-greg-abbott-texas-rangers-dcd4d8bf0c62904f8c392522304b1bf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARLINGTON, Texas (AP) — The Texas Rangers could have a full house for their home opener next month after debuting their new 40,518-seat stadium without fans in the stands for their games last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sober living rising in popularity...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2021/03/10/sobriety-alcohol-free-lifestyle-chrissy-teigen-more/4635330001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the start of the pandemic, a grip on a wine glass felt like a grip on life. But recent evidence conveys sobriety is far from getting a last call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter acquitted in case seen as attack on press rights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-iowa-freedom-of-the-press-iowa-city-cd95fea66c260ec7990a2ccda06a6ca7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — An Iowa jury on Wednesday acquitted a journalist who was pepper-sprayed and arrested by police while covering a protest in a case that critics have derided as an attack on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Songbirds dying across Bay Area. Bird feeders might be why...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/local/article/Songbirds-dying-Bay-Area-pine-siskin-CDFW-16012798.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local bird rescue centers have been “inundated with calls” from residents who have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girl admits to lying after her story led to teacher being beheaded on street...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/europe/girl-admits-to-lying-after-her-story-led-to-teacher-being-beheaded-on-the-street/news-story/7f5b1d4dc03ec88fdc09c885f36f640b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French schoolgirl has admitted to making up a story about her teacher that resulted in him being beheaded on the street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beth Moore, Prominent Evangelical, Splits With Southern Baptists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/beth-moore-a-prominent-evangelical-splits-with-southern-baptists/ar-BB1esaW1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most prominent Southern Baptists in the country is leaving the denomination. Beth Moore, an author and speaker who teaches on biblical topics to arenas filled with evangelicals, cited the “staggering” disorientation of seeing denominational leaders support Donald J. Trump, among other issues. “There comes a time when you have to say, this is not who I am,” Ms. Moore told Religion News Service in a bombshell interview published...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI database stores info on 3 billion people...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/suit-company-built-most-dangerous-facial-recognition-ai-database-in-nation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit said Clearview AI scrapes dozens of internet sites, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google and Venmo, to gather facial photos. Scraping involves the use of computer programs to automatically scan and copy data, which the lawsuit says is analyzed by Clearview AI to identify individual biometrics such as eye shape and size that are then put into a “faceprint” database that clients can use to ID people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN broadcaster crushed by falling wall in scary accident...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/10/espn-broadcaster-crushed-by-falling-wall-in-scary-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not all sets are created equal. That was evident Tuesday night in Colombia, as an entire wall came crashing down on journalist Carlos Orduz during the soccer show “ESPNFC Radio.” In the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula blasts 'imbecile' Bolsonaro for mishandling pandemic, economy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210310153711-e9hd0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/LULA (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Lula blasts 'imbecile' Bolsonaro for mishandling pandemic, economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKE THAT, JACK!  PUTIN THREAT TO CANCEL TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210310110716-835op</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-TWITTER/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Russia moves to slow Twitter's speed after protest row, threatens total block</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Towns of Fukushima Remain Empty After Decade-Long Rebuild...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ghost-towns-of-fukushima-remain-empty-after-decade-long-rebuild/ar-BB1esjQo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laid waste by a nuclear disaster a decade ago, Japan’s Fukushima is still struggling to recover, even as the government tries to bring people and jobs back to former ghost towns by pouring in billions of dollars to decontaminate and rebuild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activist Milo Yiannopoulos now 'Ex-Gay,' consecrating life to St. Joseph...</title>
      <link>https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/activist-milo-yiannopoulos-is-now-ex-gay-consecrating-his-life-to-st-joseph</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifesitenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Secular attempts at recovery from sin are either temporary or completely ineffective. Salvation can only be achieved through devotion to Christ and the works of the Holy, Catholic and Apostolic Church.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver could see one of biggest snowstorms since 1885! Developing....</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/denver-could-get-one-of-biggest-snowstorms-since-1885/912929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only three times in recorded history has the Mile High City measured more than 24 inches of snow from one storm. That could change when a long-duration winter storm pummels the city and surrounding area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NET NIGHTMARE:  At least 10 hacking groups using MICROSOFT software flaw...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210310152040-foj30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CYBER/MICROSOFT (PIX):At least 10 hacking groups using Microsoft software flaw -researchers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  LA Mansion Once Set for $500 Million Price Tag Is in Default...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/la-mansion-once-set-500-161500243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A massive Los Angeles hilltop mansion with an asking price once touted at $500 million now faces a notice of default.An $82.5 million loan for “The One,” a 100,000-square-foot (9,300-square-meter) home built by developer and film producer Nile Niami, is delinquent, according to Don Hankey, who advanced the money in 2018 and filed the default notice.The debt on the property, which has yet to go on the market, has climbed to $110 million, with unpaid interest, he said.“Not only myself, but other people he owes money are trying to force him to list the property,” Hankey, a Los Angeles financier whose biggest source of lending is subprime auto loans, said in an interview.Niami didn’t respond to email messages seeking comment on the default, which was reported earlier by the Los Angeles Times.In the worst case for Niami the lender can foreclose and repossess the property. The developer started construction on the project in 2013, part of a wave of speculative Los Angeles mansions built by developers with lofty price expectations that have often proved unrealistic.Last year, his Opus -- a 20,000 square-foot seven-bedroom, 11-bath mansion in Beverly Hills -- sold for $52 million, down from an initial $100 million asking price.The ultra high-end real estate market in Los Angeles had a strong 2020 despite the pandemic. Amazon.com Inc. Founder Jeff Bezos paid $165 million, a California record, for a Beverly Hills estate from entertainment mogul David Geffen.The billionaire co-founder of WhatsApp, Jan Koum, paid $125 million for a Beverly Hills mansion sold by Jeffrey Katzenberg, another entertainment mogul.Overall, sales of luxury homes in Los Angeles thrived as homebuyers sought more space while taking advantage of record-low interest rates. The median price of a luxury Los Angeles home -- the top 10% of the market -- climbed 11.6% in the fourth quarter from a year earlier to $10.7 million, according to a report by appraiser Miller Samuel Inc.Niami’s plan was to list The One for about $340 million in January, with the Williams &amp; Williams Estates Group serving as the agents, according to Hankey. A spokesman for the brokerage declined to comment.Niami is waiting for the market to improve before listing it for sale, according to Hankey, who said the developer’s plans “didn’t make a lot of sense.” He said the property is complete and ready for showings.“The furniture’s in,” Hankey said. “Water’s in the swimming pool.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MESS IN MAUI:  Hawaii declares state of emergency after historic flooding...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2485917/hawaii-floods-state-emergency-oahu-maui-tourists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAWAII floods have triggered a state of emergency and evacuations as homes in Oahu and Maui are destroyed and tourists are advised to “stay inside.” Hawaii’s governor David Ige de…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal family contests Harry and Meghan's racism claims...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/royal-family-contests-harry-meghans-112930982.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's royal family has begun a fight back against racism claims made by Prince Harry and his wife Meghan, indicating the couple's comments will not go unchallenged as the country divides into partisan camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Son witnessed rape of mother, 83, via webcam in assisted living facility...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/minnesota-assault-834026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 10--An employee of an assisted living facility in Minnesota has been charged with sexually assaulting an 83-year-old Alzheimer's patient, an attack that was witnessed remotely by the victim’s so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to deploy long-range missiles in Asia...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/mar/9/Adm-Philip-Davidson-US-deploy-missiles-deter-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military plans to deploy long-range missiles in Asia capable of threatening China as part of efforts to deter a conflict with Beijing, the commander of American military forces in the Pacific said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Alexa could monitor your heart beat 'using invisible sound waves'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2484804/smart-speaker-heartbeat-monitor-amazon-alexa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOUR smart speaker could one day monitor your heartbeat as you go about your daily business at home. US scientists have been working on a smart speaker system that could give your Amazon Alexa or G…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She brought diverse skin tones emoji to the iPhone. Now she's suing APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/She-brought-diverse-skin-tones-emoji-to-the-16014283.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Katrina Parrott, being invited to present her idea to Apple at its campus in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with assault for BLOWING on activists at Trump Club settles case...</title>
      <link>https://www.loudountimes.com/news/sterling-man-charged-with-assaulting-protesters-at-trump-golf-club-donates-3k-to-naacp-scholarship/article_c99061da-73a9-11eb-9d70-2f3baa928fbf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.loudountimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Sterling man charged with assault for blowing on two activists in November outside Trump National Golf Club in Sterling is settling his case by donating $3,000 to the NAACP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Hollywood Require Vaccinations for Workers?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/will-hollywood-require-covid-19-vaccinations-for-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKE THAT, JACK!  Russia says it's slowing down TWITTER to protect citizens from illegal content...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/10/russia-slows-down-twitter-to-protect-citizens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has announced that it plans to throttle speeds on social media platform Twitter for failing to remove illegal content from its platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans can still be arrested for violating business mask rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/09/police-chief-texans-can-be-arrested-for-violating-business-mask-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If a business asks an individual to wear the mask and they refuse to leave, they can be arrested for criminal trespass," Houston Police Chief Art Acevedo said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French theatres occupied as protesters demand reopening...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-theatres-occupied-protesters-demand-101411823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French protesters were occupying three of the country's leading theatres on Wednesday as frustration grew over the months-long halt to cultural activities imposed due to the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Begs California Not To Kick Him Out As Recall Looms...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/gavin-newsom-recall-covid-vaccines-state-of-the-state-speech-kevin-faulconer-1234710995/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing an almost certain recall and harsh criticism over his handling of the coronavirus pandemic and vaccination rollout, California Gov. Gavin Newsom was in full campaign mode tonight in his thir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to restrict aid to Central American governments, set new conditions for money...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/biden-to-restrict-us-aid-to-central-american-governments-set-new-conditions-for-money/article_9d1aa0d7-9ee0-5933-8747-17839c3c3c37.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Weeks after earmarking $4 billion in U.S. aid for Central America, the Biden administration is fine-tuning its plans and sharply limiting how much money will go directly to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU debating declaration of LBGT 'freedom zone'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/542506-eu-debating-declaration-of-lbgt-freedom-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Parliament on Wednesday is set to debate a resolution that would declare the European Union’s 27 member countries a “freedom zone” for LGBTQ people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body Of NJ Man Missing Since January Found Under Melting Mound Of Snow...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/andrew-fraioli-wyckoff-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-year-old Andrew Fraioli was last seen leaving his parents' Wyckoff home during the snow storm on Jan. 31.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals 'close to collapse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-56342303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts fear Brazil's variants may slow down pandemic recovery, as intensive care units there fill up.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
