<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan financer jumps death from skyscraper...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9519477/Manhattan-financer-59-jumps-death-skyscraper-weeks-firm-liquidated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charles de Vaulx, 59, was the chairman and chief investment officer of International Value Advisers when he allegedly took his own life on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy SEALs to shift from counterterrorism to global threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-osama-bin-laden-china-russia-government-and-politics-8f277ce1a284b227afcdcffabfb51ffc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Ten years after they found and killed Osama bin Laden, U.S. Navy SEALs are undergoing a major transition to improve leadership and expand their commando capabilities to better battle threats from global powers like China and Russia. The new plan cuts the number of SEAL platoons by as much as 30% and increases their size to make the teams more lethal and able to counter sophisticated maritime and undersea adversaries. And there will be a new, intensive screening process for the Navy's elite warriors, to get higher-quality leaders after scandals that rocked the force and involved charges of murder, sexual assault and drug use. Rear Adm. Hugh Howard, top commander for the SEALs, laid out his plans in an exclusive interview with The Associated Press. He said the Navy’s special operations forces have been focused on counterterrorism operations but now must begin to evolve beyond those missions. For the past two decades, many have been fighting in the deserts of Iraq and mountains of Afghanistan. Now they are focused on going back to sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hamburglar? How a story about meat limits fell apart...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-new-york-climate-climate-change-media-529b0cb6d7393c225c8b9baf040c1904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Joe Biden spent only a weekend as the “Hamburglar” in the conservative media world. But while the false story lasted, it moved with a damaging speed and breadth, another example of a closed ecosystem of information affecting public opinion. An academic study published a year before Biden became president was used to speculate that he would place limits on how much red meat Americans can consume as part of his stated goal to sharply reduce greenhouse gas pollution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil begins parliamentary inquiry into Bolsonaro's Covid response ...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/27/brazil-begins-parliamentary-inquiry-into-bolsonaros-covid-response</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opponents hope investigation will torpedo chances of re-election for far-right president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media algorithms threaten democracy, researchers tell senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/04/27/social-media-algorithms-threaten-democracy-experts-tell-senators/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Google, Twitter go up against researchers who say algorithms pose existential threats to individual thought, and democracy itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your tech devices want to read your brain. What could go wrong?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/your-tech-devices-want-to-read-your-brain-what-could-go-wrong/ar-BB1g7b0x?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neurable, NextMind, Facebook and other tech firms are working to develop computer devices that you control with your thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing warnings ...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beijing-responds-u-alliances-wolf-120050699.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing's rejection of criticism from America and its friends has grown shriller as the Biden administration demonstrates its ability to pull allies together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chewbacca street performer wanted in New Orleans stabbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wwltv.com/article/news/crime/wanted-chewbacca-street-performer-suspected-in-french-quarter-stabbing/289-70f7ba0a-87ff-4087-8a7a-7e24c676fb48</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wwltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the street performer got into an argument and then stabbed the victim before fleeing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN SET TO PITCH TRILLIONS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210427215442-79gip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/SPEECH (PIX, GRAPHICS):After somber tone in first 100 days, Biden plans to try to sell spending to U.S. public</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPITOL ON HIGH ALERT FOR FIRST ADDRESS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210427085342-jsh12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/CAPITOL-SECURITY (PIX):Shaken U.S. Capitol on high alert for Biden's first address to Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's stolen-election talk keeps backers locked up...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/27/trump-rhetoric-capitol-rioters-legal-fight-484787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judges are citing former President Donald Trump’s rhetoric on election fraud as they deny some accused Capitol rioters bail, saying there’s a risk they’ll commit violent acts in Trump’s name again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did the covid outbreak in India get so bad?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-did-the-covid-19-outbreak-in-india-get-so-bad/ar-BB1g6Ok8?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viral images show seas of burning bodies in makeshift crematoriums. Hospital beds and oxygen are scarce. Desperate patients and relatives have turned to the black market for medicine, while others die as they wait for care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Returns to Top of Ratings; All Nets Bleed Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/premium/april-ratings-fox-news-returns-to-dominance-but-all-networks-see-steep-declines-from-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;April saw Fox News top the ratings charts in all of cable in both total day and prime time among total viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger Says Caitlyn Has Chance!</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/arnold-schwarzenegger-talks-caitlyn-jenner-california-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arnold Schwarzenegger said he believes Caitlyn Jenner has a chance to become the next governor of California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY SPEARS TO SPEAK IN COURT...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/music/news/britney-spears-speak-court-conservatorship-1234961772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of silence, Britney Spears will speak to the probate court in June regarding her long-standing legal conservatorship. At a hearing on Tuesday, Los Angeles Superior Court Judge Brenda Pe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So far, her campaign is virtual...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-government-and-politics-california-coronavirus-c971cb795cae10e9f3e3ccb279c5c3cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — In her five days as a Republican candidate for California governor, Caitlyn Jenner had a Twitter spat with a Democratic congressman, unveiled a website to sell T-shirts and other campaign swag and posted a photograph of herself with a startup business owner. But she hasn’t spoken a word in public. Jenner’s written statement last week that she would enter a likely recall election that could oust Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom generated international publicity. But so far the political newcomer’s campaign exists in the virtual realm, a string of tweets and vaguely worded posts with no specifics about what she might do if elected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill to kill up to 90% of Idaho wolves heads to governor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bills-idaho-wolves-environment-and-nature-lifestyle-7e18d06ccff0705ca4282e2b097040a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — The Idaho House on Tuesday approved legislation allowing the state to hire private contractors and expand methods to kill wolves roaming Idaho. Lawmakers voted 58-11 to send the agriculture industry-backed bill to Republican Gov. Brad Little. The fast-tracked bill that allows the use of night-vision equipment to kill wolves as well as hunting from snowmobiles and all-terrain vehicles, among other measures, passed the Senate last week. Backers said changes to Idaho law could help cut the wolf population from about 1,500 to 150, alleviating wolf attacks on cattle, sheep and wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPOST Reporter Resigns, Says She Was 'Ordered to Write' False Kamala Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/new-york-post-laura-italiano-resignation-kamala-harris-book-false-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NY Post reporter said she resigned after being "ordered to write" a false story about migrant children receiving a copy of Kamala Harris' book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publisher pulls Philip Roth bio, cuts ties with author...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-philip-roth-business-arts-and-entertainment-d020172e4f2034f2a598c494145c0a95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The publisher of a highly anticipated and widely debated biography of Philip Roth is pulling the book and cutting ties with author Blake Bailey, who faces multiple allegations of sexual harassment and assault. W.W. Norton and Company previously released Bailey's memoir “The Splendid Things We Planned.” “Norton is permanently putting out of print our editions of ‘Philip Roth: The Biography’ and ‘The Splendid Things We Planned,’ Blake Bailey’s 2014 memoir,” the publisher announced Tuesday. “Mr. Bailey will be free to seek publication elsewhere if he chooses. In addition, Norton will make a donation in the amount of the book advance for ‘Philip Roth: The Biography’ to organizations that fight against sexual assault or harassment and work to protect survivors.” The stunning decision follows reports last week from The New York Times, The New Orleans Times-Picayune and The Associated Press among others that Bailey, who in the 1990s taught eighth grade English in New Orleans, had behaved inappropriately with students and later sought sexual relationships. Two former students and a publishing executive have alleged that he assaulted them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loneliness increases risk of cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9517489/Loneliness-increases-risk-CANCER-middle-aged-men.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was a 'clear link' between loneliness and an increased risk of cancer, the team explained, with being lonely increasing the risk of cancer by about ten per cent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Beats Top and Bottom Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/27/microsoft-msft-earnings-q3-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft delivered better-than-expected revenue growth thanks in part to strong PC sales in the quarter. Azure revenue growth was flat from the prior quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmanned helicopter crashes into Navy ship...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/04/27/mq-8b-fire-scout-crashes-into-littoral-combat-ship-uss-charleston-on-deployment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An MQ-8B Fire Scout unmanned aerial vehicle crashed into the side of Littoral Combat Ship USS Charleston (LCS-18) after taking off from the ship today, the Navy announced. The rotary-wing UAV was operating from the ship around 9:40 a.m. when the collision happened in the Eastern Pacific, according to a U.S. 3rd Fleet news release. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Footage of NRA LaPierre's Botched Elephant Hunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/the-secret-footage-of-nra-chief-wayne-lapierres-botched-elephant-hunt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief executive has cultivated his image as an exemplar of American gun culture, but video of his clumsy marksmanship—and details regarding his Rodeo Drive shopping trips—tells another story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Blair shocks with 'mullet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/viewers-shock-tony-blair-unveils-23994473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-Labour Party leader's straggly locks saw him trending on Twitter, along with the likes of ‘lookalikes’ Gerry Francis and Peter Stringfellow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas shortages predicted this summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/27/business/summer-gasoline-shortage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people stuck at home for more than a year are expected to hit the road for much-needed post-pandemic vacations this summer. Good luck finding gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Have I touched people? Yes,' Cuomo admits on sex harass complaints...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/27/have-i-touched-people-yes-cuomo-admits-on-sex-harass-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo admitted Tuesday that he has “touched people” amid mounting allegations of sexual harassment against him. “Have I touched people? Yes,” Cuomo matter-of-factly responded during a C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER at-home pill could be available by year-end...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/27/pfizer-at-home-covid-pill-could-be-available-by-year-end-ceo-albert-bourla-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company in March began an early stage clinical trial testing a new antiviral therapy for Covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian President Unleashes Profane Rant...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/palestinian-president-unleashes-profane-rant-against-rest-of-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinian president Mahmoud Abbas was recently caught badmouthing several countries, including the United States and his Arab neighbors, during a profanity-laced rant that raises new concerns about the 85-year-old leader's deteriorating health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu ignores law to appoint loyalist justice minister...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/netanyahu-appoint-loyalist-justice-minister-7d8843d4-5d47-4361-8e07-c01d090f1cbe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is on trial, and six days from losing his mandate to form a government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Powerful Person in Washington? Senate Parliamentarian...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/27/lobbyist-reconciliation-484765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Budget reconciliation, which lets the party in power pass bills without the minority, has changed the game on K Street and Pennsylvania Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 50+ Dogs Removed From Feces-Covered, Trash-Filled Residence...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/26/texas-dogs-living-3-feet-feces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement officials joined The Humane Society of North Texas in removing more than 50 dogs from a dilapidated, trash-filled and feces-covered home still inhabited by its human owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER account goes silent after PUBLIX objects...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/gainesville-florida-business-technology-df8fb4ac5789926e7e27c7b2686ffcf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — A popular Twitter account that notified people when Publix chicken-tender subs were on sale has been abandoned after lawyers for the Florida-based grocery chain apparently objected. The account “Are Publix Chicken Tender Subs On Sale?” — with nearly 40,000 followers — has been dormant since March 11. One of its final tweets noted that the subs were, indeed, on sale, and added ominously: “This may be our last Tweet.” Since then, it stopped sharing updates altogether. An accompanying Facebook page also went silent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger as ex-generals warn of civil war in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-56899765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ministers condemn the open letter, which was published on the 60th anniversary of a failed coup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi accused of being covert Christian missionary...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/27/jerusalem-rabbi-accused-of-being-covert-christian-missionary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultra-Orthodox rabbi in Jerusalem stands accused of being an undercover Christian missionary with his family, originally from New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brussels bracing for illegal festival amid fears of violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-lifestyle-government-and-politics-europe-brussels-74df6024cd20738f523206928b764930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Brussels prosecutor's office warned potential partygoers they should stay away from an unauthorized gathering planned this weekend in one of the city's biggest parks as police briefly detained one of the organizers on Tuesday. After an April Fools’ party drew thousands of people to Brussels’ Bois de la Cambre and ended in clashes with police last month, a sequel to the the event has been advertised by a group called the Abyss for Saturday in the same park. In a statement Tuesday, prosecutors said the manager in charge of the group's Facebook page was arrested and questioned as part of an investigation into the party before he got released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUI driver kills cop investigating DUI crash.</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-killed-while-directing-traffic-on-long-island-expressway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NYPD officer was killed by a hit-and-run driver early Tuesday while directing traffic on the Long Island Expressway in Queens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZEROHEDGE</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Saudi Lobbyists Monitored Activists At DC Summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.theuprising.info/p/documents-show-saudi-lobbyists-monitored</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theuprising.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia Mohammed bin Salman al Saud during diplomatic talks in Riyadh in 2019..(Photo by Mikhail Metzel\TASS via Getty Images) In March of 2016, about 250 activists gathered at a law school in Washington D.C. for a summit where speakers blasted the alliance between the U.S. and Saudi Arabia. One of the people watching the proceedings was a junior staffer from a D.C. lobbying firm who monitored the proceedings for the Saudi government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia Will Pay Young People $100 To Get Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2021/04/27/991173625/west-virginia-will-pay-young-people-100-to-get-vaccinated-against-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican-led state will offer savings bonds to residents between the ages of 16 and 35 in an effort to tackle vaccine hesitancy among its younger population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Scraps Plans to Launch FOXNEWS-Style UK Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/news-corp-scraps-plans-to-launch-fox-news-style-u-k-network</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch's News Corp will not launch a fully fledged Fox News-style news channel in the U.K., finding that this would not be financially viable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustration Builds on Border as Canada Reopening Goes Slow...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/frustration-builds-on-world-s-longest-border-as-canada-goes-slow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustration Builds on World’s Longest Border as Canada Goes Slow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: NO MASK WITH VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-cdc-coronavirus-guidance-masks-190a4299-05f1-4690-b4c5-d7c4e2c2f38f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is expected to address the guidelines later today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma new lightning capital of America...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/florida-oklahoma-lightning-capital-of-america/938423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New technology shows that the state with the long-held reputation of being America’s lightning capital may no longer hold that dubious title.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman brutally whipped by Taliban -- for talking on phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2781337/woman-screams-brutally-whipped-by-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VILE footage of a woman screaming for mercy as she is savagely whipped 40 times by the Taliban for “talking to a man on the phone” has emerged. The shocking clip shows crowds of men wat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD DEAD?  Why Movies Will Survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/oscar-ratings-plunge-blame-un-fun-movies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar ratings are way down, and some prominent pop culture critics blame un-fun movies. These people are forgetting a kind of big thing that happened in 2020. Also: We’d like to help you make your movie. All in today’s Movie News Rundown. But First: Master of None is back, with less Aziz Ansari and more cottage […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetically Modified Mosquitoes Released In Florida Keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9514527/Florida-residents-say-release-BILLION-genetically-engineered-mosquitos-Keys-TERRORISM.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first-ever U.S. release of genetically engineered Aedes aegypti mosquitoes this week in the Florida Keys and residents are furious over the 'live experiment' saying it is terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Furious!</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/furious-gene-hacked-mosquitoes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They're using us for their bottom line."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market performance best since Eisenhower...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-business-coronavirus-economy-ff9a0848d26f49ceb4b2e78c474b8524</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Hiring is accelerating as Americans increasingly venture out to shop, eat at restaurants and travel, and inflation pressures are even picking up after lying dormant for years. Yet this week, the Federal Reserve is all but sure to reiterate its commitment to ultra-low interest rates. At a news conference Wednesday after the Fed's latest policy meeting ends, Chair Jerome Powell will likely underscore his view that the economy is far from fully recovered and needs the central bank’s continued support in the form of low borrowing costs. There are still 8 million fewer jobs than there were before the pandemic struck. And the unemployment rate, at 6%, though well below where it was a year ago, remains elevated. Powell has stressed that further gains in the job market are needed to help the many Americans — especially low-income workers and people of color — who have been disproportionately hurt by the loss of jobs and incomes and have yet to benefit from the early stages of the recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO of $2 Billion Startup Ousted for Taking LSD at Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/ceo-of-242-billion-startup-ousted-for-taking-lsd-at-work/ar-BB1g6oAa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Zhu, co-founder of Iterable, said he was trying microdosing as a way to boost focus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker compares kids wearing masks outside to child abuse. 'Call the police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tucker-carlson-urges-audience-to-call-the-police-immediately-if-they-see-kids-wearing-masks-outdoors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During his Monday night show on Fox News, Tucker Carlson railed against wearing masks outdoors and told viewers to “call the police immediately” if they see children doing so. He also said seeing vaccinated people wear masks outside is like “watching a grown man expose himself in public.” After declaring, “The only people who wear […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk, Bezos collide after SPACEX wins moon landing contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/blue-origin-protests-nasas-awarding-moon-lander-contract-spacex-2021-04-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space race between the world's two richest men went into hyperdrive on Tuesday after Tesla chief Elon Musk took a swipe at Jeff Bezos' attempt to challenge a major NASA contract.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Can't get it up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/elon-musk-teases-jeff-bezos-battle-space-contract</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla and SpaceX CEO teased Amazon founder Jeff Bezos on Monday night after it was reported that Bezos’ Blue Origin planned to contest a NASA award recently given to SpaceX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions rise as return-to-work plans gain steam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/27/tensions-rise-as-return-to-work-plans-gain-steam.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Covid vaccinations increase, so are plans to return to the office, whether workers are ready or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funeral pyres in parks as Covid grips Delhi...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-56897970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India's capital struggles to find space to cremate its dead during the second wave of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Divide Between Vaccinated And Non-Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/04/27/the-growing-divide-between-the-vaccinated-and-the-non-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a difference a couple of months can make. The race to vaccinate has changed from a supply issue to a lack of demand issue. The result is a growing divide between the vaccinated and the not vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARVILLE: Wokeness is problem and we all know it...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/22338417/james-carville-democratic-party-biden-100-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Carville on the state of Democratic politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Night Shift' On Smartphone Does Not Help People Sleep Better...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/night-shift-smartphone-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Night Shift is not superior to using your phone without Night Shift or even using no phone at all,” researchers conclude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker compares kids wearing masks outside to child abuse. 'Call the police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article250971964.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“What you’re seeing is abuse. It’s child abuse, and you’re morally obligated to try to prevent it,” Carlson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raises minimum wage for federal contractors to $15 an hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/27/politics/minimum-wage-federal-contractors-biden/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two months after his effort to raise the federal minimum wage to $15 an hour ran into the Senate parliamentarian buzz saw, President Joe Biden is set to use his executive powers to hike the pay of hundreds of thousands of federal contract workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard's end: Shock jock Stern has lost his sting -- and his mojo...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/27/howard-stern-has-lost-his-sting-and-his-mojo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stern has no intention of ever returning to his Midtown studio, his luxury Upper West Side apartment, or any semblance of pre-pandemic life again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden fares better than Trump over his first 100 days...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210427103019-tr53f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/POLL (POLL, REPEAT, PIX, GRAPHICS):POLL-Biden fares better than Trump over his first 100 days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Now World's Best Place to Be During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/27/new-zealand-loses-top-spot-for-best-place-to-be-during-covid-to-singapore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slow vaccine rollout cited as the difference between the two countries, both of which have virtually no community coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No sign' of infection after Barcelona concert trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/no-sign-of-infection-after-barcelona-covid-concert-trial-organisers-2422979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been "no sign" of coronavirus infection among 5,000 unvaccinated people who took part in an indoor trial concert last month in Barcelona seeking pandemic-safe ways to celebrate mass events, organisers said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Quality first gray horse favored to win Kentucky Derby in 25 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kentucky-derby-kentucky-sports-11c27d51c584e7649bee16344c9c2fac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Goodlett has walked around Churchill Downs many times since joining the Kentucky Derby Museum and heard admiring fans say to each other, “Oh, look at that beautiful gray horse.” Not many of those remarks have come while looking at the winner's circle after the Derby. Essential Quality is expected to be the first gray horse to go off as the Kentucky Derby favorite in 25 years. A gray horse hasn’t won the Derby since Giacomo in 2005, and only eight grays have won it since 1930.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami private school says teachers who get vax aren't welcome, citing debunked misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/miami-school-says-it-wont-employ-vaccinated-teachers-citing-debunked-covid-myths/3021437/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A private school in Miami is discouraging teachers from getting the COVID-19 vaccine— and in a letter to parents, the school says it will not employ anyone who has taken it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Proliferation of space junk blocking view of cosmos, research shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/a-proliferation-of-space-junk-is-blocking-our-view-of-the-cosmos-research-shows/ar-BB1g6inC </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed helped fuel stock boom that benefited wealthy -- and left behind everyone else...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-fed-helped-fuel-a-stock-market-boom-that-benefited-wealthy-americans-%E2%80%94-and-left-behind-everyone-else/ar-BB1g6f5R </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran, U.S. warships in first tense Mideast encounter in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/iran-u-s-warships-first-tense-mideast-encounter-year-n1265441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tehran did not immediately acknowledge the incident in the southern reaches of the Persian Gulf, which resulted in no injuries or damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiji fears virus 'tsunami' after outbreak found to be Indian variant...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210427-fiji-fears-virus-tsunami-after-outbreak-found-to-be-indian-variant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiji fears virus 'tsunami' after outbreak found to be Indian variant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years after death, Bin Laden still mobilizes jihadists...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210427-10-years-after-death-bin-laden-still-mobilises-jihadists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;10 years after death, Bin Laden still mobilises jihadists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup aims to leave mark with ephemeral tattoos...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/york-startup-aims-leave-mark-014632412.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neither a permanent mark nor a paper transfer: a New York start-up has created the first tattoos that fully disappear after a while, aiming to open the body inking market to new clientele.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC police server hacked, Russian-speaking group claims responsibility...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210427061403-k0165</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CYBER/WASHINGTONDC:Washington D.C. police server hacked, Russian-speaking group claims responsibility -reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooling the temperature: President faces fractious Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-coronavirus-pandemic-impeachments-barack-obama-4c79ff8d59f8ce19f9dae6b550223bf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Can lawmakers all just listen to the president — even for one night? Recent history is not assuring. Republican Rep. Joe Wilson shouted “you lie!” at President Barack Obama when he was giving a joint speech to Congress in 2009. Eleven years later, Democratic House Speaker Nancy Pelosi ripped up a copy of President Donald Trump’s State of the Union speech as she stood behind him on the House rostrum. Partisan tensions have only deepened on Capitol Hill since Pelosi’s defiant act last year, which came days before the Senate acquitted Trump in his first impeachment trial. Since then, the U.S. Capitol has been through the Jan. 6 insurrection , a second impeachment of Trump and another acquittal .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fancy French Winemakers Buying Big Vineyards from Americans Ready to Sell...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/posh-french-winemakers-pounce-on-big-american-vineyard-selloff/ar-BB1g5U4Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European vintners are finding toeholds in the U.S. just as some of America’s oldest wineries are ready to cash in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces mounting pressure on forgiving student loan debt...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/550339-biden-faces-mounting-pressure-on-forgiving-student-loan-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive groups are vowing to raise the heat on President Biden to cancel student debt, a priority issue for a number of Democratic lawmakers including Senate Majority Leader Charles Schumer (D-N.Y.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeks $80 Billion to Beef Up IRS Audits of High-Earners...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/27/biden-seeks-80-billion-to-beef-up-i-r-s-audits-of-high-earners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden, in an effort to pay for his ambitious economic agenda, is expected to propose giving the</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
