<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Have Canadians wearied of Trudeau's vapid wokeness?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/have-canadians-wearied-of-trudeaus-vapid-wokeness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will the world’s wokest leader be reelected? When Justin Trudeau called the election to Canada’s 44th Parliament at the end of August, he was comfortably ahead in the polls. Crises bolster all but the most obviously useless incumbents, and Canada has had, as measured by deaths, vaccine rollout, and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon prepped Epstein for CBS interview, Wolff claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2021/sep/13/steve-bannon-jeffrey-epstein-cbs-interview-michael-wolff-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Trump strategist told financier to ‘stick to his message, which is that he is not a paedophile’, New York Times reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions mount over boosters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/13/cdc-biden-health-team-vaccine-boosters-511529</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior officials from the White House and the FDA say the CDC is withholding critical data needed to develop the booster plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They could be your neighbors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/they-could-be-your-neighbors-and-they-re-going-to-space-spacex-gets-ready-to-fly-the-inspiration4-crew/ar-AAOo1E7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;None of the crew has been to space before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh China outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/13/china/fujian-covid-outbreak-mic-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who completed 21 days of mandatory quarantine upon returning to China from overseas has been identified as the likely source of a new outbreak, raising questions over the sustainability of the country's stringent zero-Covid strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for $3.5 trillion spending plan...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/571905-democrats-brace-for-battle-on-bidens-35-spending-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are bracing for battle as they try to unify their slim majorities behind a sweeping social spending package at the heart of President Biden’s economic and political agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Former aide sees Melania as doomed French queen...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/571925-former-aide-sees-melania-trump-as-doomed-french-queen-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former top aide reportedly describes former first lady Melania Trump as "the doomed French queen" in a new book set to be released next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to launch private, all-civilian crew into Earth orbit...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-09-spacex-private-all-civilian-crew-earth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX is set to launch four people into space Wednesday on a three-day mission that is the first to orbit the Earth with exclusively private citizens on board, as Elon Musk's company enters the space tourism fray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McGregor, Machine Gun Kelly fight on VMAs red carpet...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/12/conor-mcgregor-and-machine-gun-kelly-get-into-fight-on-vmas-red-carpet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spy told Page Six that McGregor and Machine Gun Kelly “got into a fight at the top of the carpet” and “had to be pulled apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seriously ill COVID patients double in vax pace-setter Singapore...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210913112754-w5k94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SINGAPORE:Seriously ill COVID-19 patients double in vaccine pace-setter Singapore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Long-Range Missile Test as Arms Race Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/13/north-korea-reports-long-range-cruise-missile-test-as-arms-race-intensifies-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL — North Korea said on Monday it​ had successfully launched newly developed long-range cruise missiles, its first missile test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Ford wraps NY Fashion Week with a show of disco glam...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-fashion-0fbba01be4ffaf8aed48437680820d6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Champagne was cold and the front row star studded Sunday night as Tom Ford closed New York Fashion Week at Lincoln Center with a spring-summer collection of hopeful, glitzy glam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol rally seeks to rewrite Jan. 6 by exalting rioters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-d2fb23af3f01387412a1a00b4eac531c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — First, some blamed the deadly Jan. 6 attack at the U.S. Capitol  on left-wing antifa antagonists, a theory quickly debunked. Then came comparisons of the rioters to peaceful protesters or even tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allegations fly as recall vote looms for Newsom...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-california-los-angeles-gavin-newsom-long-beach-00e1180f98406e85439616f822f6ba18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — In a blitz of TV ads and a last-minute rally, California Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom urged voters Sunday to turn back a looming recall vote that could remove him from office, while leading Republican Larry Elder broadly criticized the media for what he described as double standards that insulated Newsom from criticism and scrutiny throughout the contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer Pediatricians, More Cooks Seen in Decade Jobs Outlook...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/fewer-pediatricians-more-cooks-seen-in-dismal-us-jobs-outlook/ar-AAOmhgk?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. employment will see stunted growth during the remainder of the decade, with technology eliminating some roles and retiring Baby Boomers contributing to a drop-off in the share of Americans participating in the job market, according to federal government projections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California voters: Less Republican and white...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-elections-california-voting-race-and-ethnicity-5113544f216da2fda4f7983410313335</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — It's a familiar refrain among California's recall watchers: 2021 is not 2003. Yes, the state again is in the middle of a recall election that could remove the Democratic governor from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK SCRAPS VAX PASSPORT</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16116400/covid-vaccine-passports-scrapped-sajid-javid-confirms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLANS to introduce Covid vaccine passports have been SCRAPPED as Sajid Javid confirms people won’t need them to get into nightclubs and cinemas. The Health Secretary revealed this morning tha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper has gold chains surgically IMPLANTED in scalp...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3639772/rapper-dan-sur-gold-chains-surgically-implanted-scalp-bling/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAPPER Dan Sur says he’s the first to mint his hair with surgically implanted gold chains.  “I have it as a hook that is implanted in my head and that hook has hooks and they are all hooked i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge kills himself as FBI swoops to arrest him for 'filming nude boys'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3639743/judge-kills-self-arrest-filming-nude-boys/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MARYLAND judge shot himself dead as the FBI swooped in to arrest him for allegedly filming naked boys. Authorities showed up at the home of Jonathan Newell, 50, on Friday morning to arrest him on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brains of people who hoped to be brought back to life stolen from lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3637574/scorned-wife-raids-ex-husbands-lab/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SCORNED wife raided her ex-husband’s cryogenics lab and stole the frozen brains of people who hoped to be brought back to life. Valeria Udalova, 59, and staff from her company grabbed the r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK VIDEO:  BIDEN REPEATEDLY PROMISED VAXX CHOICE FOR AMERICANS...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-biden-admin-dont-worry-wed-never-impose-vaccine-mandate-supe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘You don’t want to mandate, and try and force anyone to take a vaccine; we’ve never done that’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dBZ8VFCcwQc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president addressed the crowd at Shanksville, Pennsylvania, where a third hijacked plane, United Flight 93 crashed into a field, killing all 40 cr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANTI-SOCIAL:  LANA DEL REY DEACTIVATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/12/shocker-music-star-lana-del-rey-deactivating-social-media-accounts-today-keeping-circle-closer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s a shock: Lana del Rey says on Instagram she’s deactivating all her social media accounts as of today, Sunday. She released a new single this week, “Arcadia,” which pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members of Congress, Staff Exempt From Biden's Vaccine Mandate?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/members-congress-staff-exempt-biden-covid-vaccine-mandate-1627859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's executive orders apply to employees of the executive branch and federal government contractors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER Tropical Storm to cause flooding in LA, TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-nicholas-to-take-aim-at-coastal-texas/1016331  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rainfall totals could be measured in feet, rather than inches, across parts of the Gulf Coast region this week, forecasters warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leno Returns: 'No Politics, No Dirty Jokes'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/jay-leno-you-bet-your-life-revival-1235062193/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven years after he signed off as host of “The Tonight Show,” Jay Leno is ready to dive back into the daily TV grind as emcee of “You Bet Your Life,” a revival of the class…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Squirrels Have Personalities...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/squirrels-personalities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Animal personality is a hard science, but if it makes you relate to animals more, maybe people will be more interested in conserving them,” researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands released from prison because of Covid. Will they have to return?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/thousands-released-prison-covid-will-return-rcna1977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 4,500 people released to home confinement from prison are facing the possibility of being returned to prison once the Covid-19 pandemic recedes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden readies campaign stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-heads-west-to-assess-wildfires-campaign-for-newsom/ar-AAOmhd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden departed on a three-state western swing Monday. In California, he'll assess wildfire damage and campaign for Newsom ahead of the recall election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer refused mask in WELLS FARGO. Waited to ambush manager after his shift...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-customer-who-refused-to-wear-a-mask-in-a-wells-fargo-bank-waited-in-the-parking-lot-to-violently-ambush-the-manager-at-the-end-of-his-shift-report-says/ar-AAOmgn3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bank manager was reportedly called a racist slur by a client and then attacked in the parking lot when his shift ended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honolulu moves to destroy 'Stairway to Heaven'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/11/honolulu-city-council-moves-to-destroy-stairway-to-heaven/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Honolulu City Council moved to remove the city’s famous Haiku Stairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Qaeda chief in new video despite rumors he was dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-syria-afghanistan-taliban-islamic-state-group-79fc96bd028a31718e3c69fc6aba2a96</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Al-Qaida leader Ayman al-Zawahri appeared in a new video marking the 20th anniversary of the Sept. 11, attacks, months after rumors spread that he was dead. The SITE Intelligence Group that monitors jihadist websites said the video was released Saturday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
