<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>INFOWARS Host Booted From House Judiciary Committee After Protesting...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/infowars-host-booted-from-house-judiciary-committee-after-interrupting-impeachment-hearing-with-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee's second hearing on the Donald Trump impeachment inquiry was instantly derailed on Monday when a supporter of the president launched a protest at the start of the pr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodybuilder set to marry his sex robot girlfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/bodybuilder-set-marry-sex-robot-21055600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yuri Tolochko, from Kazakhstan, will marry his sex robot girlfriend Margo after paying for the doll to have plastic surgery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GAME OF THRONES' Fans Furious...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/tv-shows/2019/12/09/game-of-thrones-fans-furious-golden-globes-final-season-snub/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Game of Thrones fans were furious Monday morning to discover that the final season of the HBO [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Industry Suffers Steepest Drop in Ad Sales Since Recession...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tv-industry-suffers-steepest-drop-133000490.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global TV advertising sales fell almost 4% in 2019, the steepest drop since the depths of the economic recession in 2009, in the latest sign that advertisers are following viewers to the internet.Declines in TV viewership have suppressed the medium’s advertising dollars, according to research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Arrested For Driving Drunk On Highway -- On Horseback!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/12/08/drunken-man-arrested-after-injuring-horse-while-riding-it-on-dallas-highway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has been arrested in downtown Dallas after witnesses say he was riding a horse — drunk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro Snubbed...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/golden-globe-snubs-nominations-surprises-game-of-thrones-robert-de-niro-female-directors-watchmen-the-politician-1202804345/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day perhaps the Hollywood Foreign Press Association will join the 21st century and realize they don’t need to announce the Golden Globes nominations before dawn anymore. However, that’s not tod…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Love for 'CATS'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e547f34fe0a07278d2e811b688646de3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Some Golden Globe nominations seemed like locks: Joaquin Phoenix, Tom Hanks, Adam Driver and Eddie Murphy. But others were shocks, like Lupita Nyong'o not getting a nomination for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials misled public about Afghan war, confidential docs reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/confidential-documents-reveal-us-officials-failed-to-tell-the-truth-about-the-war-in-afghanistan/ar-BBXY8l1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Nabs Numerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/golden-globes-joker-nabs-4-2020-nominations-1260831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Warner Bros. film inspired by the Batman villain had a total of four nominations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley psychedelic wonder drug almost here...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90436824/silicon-valleys-psychedelic-wonder-drug-is-almost-here</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new startup called MindMed could have the key to providing the upsides of psychedelic drugs for both focus and addiction treatment—while cutting out the downsides of tripping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Fed Chairman Volcker Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/09/paul-volcker-the-carter-reagan-fed-chairman-who-beat-inflation-dies-at-92.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As chairman of the Federal Reserve under Presidents Carter and Reagan, Paul Volcker helped tame inflation with 20% interest rates that also crunched American manufacturing, farming and real estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: Hearing on Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?467123-1/hearing-evidence-impeachment-inquiry&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee holds a hearing to hear evidence in the on-going impeachment inquiry against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Male Directors...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/golden-globe-nominations-female-director-snub-1203429487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year distinguished by a record number of hit movies directed by women, from “Hustlers” to “The Farewell,” the Golden Globes once again nominated five men in the best directing category. No wom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast TV Shut Out...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/12/09/golden-globe-nominations-2020-globes-awards-nominees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations for the 77th Annual Golden Globe Awards were announced on Monday morning in Beverly Hills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/golden-globes-nominees-2020-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nominees for the 77th Golden Globes are coming our way, rapid-fire. What shows, movies and talent will be up for a trophy at next month's Golden Globes?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Play Sports For Sharper Mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/play-sports-for-sharper-mind-study-finds-athletes-have-healthier-brains-than-others/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An interesting new study conducted at Northwestern University is playing devil's advocate in the debate surrounding sports and brain health in athletes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first human composting site to open...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/funeral-green-burial-climate-change-environment-soil-composting-recompose-seattle-a9238896.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Big Wake-up Call': 'Giant UFO' Over California Seen 'by More Than 100 Witnesses'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/us/201912091077520365-a-big-wake-up-call-giant-ufo-over-california-reportedly-seen-by-more-than-100-witnesses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The object could have been taken for a drone or a skydiving vehicle, if not for a combination of facts: it didn’t move and emitted no sound whatsoever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible pardons loom for former Trump aides...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/09/possible-pardons-loom-former-trump-aides-078480</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s willingness to toss aside optics is giving hope to former aides and allies that the president might grant deeply controversial pardons in the coming months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commuters face 300-mile traffic jam as French strikes bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/09/france-strike-paris-sees-500-kilometers-of-traffic-jam-amid-protestsover-pension-reform.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French commuters experienced a chaotic journey getting to work on Monday as public sector workers entered a fifth consecutive day of nationwide strikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No signs of life'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/new-zealand-pm-people-unaccounted-for-as-volcano-erupts-11882051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists recently noticed an uptick in volcanic activity on White Island, prompting questions over why visitors were allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary hearing sets stage for charges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4ed63e09b3cb2aa2119246194118470</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pushing ahead with articles of impeachment, the House Judiciary Committee convenes Monday to formally receive the investigative findings against President Donald Trump as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booed off  field by angry fans; Questions stacking up...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Questions-keep-stacking-up-against-Patriots-and-14891882.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. - Predicting the demise of the New England Patriots is a long-running parlor game that leaves no winners, only regret and fools. The onset of doom, for them, ends with trophies and parades, with Bill Belichick cracking his annual half-smile and Tom Brady somehow looking younger. Declaring the end of the Patriots is both pointless venture and folly.  But we also don't know what the end will look like, so we might not be able to identify it even when it happens in front of our eyes. What if the end looks like an impotent offense surrendering amid the strange sound of Gillette Stadium boos at halftime? What if it looks like Brady engulfed in the pocket and fuming on the sideline days after his father openly speculated in the local newspaper about his son's future? What if looks like undrafted rookie Jakobi Meyers running wide open across the middle and allowing a pinpoint pass to slip through his fingers? What if it looks like Brady sitting on his backside, a final pass having fluttered to the turf, as the visiting sideline erupts?  What if the end looks like Sunday evening?  The Patriots still hold a bye in the AFC playoffs, and they may yet win their seventh Super Bowl two months from now. If they do, they will think back to the first half of Sunday's 23-16 defeat and marvel at how they ever sailed so far ashore. In a rematch of last year's AFC championship game, the Kansas City Chiefs snapped the Patriots' 21-game home winning streak, playoffs included, and disabused anyone of the notion that the Patriots are presently a championship-caliber outfit.  The Patriots rebounded in the second half, and Brady threw a pass into the end zone with 1:06 left that could have given the Patriots a chance to tie or take the lead. If not for untimely officiating misadventures, New England may well have won. Then...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists feared dead after volcano blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10511437/new-zealand-eruption-white-island-tourists-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOURISTS are injured and feared dead after a massive volcano eruption on a remote island off New Zealand on Monday. A huge plume of smoke and rock blasted from the White Island volcano at around 2:…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live feed goes dark in New Zealand... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/injuries-feared-popular-zealand-volcano-erupts-035555827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one person was left in a critical condition when New Zealand's White Island volcano erupted suddenly on Monday, leaving authorities scrambling to treat the injured and find those unaccounted for. Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern said the volcanic island -- also known as Whakaari -- off New</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First gun-owner charged under Florida 'red flag' law found guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10511351/florida-red-flag-gun-rifle-guilty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE first person charged under Florida’s new “red flag” gun law has been found guilty of refusing to give up his weapons. Jerron Smith, 33, had built up an arsenal of weaponry inc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ON BRINK OF IMEACHMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-indispensable-man-how-giuliani-led-trump-to-the-brink-of-impeachment/ar-BBXXmsR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run Out of Comebacks... </title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28255630/patriots-home-winning-streak-ends-21-rally-falls-short</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots had their 21-game home winning streak (including playoffs) snapped on Sunday with a loss to the Chiefs. The loss included two questionable calls from the officiating crew that went against New England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS JOLTED BY HOME GAME LOSS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/08/tom-brady-patriots-booed-off-home-field-by-angry-fans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That was strange. The New England Patriots were booed off their home field Sunday as they headed off for halftime down 13 to the Kansas City Chiefs, reports said. Despite a comeback bid in the seco…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourth Woman Pimped Out To Prince Andrew By Epstein Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@dylanhoward/i-had-to-serve-him-fourth-woman-pimped-out-to-prince-andrew-by-jeffrey-epstein-revealed-ad506ce4c5a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andy also earned another nickname because of his bad boy behavior: “Randy Andy, or “Handy Andy.” In Epstein, the raucous royal found a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's defense of Kingdom grows more isolated...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Trump-s-defense-of-Saudis-grows-more-isolated-14891534.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - After a Saudi gunman killed three people at a naval base in Pensacola, Florida, some of President Donald Trump's Republican allies took to the airwaves to condemn the attack as an act of terrorism, call for a halt to the training program that admitted the shooter and sharply press the Saudi government to cooperate in the investigation.  Trump did none of that. Instead, he used his appearances before television cameras - and his Twitter account - to repeatedly offer cover for the Saudis, conveying Riyadh's condolences with more fervor than he used in relaying his personal feelings about the shooting.  "They are devastated in Saudi Arabia," Trump told reporters Saturday, unprompted. "And the King will be involved in taking care of families and loved ones. He feels very strongly. He's very, very devastated by what happened and what took place. Likewise, the Crown Prince. They are devastated by what took place in Pensacola."  Trump's defense of the Saudi government, which began just hours after Friday's shooting, steadily became a more isolated position over the weekend as more information trickled out about the gunman and other Saudi nationals who were receiving training at the base.  On Sunday, the FBI said it presumed the shooting was terrorism.  "We are, as we do in most active-shooter investigations, work with the presumption that this was an act of terrorism," said Rachel Rojas, special agent in charge of the FBI's Jacksonville division.  Earlier Sunday, Rep. Matt Gaetz, R-Fla., normally a staunch Trump ally, was among several state officials pushing for more stringent scrutiny of foreigners who come to the United States for military training. Gaetz, who earlier called the killing an act of terrorism, also suggested the incident should change America's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING ORDERS REMOVAL OF FOREIGN COMPUTERS AND SOFTWARE...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/dec/09/china-tells-government-offices-to-remove-all-foreign-computer-equipment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Directive is likely to be a blow to US multinational companies like HP, Dell and Microsoft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY IN THE SHADOWS</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Giuliani-carves-influencer-shadow-adviser-roles-14891683.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The president's personal attorney Rudy Giuliani was on the phone in late 2018, pressing administration officials about his latest agenda item.  President Donald Trump had nominated a career Foreign Service officer to become the U.S. ambassador to Qatar, a key post in a Middle Eastern country with tricky regional relationships, an important U.S. military installation and vast oil reserves.  Giuliani, who has said he had held a cybersecurity contract with Qatar in 2017 and early 2018, proposed replacing her with someone he said would be a better fit - Scott Taylor, a Trump-supporting former congressman from Virginia defeated in his reelection bid in November 2018, according to people familiar with his outreach.  Giuliani's previously unreported attempts to shape the pick for the U.S. envoy to Qatar is part of an unorthodox foreign policy portfolio he has carved out for himself while also working as a power-broker-for-hire with direct access to the president and top administration officials.  The dual roles he has embraced is part of what longtime colleagues say has been a transformation of the once-iconic New York mayor into a multimillionaire consultant to powerful figures overseas.  In the three years since Trump took office, Giuliani has expanded his lucrative foreign consulting and legal practice, taking on clients that span the globe, from Turkey to Venezuela to Romania to Ukraine.  Along the way, he also has used his singular perch to try to influence U.S. policy and criminal investigations - at times pushing the interests of foreign figures who could benefit him financially.  In 2017, Giuliani tried to get Trump and top Cabinet members to make moves sought by Turkey while working as a lawyer for a gold trader from that country with ties to top government...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denies stuttering to blame for screwups...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-stuttering-verbal-stumbles-b9238c3c-d1cc-400a-ab11-bf0f971c38d9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don't think of myself as continuing to stutter."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tells 'AXIOS ON HBO' he will slap restrictions on son Hunter if elected...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-hunter-family-restrictions-impeachment-c13a3832-b501-43e9-8709-de6243c9d21d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president said his family will be banned from making money overseas if he wins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds Warren to veep list...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-elizabeth-warren-2020-vice-president-3536f876-8239-4a31-b7c4-b9d2b39e8521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"But she's gonna to be very angry at my having said that."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS JOLTED BY HOME GAME LOSS...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/patriots-jolted-chiefs-49ers-down-saints-012840040--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most glaring officiating error occurred early in the fourth quarter, when N&amp;#39;Keal Harry was wrongly adjudged to have been forced out of bounds as he dived into the corner for a touchdown. Replays clearly showed Harry was in-bounds and the Patriots should have been awarded a touchdown -- but with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Finland prime minister is 34!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aaba1c784bf702a94ff1fea2a84c6d4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLINN, Estonia (AP) — A 34-year-old transport minister and lawmaker has been tapped to become Finland's youngest prime minister ever and its third female government leader. Finland's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here come GOLDEN GLOBES... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5af57d80e48162234e6c1b2edf1aa155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Renee Zellweger, Brad Pitt and Eddie Murphy are locks. But whether “Cats" has it in the bag, too, we won't know until the 77th annual Golden Globes are announced Monday morning....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade war goes digital: Countries eye tariffs on Internet economy...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191206133007-ia53t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRADE-WTO/INTERNET (PIX):Trade war goes digital: countries eye tariffs on Internet economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART apologizes for sweater featuring Santa with cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/08/walmart-apologizes-for-sweater-featuring-santa-with-cocaine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ho, ho, no! Walmart has apologized for an adults-only Christmas sweater that appeared to depict Santa with cocaine on its Canadian website, according to a report. The retailer pulled the holiday ou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Becomes First Studio Ever to Hit $10 Billion at Box Office in Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-becomes-first-ever-studio-with-10-billion-at-global-box-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's record-breaking 2019 continued this weekend, as it became the first studio ever to gross $10 billion at the global box office in a single year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PARASITE' Named Best Picture By LA Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/la-film-critics-association-awards-winners-list-1260643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Driver, Jennifer Lopez, Antonio Banderas won the acting prizes in the vote, which took place Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING ORDERS REMOVAL OF FOREIGN COMPUTERS AND SOFTWARE...</title>
      <link>https://www.forexcrunch.com/beijing-orders-state-offices-to-replace-foreign-pcs-and-software-ft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forexcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RIPS 'PATHETIC' FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/473591-trump-claims-fox-news-panders-to-democrats-by-having-liberal-guests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Sunday renewed his criticism of Fox News, claiming that the network was pandering to the Democratic Party by repeatedly hosting liberal lawmakers to discuss the impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI presumes terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8aef6b09fe84ba7f5ee1d0b00e7d1b0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENSACOLA, Fla. (AP) — The Saudi gunman who killed three people at the Pensacola naval base had apparently gone on Twitter shortly before the shooting to blast U.S. support of Israel and accuse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global financial watchdogs take aim at Big Tech's data dominance...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191208223020-qyfcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECH-REGULATOR/:Global financial watchdogs take aim at Big Tech's data dominance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos of Lindsey Graham are coming back to bite him. But will voters care?</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article237674979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Finland prime minister is 34!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/new-finland-prime-minister-sanna-21053251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanna Marin - a minister for the country's Social Democrats - will become the youngest leader in the world when he takes control of the country next week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE THAN 7 MILLION JOBS CREATED SINCE TRUMP WON ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/08/exclusive-treasurys-monica-crowley-on-the-explosive-trump-economy-success-boom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monica Crowley told Breitbart News that President Donald Trump’s “economic freedom agenda” has led to the lowest unemployment in 50 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrelenting chaos as French strike bites...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frances-macron-hold-meeting-pensions-strike-bites-060132547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron, Prime Minister Edouard Philippe and senior cabinet ministers met late Sunday to discuss the government's proposed pensions reforms as public transport in France was crippled for a fourth day running in protest. The country's powerful labour unions, who claim</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi military training in US under scrutiny after base attack...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/calls-halt-saudi-military-training-us-attack-175752458.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key US lawmakers called Sunday for a halt to a Saudi military training program after a shooting rampage at a naval base in Florida in which a Saudi officer killed three American sailors. US Defense Secretary Mark Esper said he has ordered a review of vetting procedures while defending the training program</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even worse travel woes; Govt seeks answers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f875ff134f42b8c3ab6d654498eb5b70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France braced for even worse transportation woes when the new work week begins Monday due to nationwide strikes over the government's redesign of the national retirement system....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Blundering Brilliance of Boris...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/12/boris-johnson-brexit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brexit has given the U.K’s self-seeking Prime Minister the opportunity to show he actually knows what he’s doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  VOTE POSSIBLE THIS WEEK</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191208184944-iu3fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Democrats zoom in on Trump impeachment charges this week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Underground introduces First Class Carriages -- With A Bar!</title>
      <link>https://www.suffolkgazette.com/news/london-underground-introduces-first-class-carriages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.suffolkgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London Underground is introducing luxurious first-class carriages so well-heeled commuters do not need to mix with common riff-raff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wailing, white light and angel wings: 'Possessed' man's terrifying exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/wailing-white-light-angel-wings-21024749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian found himself being the subject of an exorcism after visiting a throat specialist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan arrested over 'racist gesture' at soccer game...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7768919/Manchester-City-fan-accused-making-monkey-sounds-United-star-Fred-family-man-40.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Anthony Burke, 41, (pictured) from Manchester appeared to make racist gestures and monkey noises at United midfielder Fred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems embrace exact surveillance tactics they used to warn about...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/07/democrats-have-embraced-the-exact-surveillance-tactics-they-used-to-warn-about/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Democrats have been warning Americans about the dangers of law enforcement metadata collections. They cautioned that communication giants were working in cahoots with law enforcement to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheelchair thief in reindeer slippers stopped in his tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article238168529.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am Jesus Christ' lets gamers play through being crucified; Fight Satan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/i-am-jesus-christ-lets-21051487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial game allowing people to play through key moments from the Bible is due to be released on Steam for PC - but Christians have argued it is blasphemous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linda Ronstadt Needles Secretary of State Pompeo to his face for 'Enabling Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/linda-ronstadt-needles-secretary-of-state-mike-pompeo-for-enabling-trump-to-his-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exchange happened during a State Department dinner for Kennedy Center Honors recipients on Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fires warning shot at Kim Jong-un...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10508799/trump-warning-shot-north-korea-nuke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump today warned trigger-happy North Korea it has “too much to lose” hours after its latest controversial “missile” test. The tough-talking US president took to Twi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  VOTE POSSIBLE THIS WEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/08/politics/jerry-nadler-donald-trump-impeachment-obstruction-of-justice/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With sources telling CNN a vote in the Judiciary Committee to impeach President Donald Trump is expected as soon as this week, House Judiciary Chairman Jerry Nadler said Sunday that he sees the Ukraine evidence as part of "a pattern" of conduct by the President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  Vote possible THIS week...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/8/jerrold-nadler-impeachment-vote-possible-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerrold Nadler said there could be a vote as early as this week on articles of impeachment against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Typo' overvalued Utah home by $1B -- now county residents have to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/us/article/Typo-may-have-overvalued-Utah-home-at-nearly-1B-14888778.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) - Utah officials say a possible dropped phone resulted in a typo that overvalued a home for almost $1 billion.  And taxpayers may have to pay for the mistake.  The Deseret News reports a house built in 1978 in an unincorporated area of the county was recorded in 2019 tax rolls with a value of more than $987 million. That's an overestimate of about $543 million in taxable value.  Wasatch County Assessor Maureen "Buff" Griffiths told officials last month a staff member may have dropped a phone on a keyboard. Griffiths said the accident has resulted in a countywide overvaluation of more than $6 million.  Griffiths added that the blunder also produced revenue shortfalls in five taxing entities.  Wasatch County officials say residents will likely see an increased tax rate over the next three years to make up for the lower amount collected in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year after Moonves, 'toxic' culture remains in CBS TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2019-12-08/cbs-tv-stations-toxic-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Times investigation uncovers claims of discrimination, retaliation and other forms of mistreatment at CBS-owned TV stations, including L.A. outlets.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
