<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fasting, not calorie count, boosts lifespan...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211018-fasting-not-calorie-count-boosts-lifespan-in-mice-study-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fasting, not calorie count, boosts lifespan in mice: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top editor dismissed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211018165021-x8wmn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AXEL SPRINGER-EDITOR/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Germany's Axel Springer dismisses top Bild editor after media reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,200 Chicago Cops Defying...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/chicago-police-union-fop-vaccine-reporting-mandate-mayor-lori-lightfoot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago Fraternal Order of Police has said the city's vaccine mandate is a change to employment policies that must be negotiated with the union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Aimed at Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-10-18/china-sets-sights-on-taiwan-with-new-hypersonic-missile-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The game-changing technology that reportedly caught the U.S. by surprise is not designed to spark a global arms race, Chinese insiders say, rather to retake what Beijing considers its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Delays Could Soon Leave Wine Glasses Empty...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/10/16/supply-chain-delays-could-soon-leave-wine-glasses-empty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supply chain delays could soon leave your wine glasses empty, but the problem isn't the grapes, it's the packaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale nude photos highlight disappearing Dead Sea...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/18/200-israelis-strip-naked-for-photo-shoot-near-the-dead-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One photo shoot stopped 200 Israelis dead in their tracks. Two-hundred Israeli volunteers stripped naked for a photo shoot designed to draw attention to the shrinking of the Dead Sea. The uninhibit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump website taken over by 'Muslim hacktivist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3880424/donald-trumps-website-hacked-turkish-muslim-hacktivist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s website was reportedly hacked by a Turkish and Muslim Hacktivist warning, “do not be like those who forgot Allah.” Hacker RootAyyildiz took credit for the hacking o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Virginia Gov. has had 'long covid' for a year...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/news/health/vp-nw-coronavirus-northam-long-covid-20211017-zcx4uy7ojvbltc5nv7mnmzo5e4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sense of smell or taste returns within six months for four out of five COVID-19 survivors who have lost these senses, according to an ongoing Virginia Commonwealth University study. But the 20% who don’t get better means millions could have permanent loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Anchor Deletes Tweet Claiming Death Raises Questions About Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/foxs-john-roberts-slammed-for-deleted-tweet-claiming-death-of-colin-powell-raises-new-concerns-about-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' John Roberts drew a great deal of public criticism for using Colin Powell's to call the long-term effectiveness of coronavirus vaccines into question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA rapper hits top of iTunes chart with anti-Biden track...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/anti-biden-lets-go-brandon-song-tops-itunes-hip-hop-chart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anti-President Biden rap song inspired by the viral “Let's go Brandon” trend is now sitting at the top of the iTunes hip-hop chart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer nears make-or-break moment to deliver on Dem agenda...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/schumer-democrats-dwindling-time-good-060000929.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer faces staggering policy challenges -- President Joe Biden’s economic agenda, voting rights legislation and another risky debt limit fight -- constrained by GOP leader Mitch McConnell’s hardball tactics and Democratic disunity in the 50-50 Senate.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightW</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator calls for senility test for leaders in all branches of govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bill-cassidy-senility-test-biden-age-4044e32c-25b5-4cb7-bdd7-269c11a96645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"And I'm saying this as a doctor."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RAGE AGAINST MACHINE' Rocker Goes Corporate With NYT Newsletter...</title>
      <link>https://mtracey.substack.com/tom-morello-fight-the-power-by-subscribing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mtracey.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blearily scanning the New York Times homepage yesterday morning as I sometimes reluctantly do, usually out of a faint sense of obligation, I was jolted into sudden hyper-alertness by the sight of an extraordinary revelation: turns out Tom Morello, the hard-charging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Workers Protest Mandates...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/dallas-southwest-protest-vaccine-manadate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former Southwest Airlines workers gathered to protest recent COVID-19 vaccination mandates on Monday, Oct. 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For 105 days, COVID death toll in Florida counties went missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2581184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 105 days this summer, while COVID-19 deaths soared across the state, Floridians had no idea how many of their neighbors were dying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: California driest year in century...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-records-driest-century-120035397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average accumulation of rain and snowfall across the state totaled only 11.87 inches during the 2021 water year, which ran Oct. 1, 2020, through Sept. 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Communist's American Surveillance State...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/10/china-america-surveillance-hikvision/620404/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With generous state support at home and low-cost sales abroad, Hikvision has become a world heavyweight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Bipartisan Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/a-genuine-american-hero-the-death-of-colin-powell-sets-off-massive-bipartisan-tribute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tributes are pouring in from members of Congress, journalists, and others following the death of Colin Powell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War hero, historymaker haunted by Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211018-colin-powell-war-hero-historymaker-haunted-by-iraq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Powell: war hero, historymaker haunted by Iraq</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale nude photos highlight disappearing Dead Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/spencer-tunick-dead-sea-nude-photographs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 200 people in Israel have stripped bare for Spencer Tunick, an artist known for coordinating large-scale nude photos in public places around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,300-year-old mummy reveals history behind tattoos for healing and religion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/18/world/mummy-tattoos-healing-religion-partner-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ötzi the prehistoric iceman had 61 tattoos preserved on its body, and researchers have been investigating their meaning since the mummy was discovered 30 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titan of American Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3878738/colin-powell-dead-first-black-us-secretary-of-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLIN Powell, the first black US Secretary of State, has died at 84 from Covid-19 complications. The Powell family announced his death on Monday in a Facebook post. “General Colin L. Powell, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Black Secretary of State...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/18/colin-powell-former-secretary-of-state-who-made-case-for-iraq-invasion-dies-of-covid-complications-at-84.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell Fully Vaccinated; Treated At Walter Reed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/colin-powell-dies-84-first-black-secretary-of-state-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Powell was fully vaccinated, his family said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rejuvenated LeBron, LAKERS eye return to NBA summit...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/rejuvenated-lebron-lakers-eye-return-014454807.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James and the Los Angeles Lakers launch their bid to return to the summit of the NBA on Tuesday with a new roster and a rejuvenated mindset after a badly needed first full off-season in two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free food and healthy, too: Small town grows own veggies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-flint-679dae7e26c0c9c329d21ccd52aa6c17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DURAND, Mich. (AP) — Need a tomato for a sandwich? In one small community, it's as easy as picking one from a plant growing downtown. Durand in Shiawassee County, southwest of Flint, offers an “edible landscape,” a variety of free fruits and vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Haiti seek release of 17 missionaries snatched by gang...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-port-au-prince-kidnapping-haiti-b1afcce986e48e51084f4e4096877a05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — U.S. officials are working with Haitian authorities to try to secure the release of 12 adults and five children with a U.S.-based missionary group who were abducted over the weekend by a gang notorious for killings, kidnappings and extortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Thousands protest in El Salvador against 'dictator' Bukele...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20211018-thousands-protest-in-el-salvador-against-dictator-president-bukele</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people in El Salvador took to the streets on Sunday in protest against President Nayib Bukele, who has stoked concern that he is steadily concentrating power and who responded by changin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Strikes!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/enoughs-enough-tight-u-job-100623109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of workers remain on strike across the United States demanding higher pay and better conditions despite Hollywood make-up artists and camera operators reaching a deal over the weekend to avoid a walkout, and the tight jobs market has only emboldened them. Kevin Bradshaw is an employee at Kellogg Co's cereal plant in Memphis, Tennessee, where most of North America's Frosted Flakes are made. "Enough is enough," said Bradshaw, vice president of Bakery, Confectionary, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers International Union Local 252G at the Memphis plant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep calm': Georgia town calls for unity as prepares for Black jogger murder trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211018095844-jkibn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/GEORGIA-ARBERY-BRUNSWICK (PIX, TV):'Keep calm': A Georgia town calls for unity as it prepares for Black jogger murder trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China denies report of hypersonic missile test, says tested space vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211018094212-lg9ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-SPACE/DIPLOMACY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China denies report of hypersonic missile test, says tested space vehicle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Shares Roaring Back...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-shares-roaring-back-081557874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tesla Inc. shares are staging a comeback as investors expect the Elon Musk-led electric carmaker to navigate the crippling semiconductor shortage better than rivals that have been severely disrupted.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkWhy Buying a Second or Even Third Home Is Becoming More Popular Than EverGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightOut-of-Pract</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music, Barbecues, Wi-Fi: Managing Morale for Those Idled at Sea...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/music-barbecues-wi-fi-managing-060000826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Plenty of things might keep container-ship captain Markus Grote up at night while sailing across the ocean, but lately there’s another kind of sinking feeling that worries him: crew morale.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkWhy Buying a Second or Even Third Home Is Becoming More Popular Than EverGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightOut-of-Practice Airlin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Great Resignation' goes global...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-Great-Resignation-goes-global-16541578.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the United States, the phenomenon dubbed as the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferson Statue May Be Removed After More Than 100 Years at City Hall...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/18/jefferson-statue-may-be-removed-after-more-than-100-years-at-city-hall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than 100 years, a 7-foot-tall statue of Thomas Jefferson has towered over members of the New York City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Nuke Bomb Could Save Earth From Stealthy Asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/18/how-a-nuclear-bomb-could-save-earth-from-a-stealthy-asteroid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day, astronomers may spot an asteroid months away from a cataclysmic rendezvous with Earth. Our only chance of survival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA'S LEAP IN HYPERSONIC MISSILE TECHNOLOGY SHAKES U.S. INTELLIGENCE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10101953/Beijing-mocks-America-saying-new-21-000mph-nuclear-capable-missile-new-blow-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese military launched the Long March rocket, a nuclear-capable missile, in August carrying a hypersonic glide vehicle' in low orbit. It circled the globe before returning to Earth to strike its target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychosis cases soar as pandemic hits mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/oct/18/psychosis-cases-soar-in-england-as-pandemic-hits-mental-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;75% rise in referrals for first suspected episode of psychosis between April 2019 and April 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creepy Kanye goes white...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3876391/kanye-west-balenciaga-mask-venice-divorce-kim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West wore a creepy mask and an all black Balenciaga outfit after performing at a wedding in Venice, Italy, as his divorce from Kim Kardashian moves forward. Kanye, 44, went undercover in Veni…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jon Stewart Torches Media for Hyping Stories to Stir Up Conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jon-stewart-torches-the-media-on-cnn-for-hyping-stories-to-stir-up-conflict-who-gives-a-sht-about-gender-neutral-toy-laws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jon Stewart delivered a scathing critique of the media on CNN Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMITH:  At AXEL SPRINGER, POLITICO's New Owner, Allegations of Sex, Lies and a Secret Payment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/17/business/media/axel-springer-bild-julian-reichelt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high-flying German media giant is ahead on digital media but seems stuck in the past when it comes to the workplace and deal-making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MAN WHO WILL TAKE ON ORBAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/hungary-e2-80-99s-opposition-parties-unite-to-challenge-far-right-leader-orban/ar-AAPDDRU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six parties from across the political spectrum banded together to pick Catholic conservative Peter Marki-Zay as their candidate in the 2022 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Literary world chaos as acclaimed female crime writer revealed to be 3 men...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/17/europe/spanish-female-writer-revealed-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's literary world has been thrown into chaos after a coveted book prize was given to "Carmen Mola" -- a lauded female thriller writer who turned out to be the pseudonym of three men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'More immediate, more visceral' and a lot tougher on Eric Clapton: A plan for reviving ROLLING STONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/More-immediate-more-visceral-and-a-lot-tougher-16539068.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Monday in Manhattan, outside the Fifth Avenue offices of Rolling Stone, dozens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN reporter leaving company over requirements...</title>
      <link>https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/allison-williams-is-leaving-espn-over-covid-19-vaccine-mandate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;awfulannouncing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN sideline reporter Allison Williams hasn't been on CFB sidelines after choosing not to get vaccinated. She's now leaving the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21,000 mph nukes that can hit anywhere in MINUTES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3874979/china-hypersonic-arms-race-russia-north-korea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA appears to have taken a shock lead in the hypersonic arms race as the world’s powers battle it out for the next generation of devastating nuclear weapons. Revelations that Beijing flew …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE' RATINGS HIT ALL-TIME LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/17/lowest-rating-to-date-rami-malek-hosted-saturday-night-live-with-surprise-guest-daniel-craig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Bond walks into a gay bar. But should he?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nbc-out/out-life-and-style/james-bond-walks-gay-bar-rcna3115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Bond actor Daniel Craig made headwinds this week when he revealed that he is a big fan of gay bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British lawmakers could get police protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/british-lawmakers-could-get-police-protection-when-meeting-constituents-in-wake-of-david-amess-killing/ar-AAPDctw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home Secretary Priti Patel says the government is also considering asking constituents to pre-book appointments with their elected representatives for weekly public meetings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Strikes!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/strikes-are-sweeping-the-labor-market-as-workers-wield-new-leverage/ar-AAPCOoa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The labor activism runs the gamut of American industry, powered by the same grievances about wages, benefits and quality of life driving the Great Resignation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 5 Nights in Hospital, Bill Clinton Released...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bill-clinton-heads-home-spending-150526164.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clinton, 75, was treated for a urological infection that spread to his blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's health ministry warns of '6th wave'...</title>
      <link>https://mainichi.jp/english/articles/20211002/p2a/00m/0na/020000c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mainichi.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO -- The Japanese health ministry has sent a notice to prefectural governments requesting that they review their medical systems in preparation fo</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
