<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RACE IS ON: First of three Mars missions ready to arrive...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/02/08/First-of-three-Mars-missions-ready-to-arrive/9341612466213/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new era of Mars exploration begins Monday with the expected arrival of the United Arab Emirates' Hope spacecraft in vicinity of the Red Planet -- the first of three such arrivals planned for February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unleashed Bezos will shift space venture into hyperdrive...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unleashed-jeff-bezos-seek-shift-120913932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freed from his daily obligations at Amazon.com Inc, Jeff Bezos is expected to turn up the heat on his space venture, Blue Origin, as it faces a pivotal year and fierce competition from Elon Musk's SpaceX, industry sources said. The 57-year-old Bezos, a lifelong space enthusiast and the world's second-richest person behind Musk, said last week he is stepping down as chief executive of the e-commerce company as he looks to focus on personal projects. Blue Origin has fallen far behind SpaceX on orbital transportation, and lost out to SpaceX and United Launch Alliance (ULA) on billions of dollars' worth of U.S. national security launch contracts which begin in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic line judges make Grand Slam debut...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cannot-serious-electronic-line-judges-083755583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The days of tennis players arguing whether balls are in or out could be coming to a close, after the smooth introduction of electronic line judging at the Australian Open on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu walks out on his own corruption trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-e2-80-99s-netanyahu-walks-out-on-his-own-corruption-trial/ar-BB1duCPy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli leader was summoned to court for the second phase of hearings, just weeks before elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Hastens Exit from Israel's Ultra-Orthodox Community...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/08/virus-hastens-exit-from-israels-ultra-orthodox-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — When the coronavirus pandemic swept through Israel, it upended Racheli Ohayon’s life in unexpected ways. The 21-year-old phone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of maskless Tampa fans flood streets, risking superspreader event...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/thousands-of-maskless-tampa-fans-flooded-the-streets-celebrating-the-super-bowl-win-while-risking-a-superspreader-event/ar-BB1duDel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hordes of football fans crammed into bars, clogged up streets and belted chants from their uncovered mouths in Tampa this weekend, defying pleas from public health experts to help stop the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like GAMESTOP, BED BATH &amp; BEYOND reduced to stock meme. But 42,000 people work there...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Like-GameStop-Bed-Bath-amp-Beyond-has-been-15932853.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching short sellers duke it out with Reddit- and Robinhood-inspired buyers over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY SCHOOLS THE CHILDREN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-new-england-patriots-football-7418cec28100392206508c6a1496cb39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — So much of it looked familiar — from the heartfelt rendering of the national anthem, to the silvery, star-studded halftime show, to Tom Brady standing there at the end with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial to open with sense of urgency, speed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-trials-acquittals-40ef81572403c82422464169e67554d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump's historic second impeachment trial is opening this week with a sense of urgency — by Democrats who want to hold the former president accountable for the violent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense team will show clips of Dems urging violence in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/6/trumps-defense-team-will-show-clips-democrats-urgi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s defense at his Senate impeachment trial next week will include videos of Democrats encouraging violence, one of his lawyers said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Commercial Draws Heat...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cure-auto-insurance-draws-heat-for-offensive-super-bowl-spot-casually-joking-about-workplace-harassment-ad-fail-of-the-decade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Super Bowl ad from Cure Auto Insurance is drawing criticism for belittling the seriousness of workplace harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moment of Silence For Covid Victims Booed...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/news/joe-biden-super-bowl-moment-silence-garners-boos-crowd-surprising-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Super Bowl LV is underway, and fans can watch the game for free. Before the big game, President [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY SCHOOLS THE CHILDREN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-football-super-bowl-fbabcae4076a95ad2ba653d72e5a8a10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on Super Bowl 55 (All times EST): ___ 9:05 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder at Yale...</title>
      <link>http://www.newhavenindependent.org/index.php/archives/entry/homicide_in_east_rock/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newhavenindependent.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Updated) A week after his marriage engagement, a 26-year-old Yale forestry graduate student was shot to death Saturday night in the Goatville section of the East Rock neighborhood, the city’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Reporter Aghast at Maskless, Drunk Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/cnn-reporter-aghast-at-maskless-drunk-super-bowl-crowds-in-tampa-i-asked-the-police-what-are-you-doing-about-this/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN reporter Randi Kaye found herself shocked, shocked to find that Super Bowl crowds were drinking in Tampa before the big game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS HAVE HIS BACK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-censures-roger-wicker-trials-05bdcc3475e661077295627bac922ebd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump’s defenders in the Senate on Sunday rallied around the former president before his impeachment trial, dismissing it as a waste of time and arguing that the former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioters' words loom large in President's role in attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/7/trump-supporters-words-capitol-riot-loom-large-ahe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the former president prepared to face his second impeachment trial this week, the words of his supporters, captured in court documents, are looming large as senators try to place blame for the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B.1.1.7  spreading rapidly through USA, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/U-K-coronavirus-variant-spreading-rapidly-15931664.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus variant that shut down much of the United Kingdom is spreading rapidly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Months after contracting covid, some will try anything to regain their sense of smell!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/months-contracting-covid-19-try-130043115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Loss of smell is a common symptom of COVID-19, and about 10% of patients suffer from long-term smell dysfunction. Can the nose be retrained to detect odors correctly?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There is only relentless pursuit of perfection'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/07/tom-brady-intense-pump-up-video-super-bowl-once-more-into-the-fray/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Tom Brady's most cherished traditions in recent years has involved a well-made pump-up video for big games. Super Bowl LV will be no exception.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More people choose to die at home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-pandemics-michael-brown-coronavirus-pandemic-nursing-homes-3e51d0fe283d3075fcecf413f8ad8ae3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — Mortuary owner Brian Simmons has been making more trips to homes to pick up bodies to be cremated and embalmed since the pandemic hit. With COVID-19 devastating...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope greets public again with wide distancing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-pandemics-israel-super-bowl-football-6e3df11b3ff68134a02cd597ff4b3054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG — South Africa has suspended plans to inoculate its front-line health care workers with the AstraZeneca vaccine after a small clinical trial suggested that it isn’t effective in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial brings reckoning even if acquittal likely...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-trials-impeachments-trump-impeachment-michael-pence-187a66133bc8932db712d71f6ef714a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — This matters. The outcome may seem preordained in the unprecedented second impeachment trial of Donald Trump.  Democrats prosecuting the former president for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial brings reckoning even if acquittal likely...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/trump-s-trial-brings-a-reckoning-even-if-acquittal-is-likely/article_3c74c449-60a4-576c-9769-45cba3de155a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s second impeachment trial is almost certain to end in acquittal, yet it will deliver a public reckoning for his presidency and influence whether his populist supporters continue to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KC 52.1% CHANCE OF WINNING</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/game/_/gameId/401220403</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get a summary of the Kansas City Chiefs vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers football game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE STREAM</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/superbowl/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the Kansas City Chiefs vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers in Super Bowl LV on February 7, 2021. See the official broadcast live from Raymond James Stadium in Tampa, Florida right here on CBSSports.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/super-bowl-2021-chiefs-vs-buccaneers-live-updates-start-time-kickoff-live-stream-online-odds-spread/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Live coverage of the lead up to Super Bowl LV as Kansas City and Tampa Bay battle for the championship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE SHULTZ DEAD AT 100...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/george-shultz-secretary-state-shaped-175328917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George P. Shultz, who as secretary of State in the 1980s shaped U.S. foreign policy in the closing phase of the Cold War, died Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Shultz dies at 100...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2288159/george-shultz-dead-secretary-state-under-ronald-reagan-100/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER Secretary of state George Shultz has died at the age of 100. He led President Ronald Reagan’s efforts against the Soviet Union during the Cold War. The Hoover Institution, of which Shu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' Skewers 'Former Social Media Influencer'...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/02/06/snl-skewers-joe-biden-and-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Jost mocked Joe Biden's memory lapses and Donald Trump's absence from Twitter during the 'Weekend Update' portion of 'SNL.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest win: In 2020, NFL found ways to play every game...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-football-coronavirus-pandemic-71defaceb1b8c4b12781bc8ae7277801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than the youth of Patrick Mahomes or the agelessness of Tom Brady, the most compelling story surrounding this year’s Super Bowl was that it was happening at all. It took nearly 1...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dem version of John McCain'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/07/joe-manchin-senate-congress-466132</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the critical swing vote in a 50-50 Senate, Joe Manchin has emerged as the most powerful man in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa members threaten to 'burn' down DC during BLM march...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/antifa-members-threatens-to-burn-down-dc-during-black-lives-matter-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "DC Queer and Trans Black History Month March and Rally" took place in the afternoon Saturday, and Black Lives Matter protesters marched in the evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgruntled NRA Donors Push to Oust LaPierre...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/guns/disgruntled-nra-donors-move-to-oust-lapierre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgruntled NRA donors will petition a bankruptcy court to purge the group's leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Majority say Trump should be convicted, barred from office...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/majority-americans-trump-convicted-barred-holding-federal-office/story?id=75729878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new ABC News/Ipsos poll, a majority of Americans support the Senate convicting former President Trump in his second impeachment trial, but the partisan gap persists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans fined for bypassing security...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/two-republicans-fined-for-bypassing-security-just-days-after-house-approved-the-new-penalties/ar-BB1dslji</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawmakers, Representatives Louie Gohmert of Texas and Andrew Clyde of Georgia, appear to be the first members punished under a new rule approved by the House on Tuesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona seniors giving up on getting jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona-health/2021/02/06/arizona-seniors-giving-up-covid-19-vaccines/4406940001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many older Arizonans say the COVID-19 vaccination registration process is too complicated and others without cars and computers say it's impossible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana AG sues reporter over records request...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/intimidation-measure-louisiana-ag-criticized-for-suing-reporter-over-records-request/ar-BB1dt6RU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Allegations of sexual harassment that turn out to be unsupported, inaccurate and unfounded can destroy marriages, damage employee’s children, wreck families and ruin reputations," staff for the attorney general wrote to a reporter who requested complaints against a top deputy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDakota AG Killed a Man. Everything Else Is Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/south-dakota-attorney-general-killed-095845266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg/GettyOn a remote section of highway in a sparsely populated part of South Dakota, the state’s highest-ranking law enforcement official struck and killed a man while returning from a Republican Party dinner one night in late summer.In the months since, Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg hasn’t missed a day of work—and has not faced any charge in connection with the death of Joe Boever.Many South Dakotans are growing restless, including Boever’s family. Markers indicating a death went up at the crash site on Highway 14 in Hyde County last week, a grim reminder of the tragedy that had cousin Nick Nemec in tears.“I’m very disappointed,” he told The Daily Beast during a video call. “Next week will mark five months since the crash. I’ve prepared myself mentally for some sort of guilty plea to a minor traffic violation on the order of ‘crossing the white line.’”Gov. Kristi Noem, like Ravnsvorg a Republican elected in 2018, has also questioned why it is taking so long for the investigation to conclude.“We continue to call it a great disservice to the victim’s family,” Noem said at a Jan. 21 press conference. “I am disappointed that we haven’t seen some action taken by the states attorney involved and hope certainly that they soon will.”Noem cannot remove or even suspend Ravnsborg, according to the governor’s communications director, Ian Fury.“Since the attorney general is a separately elected constitutional official, she has no such authority,” Fury said.The person who will decide what if any charges will be filed is Emily Sovell, the Sully County state’s attorney and the Hyde County deputy state’s attorney. Sovell is handling the case for her father, Hyde County State’s Attorney Merlin Voorhees, who is not involved in the investigation or the charging decision. No reason for that has been provided. (Voorhees, who was disbarred in 1980 for his role in a cattle feedlot scheme, was reinstated to the bar in 1987. He has served as state’s attorney in both Sully and Hyde counties.)Sovell has not responded to requests for comment left with both county attorneys’ offices and has not spoken a word on the case publicly, even as questions about the investigation have piled up.Mike Deaver, a veteran public relations consultant and strategist from Salt Lake City, has been serving as Ravnsborg’s personal spokesman. He said the attorney general wants the investigation to end and would prefer more transparency.“I would say, the attorney general shares the governor’s sentiment and would like to see this come to a conclusion, or at least remarks from the investigators on the time forecast on when this might be wrapped up,” he said last month.In the course of her probe, Sovell has sought the counsel of Beadle County State’s Attorney Michael Moore and Pennington County State’s Attorney Mark Vargo, as well as the Minnehaha County State’s Attorney’s Office.Moore said the prosecutor has four options in this case.“When dealing with an automobile accident that results in a death of another person, the law provides four different actions of an operator of the motor vehicle,” he said. “Negligent, careless, reckless, and intentional. Vehicle homicide and vehicle battery require the operator to be under the influence and also operating the vehicle in a negligent manner.“In order for the operator to be criminally responsible for the death (if they are not under the influence) their actions must be reckless or intentional,” Moore said. “The South Dakota Legislature, I believe in 2019, rejected a negligent homicide law, thus leaving reckless or intentional actions as the only means of an operator to have criminal liability.”‘I hit something’The 911 call Ravnsborg made after the crash was released a month later. He mentioned his title right away when the dispatcher answered.“This… well… Ally, I’m the attorney general. And I am… I don’t know… I hit something.”Dispatcher: “You hit something?”Caller: “By Highmore. Highmore. And it was in the middle of the road.”The location remains under dispute. A South Dakota Highway Patrol report states that Ravnsborg’s car was actually on the north shoulder when he struck Boever.The crash site is on the west edge of town. A convenience store is nearby, as are a gas station, a machinery business, and a state Department of Transportation shop. All have lights that are on all night, so the fatal crash didn’t happen in the darkness of a prairie night.“I’ve driven the highway in the middle of the night many times since Joe's death,” Nemec told The Daily Beast. “The area between two reflector posts is lit up from your headlights bright enough to see a mouse running across the road.”The speed limit increases to 65 mph a few feet from where Ravnsborg struck Boever, who was apparently walking back to town. He had driven his pickup off the road earlier in the evening—the cause will never be known—and struck a large round bale in the ditch.Boever, 55, who had worked in nursing homes and a grocery store and as a farm hand, called his cousin and friend Victor Nemec, who lives nearby and came to pick him up. They left and planned to return in the morning to repair and retrieve the truck.A few hours later, for some reason, Boever decided to walk to his pickup, carrying a light. As he returned, and just a minute or two before he would have turned off Highway 14 to walk down Iowa Avenue, Highmore’s wide main thoroughfare, he was struck and killed.That’s when things got weird.After Ravnsborg called 911, Hyde County Sheriff Mike Volek, who lives at a nearby rural address, responded. Ravnsborg claims he didn’t know what he struck, but the dispatcher suggested it could have been a deer. They are common sights in the countryside, and vehicle-on-deer crashes are regular events.Ravnsborg, 44, said he used the flashlight app on his cellphone but could not find the object he had struck. His car was not drivable, with the passenger side front and the windshield extensively damaged.At the crash scene, tire marks clearly showed Ravnsborg’s car had moved sharply to the north and come to a stop 100 feet or less from where Boever’s body, later identified by his cousins, was discovered. Nick Nemec, in red, and his brother, Victor, at the site where their cousin Joe Boever was struck and killed by South Dakota Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg on Sept. 12. Courtesy Tom Lawrence It’s unclear how hard Volek, who has refused to speak to the media, looked for the deer or whatever the attorney general had struck. A tow truck was called, and the driver removed the 2011 Ford Taurus, which was Ravnsborg’s personal car.While all this activity was underway, Boever’s body was on the side of the road on the north shoulder, inches from the westbound land. There it would remain for approximately 10 hours.Was he killed immediately? Could help have been summoned? Those are just two of the unanswered questions surrounding this case.Ravsnborg had been in Redfield, a small town 70 miles away, where he had appeared at a GOP gathering. He was returning home to Pierre, the state capital, when he hit Boever.Ravnsborg said he had not consumed any alcohol that day. The manager of Rooster’s Bar &amp; Grill in Redfield, where the event had been held, declined to answer this reporter in September when asked if Ravnsborg had been served a drink, saying it was “an open investigation.”Volek did not give Ravnsborg a blood-alcohol test. In fact, he loaned the attorney general, whom he knew, his private car so he could drive home to Pierre.Then another truly bizarre twist unfolded.Early Sept. 13, Ravnsborg was returning the sheriff’s car, accompanied by Tim Bormann, his chief of staff and a former Faulk County state’s attorney, in another vehicle. Ravnsborg said he spotted a body on the side of the road and alerted the sheriff.“I discovered the body of Mr. Boever in the grass just off the roadway,” Ravnsborg said in a statement released Sept. 14. “It was apparent that he was dead,” he added.At this point, around 15 hours after the accident, Ravnsborg did have a blood test, which showed no sign of alcohol.The crash was investigated by the South Dakota Highway Patrol, which is under state Secretary of Public Safety Craig Price’s supervision, with assistance from other law enforcement agencies.‘A minute either way’Price said evidence indicates Ravnsborg was distracted, but he has not provided details. Was he on the phone? Was he adjusting his radio? Why did he not see Boever, who was dressed in dark clothing?The attorney general has a history of driving offenses, including six speeding tickets in South Dakota and two in Iowa between 2014 and 2018. He also was cited for a seat belt violation and driving without a proper muffler and exhaust system. In all cases, he pleaded guilty and paid small fines.Ravnsborg—a lieutenant colonel in the Army Reserves who has served 24 years in uniform—sought the Republican nomination for a U.S. Senate seat in 2014. He lost to former Gov. Mike Rounds, who was elected to his second term in the Senate in November.Deaver said while Ravnsborg has been through difficult situations before, he has been deeply impacted by this.“Absolutely, I talk to him on a very regular basis,” he said in January. “This is tough on him personally, and he certainly feels for the family and for the public and wants it to be concluded.”Nick Nemec said he fears Boever has been forgotten in all the discussion about Ravnsborg.“I’m afraid so. He was a mild-mannered guy and often overlooked in life,” he said last month. “Although I was pleased to have many people come forward to me who said he was kind to them at his grocery store job, and always remembered their name and details.”To Nemec’s mind, the fatal crash could have so easily been avoided.“Yeah, a minute either way would have made the difference,” he said, wondering what Boever might have done differently. “Had he stopped to take a leak by a ditch bale, the AG would have missed him. He might have driven in the ditch 100 yards before Joe got there—and Joe would have helped him get out of the ditch.”The Nemecs, both area farmers, said they just want the truth to emerge. Nick, a former Democratic state legislator and Public Utility Commission candidate, has another wish.“I will do all I can to try to ensure Jason Ravnsborg is never elected to another public office,” he said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece's #MeToo leads to calls for reckoning on incest...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/greeces-metoo-movement-leads-calls-113710824.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece's emerging #MeToo movement, sparked by an Olympian's taboo-breaking decision to go public with allegations of sexual abuse, has raised hopes it can also uncover long-hidden stories of incest in the patriarchal country.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
