<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China Military Preparing for U.S. Intervention in Taiwan Strait...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/chinas-military-preparing-us-intervention-taiwan-strait-1579788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts in Beijing and Taipei said the Chinese military's pincer movement around Taiwan on Monday was the PLA's way of showing it could isolate the island in the event of a conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron under pressure to lock down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/31/europe/france-macron-lockdown-coronavirus-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron is expected to tighten coronavirus restrictions on Wednesday as case numbers and admissions to intensive care units soar across France, where the government has been resisting a third nationwide lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Empty Amsterdam, Reconsidering Tourism...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/31/in-empty-amsterdam-reconsidering-tourism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When international travel came to a halt last year, Amsterdam — like cities everywhere — was drained of tourists almost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brisk Walking Good for Aging Brain...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/31/brisk-walking-is-good-for-the-aging-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brisk walking improves brain health and thinking in aging people with memory impairments, according to a new, yearlong study of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD: MILLION MIGRANTS COULD CROSS BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-border/more-than-a-million-migrants-expected-at-us-mexico-border-this-year-us-official-idUSKBN2BM3FN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top U.S. border official said on Tuesday he expects more than a million migrants will arrive at the U.S.-Mexico border this year, a sign of a growing humanitarian challenge for President Joe Biden on the southwest border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden $2.25 Trillion Investment Plan to Rival Space Race... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/biden-to-lay-out-us-economic-renewal-in-rejuvenated-pittsburgh/ar-BB1f8zAk </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's First' Animal Jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2021/03/31/worlds-first-animal-covid-19-vaccine-registered-in-russia--heres-what-that-means/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of mink were culled due to widespread outbreaks of Covid-19, sparking fears for the future of the fur industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's girlfriend 'ready to die on Mars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/elon-musks-girlfriend-ready-die-23826057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Elon Musk's girlfriend Grimes, whose real name is Claire Elise Boucher and is a Canadian musician, has said on Instagram that she is willing to die on the red planet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER says shot 100% effective in kids 12 to 15...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/31/covid-vaccine-pfizer-says-shot-is-100percent-effective-in-kids-ages-12-to-15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer plans to submit the new vaccine data to the FDA "as soon as possible," CEO Albert Bourla said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle rages over 'passports'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/545670-battle-rages-over-vaccine-passports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are up in arms over the possibility that businesses and local governments may require vaccine passports for people to get access to certain activities, buildings or events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 3 GEORGE FLOYD CASE: Firefighter blocked from helping returns to stand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trials-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-minneapolis-us-news-00cfa62f9b1c12076316845c100d6b97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A Minneapolis firefighter who voiced frustration at being prevented from using her EMT training to help George Floyd will be back on the stand Wednesday in the trial of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G GORDON LIDDY DEAD AT 90...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/g-gordon-liddy-undercover-operative-convicted-in-watergate-scandal-dies-at-90/ar-BB1f8CKT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His can-do ruthlessness, loyalty to Nixon and ends-justify-the-means philosophy made him a natural fit in a White House determined to get even with its political enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgue workers accused of stealing from the dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/2-medical-examiners-accused-of-stealing-thousands-of-dollars-from-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two mortuary technicians in the New York City medical examiner’s office are accused of using credit and debit cards belonging to the dead to steal thousands of dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor's wife plotted his murder amid love triangle, authorities say...</title>
      <link>https://kfor.com/news/local/court-documents-giving-further-details-into-alleged-love-triangle-involving-murdered-ada-pastor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kfor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two arrests were made in the murder of Ada pastor David Evans. The Oklahoma State Bureau of Investigation tells KFOR his wife, Kristie Evans, was arrested Wednesday after confessing to his murder a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE WAS 17?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9420481/Rep-Matt-Gaetz-investigation-sex-trafficking-teenage-girl-17.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican congressman fired out a series of tweets Tuesday claiming a former DOJ employee was trying to extort $25 million from him and slamming the allegations as 'lies.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Actor Shares Homophobic DMs from NBA Superstar Kevin Durant...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2938918-michael-rapaport-shares-homophobic-misogynistic-dms-from-kevin-durant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Michael Rapaport posted screenshots Tuesday of a conversation between himself and Kevin Durant , in which the Brooklyn Nets star used homophobic, misogynistic and profane ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA COVID NUMBERS GET NEW SCRUTINY; RESEARCH FINDS 5,000 MORE DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-covid-numbers-face-new-scrutiny-090058319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research published earlier this month in the American Journal of Public Health argues that Florida is undercounting the number of people who have died from COVID-19 by thousands of cases, casting new doubt on claims that Gov. Ron DeSantis navigated the pandemic successfully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skin 'peeled off' in rare reaction to JOHNSON &amp; JOHNSON...</title>
      <link>https://www.wric.com/news/local-news/goochland-county-man-suffers-rare-severe-reaction-to-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wric.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: GRAPHIC IMAGES Richard Terrell was released from the hospital and is now sharing his vaccination story as he recovers. He tells 8News that he’s still very weak and that it will take …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People's Expensive NFTs Keep Vanishing...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkdj79/peoples-expensive-nfts-keep-vanishing-this-is-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There was no history of my ever purchasing it, or ever owning it,” said one confused NFT buyer. “Now there’s nothing. My money’s gone.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINUTES' TOP SHOW IN PRIMETIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.viacomcbspressexpress.com/cbs-news/releases/view?id=57259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.viacomcbspressexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50%  in UK now have antibodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/30/about-50-of-people-in-uk-have-antibodies-against-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study by Office for National Statistics based on data from blood test results across four nations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidency is over. So are many relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/03/trump-friend-family-relationships/618457/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden wants the country to heal from its political divisions. But some people say they aren’t ready to reconnect with their estranged friends and family members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake's mansion stormed by knife-wielding woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/2610995/drake-toronto-home-stormed-knife-wielding-woman-arrested-striking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAKE’S Toronto mansion was stormed by a knife-wielding woman who allegedly “struck a security guard with a pipe.”  Law enforcement confirmed to The Sun that an adult female who was carrying a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which world leader has worst pandemic record? Competition is fierce...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/Which-world-leader-has-the-worst-pandemic-record-16064411.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A catastrophic pandemic and a calamitous presidency combined to give the United States...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents of 5 killed by falling redwood...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/Jessica-Jake-Woodruff-falling-redwood-death-199-16061157.php?IPID=SFGate-HP-CP-Spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials called it a very unusual tragic accident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  17% SAY WAS 'GREAT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2021/03/29/a-partisan-chasm-in-views-of-trumps-legacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans and Democrats offer starkly different assessments of Donald Trump’s presidential legacy, a new survey finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather Service internet systems crumbling as key platforms are taxed and fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Weather-Service-internet-systems-crumbling-as-key-16064001.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service experienced a major, systemwide internet failure Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite NYC Hospital Charges $3,358 for Test...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/it-felt-like-deception-an-elite-nyc-hospital-charges-huge-covid-test-fees/ar-BB1f83i0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lenox Hill Hospital in Manhattan advertised its “Covid-19 Testing” on a large blue and white banner outside its Greenwich Village division’s emergency room. The banner said nothing about cost. But cost turned out to be the testing’s most noteworthy feature. Lenox Hill, one of the city’s oldest and best-known hospitals, repeatedly billed patients more than $3,000 for the routine nasal swab test, about 30 times the test’s typical cost. “It was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Epstein forced real estate broker to have sex with judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-lawsuit-names-jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-and-alleges-actions-sinister-even-by-his-standards/ar-BB1f8u9x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — In early 2008, as financier Jeffrey Epstein’s lawyers were waging what would become a successful campaign to get the Justice Department to drop its sex trafficking case against their client, Epstein and his purported madam, Ghislaine Maxwell, were allegedly raping a 26-year-old South Florida real estate broker who claims in a lawsuit filed last week that Epstein trafficked her to other ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers giving in-person instruction to migrant kids -- but not own students?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/psaki-migrant-kids-teachers-in-person-instruction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: White House press secretary Jen Psaki on Tuesday was grilled about San Diego public school teachers volunteering to teach migrant children in-person before returning to the classroom to teach the students in their own district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO scrambles jets 10 times to track Russian military planes across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/30/politics/nato-russia-jets/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO scrambled fighter jets 10 times Monday to track and intercept an unusually "rare peak" of Russian bombers and fighters flying over the North Sea, Black Sea and Baltic Sea, according to a NATO official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 Senate Dems urge recurring stimulus checks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/30/stimulus-check-update-senators-push-biden-to-send-recurring-payments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden is set to unveil his infrastructure and recovery plan, and some Democrats want it to include emergency economic aid like stimulus payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil rocked by political turmoil as pandemic outlook darkens...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Brazil-is-rocked-by-political-turmoil-as-pandemic-16064821.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO - Six cabinet members are out. The military's top leaders are also gone....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police bust 'world's biggest' video-game-cheat operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56579449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese police seize a collection of luxury sports cars in the raid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOUSEWIVES' star busted for alleged fraud, money laundering...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/03/30/real-housewives-star-jen-shah-busted-for-alleged-fraud-money-laundering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embattled “Real Housewives of Salt Lake City” cast member Jen Shah was arrested by the feds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands held in cramped Texas tent facility...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/30/more-than-4000-migrants-many-children-packed-in-texas-facility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US government’s main border detention facility for migrant children is an overcrowded tent structure currently packed with more than 4,000 people, despite a 250 person capacity, it was re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$4 TRILLION spending plan...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/30/biden-to-announce-up-to-4-trillion-infrastructure-plan-with-tax-hike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will outline his massive $3 to 4 trillion infrastructure plan Wednesday, which will create four tax increases worth around $1.8 trillion, the White House revealed. Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Company's Bid to Buy Military Tech Firm Raises National Security Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://insidesources.com/singapore-companys-bid-to-buy-military-tech-firm-raises-national-security-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;insidesources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A buyout bid from a Singapore-based aerospace and defense company for Cubic Corp. of San Diego is the latest flashpoint in a fundamental debate about the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAETZ IN SEX PROBE</title>
      <link>https://axios.com/matt-gaetz-sexual-misconduct-investigation-2755fd4f-f72e-4283-b8ac-9233c952b914.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The allegations against me are as searing as they are false," Gaetz said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big tech, Nevada repair shops clash over 'right to repair'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/legislature-nevada-coronavirus-pandemic-cd337d1335c7f27aea8f5a82e94bead3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARSON CITY, Nev. (AP) — Trade groups representing big tech companies faced off with independent repair shop owners Monday during a committee hearing in the Nevada Legislature over a proposal that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON vote may spark more union pushes... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-amazoncom-inc-alabama-health-coronavirus-pandemic-747ea42198655bfbca000c2e0665c3ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happens inside a warehouse in Bessemer, Alabama, could have major implications not just for the country's second-largest employer but the labor movement at large. Organizers are pushing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heir to O? Drew Barrymore launches lifestyle mag...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2021/mar/30/drew-barrymore-launches-quarterly-us-lifestyle-magazine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor and talkshow host will also pen an agony aunt column for Drew, to be published by Bauer Media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARPA Developing Giant Flying Aircraft Carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2606638/usa-darpa-flying-aircraft-carrier-nick-fury-avengers-ship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON is planning to change the face of warfare with the development of flying aircraft carriers. The experimental planes would take the form of a mothership that deploys drones instead of f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to restore Jewish names to phonetic alphabet...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/germany-to-restore-jewish-names-to-phonetic-alphabet-663581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA double-charged some customers for new cars, leaving them desperate for refunds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/29/tesla-double-charged-some-customers-for-new-cars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla double-charged some customers for new cars. Now those customers are trying to get refunds for the added charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey reimposes restrictions after sharp rise in infections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/turkey-coronavirus-pandemic-recep-tayyip-erdogan-ankara-europe-22adbf45d3773d1e84f05788ec73dae5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Turkey is re-introducing weekend lockdowns in most of its provinces and will also impose restrictions over the Muslim holy month of Ramadan following a sharp increase in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 2  George Floyd case: 'I witnessed a murder'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/derek-chauvin-trial-latest-updates-bba19d0f75c2cd71c135eed69f5e8200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A man who was among the onlookers shouting at a Minneapolis police officer to get off George Floyd last May testified Tuesday that he called 911 after paramedics took Floyd...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUIR'S 'WORLD NEWS' #1 ACROSS ALL BROADCAST AND CABLE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/647095514870988800/for-first-time-in-25-years-world-news-tonight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAST WEEK MARKS ONE YEAR STRAIGHT WITH ‘WORLD NEWS TONIGHT’ WINNING IN TOTAL VIEWERS, ADULTS 25-54 AND ADULTS 18-49 ‘World News Tonight’ Is Delivering Largest Season Viewership in 16 Years 1st Quarter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suez canal chaos blamed on 'Pharaoh's curse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14495350/suez-chaos-train-crash-blamed-move-body-king/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SERIES of unfortunate incidents in Egypt including the Suez Canal chaos and a train crash that killed 32 have been pinned on the so-called curse of the Pharaohs by superstitious social media user…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Promotes Kayleigh McEnany to Host...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/fox-news-promotes-kayleigh-mcenany-to-host-of-outnumbered-after-initially-balking-in-wake-of-capitol-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House Press Secretary Kayleigh McEnany is already reportedly getting promoted to a Fox News hosting gig.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GAME OF THRONES' headed to B'WAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/game-of-thrones-play-in-the-works-for-broadway-will-revive-iconic-characters-exclusive </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A live stage spectacular will bring fan-favorites like Ned Stark and Jaime Lannister back to life in a new story from George R.R. Martin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas UFO hotspot as military testing secret tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/las-vegas-ufo-hotspot-military-23822643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Nick Pope spent three years working for the Ministry of Defence's UFO department and claims sightings above Las Vegas could be down to the military testing technology "seen in sci-fi films"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus surges globally...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-cases-rising-around-world-europe-india-7e3e9d42-4eba-4b16-8a35-490e6f7a864c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Europe to Brazil to India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN EYES 39.6% TOP RATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-tax-plan-increases-b8905001-1ef2-45c8-8165-87ac89d1c2fe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four tax increases are worth about $1.8 trillion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN NOMINATES FIRST MUSLIM FEDERAL JUDGE IN U.S. HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-federal-courts-judges-diversity-nominees-d9bd49e9-d249-4fea-8381-edfc7e7de7c9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zahid N. Quraishi would be the first Muslim American to serve on the federal bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARPA Developing Giant Flying Aircraft Carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2606638/usa-darpa-flying-aircraft-carrier-nick-fury-avengers-ship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON is planning to change the face of warfare with the development of flying aircraft carriers. The experimental planes would take the form of a mothership that deploys drones instead of f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD: 800,000 MIGRANTS COULD CROSS BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9418437/Kamala-Harris-lead-diplomatic-efforts-border-numbers-double.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House officials are downplaying Kamala Harris' first major public charge as Department of Homeland Security statistics show the number of migrants crossing the border could double.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan departs in Honduras...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210330134438-9fb26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/HONDURAS (PIX):Migrant caravan of hundreds departs in Honduras for United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball Cards Go Crypto as Auction Houses Warm to New Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/baseball-cards-go-crypto-as-auction-houses-warm-to-new-currency/ar-BB1f7iNQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldin Auctions, the trading card and memorabilia auction house, is the latest to hop on the crypto bandwagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're doing shots! Vaccinated or not, America wants to party again...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/article/We-re-doing-shots-Vaccinated-or-not-America-16063404.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been over a year since Ryn Pfeuffer slipped into her black sheer bodysuit, fastened...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'death-streaming' craze where YOUTUBE viewers pay to watch torture, humiliation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14466280/russias-disturbing-trash-streaming-trend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DARK and sinister new trend has emerged in live streaming as sick YouTubers inflict torture, bury people alive and even kill for cash. Known as “trash-streaming”, the disturbing yet l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery brain disorder baffles Canadian medicine...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/30/mystery-brain-disorder-baffles-canadian-medicine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spasms, memory loss and hallucinations among symptoms of patients, mostly in Acadian peninsula of New Brunswick province</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How COVID-Infested Cruise Ship Devolved Into Class Warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-a-covid-infested-cruise-ship-devolved-into-class-warfare/ar-BB1f7oLV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the final evening of a two-week cruise with stops in Hong Kong, Vietnam, Taiwan, and Japan, the 3,700-plus passengers and crew members aboard the Diamond Princess ship received a message from their captain. “Please be advised that we have been notified that a Hong Kong resident who traveled for five days on Diamond Princess from Yokohama to Hong Kong tested positive for coronavirus,” he announced. “As you can see ladies and gentlemen, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC unveils next-gen series...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/30/virgin-galactic-unveils-vss-imagine-the-first-of-spaceship-iii-series.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rollout of VSS Imagine gives the space tourism company a second spacecraft to begin testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE: SPACEX rocket crashes during landing attempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/30/spacex-launches-starship-sn11-but-appears-to-crash-on-landing-attempt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest SpaceX prototype of its Starship rocket appears to have been destroyed during a landing attempt after a clean launch on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Hypnosis Changes Way Brain Processes Information...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hypnosis-changes-brain-processes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While hypnotized, the brain seems to "shift gears" toward a more singular approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic people could become reality, scientists researching snake venom say...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/world/arid-40254002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mice and even humans have the potential to become venomous – giving a new meaning to the description of someone as a toxic person – according to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Former Convent Became $40 Million L.A. House...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amydobson/2021/03/29/how-a-former-convent-became-this-40-million-la-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once a convent, this $40 million listing is one of the most expensive in Los Angeles' Silver Lake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Thriving Marriage, Sex Life -- Playfulness...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/playfulness-key-to-thriving-happy-love-life-relationship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprising your partner or recreating special moments through role play are some of the playful things that can boost one's relationship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's rarest great ape on brink of extinction...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/sustainability/environment/545427-worlds-rarest-great-ape-is-on-the-brink-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tapanuli orangutan, the most endangered great ape species, is at a greater risk of extinction than previously thought because of rapid habitat loss and unsustainable hunting, according to a new scientific report published at the beginning of January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Flight Test Of Air Force Hypersonic Missile Imminent...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39975/signs-point-to-imminent-debut-flight-test-of-the-air-forces-first-hypersonic-missile</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the pieces appear to be falling into place for what will be a historic event for the Air Force and American hypersonic weapons development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected men have three times risk of developing ED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9418125/Covid-19-Men-contract-coronavirus-THREE-TIMES-risk-developing-erectile-dysfunction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors at the University of Rome asked 100 men, with an average age of 33, to report recent problems with sexual function. Three times as many Covid survivors suffered erectile dysfunction afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4th wave...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/545505-new-covid-19-cases-surge-12-percent-in-past-week-fourth-wave-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New coronavirus cases in the United States have surged by double digits over the last seven days, as the country prepares for another potentially deadly wave of infections and hospitalizations in the coming weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two space fans get seats on billionaire's private flight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-tennessee-memphis-0a1221b78bba4ae53fb2613bb86e9f7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A billionaire’s private SpaceX flight filled its two remaining seats Tuesday with a scientist-teacher and a data engineer whose college friend actually won a spot but...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian American woman, 65, beaten in racist attack, NYPD says. Bystanders didn't help, video suggests...</title>
      <link>https://www.news10.com/news/ny-news/watch-elderly-asian-american-woman-assaulted-outside-nyc-apartment-building-as-staff-look-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are trying to identify a man accused of punching and kicking a woman outside a New York City apartment building as he made anti-Asian remarks toward her Monday, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union vote to have broad implications for labor nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/amazon-labor-balloting-ending</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voting on whether to unionize workers at an Amazon facility in Alabama is set to end on Monday as the company feuds with politicians over a vote that could have nationwide implications for organized labor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>76 all-cash offers on one home. Housing madness shows no signs of slowing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/29/success/when-will-housing-market-cool-off-feseries/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen Coleman had never received so many offers on a house in her 15 years of selling real estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Dakota wildfires prompt mass evacuations, shut down Mount Rushmore...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-wildfires-rapid-city-evacuations-9281e741f0583f85b311acf35c7b2b73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEMO, S.D. (AP) — Three separate wildfires in the Black Hills of South Dakota have forced evacuations of more than 400 homes northwest of Rapid City and shut down Mount Rushmore, authorities said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 4,000 MPH Passenger Jet...</title>
      <link>https://robbreport.com/motors/aviation/aerion-as3-airliner-1234604004/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;robbreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commercial jet will be able to transport 500 passengers at speeds nearing 4,000 miles per hour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans Rapidly Losing Ability to Procreate, Scientist Warns...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/neoscope/humans-are-rapidly-losing-the-ability-to-procreate-scientist-warns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Shanna Swan says that fertility rates are rapidly declining throughout western nations — and she says chemicals are largely to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World leaders call for pandemic treaty...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-mario-draghi-rwanda-coronavirus-pandemic-covid-19-pandemic-9b5db1741b963094736ff1e2606b4326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — More than 20 heads of government and global agencies called in a commentary published Tuesday for an international treaty for pandemic preparedness that they say will protect future...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence reemerges, lays groundwork for 2024 run...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-michael-pence-ted-cruz-ron-desantis-josh-hawley-df46fb0af0c353a2f13d265bd041cffe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When former President Donald Trump was asked to list those he considers the future leaders of the Republican Party, he quickly rattled off names including Florida Gov. Ron...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
