<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Beats Top and Bottom Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/27/microsoft-msft-earnings-q3-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft delivered better-than-expected revenue growth thanks in part to strong PC sales in the quarter. Azure revenue growth was flat from the prior quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmanned helicopter crashes into Navy ship...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/04/27/mq-8b-fire-scout-crashes-into-littoral-combat-ship-uss-charleston-on-deployment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An MQ-8B Fire Scout unmanned aerial vehicle crashed into the side of Littoral Combat Ship USS Charleston (LCS-18) after taking off from the ship today, the Navy announced. The rotary-wing UAV was operating from the ship around 9:40 a.m. when the collision happened in the Eastern Pacific, according to a U.S. 3rd Fleet news release. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Footage of NRA LaPierre's Botched Elephant Hunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/the-secret-footage-of-nra-chief-wayne-lapierres-botched-elephant-hunt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief executive has cultivated his image as an exemplar of American gun culture, but video of his clumsy marksmanship—and details regarding his Rodeo Drive shopping trips—tells another story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Blair shocks with 'mullet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/viewers-shock-tony-blair-unveils-23994473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-Labour Party leader's straggly locks saw him trending on Twitter, along with the likes of ‘lookalikes’ Gerry Francis and Peter Stringfellow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas shortages predicted this summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/27/business/summer-gasoline-shortage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people stuck at home for more than a year are expected to hit the road for much-needed post-pandemic vacations this summer. Good luck finding gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Have I touched people? Yes,' Cuomo admits on sex harass complaints...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/27/have-i-touched-people-yes-cuomo-admits-on-sex-harass-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo admitted Tuesday that he has “touched people” amid mounting allegations of sexual harassment against him. “Have I touched people? Yes,” Cuomo matter-of-factly responded during a C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER at-home pill could be available by year-end...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/27/pfizer-at-home-covid-pill-could-be-available-by-year-end-ceo-albert-bourla-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company in March began an early stage clinical trial testing a new antiviral therapy for Covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian President Unleashes Profane Rant...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/palestinian-president-unleashes-profane-rant-against-rest-of-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinian president Mahmoud Abbas was recently caught badmouthing several countries, including the United States and his Arab neighbors, during a profanity-laced rant that raises new concerns about the 85-year-old leader's deteriorating health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu ignores law to appoint loyalist justice minister...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/netanyahu-appoint-loyalist-justice-minister-7d8843d4-5d47-4361-8e07-c01d090f1cbe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is on trial, and six days from losing his mandate to form a government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Powerful Person in Washington? Senate Parliamentarian...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/27/lobbyist-reconciliation-484765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Budget reconciliation, which lets the party in power pass bills without the minority, has changed the game on K Street and Pennsylvania Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 50+ Dogs Removed From Feces-Covered, Trash-Filled Residence...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/26/texas-dogs-living-3-feet-feces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement officials joined The Humane Society of North Texas in removing more than 50 dogs from a dilapidated, trash-filled and feces-covered home still inhabited by its human owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER account goes silent after PUBLIX objects...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/gainesville-florida-business-technology-df8fb4ac5789926e7e27c7b2686ffcf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAINESVILLE, Fla. (AP) — A popular Twitter account that notified people when Publix chicken-tender subs were on sale has been abandoned after lawyers for the Florida-based grocery chain apparently objected. The account “Are Publix Chicken Tender Subs On Sale?” — with nearly 40,000 followers — has been dormant since March 11. One of its final tweets noted that the subs were, indeed, on sale, and added ominously: “This may be our last Tweet.” Since then, it stopped sharing updates altogether. An accompanying Facebook page also went silent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger as ex-generals warn of civil war in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-56899765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ministers condemn the open letter, which was published on the 60th anniversary of a failed coup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi accused of being covert Christian missionary...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/27/jerusalem-rabbi-accused-of-being-covert-christian-missionary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultra-Orthodox rabbi in Jerusalem stands accused of being an undercover Christian missionary with his family, originally from New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brussels bracing for illegal festival amid fears of violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-lifestyle-government-and-politics-europe-brussels-74df6024cd20738f523206928b764930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Brussels prosecutor's office warned potential partygoers they should stay away from an unauthorized gathering planned this weekend in one of the city's biggest parks as police briefly detained one of the organizers on Tuesday. After an April Fools’ party drew thousands of people to Brussels’ Bois de la Cambre and ended in clashes with police last month, a sequel to the the event has been advertised by a group called the Abyss for Saturday in the same park. In a statement Tuesday, prosecutors said the manager in charge of the group's Facebook page was arrested and questioned as part of an investigation into the party before he got released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUI driver kills cop investigating DUI crash.</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-killed-while-directing-traffic-on-long-island-expressway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NYPD officer was killed by a hit-and-run driver early Tuesday while directing traffic on the Long Island Expressway in Queens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZEROHEDGE</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Saudi Lobbyists Monitored Activists At DC Summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.theuprising.info/p/documents-show-saudi-lobbyists-monitored</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theuprising.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia Mohammed bin Salman al Saud during diplomatic talks in Riyadh in 2019..(Photo by Mikhail Metzel\TASS via Getty Images) In March of 2016, about 250 activists gathered at a law school in Washington D.C. for a summit where speakers blasted the alliance between the U.S. and Saudi Arabia. One of the people watching the proceedings was a junior staffer from a D.C. lobbying firm who monitored the proceedings for the Saudi government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia Will Pay Young People $100 To Get Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2021/04/27/991173625/west-virginia-will-pay-young-people-100-to-get-vaccinated-against-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican-led state will offer savings bonds to residents between the ages of 16 and 35 in an effort to tackle vaccine hesitancy among its younger population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Scraps Plans to Launch FOXNEWS-Style UK Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/news-corp-scraps-plans-to-launch-fox-news-style-u-k-network</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch's News Corp will not launch a fully fledged Fox News-style news channel in the U.K., finding that this would not be financially viable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustration Builds on Border as Canada Reopening Goes Slow...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/frustration-builds-on-world-s-longest-border-as-canada-goes-slow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustration Builds on World’s Longest Border as Canada Goes Slow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: NO MASK WITH VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-cdc-coronavirus-guidance-masks-190a4299-05f1-4690-b4c5-d7c4e2c2f38f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is expected to address the guidelines later today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma new lightning capital of America...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/florida-oklahoma-lightning-capital-of-america/938423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New technology shows that the state with the long-held reputation of being America’s lightning capital may no longer hold that dubious title.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman brutally whipped by Taliban -- for talking on phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2781337/woman-screams-brutally-whipped-by-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VILE footage of a woman screaming for mercy as she is savagely whipped 40 times by the Taliban for “talking to a man on the phone” has emerged. The shocking clip shows crowds of men wat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD DEAD?  Why Movies Will Survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/oscar-ratings-plunge-blame-un-fun-movies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar ratings are way down, and some prominent pop culture critics blame un-fun movies. These people are forgetting a kind of big thing that happened in 2020. Also: We’d like to help you make your movie. All in today’s Movie News Rundown. But First: Master of None is back, with less Aziz Ansari and more cottage […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetically Modified Mosquitoes Released In Florida Keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9514527/Florida-residents-say-release-BILLION-genetically-engineered-mosquitos-Keys-TERRORISM.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first-ever U.S. release of genetically engineered Aedes aegypti mosquitoes this week in the Florida Keys and residents are furious over the 'live experiment' saying it is terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Furious!</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/furious-gene-hacked-mosquitoes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They're using us for their bottom line."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market performance best since Eisenhower...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-business-coronavirus-economy-ff9a0848d26f49ceb4b2e78c474b8524</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Hiring is accelerating as Americans increasingly venture out to shop, eat at restaurants and travel, and inflation pressures are even picking up after lying dormant for years. Yet this week, the Federal Reserve is all but sure to reiterate its commitment to ultra-low interest rates. At a news conference Wednesday after the Fed's latest policy meeting ends, Chair Jerome Powell will likely underscore his view that the economy is far from fully recovered and needs the central bank’s continued support in the form of low borrowing costs. There are still 8 million fewer jobs than there were before the pandemic struck. And the unemployment rate, at 6%, though well below where it was a year ago, remains elevated. Powell has stressed that further gains in the job market are needed to help the many Americans — especially low-income workers and people of color — who have been disproportionately hurt by the loss of jobs and incomes and have yet to benefit from the early stages of the recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO of $2 Billion Startup Ousted for Taking LSD at Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/ceo-of-242-billion-startup-ousted-for-taking-lsd-at-work/ar-BB1g6oAa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Zhu, co-founder of Iterable, said he was trying microdosing as a way to boost focus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker compares kids wearing masks outside to child abuse. 'Call the police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tucker-carlson-urges-audience-to-call-the-police-immediately-if-they-see-kids-wearing-masks-outdoors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During his Monday night show on Fox News, Tucker Carlson railed against wearing masks outdoors and told viewers to “call the police immediately” if they see children doing so. He also said seeing vaccinated people wear masks outside is like “watching a grown man expose himself in public.” After declaring, “The only people who wear […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk, Bezos collide after SPACEX wins moon landing contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/blue-origin-protests-nasas-awarding-moon-lander-contract-spacex-2021-04-26/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space race between the world's two richest men went into hyperdrive on Tuesday after Tesla chief Elon Musk took a swipe at Jeff Bezos' attempt to challenge a major NASA contract.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Can't get it up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/elon-musk-teases-jeff-bezos-battle-space-contract</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla and SpaceX CEO teased Amazon founder Jeff Bezos on Monday night after it was reported that Bezos’ Blue Origin planned to contest a NASA award recently given to SpaceX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions rise as return-to-work plans gain steam...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/27/tensions-rise-as-return-to-work-plans-gain-steam.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Covid vaccinations increase, so are plans to return to the office, whether workers are ready or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funeral pyres in parks as Covid grips Delhi...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-56897970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India's capital struggles to find space to cremate its dead during the second wave of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Divide Between Vaccinated And Non-Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/04/27/the-growing-divide-between-the-vaccinated-and-the-non-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a difference a couple of months can make. The race to vaccinate has changed from a supply issue to a lack of demand issue. The result is a growing divide between the vaccinated and the not vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARVILLE: Wokeness is problem and we all know it...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/22338417/james-carville-democratic-party-biden-100-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Carville on the state of Democratic politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Night Shift' On Smartphone Does Not Help People Sleep Better...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/night-shift-smartphone-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Night Shift is not superior to using your phone without Night Shift or even using no phone at all,” researchers conclude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker compares kids wearing masks outside to child abuse. 'Call the police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article250971964.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“What you’re seeing is abuse. It’s child abuse, and you’re morally obligated to try to prevent it,” Carlson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raises minimum wage for federal contractors to $15 an hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/27/politics/minimum-wage-federal-contractors-biden/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two months after his effort to raise the federal minimum wage to $15 an hour ran into the Senate parliamentarian buzz saw, President Joe Biden is set to use his executive powers to hike the pay of hundreds of thousands of federal contract workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard's end: Shock jock Stern has lost his sting -- and his mojo...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/27/howard-stern-has-lost-his-sting-and-his-mojo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stern has no intention of ever returning to his Midtown studio, his luxury Upper West Side apartment, or any semblance of pre-pandemic life again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden fares better than Trump over his first 100 days...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210427103019-tr53f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/POLL (POLL, REPEAT, PIX, GRAPHICS):POLL-Biden fares better than Trump over his first 100 days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Now World's Best Place to Be During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/27/new-zealand-loses-top-spot-for-best-place-to-be-during-covid-to-singapore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slow vaccine rollout cited as the difference between the two countries, both of which have virtually no community coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No sign' of infection after Barcelona concert trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/no-sign-of-infection-after-barcelona-covid-concert-trial-organisers-2422979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has been "no sign" of coronavirus infection among 5,000 unvaccinated people who took part in an indoor trial concert last month in Barcelona seeking pandemic-safe ways to celebrate mass events, organisers said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Quality first gray horse favored to win Kentucky Derby in 25 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kentucky-derby-kentucky-sports-11c27d51c584e7649bee16344c9c2fac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Goodlett has walked around Churchill Downs many times since joining the Kentucky Derby Museum and heard admiring fans say to each other, “Oh, look at that beautiful gray horse.” Not many of those remarks have come while looking at the winner's circle after the Derby. Essential Quality is expected to be the first gray horse to go off as the Kentucky Derby favorite in 25 years. A gray horse hasn’t won the Derby since Giacomo in 2005, and only eight grays have won it since 1930.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami private school says teachers who get vax aren't welcome, citing debunked misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/miami-school-says-it-wont-employ-vaccinated-teachers-citing-debunked-covid-myths/3021437/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A private school in Miami is discouraging teachers from getting the COVID-19 vaccine— and in a letter to parents, the school says it will not employ anyone who has taken it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Proliferation of space junk blocking view of cosmos, research shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/a-proliferation-of-space-junk-is-blocking-our-view-of-the-cosmos-research-shows/ar-BB1g6inC </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed helped fuel stock boom that benefited wealthy -- and left behind everyone else...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-fed-helped-fuel-a-stock-market-boom-that-benefited-wealthy-americans-%E2%80%94-and-left-behind-everyone-else/ar-BB1g6f5R </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran, U.S. warships in first tense Mideast encounter in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/iran-u-s-warships-first-tense-mideast-encounter-year-n1265441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tehran did not immediately acknowledge the incident in the southern reaches of the Persian Gulf, which resulted in no injuries or damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiji fears virus 'tsunami' after outbreak found to be Indian variant...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210427-fiji-fears-virus-tsunami-after-outbreak-found-to-be-indian-variant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiji fears virus 'tsunami' after outbreak found to be Indian variant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years after death, Bin Laden still mobilizes jihadists...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210427-10-years-after-death-bin-laden-still-mobilises-jihadists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;10 years after death, Bin Laden still mobilises jihadists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup aims to leave mark with ephemeral tattoos...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/york-startup-aims-leave-mark-014632412.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neither a permanent mark nor a paper transfer: a New York start-up has created the first tattoos that fully disappear after a while, aiming to open the body inking market to new clientele.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC police server hacked, Russian-speaking group claims responsibility...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210427061403-k0165</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CYBER/WASHINGTONDC:Washington D.C. police server hacked, Russian-speaking group claims responsibility -reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooling the temperature: President faces fractious Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-coronavirus-pandemic-impeachments-barack-obama-4c79ff8d59f8ce19f9dae6b550223bf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Can lawmakers all just listen to the president — even for one night? Recent history is not assuring. Republican Rep. Joe Wilson shouted “you lie!” at President Barack Obama when he was giving a joint speech to Congress in 2009. Eleven years later, Democratic House Speaker Nancy Pelosi ripped up a copy of President Donald Trump’s State of the Union speech as she stood behind him on the House rostrum. Partisan tensions have only deepened on Capitol Hill since Pelosi’s defiant act last year, which came days before the Senate acquitted Trump in his first impeachment trial. Since then, the U.S. Capitol has been through the Jan. 6 insurrection , a second impeachment of Trump and another acquittal .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fancy French Winemakers Buying Big Vineyards from Americans Ready to Sell...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/posh-french-winemakers-pounce-on-big-american-vineyard-selloff/ar-BB1g5U4Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European vintners are finding toeholds in the U.S. just as some of America’s oldest wineries are ready to cash in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces mounting pressure on forgiving student loan debt...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/550339-biden-faces-mounting-pressure-on-forgiving-student-loan-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive groups are vowing to raise the heat on President Biden to cancel student debt, a priority issue for a number of Democratic lawmakers including Senate Majority Leader Charles Schumer (D-N.Y.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeks $80 Billion to Beef Up IRS Audits of High-Earners...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/27/biden-seeks-80-billion-to-beef-up-i-r-s-audits-of-high-earners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden, in an effort to pay for his ambitious economic agenda, is expected to propose giving the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL GOODWIN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/michael-goodwin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doomed submarine crew filmed singing in final video before all 53 died...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2778186/doomed-indonesia-submarine-crew-singing/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HAUNTING video shows a doomed submarine crew singing just weeks before all 53 of them died when the vessel sank. The chilling final footage of the Indonesian sailors shows them smiling around a g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.newsmax.com/insiders/michaelsavage/id-526/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KYLE SMITH</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/kyle-smith/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala has been visible.  But is she influential?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2021-04-26/kamala-harris-100-days-vice-president-influential</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris is often at President Biden’s side publicly, and plays a key role in selling his agenda, but her level of pull behind the scenes is uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80-year-old former NFL player accused of dealing cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/1960s-ny-giants-player-arrested-on-drug-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elderly former NFL player is accused of trying to sell a large amount of cocaine out of his Manhattan apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>https://www.creators.com/features/ben-shapiro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.creators.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL O'REILLY</title>
      <link>https://www.billoreilly.com/currentcolumn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billoreilly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN CALLAHAN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/maureen-callahan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11-Year-Old Whiz Kid Offering Financial Advice To More Than 5,000 Subscribers Online...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/04/26/rishi-vamdatt-easy-peasy-finance-financial-literacy-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People all over the world looking to learn about stocks, bonds and even how to improve their credit score are turning to a New Jersey sixth grader!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARLES HURT</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/staff/charles-hurt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two dead as suicidal man jumps off building, lands on woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/26/man-jumps-building-lands-woman-san-diego-both-die/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was killed when an apparently suicidal man jumped off a parking structure and landed on her in downtown San Diego, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S.E. CUPP</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/ny-se-cupp-staff.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>https://thebulwark.com/author/billkristol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATT TAIBBI</title>
      <link>https://taibbi.substack.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taibbi.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regular news and features by award-winning author and investigative reporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRANDA DEVINE</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/author/miranda-devine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://greenwald.substack.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;greenwald.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Independent, unencumbered analysis and investigative reporting, captive to no dogma or faction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BART</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/author/peter-bart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter moved to Deadline in 2016 from his longtime home at Variety, where he had been a fixture since 1989 as that trade's Editor-In Chief. He began his career as a staff reporter for The Wall Street Journal and The New York Times before his entry into the movie business, becoming Vice President for Production at Paramount. At that studio, he played a key role in such films as The Godfather, Rosemary’s Baby and Harold &amp; Maude. He later served as Senior Vice President for Production at MGM and, later, as President of Lorimar films. Peter is also the author of nine books, and is a member of PMC's board of advisors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL FLEMING</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/author/mikefleming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike joined Deadline in 2010 after working at Variety for 20 years as a reporter, writer and columnist. He was not only nationally recognized as Variety's premiere film reporter but also for his “Dish” and “The Buzz” columns. Mike is known for his industry relationships and his ability to break news wherever it happens, including on the ground at festivals like Sundance, Cannes and Toronto. He also is an author: Doubleday published his book about The Three Stooges, "From Amalgamated Morons to American Icons," which ABC turned into a telepic executive produced by Mel Gibson. One of Mike’s early jobs in journalism was editor of the well-known Media Industry Newsletter (MIN). He then joined New York Newsday as a columnist, reviewer and entertainment writer. During his career, he has written for numerous magazines including Playboy, Details, TV Guide and Esquire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARD TIME:  Appeals judges weigh Ghislaine Maxwell's harsh confinement at federal jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-ghislaine-maxwell-bail-appeal-20210426-5rk3l6bvezbttnmdequ66bee74-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judges for the 2nd Circuit Court of Appeals seemed alarmed Monday by Ghislaine Maxwell’s treatment behind bars, asking why it was necessary jail staff shine a light in her cell every 15 minutes overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB Founder's Mansion Burns Down 'in Suspected Arson'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9513573/Montreal-mansion-embattled-Pornhub-founder-burns-arson-fire.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syrian-born Pornhub founder Feras Antoon's, 45, unfinished Montreal home burned down Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Troubles Grow as UK Govt Battles Sleaze Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-s-troubles-grow-as-u-k-government-battles-sleaze-claims/ar-BB1g4Uic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson is facing mounting questions over the way he operates at the top of the government, as the row over allegations of sleaze and incompetence intensifies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos challenges NASA moon contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/jeff-bezos-challenges-nasa-moon-contract-award-to-elon-musk-e2-80-99s-spacex/ar-BB1g4Zz0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin said NASA had inappropriately allowed SpaceX to revise its pricing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will set $1 million threshold for capital gains tax hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/04/26/business/biden-set-1-million-threshold-capital-gains-tax-hike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden intends to raise capital gains taxes for those earning more than $1 million a year his top economic adviser confirmed Monday, arguing that the move would affect only a tiny share of American households.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California now has lowest coronavirus case rate in nation!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-coronavirus-case-rate-now-184916537.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's latest seven-day new case rate — 40.3 per 100,000 people — is dramatically lower than the nationwide rate of 135.3 over that same time period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Congress 'Bailout' Utah For $1.5 Billion --  When State Has A $1.5 Billion Budget Surplus?</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamandrzejewski/2021/04/26/why-did-congress-bailout-utah-for-15-billion--when-utah-has-a-15-billion-budget-surplus/?sh=36cd43a06929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans voted no, but took the dough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE ROLLS OUT DREADED 14.5...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/26/apple-ios-14point5-iphone-update-is-out-now-heres-whats-new.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOS 14.5 adds a lot of new features, such as privacy changes, new Siri voices and the option to unlock your iPhone with an Apple Watch if you're wearing a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY BACK AT FULL LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210426174032-vu2ja</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/TURKEY (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Turkey announces "full lockdown" from April 29 to curb COVID spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ GOES BUST</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arts-and-entertainment-entertainment-academy-awards-television-d17308440bfa7388a2d21ca8c2d7fee8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Academy Awards television audience plunged to 9.85 million viewers on ABC, less than half of the Oscars' previous low and continuing a startling trend of viewer tune out for awards shows. The Nielsen company's preliminary estimate shows that the audience who watched “Nomadland” win best picture on Sunday was 58% below last year's tally of 23.6 million, which had set the previous record for least-watched Oscars telecast. Following a year where movie theaters were mostly closed due to COVID-19, people were unexcited about or unfamiliar with movies they primarily streamed at home. Producers tried to fight through pandemic fatigue with a hostless program and a small, socially-distanced audience that didn't wear masks during the broadcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Winners and losers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/electoral-college-census-2020-government-and-politics-politics-86e1a31aeeea02004a3c71abd58097ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a year since the 2020 census began in a remote Alaska village, the first numbers to emerge from the nation's once-a-decade head count were released on Monday, showing how many congressional seats and Electoral College votes each state is getting based on its population. Because the number of seats in the House of Representatives is set at 435, it's a zero-sum game with one state's gain resulting in another state's loss — like a pie with uneven slices. As one state gets a larger slice because of population gains, that means a smaller slice for a state that lost population or didn't grow as much. Here's a look at the 13 states that will gain or lose political power — and federal money — through the apportionment process because of changes in population over the past decade:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Drought Drains CA Lake, Stunning Sea Of Purple Wildflowers Blooms In Place...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/04/25/theyre-incredible-people-visit-drained-folsom-lake-after-super-bloom-pops-up-in-its-place/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Folsom Lake doesn't look like much of a lake right now. A dry season drained the lake, but what popped up in its place has people in awe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC sees bloodiest week this year with 46 shootings...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/26/nyc-sees-bloodiest-week-this-year-with-46-shooting-incidents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYPD data shows 50 people were shot in 46 separate shooting incidents over a seven-day period ending Sunday evening — a more than 300 percent surge from the same week in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Court Reveals: FBI Hunted for Domestic Terrorists Without Warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/secret-court-reveals-fbi-hunted-for-domestic-terrorists-without-a-warrant/ar-BB1g4UPz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI, without any court order, sifted through the National Security Agency’s massive troves of foreign communications for information on American “racially motivated violent extremists,” a newly declassified order from the secret surveillance court details. Even though the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance (FISA) Court warned the FBI in 2018 that its warrant-free queries, known as backdoor searches, were constitutionally alarming, the bureau...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES retiring 'op-ed'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/26/the-new-york-times-is-retiring-the-word-op-ed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Old Gray Lady’s opinion pages will simply refer to columns by the paper’s staff writers and editorial board as editorials and pieces by external contributors as “guest essays.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
