<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HELL:  Ebola worker shot dead at hospital in eastern DR Congo...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ebola-worker-killed-hospital-eastern-dr-congo-181745813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health worker fighting an Ebola outbreak in DR Congo was shot dead Friday in an attack on a hospital in the eastern city of Butembo, the World Health Organization said. The WHO said that Dr. Richard Valery Mouzoko Kiboung, an epidemiologist it had deployed to help rein in the Ebola outbreak, was killed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 40 Years, C-SPAN Founder Signs Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/after-40-years-c-spans-founder-signs-off-11555713751?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Lamb, the man who put Congress on live television, reflects on the results and explains why the Supreme Court ought to be next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr v. Mueller: Friends pitted against each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/18/barr-mueller-friends-against-each-other-1282649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite close ties, the attorney general and special counsel face increasing scrutiny of their disagreements on the Trump probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOTAL BULLSH*T'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-seethes-foul-mouthed-tirade-against-mueller-report-152111210.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seething President Donald Trump launched a tirade Friday against the "bullshit" Mueller report on how he tried to thwart the probe into Russian interference in the 2016 election, while a leading Democratic opponent urged his impeachment. Just 24 hours earlier, the president crowed "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Numb To It All?</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/e4321f0fea1d4d57acf971a83d96c3a7/after-2-years-russia-probe-drips-are-you-numb-it-all</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For two years there's been the drip-drip-drip of the Russia investigation and the tweet-tweet-tweet of President Donald Trump assailing it. Numb yet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame rector: 'Computer glitch' possible fire culprit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/92db19558da04f09b94cc31fb5ce16a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Architects and construction workers have now stabilized the damaged structure of Notre Dame cathedral, four days after a fast-spreading fire ravaged the iconic Paris building, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIBAL GRIDLOCK CONTINUES...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190419204919-ugqh1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA-BATTLEGROUNDS (UPDATE 1, PIX, POLL):UPDATE 1-Stridently divided, Mueller report strengthen resolves on both sides</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's Guaido calls for 'largest march in history' to oust Maduro...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190419184538-rj07j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/GUAIDO (PIX, TV):Venezuela's Guaido calls for 'largest march in history' to oust Maduro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syphilis Invading Rural America...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-04-19/syphilis-is-invading-rural-america-and-a-fraying-health-safety-net-is-failing-to-stop-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers could be WEIGHED before flights to cut fuel costs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/8895844/passengers-weighed-flights-airlines-save-fuel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AIR passengers could be WEIGHED before they board flights in a bit to cut fuel costs and emissions. Discreet “pressure pads” could be used as passengers pass through the airport –…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOTAL BULLSH*T'</title>
      <link>https://www.syracuse.com/us-news/2019/04/president-trump-says-some-of-mueller-report-is-total-bulls-t.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.syracuse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Watch out for people that take so-called ‘notes,’" Trump tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS POLL:  TRUMP APPROVAL FALLS TO 37%...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-poll/trump-approval-drops-3-points-to-2019-low-after-release-of-mueller-report-reuters-ipsos-poll-idUSKCN1RV16S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans who approve of President Donald Trump dropped by 3 perce...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOODWARD:  NOW WE WAIT FOR THE TAPES...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/04/19/bob_woodward_on_mueller_report_now_we_wait_for_the_tapes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Watergate" journalist Bob Woodward told MSNBC's "Morning Joe" on Friday that in the wake of the Mueller report, he is waiting for someone to come forward with "tapes or new evidence." WILLIE GEIST, MSNBC: Having been through a few of these fights and a few of these administrations, particularly one comes to mind. What did you make of the report and what do you believe happens next?  BOB WOODWARD: Well, first of all, I think the report is quite amazing, and the Attorney General Barr did himself a mass of disservice because his letter quoted a portion of the report that looked like Trump was off the hook on obstruction of justice, but as we know on page 182, Mueller makes it very clear that they did not reach this issue because of evidence, because they could not make a determination determination. Joe may remember this, but the day Reagan was shot 1981 was it was Al Hague who rushed in and defined the way people were going to remember him by saying 'I'm in charge here.' Of course, he wasn't.  And Barr is going to be remembered for this because it was not -- it was just a deception and a misrepresentation of what this report shows.  Now, where it goes, I think it turns on the quality of evidence. In the Nixon case again, I'm sorry to go back but the tapes showed conclusively the President of the United States ordered the payment of hush money to the Watergate burglars and their overseers. He did it again and again, said, 'Let's blow the safe, let's break in.'  Now, in the case of the Trump case here, as Michael Schmidt I think was wisely pointing out, they stumbled, Trump stumbled. It was kind of obstruction of justice-lite. And as I reported in my book, there were lots of people who said, 'I'm not going to do these things that he ordered.' So where this goes, does somebody come up with tapes or new evidence? I think that would be the propellant here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAPOLITANO:  Mueller Report Might Be Enough to Prosecute...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-napolitano-mueller-report-might-be-enough-to-prosecute-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHOMSKY: Dems May Have Handed Trump Next Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/noam-chomsky-calls-dem-focus-on-russia-a-huge-gift-to-trump-they-may-have-handed-him-the-next-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY: I Am Sickened...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/i-am-sickened-romney-blasts-trump-in-scathing-reaction-to-mueller-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELIZABETH WARREN CALLS FOR IMPEACHMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elizabeth-warren-calls-on-congress-to-begin-impeachment-proceedings-against-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren became the first Democratic presidential candidate to call for impeachment in the wake of the Mueller report's release</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Fear Hits Fever Pitch With Holiday Weekend ; Packed Flights...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/04/18/concern-measles-spreading-spring-break-easter-passover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're over the age of 30, it might be hard to know if you have been adequately vaccinated against the measles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Suspect groped jail technician while being fingerprinted...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/fingerprint-groping-bust-184937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 19--While being booked for causing a disturbance at a bar, a Florida Man rubbed the buttocks of a fingerprint technician, according to a police report which notes that the suspect said he pawed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Subway Using Real-Time ID Software?</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/4/19/18507552/mta-nyc-subway-times-square-fare-evasion-cameras-facial-recognition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The camera feed is just there to scare fare-evaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steele Dossier Scrutiny: Russian Informants Pressured to Feed Disinformation?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/19/us/politics/steele-dossier-mueller-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel revealed that some claims in the dossier appeared to be false while others were impossible to prove. Republicans have vowed to investigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMA fighter pummels fan 'masturbating' to her photo shoot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6939877/Female-MMA-fighter-punches-fan-performing-sex-act-photo-shoot-Brazil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joyce Vieira and a friend were taking photos on a beach in Rio de Janeiro when she claims she saw a man masturbating in front of her. She launched a series of punches at the alleged pervert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY: IT SICKENS ME...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/SenatorRomney/status/1119322471105216512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I have now read the redacted Mueller report and offer my personal reaction:”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: COMEDIAN POISED FOR UKRAINE PRESIDENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/18/ukraine-elections-actor-and-comedian-volodymyr-zelenskiy-poised-to-win-crushing-victory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volodymyr Zelenskiy is hot favourite to triumph in Sunday’s presidential election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state cusp of first to legalize human composting...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/washington-on-the-cusp-of-becoming-first-state-to-legalize-human-composting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passage of the bill fulfills a longtime hope for Seattle-based Katrina Spade, and is another step in a long effort to realize her vision for an urban, soil-based, ecologically friendly death-care option. She is founder and CEO of Recompose, which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searchable report provides detailed view...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/explore-a-detailed-version-of-the-mueller-report-5f7cab5b-9c53-46bc-abaa-bd6b7b3e6d66.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each part of the document is categorized and tagged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN reporter stomps on lizard while doing live TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/florida/watch-cnn-reporter-stomps-florida-lizard-during-live-report/1938912247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A frisky Florida lizard made a brief appearance on CNN Friday and got "stomped out" on live television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK PENN: Dems Need To Get Grip On Selves...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/439691-mueller-done-dems-should-be-too-trump-is-no-nixon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was nothing but a president frustrated at being wrongly accused and wrongly investigated over a very effective hoax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living on wrong side of a time zone hazardous to health...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2019/04/19/living-on-the-wrong-side-of-a-time-zone-can-be-hazardous-to-your-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less sleep but perhaps more enjoyment for those who live on the eastern edge of a time zone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Kraft video leaked? Spa workers want prosecutor contempt charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/04/19/attorneys-accuse-police-prosecutors-of-leaking-kraft-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for two of the women charged in a Florida prostitution sting asked a judge on Thursday to hold police and prosecutors in contempt of court following reports that someone was shopping arou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Can't believe in jail' says lady who sent man 159,000 texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/scottsdale/2019/04/18/jacqueline-ades-accused-sending-man-159-k-messages-speaks-jail/2961779002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arizona woman accused of sending a date over 159,000 text messages and breaking into his Paradise Valley home has been found mentally incompetent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit shock as 18-ft PYTHON spotted on garage roof...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox2detroit.com/news/local-news/18-foot-python-found-on-garage-roof-in-detroit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox2detroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's 18-feet long, got scales and hiding on top of a Detroit roof? Here's a hint: it's a man's pet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeach? Impeach! Impeach? TV Talkers Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/bill-dagostino/2019/04/19/terms-impeachment-media-mention-i-word-309-times-one-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the Mueller report did not recommend any charges against the President, liberal journalists on cable and broadcast networks spent Thursday suggesting to audiences that impeachment was imminent, if not inevitable. Throughout Thursday afternoon and Friday morning, liberal talking heads on cable and broadcast news networks mentioned impeachment an astonishing 309 times during their coverage the of the newly-released Mueller report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighter lives saved by robot called 'Colossus', chief says...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/notre-dame-fire-latest-robot-colossus-a8877526.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt collectors soon to text, email consumers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/text-me-debt-collectors-may-soon-be-able-to-text-and-email-consumers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal agency wants to update rules about how debt collectors contact borrowers. Consumer advocates fear abuses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-wave flu season now longest in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.bradenton.com/news/local/health-care/article229459754.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bradenton.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Drunk on smoke' bees  protect queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a5415871628a45aa959268a93c32ed13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Hunkered down in their hives and drunk on smoke, Notre Dame's smallest official residents — some 180,000 bees — somehow managed to survive the inferno that consumed the cathedral's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Counties where American dream may be dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/04/19/counties-where-the-american-dream-is-dead/39353483/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research shows reaching the American dream is not uniform across the USA as many counties have high poverty rates and below average household incomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK's tiniest baby home after weighing 12oz at birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8894965/uk-tiniest-miracle-baby-home-born/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN’S tiniest baby is back home after weighing just 12oz at birth. Isabella Evans was born at 24 weeks and given a five per cent chance of survival. She is now smiling for parents Kym Brown and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: The Trouble With Dentistry...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/05/the-trouble-with-dentistry/586039/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s much less scientific—and more prone to gratuitous procedures—than you may think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is NYC's 'Remarkable Growth Story' Ending?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/18/nyregion/new-york-city-population.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City planning officials dispute the latest census figures, which suggest that New York’s post-recession growth has finally slowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby snatched from cot, decapitated by leopard...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/baby-snatched-cot-decapitated-leopard-14433607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The animal is believed to have dragged nine-month-old Dhaval Rathwa by his teeth while he was sleeping beside his mum in Zari, India, at around 4am on Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fraud scams proliferate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49b43ed501724e7fa01da2a891fc00eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Latest on the fire that ravaged Notre Dame Cathedral in Paris (all times local): 4:15 p.m. The Paris prosecutor's office is urging those making donations for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Upholds Mandatory Measles Vaccinations...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/04/19/715016284/brooklyn-judge-upholds-mandatory-vaccinations-as-new-york-city-closes-more-schoo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Lawrence Knipel refused a request from parents to lift the vaccination order that was imposed last week to stem a measles outbreak. The parents claimed the city had overstepped its authority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKES -- buy, sell or hold? Sneakers now trading like stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-sneakers-wall-street-stockx-reseller-20190419-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now popular sneaker resale platform StockX is hoping its new way of auctioning exclusive releases directly to a bidding market will attract major brands, designers and deep-pocketed buyers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interest in 2020 already at Election Day levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-poll-interest-in-2020-already-at-election-day-levels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC to send $50 checks to taxpayers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article229414084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS carrier helps man steal $374,000 from one zip code...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article229414309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People pooping more than ever on San Fran streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/technology/businessinsider/article/People-are-pooping-more-than-ever-on-the-streets-13778680.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of America's wealthiest cities has a huge problem with public poop.  Between 2011 and 2018, San Francisco experienced a massive increase in reported incidents of human feces found on public streets.  In 2011, just over 5,500 reports were logged by the San Francisco Department of Public Works; in 2018, the number increased to more than 28,000.  The government watchdog Open the Books documented the sharp increase over time in a stunning chart , first spotted by the BuzzFeed editor John Paczkowski .   Open the Books/City of San Francisco  Notably, this is a chart of only documented reports - the actual amount of feces on San Francisco's streets is likely even higher than these statistics suggest.  "I will say there is more feces on the sidewalks than I've ever seen growing up here," San Francisco Mayor London Breed told NBC in a 2018 interview . "That is a huge problem, and we are not just talking about from dogs - we're talking about from humans."  San Francisco has struggled with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER SUBPOENAS</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/19/nadler-subpoena-full-mueller-report-1282969</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subpoena, which demands the material by May 1, escalates the House’s confrontation with Attorney General William Barr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANKEES dump Kate Smith's 'God Bless America' over singer's racist songs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/sports/baseball/yankees/ny-kate-smith-god-bless-america-20190418-wfkyednrvrherh57sfmb4h7s5y-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Yankees have taken a stand against racism for their seventh-inning stretch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunger Strikes At ICE Detention Centers Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/04/19/713910647/hunger-strikes-at-ice-detention-centers-spread-as-parole-bond-is-denied</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been at least six hunger strikes at detention centers in the first three months of 2019 alone. One of the detainees' demands was to be released while their cases were adjudicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS worried about Bernie winning...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/18/cenk-uygur-on-why-democrats-are-afraid-of-bernie-sanders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Bernie right now has a better chance of winning than rest of field combined," said Cenk Uygur, founder of progressive news network TYT and host of "The Young Turks," who supported Sanders in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS EYE ZUCK IN PRIVACY PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Federal-Facebook-investigation-could-hold-13779470.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal regulators investigating Facebook for mishandling its users' personal information have set their sights on the company's CEO, Mark Zuckerberg, exploring his past statements on privacy and weighing whether to seek new, heightened oversight of his leadership.  The discussions about how to hold Zuckerberg accountable for Facebook's data lapses have come in the context of wide-ranging talks between the Federal Trade Commission and Facebook that could settle the government's more than year-old probe, according to two people familiar with the discussions. Both requested anonymity because the FTC's inquiry is confidential under law.  Such a move could create new legal, political and public-relations headaches for one of Silicon Valley's best known - and image conscious - corporate leaders. Zuckerberg is Facebook's co-founder, chief executive, board chairman and most powerful stock owner, and a sanction from the federal government would be seen as a rare rebuke to him and the tech giant's historic "move fast and break things" ethos.  Often, the FTC does not target executives in cases in which it finds a company's business practices have violated web users' privacy. But critics said targeting Zuckerberg could show other tech giants that the agency is willing to hold top executives directly accountable for their firms' repeated data misdeeds.  "The days of pretending this is an innocent platform are over, and citing Mark in a large-scale enforcement action would drive that home in spades," said Roger McNamee, an early investor in the company and one of Zuckerberg's critics.  In past investigations of Facebook, the U.S. government opted to spare Zuckerberg from the most onerous scrutiny. Documents obtained from the FTC under federal open-records rules reflect that the agency considered, then backed down from, putting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN: TRUMP LIBERATED...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/18/release-of-mueller-report-finally-sets-trump-and-america-free/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good God, free at last, free at last. Donald Trump is now free to be president without the cloud that hovered over him since his election. No president ever faced, let alone survived, a probe as fi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brands roll with stoner 'holiday' as pot legalization grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/65e8f00e740247a2a00786ed91ed4dc1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Potheads have for decades celebrated their love of marijuana on April 20, but the once counter-culture celebration that was all about getting stoned now is so mainstream...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dingo drags sleeping toddler from bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/national/queensland/infant-recovering-in-hospital-after-terrifying-dingo-attack/news-story/517dca54aa0814187d700b746798844a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A heroic dad saved his baby son from a dingo’s jaws after the child was dragged from a camper trailer as his family slept at Fraser Island overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist shot dead covering riot in Northern Ireland...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/journalist-lyra-mckee-fatally-shot-during-northern-ireland-riot-n996241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We believe this to be a terrorist act," police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papa roach: Farmer breeds bugs for table...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190419-papa-roach-chinese-farmer-breeds-bugs-table</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Papa roach: Chinese farmer breeds bugs for the table</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could be never-ending story on Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/why-mueller-report-could-turn-into-a-never-ending-story-on-the-hill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The release of the redacted report may not be the end of the political battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devotees nailed to crosses on Good Friday in Philippines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/906717f74e82464db4e2923d78f4fba8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN PEDRO CUTUD, Philippines (AP) — Several Roman Catholic devotees were nailed to wooden crosses in a gory Good Friday ritual in the Philippines, and others flogged themselves or took part in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN RUNNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/04/joe-biden-running-president/587560/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president has finally decided he’s in, and he’s announcing in less than a week. Now he just has to finish putting a campaign together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College golfer in hijab out to blaze trail for Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsday.com/sports/college-golfer-in-hijab-out-to-blaze-trail-for-muslim-girls-1.29978063</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(AP) -- Noor Ahmed outwardly lives her Muslim faith, and even growing up in a state as diverse as California she says she encountered hostility on the street, in school and on the golf course.One of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans, Democrats split on meaning...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/18/republicans-democrats-split-on-what-mueller-report-means/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They read the same report, but Democrats and Republicans came away with wildly different reactions. Democrats held up the redacted report by special counsel Robert Mueller as a damning indictment o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More yellow vest protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/efb3aba4f029493a9b730d0b532c01bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — For many yellow vest protesters, the stinging sadness that came with the devastating fire at Notre Dame Cathedral has quickly given way to boiling anger. Some of the activists,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tCyoHZc6hNg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump hit the town of Adzope on the Ivory Coast on Wednesday and totally showed off her dancing skills as she boogied down with some traditional local...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech Wants Centralized Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/platforms-centralized-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opinion: Controlling the spread of insidious content online is extremely difficult—but combining efforts across platforms raise serious threats to free expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Found! Genes that stop us from getting fat...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/04/18/genes-prevent-four-million-people-gaining-weight-discovered/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The genes which protect around four million people in the UK from obesity have been discovered following a major research project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI's Facial Recognition Programs Under Fire Over Privacy, Accuracy Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/04/fbis-facial-recognition-programs-under-fire-over-privacy-accuracy-concerns/156409/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bureau has largely ignored the Government Accountability Office’s concerns about its use of facial recognition in criminal investigations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller finds Jared was top target of Russian influence, but he DID NOT engage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article229428389.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY: Trump is cancer on presidency. Congress should remove...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/George-Conway-Trump-is-a-cancer-on-the-13779435.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So it turns out that, indeed, President Donald Trump was not exonerated at all, and certainly not "totally" or "completely," as he claimed. Special counsel Robert Mueller didn't reach a conclusion about whether Trump committed crimes of obstruction of justice - in part because, while a sitting president, Trump can't be prosecuted under long-standing Justice Department directives, and in part because of "difficult issues" raised by "the President's actions and intent." Those difficult issues involve, among other things, the potentially tricky interplay between the criminal obstruction laws and the president's constitutional authority, and the difficulty in proving criminal intent beyond a reasonable doubt.  Still, the special counsel's report is damning. Mueller couldn't say, with any "confidence," that the president of the United States is not a criminal. He said, stunningly, that "if we had confidence after a thorough investigation of the facts that the President clearly did not commit obstruction of justice, we would so state." Mueller did not so state.  That's especially damning because the ultimate issue shouldn't be - and isn't - whether the president committed a criminal act. As I wrote not long ago, Americans should expect far more than merely that their president not be provably a criminal. In fact, the Constitution demands it.  The Constitution commands the president to "take Care that the Laws be faithfully executed." It requires him to affirm that he will "faithfully execute the Office of President" and to promise to "preserve, protect and defend the Constitution." And as a result, by taking the presidential oath of office, a president assumes the duty not simply to obey the laws, civil and criminal, that all citizens must obey, but alsoto be subjected to higher duties - what some excellent recent legal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE:  Militia in New Mexico Detains Asylum Seekers at Gunpoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6932583/More-300-asylum-seekers-surrender-armed-militia-New-Mexico-citizens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video recorded by one of the militia, Jim Benvie, shows the asylum seekers walking on a dirt road having crossed through a fence gap in Sundland Park, New Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOD TIMES!  Ivanka shows off dance moves in Africa; Trades laughs and kisses with locals...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6932187/Ivanka-Trump-shows-dance-moves-Ivory-Coast-celebration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka, 37, arrived in Adzope on the Ivory Coast on Wednesday to tour Cayat, a Fairtrade cocoa and coffee collective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Americans moving, mostly to Sun Belt suburbs...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/439561-more-americans-are-moving-mostly-to-sun-belt-suburbs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade after the worst recession in modern history froze many Americans in place, the number of people with enough economic security to move is starting to rise once again, according to new population estimates from the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 68% say paid same or MORE in taxes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/what-americas-thinking/439552-36-percent-say-they-paid-the-same-in-taxes-in-2018-as-they-did</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About two-thirds of Americans, 68 percent, say they paid the same or more in taxes for 2018 than the previous year, while less than a quarter said they paid less, according to a new Hill-HarrisX survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surviving Eisner and Ovitz Snubs, DISNEY's Iger Dazzles Wall Street... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/bob-iger-wall-street-darling-peter-bart-streaming-plans-1202597465/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars like to boast that they never read their reviews, but does Bob Iger? The Disney czar received a litany of raves for his three-hour performance last week aimed at demonstrating his company’s i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus identified as cause of paralyzing condition in children...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/virus-identified-as-a-cause-of-paralyzing-condition-in-minnesota-children-acute-flaccid-myelitis/508757812/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Minnesota and the CDC made the breakthrough on the puzzling ailment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: CONSPIRACY THEORIES, 'BOMBSHELLS' OBLITERATED...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/04/18/robert-mueller-did-not-merely-reject-the-trumprussia-conspiracy-theories-he-obliterated-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Certain facts will never go away no matter how much media elites deny them. That Mueller charged no Americans with election conspiracy crimes is the most fatal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 SECRET CRIMINAL REFERRALS</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/mueller-made-14-criminal-referrals-outside-offices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller referred 14 cases of potential criminal activity to outside offices because the cases were &amp;#8220;outside the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President cracks term limit joke after big win...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/18/trump-cracks-term-limit-joke-after-mueller-report-released/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – President Trump trolled his critics following the release of the Mueller report, joking that he was going to be in office for the next 10 to 14 years. The president was hosting p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA CONTINUES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91b640225af04df3abd9b7a33f9c7f01</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — To Donald Trump, the start of special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation looked alarmingly like the end of his presidency. So he tried to stop it. His months-long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS EYE ZUCK IN PRIVACY PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/04/19/federal-investigation-facebook-could-hold-mark-zuckerberg-accountable-privacy-sources-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal regulators investigating Facebook for mishandling its users’ personal information have set their sights on the company’s chief executive, Mark Zuckerberg, exploring his past statements on privacy and weighing whether to seek new, heightened oversight of his leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DC War: Subpoenas, payback...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mueller-report-sparks-new-dc-war-over-russia-probe-subpoenas-payback-and-more</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public release of Special Counsel Robert Mueller's report on Thursday marked the dramatic final note of a lengthy and contentious investigation, but also sparked a tinderbox of new calls for subpoenas, congressional testimony, resignations, and even impeachment proceedings -- all despite the probe's central finding that no evidence showed collusion between President Trump's team and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>855 SEPARATE REDACTIONS</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/donald-trump/mueller-redactions-738952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The version of the Mueller Report released this morning contains 855 separate redactions, the bulk of which appear in the section devoted to the Russian government’s actions to influence the 2016 el</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA Memers Unionizing: 'Exploited for too long'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/04/instagram-memers-are-unionizing/587308/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re hoping to solve some of the new economy’s problems with an old tactic: collective bargaining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Castro luxurious Havana mansion for rent on AIRBNB...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6936503/Cuban-leaders-granddaughter-rents-mansion-Havana-650-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vilma Rodríguez, the granddaughter of Cuban leader Raul Castro, is renting a four-bedroom mansion with a Jacuzzi on Airbnb for $650 a night in Havana, Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' Considers Classifying Fetanyl as WMD...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/dhs-fentanyl-wmd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security is considering classifying the painkiller drug fentanyl as a weapon of mass destruction "when certain criteria are met," according to an internal memo obtained by Task &amp; Purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell says raising age to buy tobacco to 21 'top priority'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/18/mcconnell-tobacco-age-21-1280950</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate majority leader’s move comes one day after he announced his reelection campaign and shows the changing politics of tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Panic Over Political Bias Leaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/04/18/exclusive-google-leftists-panic-about-leaks-threaten-employment-of-colleagues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Left-wing employees at Google are threatening the employment of their colleagues amid a panic about frequent leaks revealing political bias in the company’s products and working atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
