<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Accuses her of adultery...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/celebrity/stormy-daniels-divorce-745923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 23--In a court filing, the husband of Stormy Daniels accuses the porn actress of committing adultery and cites the alleged extramarital activity as a grounds for divorce. &amp;nbsp; Glendon Crain, 41</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge grants immunity for five witnesses in Manafort case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/23/politics/manafort-witnesses-immunity/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge in Alexandria, Virginia, has granted the request for five witnesses to testify with immunity in the criminal trial of former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concerns over HIV resurgence dominates...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dangerous-complaceny-feared-aids-conference-opens-031009112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerns over an HIV resurgence caused by strict drug laws fuelling an epidemic blamed on needle sharing dominated a world AIDS assembly that opened in Amsterdam Monday. The 22nd International AIDS conference will seek to harness the star power of celebrity activists Charlize Theron, Elton John, and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First drive-through pot shop opens...</title>
      <link>https://www.king5.com/article/news/local/first-drive-through-pot-shop-opens-in-auburn/281-576292046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.king5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now you can add marijuana to the list of things to get on the go in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow Hand Surgery; Out For Season...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/23/tim-tebow-needs-surgery-in-another-surreal-mets-blow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet another injury has befallen the Mets — this one to their best chance at selling tickets in September. Tim Tebow suffered a broken hamate bone in his right hand while swinging a bat last T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST DANCE: Stormy's Husband Files For Divorce...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/07/23/stormy-daniels-getting-divorced/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman at the center of a political scandal - Stormy Daniels - will soon join the single life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In first, Israel fires 2 David Sling interceptor missiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/In-a-first-Israel-fires-two-David-Sling-interceptor-missiles-563179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Syrian rockets landed in Syria. Israel suffered no damage or injuries from the rockets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet U.S. Officials Who Now Lobby for China...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/meet-the-us-officials-who-now-lobby-for-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Nobody in the 1980s would have represented the Russian government. And now you find so many lobbying for the Chinese government.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour de France rider punches opponent mid-race...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/23/tour-de-france-villain-punches-opponent-mid-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Team Sky’s Tour de France bid plunged into turmoil after one of its riders was disqualified for punching an opponent. Italian Gianni Moscon was kicked out of the race after striking a rider f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to Seek Repeal of California's Smog-Fighting Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-23/trump-is-said-to-seek-repeal-of-california-s-smog-fighting-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration will seek to revoke California’s authority to regulate automobile emissions -- including its mandate for electric car sales -- in a proposed revision of Obama-era standards, according to three people familiar with the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2.5 Billion Pounds of Meat Piles Up as Production Grows, Exports Slow...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/meat-piles-up-as-production-grows-and-exports-slow-1532268000 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meat is piling up in U.S. cold-storage warehouses, fueled by a surge in supplies and trade disputes that are eroding demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Kelly Drops 19-Minute Song 'I Admit' Addressing Accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/r-kelly-i-admit-19-minute-song-pedophile-sex-slave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;R. Kelly released 19-minute track "I Admit" on Monday -- the song covers the "pedophile" and "sex slave" accusations against the R&amp;B singer (Audio)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook blocks links to women's rights group after 'transphobia' complaints...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6841801/facebook-block-womens-rights-group-transphobia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK has been slammed for “censoring” a feminist campaign group after it was accused of “transphobia”. Woman’s Place UK campaigns for women-only spaces and raises …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawn Company Slogan Under Fire By Residents: 'American Owned: Your Alternative To Illegal Lawn Services'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/07/20/controversy-sample-lawn-mowing-company-business-card/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Texas lawn mowing company has come under fire, after an old business card resurfaced. "Your alternative to illegal lawn services" offended some.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Body-Shamed On Socials, Called 'Out Of Shape' After Beach Photos Surface...</title>
      <link>http://sports.cbslocal.com/2018/07/23/tom-brady-shirtless-photo-body-shaming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots QB found himself the subject of some body shaming on Twitter after a shirtless photo of him with his wife Gisele made its rounds on the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORN TO RUN...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2018/07/elizabeth-warren-fight-to-defeat-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts senator has emerged in the past few weeks as the de facto leader of the Democratic Party, and the candidate-of-the-moment for 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump warns Bezos!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5982733/Trump-slams-Washington-Post-North-Korea-claim-warns-sister-company-Amazon-postal-rates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president lashed out at the storied newspaper on Monday, blaming the Post and threatening its sister company Amazon –instead of Kim Jong-un – for gumming up the works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL CAPS WAR</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33bbdee2506645859222e0f5252b288f/White-House-blames-Iran-for-war-of-words-with-Trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House on Monday blamed Iranian President Hassan Rouhani for inciting a war of words with President Donald Trump, who warned that verbal threats could e</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayoral candidate hands out cash to potential voters...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2018/07/22/chicago-mayoral-candidate-willie-wilson-hands-out-cash-to-potential-voters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Willie Wilson, the millionaire businessman and candidate for Chicago mayor, handed out cash to potential voters Sunday morning at a church on Chicago’s South Side.  Illinois Governor Bruce Rauner, himself seeking reelection, joined Wilson at New Covenant Missionary Baptist Church at the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lennon's killer coming up for parole for 10th time...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5982581/John-Lennons-killer-coming-parole-10th-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark David Chapman is scheduled to face a New York parole hearing board in August - 38 years after he gunned down the Beatles legend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul to ask Trump to revoke security clearance of ex-CIA chief Brennan...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/23/rand-paul-john-brennan-security-clearance-735620</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Is John Brennan monetizing his security clearance?&amp;quot; the Kentucky senator asks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR IS BORN' to World Premiere at Venice Film Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2018/07/a-star-is-born-venice-film-festival-bradley-cooper-lady-gaga-oscars-1201987049/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bradley Cooper’s directorial debut will be one of the big titles to play at the start of the festival’s 75th edition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Average Child Spends Just 7 Hours A WEEK Outside...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/great-indoors-screen-hungry-kids-video-games-going-outside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average child between 6 and 16 years old spends only an hour a day outside, playing video games over twice as long, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas power use to break record during heat wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/texas-power-break-record-monday-during-heat-wave-124723971--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - Homes and businesses in Texas will likely use record amounts of power again on Monday as consumers keep their air conditioners cranked up on what is expected to be the last day of a week-long heat wave, the operator of much of the state's power grid said. The Electric Reliability Council</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Third of newspapers suffered layoffs since '17...</title>
      <link>http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2018/07/23/about-a-third-of-large-u-s-newspapers-have-suffered-layoffs-since-2017/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larger newspapers were more likely than smaller papers to have had layoffs between January 2017 and April 2018. Digital-native outlets have also suffered losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans outlined for 2,000 supersonic jets to link hundreds of cities across planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/boom-supersonic-travel-economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CONSEQUENCES FEW HAVE SUFFERED'</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/23/trump-warns-irans-rouhani-to-stop-threats-or-face-or-suffer-historic-consequences.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump late Sunday tweeted out to Iranian President Rouhani to “never” threaten the U.S. again or face the consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TWEET BOMB</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/398298-trump-warns-irans-rouhani-threaten-us-and-you-will-suffer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Sunday night warned that if Iran continued with its threats to the U.S. the country would suffer unspecified "consequences."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth's resources consumed in ever greater destructive volumes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/jul/23/earths-resources-consumed-in-ever-greater-destructive-volumes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study says the date by which we consume a year’s worth of resources is arriving faster</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-deal Brexit risks 'civil unrest', warns AMAZON boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/jul/23/no-deal-brexit-civil-unrest-amazon-uk-dominic-raab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doug Gurr reportedly made comment in meeting with the Brexit secretary, Dominic Raab</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmaker Strips Down, Screams 'N-Word' on Sacha Baron Cohen Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gop-lawmaker-jason-spencer-strips-screams-n-word-on-sacha-baron-cohens-who-is-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second episode of Baron Cohen’s Showtime series upped the ante with Dick Cheney and a seriously unhinged state representative from Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Grids Stretched Across Region...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/2018/07/23/power-grids-stretched-as-deadly-heat-wave-scorches-north-asia#gs.enw81lw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Power Grids Stretched as Deadly Heat Wave Scorches North Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Translate warns of APOCALYPSE in 'end times' message about Antichrist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6842131/google-translate-doomsday-clock-end-times-antichrist-apocalypse-dog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEARS of an imminent apocalypse have been sparked by a mysterious warning from Google Translate. The language-translation app is telling users that we’re “approaching the end times̶…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record heat broils Japan, prompting warnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/record-heat-broils-japan-prompting-warnings-061956266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese officials issued new warnings Monday as a deadly heatwave blankets the country, producing record high temperatures in Tokyo just two years before the city hosts the 2020 Summer Olympics. Officials said last week that the heatwave had killed at least 15 people and forced the hospitalisation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying groundskeeper to testify in ROUNDUP cancer trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/dying-groundskeeper-testify-roundup-cancer-trial-doc-17u0b71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gays strike, march in Tel Aviv...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/22/gays-go-strike-israel-over-surrogacy-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Israeli LGBT advocates and their supporters are on strike, protesting the exclusion of gay men from a recently passed surrogacy law. Protesters marched in Tel Aviv and other Israeli cities on Sunday, waving rainbow flags and briefly blocking a major highway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risks for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/22/trump-manafort-trial-mueller-russia-probe-735084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's former campaign chairman is set to be the first to go before a jury in the Mueller investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort faces trial in first court test of special counsel prosecution...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-manafort-mueller-trial-20180723-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort spent decades wheeling and dealing with U.S. politicians and foreign despots. Now President Trump's former campaign chairman faces his toughest audience yet — a federal judge and jury. He's the first person to face trial on charges brought by special counsel Robert S. Mueller</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vaccine scandal sparks fury, roils markets...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180723102815-y5p0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-VACCINES/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Bitter pill: China vaccine scandal sparks fury, roils markets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration and Border Suddenly Tough Issues for Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/23/immigration-and-the-border-are-suddenly-tough-issues-for-trudeau#gs.fJcFMU8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration and the Border Are Suddenly Tough Issues for Trudeau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chemicals in Food May Harm Children, Pediatricians' Group Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/chemicals-in-food-may-harm-children-pediatricians-group-says/17714679/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major pediatricians’ group is urging families to limit the use of plastic food containers, cut down on processed meat during pregnancy and consume more whole fruits and vegetables rather than processed food. Such measures would lower children’s exposures to chemicals in food and food packaging that are tied to health problems such as obesity, the group says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems get set for 2020 starting gun...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/398102-dems-get-set-for-2020-starting-gun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dozens of Democrats considering running for president in 2020 are pondering how, and when, to formally declare their candidacies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-Setting Heatwave In Japan Kills Dozens...</title>
      <link>http://malaysiandigest.com/frontpage/29-4-tile/749028-record-setting-heatwave-in-japan-kills-dozens-as-temps-soar-to-40c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;malaysiandigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran dismisses Trump threat, says he 'won't dare' attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/iran-dismisses-trump-threat-says-he-wont-dare-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gen. Gholam Hossein Gheibparvar downplays US president's tweeted warning as simply 'psychological warfare' against Tehran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient boulder dislodges from Western Wall, crashes onto prayer platform...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/ancient-boulder-dislodges-from-western-wall-crashes-onto-egalitarian-plaza/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic footage shows large stone coming loose from revered site, shattering on platform below; no injuries reported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger pees on floor in cabin as plane refuels...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6842956/shocking-moment-female-passenger-wees-on-the-floor-of-a-wizz-air-flight-from-britain-to-poland-because-the-toilet-was-engaged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a female passenger squats and pees in the galley of a Wizz Air flight from the UK to Poland. The woman is seen relieving herself on the flight from London Luton to Warsa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers claim injuries all over bodies for big payouts -- but continue active lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/workers-claim-injuries-all-over-their-bodies-for-big-payouts/article_2eac03e0-6bf8-5e8e-9d55-2abb1b2e2487.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — After nearly two decades on the force, former LAPD Officer Jonathan Hall ended his career the way many veteran officers do these days, claiming job-related injuries across</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious creatures frozen for MILLENNIA holding lost secrets of past...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/717845/weird-news-ancient-history-mysterious-creatures-frozen-ice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought forces emergency measures for West's wild horses...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/drought-forces-emergency-measures-us-wests-wild-horses-56750967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harsh drought conditions in parts of the American West are pushing wild horses to the brink and spurring extreme measures to protect them. For what they say is the first time, volunteer groups in Arizona and Colorado are hauling thousands of gallons of water and truckloads of food to remote...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia has billions in sunken treasure off coast, but ownership disputed...</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/colombia-has-billions-in-sunken-treasure-off-its-coast-but/article_05925497-9c02-5a11-b336-443937f247c3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTA, Colombia—Sitting at the bottom of the ocean, just off Colombia’s coast, is one of the Western Hemisphere’s richest treasures: a Spanish galleon packed with billions of dollars worth of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert makes case for $400 barrel oil...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy/expert-makes-the-case-for-400-per-barrel-oil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new analysis shows oil prices could rise to $200 per barrel, and even higher, in the next 12 to 18 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tremors shove Washington westward, offer clues into next big quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/science/tremors-shove-washington-westward-offer-clues-into-next-big-earthquake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pacific Northwest last saw a big earthquake about 300 years ago. Scientists widely expect the region to experience a similar event every 500 years on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 9 injured after gunman opens fire in Toronto... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/at-least-9-injured-after-shooting-in-busy-toronto-neighbourhood-1.4023591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China robotic submarines to launch new sea power era...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2156361/china-developing-unmanned-ai-submarines-launch-new-era-sea-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unmanned AI subs, expected in the 2020s, could challenge the advantage Western naval powers have in strategic waters like the South China Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMLO Letter Floats 'New Relationship'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexicos-lopez-obrador-floats-idea-relationship-letter-trump-012622637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's incoming president on Sunday said he had floated the idea of a new relationship between the neighboring countries in a letter to US President Donald Trump. Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said he sent Trump proposals on bilateral relations -- which have reached one of their lowest points in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOWDY: If There Was Collusion, Schiff Would Have Leaked It...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2018/07/22/gowdy_if_there_was_evidence_that_president_trump_commited_any_crime_adam_schiff_would_have_leaked_it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Trey Gowdy told FNC's Bret Baier on FOX News Sunday that while there are documents he has not seen, he knows that if there were any evidence that President Trump committed any crime with regard to Russia "Adam Schiff would have leaked it."  Schiff, the top Democrat on the House Intelligence Committee, said this week that President Trump is compromised by the Russians, offering possible recordings of his meeting with Putin as evidence.   "I have not seen one scintilla of evidence that this president colluded, conspired, collaborated, with Russia. And neither has anyone else, or you can rest assured, Adam Schiff would have leaked it," Gowdy said. "That is why they have moved on from collusion on to obstruction of justice, which is now their current preoccupation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Clinton dinner with Weinstein after election...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5976133/PICTURED-Hillary-Clinton-having-dinner-Harvey-Weinstein-election-loss.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of Hillary Clinton having dinner with longtime pal Harvey Weinstein weeks after her election loss have emerged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUPERGIRL' to feature TV's first trans superhero...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/supergirl-feature-first-ever-transgender-superhero-2357819</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transgender activist and actor Nicole Maines will play Nia Nal in the fourth season of the show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at Mormon Church Leaves 1 Dead...</title>
      <link>https://fox13now.com/2018/07/22/two-people-injured-in-shooting-at-lds-church-in-fallon-nevada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox13now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FALLON, Nevada -- One person is dead and another injured after a shooting Sunday at a Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints meetinghouse in Fallon, Nev.  The shooting took place at the church located at 750 West Richards Street during services according to Kaitlin Richins, a spokeswoman for the City of Fallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest aircraft has GLASS floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cntraveler.com/story/the-worlds-largest-aircraft-will-have-luxurious-bedrooms-and-glass-floors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cntraveler.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Airlander 10 could take up to 19 passengers on three-day expeditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP Governor Touted As Potential DEM 2020 Candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/07/21/conservatives-wonder-there-any-republican-left-baker-moderate-republicanism/AEH1hTPFdgVkE3kYHkkJiK/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlie Baker’s record would be good for a Democrat. But he’s a Republican, and some conservatives are fuming he’s too far to the left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron cites 'ART OF DEAL' in negotiation pushback...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-turning-trump-tricks-against-him--e1fe83d1-d045-4747-afa9-01905696f59d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using his own set of predictable negotiating tricks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
