<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump hosted Zuckerberg for undisclosed dinner at White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/trump-hosted-zuckerberg-undisclosed-dinner-white-house-october-n1087986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting took place during Zuckerberg’s most recent visit to Washington, where he testified before Congress about Facebook’s new cryptocurrency Libra.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden stumbles with gaffes on women and race...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-blog/nov-20-democratic-debate-live-updates-n1087226/ncrd1088101#liveBlogHeader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten candidates take the stage for the fifth Democratic debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg Boasts He's Least Wealthy Person on Stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/populist-pete-buttigieg-boasts-that-hes-the-least-wealthy-person-on-debate-stage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sound Bend mayor Pete Buttigieg had a moment at the Wednesday night 2020 Democratic Debate when he boasted that he was the least wealthy candidate standing on the stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala roasts Tulsi... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/kamala-harris-rips-tulsi-gabbard-over-assad-bannon-criticizing-fellow-dems-spent-years-on-fox-news-hitting-obama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's unfortunate that we have someone on this stage who ... spent four years full time on Fox News criticizing President Obama."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Cancels Movie Premiere After Producer Accused of Sex Assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/apple-canceled-banker-premiere-sexual-abuse-claims-real-life-subjects-son-1256695</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cynthia and Sheila Garrett allege they were assaulted by their half-brother Bernard Garrett Jr., the son of the subject of the drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaks Into Southern Accent...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/2020-election/2019/11/20/watch-kamala-harris-deploys-southern-fried-accent-for-single-debate-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris, who was born in Oakland, California, and grew up in Berkeley, broke into a fake southern accent during the Democrat debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexicans sue WALMART over El Paso shooting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexicans-sue-walmart-over-el-paso-shooting-185938190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's government said Wednesday it has helped 10 Mexican citizens file lawsuits against Walmart over an August shooting at a store in El Paso, Texas, where a suspected white nationalist killed 22 people. "The objective of these suits, presented in El Paso county, is to hold the company responsible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European center-right's new leader vows to fight populism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/european-centre-leader-vows-fight-populism-185108452.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former EU Council president Donald Tusk pledged Wednesday to fight political populism as he was elected leader of Europe's main conservative parties during their group meeting in Croatia. The former Polish prime minister will be tasked with boosting the fortunes of the European People's Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate exposes divides despite united front on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-debate-buttigieg-rises-impeachment-engrosses-voters-063548891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an opening phase dominated by talk of impeachment of Donald Trump, participants in the fifth Democratic debate locked horns over health care, in particular the costly universal coverage program supported by liberal senators Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders. "The fact is that right now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montage: Moderators Urge Attacks on Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-supercut-msnbc-debate-moderators-challenge-dems-left-urge-go</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Would you support a potential criminal investigation into President Trump after he leaves office?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Under Mosquito Alert After Another Case Of Dengue... </title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/20/miami-dade-under-mosquito-borne-illness-alert-after-another-case-of-dengue-fever-detected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami-Dade is under a mosquito-borne illness alert after another case of Dengue fever has been confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren defends wealth tax: 'I'm tired of freeloading billionaires'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/democratic-debate-elizabeth-warren-defends-wealth-tax-tired-of-freeloading-billionaires-031040597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren defended her proposed wealth tax during the Democratic presidential debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow throws first question softball...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/20/maddow-democratic-debate-warren/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC host Rachel Maddow started off Wednesday night's Democratic debate by lobbing a softball question to Democratic Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC'S HORRID FUNDRAISING NUMBERS CONTINUE...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/20/dnc-fundraising-numbers-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Committee (DNC) released its disappointing October fundraising numbers in the middle of the party's fifth presidential primary debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS MAKE NICE</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191121034952-o6bxf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/DEBATE (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Democratic White House candidates unite on impeachment in most polite debate yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro: Scorsese Believes Trump Will Start War to Get Third Term...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/robert-de-niro-believes-trump-will-start-a-war-so-he-can-serve-three-terms-as-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The theory, apparently, began with his good pal—and “The Irishman” director—Martin Scorsese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/video/watch-live-msnbc-washington-post-november-democratic-debate-73562693607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Livestream of the fifth Democratic presidential debate on November 20th, 2019 as 10 candidates spar in Atlanta, Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBATE NIGHT DEMS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-blog/nov-20-democratic-debate-live-updates-n1087226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten candidates take the stage for the fifth Democratic debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone was in the loop. It was was no secret'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7704917/Unpredictable-Sondland-faces-questions-Trump-Ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambassador Gordon Sondland will face questions about his evolving accounts of dealings with Ukraine and a report he kept Secretary of State Mike Pompeo apprised of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE MADE IN THE USA!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/20/apple-ceo-tim-cook-and-preident-trump-tour-texas-computer-factory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When you build in the United States you don't have to worry about tariffs," Trump said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRISIS AT PALACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10389442/queen-prince-andrew-royal-duties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen put on a brave face tonight after ­summoning sex scandal-hit Prince Andrew to Buckingham Palace to strip him of all royal duties. Her Majesty’s extraordinary intervention this afternoon c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accusing Netanyahu of stealing election, Gantz launches campaign for another...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/accusing-netanyahu-of-stealing-election-gantz-launches-campaign-for-another/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Repeatedly contrasting his own outlook with Netanyahu's, the Blue and White chief succeeds in painting a picture of two different leaders and two different Israels</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466379-1/impeachment-hearing-laura-cooper-david-hale&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Cooper, a deputy assistant Defense secretary, and David Hale, a State Department under secretary for political affairs, testifies before the House Intelligence Committee as part of its…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy slams GOP impeachment lawyer, demands apology...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/20/giuliani-slams-gop-impeachment-lawyer-demands-apology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani on Wednesday slammed the Republicans’ staff counsel during the impeachment inquiry — charging him with parroting “Democrat lies.” “Republican lawyer doesn’t do his own research and pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSED:  Biden emails post-debate fundraising plea -- hours early...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/20/biden-team-debate-fundraising-plea-2020-072212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The email went out around 3 p.m., a good six hours before the event is set to begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Decode Human Thoughts, Emotions Using MRI, Computer Analysis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mind-reading-scientists-decode-human-thoughts-and-emotions-using-mri-and-computer-analysis-60-minutes-2019-11-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Pittsburgh's Carnegie Mellon University have found a way to map brain activation patterns using MRI scans to read peoples' thoughts and emotions. 60 Minutes reports, Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA test shows Hunter Biden is father of Arkansas woman's baby...</title>
      <link>https://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2019/nov/20/dna-test-shows-hunter-biden-father-arkansas-womans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arkansasonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DNA testing has established, “with scientific certainty,” that Hunter Biden is the father of an Arkansas baby, according to a motion filed Wednesday in Independence County on behalf of the child’s mother, Lunden Alexis Roberts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZOGBY: Is he finished?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/471262-is-joe-biden-finished</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has his challenges ahead, but he is very much in this race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Unmasks WIKIPEDIA's Anti-Israel Editors...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/wikipedias-anti-israel-editors-unmasked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pro-Israel organization has exposed the identities of top Wikipedia editors who use the online encyclopedia to promote anti-Israel bias and causes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Buttigieg's rise positions him as top target at debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3007c4c1b2e4772a9bb1a26ade5d9c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Pete Buttigieg’s rise in the Democratic presidential primary makes him a prime target at Wednesday’s debate as the four candidates now bunched at the top seek to distinguish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son of former German president stabbed to death while giving lecture...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/11/20/fritz-von-weizsaecker-stabbed-death-son-former-german-president/4249150002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 57-year-old German man is in custody after he jumped up from the lecture audience and attacked Fritz von Weizsaecker on Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabbed on way to synagogue in NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-man-stabbed-on-way-to-synagogue-20191120-2pjkiktsgzb3vj5tczqijbv76y-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim was heading to temple when at least two men pulled up in a car, jumped out and attacked him on Howard Drive in Monsey, about 35 miles from Manhattan, about 5:45 a.m., Yeshiva World News reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family drags uncle's corpse to insurance company to prove he's dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7706145/Relatives-bring-family-members-CORPSE-insurance-firms-office-South-Africa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ntombenhle Mhlongo and Thandaza Mtshali dragged the body of uncle Sifiso Justice Mhlongo into a branch of Old Mutual in South Africa after the firm refused to pay out on a claim for funeral expenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Trying To Stop Facial Recognition From Ever Coming To Denver...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/11/19/facial-recognition-denver-ballot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If one group has their way, the city of Denver won’t be able to use facial recognition technology now, or ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg opens the spigot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/16abd2f36e624f2e8065303d4b8d9c50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As he moves toward a presidential announcement, New York billionaire Michael Bloomberg is rolling out plans to spend an estimated $15 million to $20 million on a voter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside New Mexico ranch...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7703257/New-photos-Jeffrey-Epsteins-New-Mexico-ranch-pedophiles-eight-person-party-shower.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of new photos and video give the most revealing insight yet into Jeffrey Epstein's notorious 'baby making ranch' in the New Mexico desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake news amplifies fear, confusion in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fake-news-amplifies-fear-confusion-hong-kong-075057098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impending 'terrorist' attacks: false news online is amplifying fear and confusion in Hong Kong as months of pro-democracy unrest turns increasingly violent in the real world. "I just assume everything is fake until I have seen sources from both sides and more than two news agencies I trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES employee's secret meet with Dem donor group scrutinized...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/nyt-columnist-joins-secretive-dem-donor-conference/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Times columnist and CBS News political analyst Jamelle Bouie addressed a closed-door gathering of the Democratic Party's top donors last week in potential violation of the paper's ethical guidelines, which prohibit paid speeches to political groups and urge staff members to be "especially sensitive to the appearance of partiality when they address groups that might figure in coverage they provide."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems ponder huge tax hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-democrats-would-tax-high-income-professionals-not-just-the-mega-rich/ar-BBWZiV2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mogul arrested on yacht in journalist murder case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/malta-businessman-arrested-journalist-murder-case-104043689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malta on Wednesday arrested a tycoon in connection with the murder of journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia, the day after an alleged middleman was offered a pardon to identify the mastermind behind the killing. Maltese national Yorgen Fenech was detained on his yacht at dawn as he tried to leave Malta,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy distances himself from Sondland...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/20/rudy-giuliani-tweets-attacks-gordon-sondland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani, President Trump's personal attorney, tweeted then deleted a rebuttal of Gordon Sondland's testimony during Wednesday's impeachment hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge fund becomes TRIBUNE's largest shareholder...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/30b2b8288fc0413eac7def72fe1457a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hedge fund Alden Global Capital is now the largest shareholder of Tribune Publishing, the company that owns the Chicago Tribune, Baltimore Sun and New York Daily...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew To Step Back from Public Duties Over Epstein Relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7707443/Duke-York-step-public-duties.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen has given permission for the Duke of York to 'step back from public duties for the foreseeable future'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy deletes tweet saying he had 'VERY little contact' with Sondland...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/trump-impeachment-hearing-coverage-eu-ambassador-gordon-sondland-testimony-live-stream-2019-11-20/#post-update23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ambassador to the EU said the White House and State Department were fully aware of the effort to pressure Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk's satellites 'blocking view of stars', say astronomers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10384295/elon-musk-spacex-starlink-block-view-stars/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has been accused of blocking our view of the stars with his Starlink internet satellites. The billionaire’s firm SpaceX has launched dozens of “broadband” probes into or…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein's A-list guests 'secretly filmed in every bedroom and bathroom'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10385875/jeffrey-epsteins-a-list-guests-filmed-bathroom-accuser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein’s guests were secretly filmed in every bedroom and toilet of his New York City home, one of his accusers has claimed. Maria Farmer alleges she was abused by the disgraced paed…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphones Covered In Bacteria, Dirtier Than Bathroom!  </title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sickening-survey-most-smartphones-covered-in-bacteria-yet-1-in-4-never-clean-theirs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey of 1,200 Americans and their cleaning habits finds that one in four (23%) have never cleaned their smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PENCE KNEW'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-sondland-throws-mike-pence-under-bus-says-he-knew-of-quid-pro-quo-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambassador Gordon Sondland opened his public impeachment testimony by dropping Vice President Mike Pence into the middle of the Ukraine scandal, telling the House Intelligence Committee that he raised</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew Considers Nuclear Option: Another TV Interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/prince-andrew-considers-the-nuclear-option-after-new-epstein-accuser-revelations-another-tv-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abandoned, ostracized, despised, and ridiculed, the Duke of York may have little to lose from pleading his case on TV again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEN STARR: Republican Senators May Push Trump To Resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ken-starr-suggests-on-fox-that-gop-senators-may-need-to-make-a-trip-to-white-house-after-sondland-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Fox News, Clinton prosecutor raises the specter of Nixon resignation by wondering aloud about how EU ambassador’s testimony could be a “game-changer” for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians turn to artificial intelligence to stop porn use...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-relig-combating-porn-20191120-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelical groups are turning to artificial intelligence and machine learning technologies to help their members fight addiction to online pornography in a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI seeks interview with CIA whistleblower...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fbi-seeks-interview-with-cia-whistleblower-121637359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI recently sought to question the CIA whistleblower who filed a complaint over President Trump’s July 25 Ukraine call — a move that came after a vigorous internal debate within the bureau over how to respond to some of the issues raised by the complaint’s allegations and whether they needed to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Israel polls loom as kingmaker refuses to back PM or rival...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deadline-looms-israeli-politicians-seek-avoid-third-election-111336928.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel edged closer to a third general election in a year Wednesday, as kingmaker Avigdor Lieberman refused to back either incumbent Benjamin Netanyahu or challenger Benny Gantz for prime minister ahead of a midnight deadline. Right-wing incumbent Netanyahu and centrist Gantz were nearly deadlocked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia to close borders in attempt to contain mass protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/20/colombia-border-closed-protests-ivan-duque</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border closures, curfews and bans on sale of alcohol announced as tens of thousands are expected to march amid wave of turmoil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT DAY 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/sondland-testimony-targets-trump-pompeo-confirms-deal-ukraine-n1086541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ambassador is testifying before the House Intelligence Committee and will be revealing emails and texts to back up his claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence in Mexico peaks as cartels fight over drugs and avocados...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-11-20/mexico-cartel-violence-avocados</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not just drugs. Mexico's cartels are fighting over avocados.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Sequel in the Works...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/joker-sequel-works-as-todd-phillips-eyes-more-dc-origin-movies-1256255</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director is likely to reteam with star Joaquin Phoenix on a follow-up to the $1 billion-grossing R-rated hit, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMBASSADOR IN SPOTLIGHT</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-envoy-says-followed-trump-orders-ukraine-quid-143109159.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US ambassador to the European Union told an impeachment hearing Wednesday that he was following the orders of President Donald Trump in seeking a "quid pro quo" from Ukraine. Gordon Sondland -- whose appearance before Congress is being watched especially closely as he was a Trump ally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran missiles unrivaled in Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pentagon-says-irans-missiles-unrivaled-middle-east-211808212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite decades of sanctions, Iran has succeeded in developing its missile arsenal, which is larger than that of any other Middle Eastern country including Israel, a Pentagon study said Tuesday. "Iran has an extensive missile development program, and the size and sophistication of its missile force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brains '20% smaller than used to be'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/11/20/brains-smaller-idiocracy-theory-geary-male-female-brain-size-11176200/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Either our brains are getting more efficient or we're getting more stupid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWIFT SNUBBED...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/20/grammy-nominations-shocker-taylor-swifts-lover-snubbed-for-album-and-record-of-the-year-in-surprise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grammy shocker: Taylor Swift was snubbed for Album of the Year and Record of the Year for the 2020 Grammy nominations. Her “Lover” album failed to get nominated for the big prize, and n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady no longer playing like elite QB...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Tom-Brady-is-no-longer-playing-like-an-elite-14846713.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots are at the top of the AFC with a 9-1 record. The Westgate SuperBook in Las Vegas has them as the favorites to win the Super Bowl. Their defense is historically good. The game charters at Pro Football Focus rank New England's special teams as the second best of 2019.  The offense, however, has been underwhelming. The Patriots are averaging just two points per drive in 2019, the fifth lowest rate for the franchise since coach Bill Belichick took over in 2000. They're struggling in the red zone (49%, ranking 25th) and in goal-to-go situations (65%, 21st).  "The strength of our team is our defense and our special teams," quarterback Tom Brady told "The Greg Hill Show" Monday morning on WEEI. "On offense we just have to take advantage when we get opportunities and understand where our strengths lie and try and play to them - not giving any short fields, not turning the ball over and try and take advantage when we get into the red area to score touchdowns. That is kind of where our offense is. That is kind of where our team is."  Brady, remarkably, appears to be at the heart of the team's offensive futility. The future Hall of Famer completed 26 of 47 passes for 216 yards and no touchdowns on Sunday, the first time in Brady's 20-year career that he played an entire game and didn't lead the team in touchdown passes, according to ESPN's Stats &amp; Information. Wide receiver Julian Edelman threw New England's only touchdown pass, a 15-yarder to Phillip Dorsett in the third quarter. Brady also had 14 incompletions in the first half against Philadelphia, a career high.  You could wave this off as a one-game clunker, but Brady, who turned 42 in August, has been trending down for a few seasons. His completion rate is on a three-year decline, from close to a career high in 2016 (67%) to one of the lowest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kanye put Osteen's prosperity gospel back under spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/How-Kanye-West-put-Joel-Osteen-s-prosperity-14846529.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A performance by artist Kanye West at Joel Osteen's Lakewood Church in Houston on Sunday has launched a debate among Christians over controversial prosperity gospel teachings and the role of race in conservative evangelicalism.  "Kanye West and Joel Osteen are a match made in market-driven heaven," said Jonathan Walton, dean of Wake Forest Divinity School, who noted how West sold $170 "Jesus is King" sweatshirts with his new album.  "Both have baptized their commercial notoriety and their financial gains in Jesus' name," Walton said. "The communion table has become a merch table."  West's recent album "Jesus is King" has earned praise in unusual corners of conservative Christianity, but his comments have raised eyebrows over their association with Osteen's controversial prosperity gospel teachings, the idea that God grants health and wealth to his followers. Some Christians are also questioning whether black hip-hop artists are being used by white evangelicals preachers to boost their own brand and falsely signal progressive racial attitudes.  "Jesus has won the victory. Now, I told you about my arrogance and cockiness already. Now, the greatest artist that God has ever created is now working for him," West told Osteen on Sunday.  The prosperity gospel has seen a boost under President Donald Trump, who has included in his administration the televangelist Paula White, who promotes those teachings.  West and Osteen are part of a "show-and-tell" prosperity gospel movement in Christianity which says that God uses people to show he blesses them, said Kate Bowler, author of the book "Blessed: A History of the American Prosperity Gospel."  "Kanye's unbreakable confidence that he is the greatest artist on the planet could not have found a better theological home," Bowler said....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space travel barrier removed as docs freeze and revive human for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/space-travel-barrier-removed-docs-20920177</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Process is initially intended to save lives on Earth, rather than to send astronauts on long haul flights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466378-1/impeachment-inquiry-hearing-eu-ambassador-gordon-sondland&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambassador Gordon Sondland testifies before the House Intelligence Committee as part of the panel's impeachment inquiry into President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicates Pompeo on Ukraine pressure campaign...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/879615/sondland-reportedly-kept-pompeo-loop-about-ukraine-pressure-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Ambassador to the European Union Gordon Sondland made Secretary of State Mike Pompeo aware of a Ukraine pressure campaign, The New York Times reports. Sondland is set to testify Wednesday and face further questions in the impeachment inquiry about an effort to pressure Ukraine to announce investigations that might benefit President Trump politically, including involving former Vice President Joe Biden. Pompeo, according to the report, was informed by Sondland in mid-August "about a draft statement" he and another diplomat had worked on with Ukrainians "that they hoped would persuade Mr. Trump to grant Ukraine's new president the Oval Office meeting he was seeking." At the time, Sondland was negotiating a statement that would have Ukraine committing to an investigation of Burisma, the gas company where Biden's son served on the board, and the 2016 election. Additionally, the Times reports Sondland discussed the idea with Pompeo of pushing Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky "to pledge during a planned meeting with Mr. Trump in Warsaw that he would take the steps being sought by Mr. Trump as a way to break the logjam in relations between the two countries." Although the Times notes it's "not clear how specific" Sondland was with Pompeo about "what was being asked of the Ukrainians," Pompeo by this point would have already heard Trump's July phone call with Zelensky, during which the president makes clear that he wants the country to conduct investigations into Biden and the 2016 election. This report is breaking just as Sondland's testimony before Congress is about to get underway. Brendan Morrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEALTHY DIET TO PRESERVE HEARING...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/healthy-diet-helps-preserve-hearing-105223283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good eating habits, for example following a Mediterranean diet, could reduce hearing loss among women aged over 50, a recent study suggests. Choosing to eat more fruit and vegetables, foods that are high in fiber, and limiting the intake of sugar and fat in your daily diet has many proven health benefits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Saudi journalists detained in Australia after asylum bid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gay-saudi-journalists-detained-australia-asylum-bid-074747935.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two gay Saudi journalists who sought asylum in Australia after being threatened at home over their relationship have been held for weeks at an immigration detention centre, their lawyer said Wednesday. The couple arrived in Australia in mid-October on tourist visas but was singled out by airport customs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: GRAMMY NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/41506570eb6547af88f669c09acae38f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Grammys are screaming “Cuz I Love You” to Lizzo: The breakthrough singer-rapper scored a whopping eight nominations, including bids for the top four awards, making her the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift vs. Scooter Braun and the Imminent Rerecording War...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/taylor-swift-scooter-braun-imminent-rerecording-war-1256382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the streaming age, "boilerplate" contract provisions may be outdated for artists who want to reclaim their older songs: "I see broader blanket prohibitions coming."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER plans to start audio-recording rides...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/uber-will-audio-record-us-rides-for-safety/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People will apparently be able to opt to have their journey recorded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby DNA Tests Used by Parents to Check for Prodigy Kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/china-baby-dna-tests-used-by-parents-to-check-for-prodigy-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wave of companies promises to uncover everything from talents to emotional intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robochef: SONY cooks up new AI unit for food revolution...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/robochef-sony-cooks-ai-unit-food-revolution-060906580.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cooking robots and tastier recipes: Japanese electronics giant Sony on Wednesday launched a new artificial intelligence unit they hope will change the way we cook and eat. The new research arm, Sony AI, will operate in Japan, Europe and the United States and also focus on the traditional areas of gaming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAT ON PETE!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/buttigieg-rivals-sights-debate-taking-090000967.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Democratic presidential race’s new pecking order will be on full display Wednesday night, with Pete Buttigieg taking the debate stage as the emerging front-runner in Iowa and top 2020 rivals Joe Biden and Senator Elizabeth Warren trying to knock him off that perch.Buttigieg’s 9 percentage-point</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambassador could upend probe... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/20/gordon-sondland-impeachment-testimony-071708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His credibility is likely to come under fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC founding astronaut prepares for flight...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/virgin-galactics-founding-astronaut-namira-salim-prepares-for-flight-195813452.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic’s founding astronaut Namira Salim joined Yahoo Finance's On the Move to discuss her upcoming journey, space suit fitting and the space race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT DAY 4...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6486944b076b4df99a583a3a7c85574d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Ambassador Gordon Sondland, the most anticipated witness in the impeachment inquiry, will confront questions Wednesday about his evolving accounts of the Trump administration’s...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
