<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MAG:   Most chilling moment in Mueller report occurs on page 446...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/04/donald-trump-mueller-report-referral-investigations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 14 potential cases referred by the special prosecutor, investigators in New York, Washington, and Congress are zeroing in on the president, his family, and his business dealings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump mistakenly tweets millions dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/04/21/sri-lanka-explosions-donald-trump-says-millions-dead-easter-blasts/3533292002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In expressing his condolences, Trump incorrectly said millions more had died in a deadly series of explosions in Sri Lanka</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems  debate impeachment... </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/04/21/democrats-may-pursue-impeachment-against-president-trump/3533315002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, said it would have been OK for the president to accept Russia's help in the campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN TURNS 93!</title>
      <link>https://www.townandcountrymag.com/society/tradition/g27216812/queen-elizabeth-birthday-messages-instagram-royal-family-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.townandcountrymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British monarch turns 93 today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida cops snuck cameras into massage parlors years before Robert Kraft's prostitution sting...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-cb-massage-parlors-cameras-past-cases-20190419-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Years before Robert Kraft's visits to a massage parlor resulted in prostitution charges, South Florida cops used sneak-and-peek warrants to spy on private rubdowns and record it all on video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer files $5 million claim, saying L.A. City Hall rat problem caused her illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/lawyer-files-million-claim-saying-l-a-city-hall-rat/article_d0b2d092-e793-5a08-af36-9791b67761df.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES – A Los Angeles city attorney who says a City Hall rat infestation caused her to contract flea-borne typhus has filed a $5 million legal claim, saying Mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomber queued at buffet then unleashed devastation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sri-lanka-bomber-queued-hotel-buffet-then-unleashed-002105741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suicide bomber waited patiently in a queue for the Easter Sunday breakfast buffet at Sri Lanka's Cinnamon Grand hotel before setting off explosives strapped to his back. Carrying a plate, the man, who had registered at the hotel the night before as Mohamed Azzam Mohamed, was just about to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest anger burns in France, fueled by Notre Dame fire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/police-arrest-yellow-vest-demonstrators-clashes-break-201418077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police said they arrested more than 200 "yellow vest" demonstrators in Paris on Saturday as clashes broke out with demonstrators turning out for a 23rd week of anti-government protests. AFP journalists reported scuffles between police and protesters in the afternoon, after hours of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage after protesters urge police suicides...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/paris-prosecutors-probe-suicide-taunts-targeting-police-protest-151411687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris prosecutors have launched an investigation after French anti-government protesters in the latest of a series of demonstrations shouted slogans mocking police over a spate of recent suicides in the force, judicial sources said Sunday. The "yellow vest" protesters took to the streets of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST LAUGH...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/last-laugh-ukraine-comedian-became-president-173215372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Volodymyr Zelensky has been elected president of Ukraine twice -- first as a character in the popular TV show "Servant of the People", now for real. Supporters see the political novice as a breath of fresh air but critics say he is a puppet of powerful rivals to Ukraine's outgoing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ethical gold rush: Gilded age for guilt-free jewellery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ethical-gold-rush-gilded-age-guilt-free-jewellery-034555286.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Geneva-based firm, which makes the Palme d'Or trophy for the Cannes Film Festival, says it now uses only verified suppliers of gold that meet strict standards to minimise negative environmental impacts of mining the precious metal. "We do not want to promote mining extraction or use recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easter blasts at Sri Lanka hotels and churches...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/52-dead-blasts-hit-sri-lanka-churches-hotels-061837160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many in Sri Lanka, the apparently coordinated attacks brought back painful memories of life during the long-running conflict, when bomb blasts were a frequent occurrence. At least two of them involved suicide bombers, including one who lined up at a hotel breakfast buffet before unleashing carnage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pizza restaurant temporarily shut down after employees 'put laxatives in food'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/04/20/springtown-mr-jims-shuts-down-employees-put-miralax-on-pizza/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Texas Mr. Jim's Pizza has been temporarily shut down after health inspectors found that three employees put a laxative into pizza that was eaten by another employee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustration grows among caravan migrants as support fades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e2c9b809291948158973a152d6ad741d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAPASTEPEC, Mexico (AP) — Madison Mendoza, her feet aching and her face burned by the sun, wept as she said she had nothing to feed her 2-year-old son who she'd brought with her on the long trek...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian headed for landslide victory in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e12117b0d26f447dac1e449d25daa2d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIEV, Ukraine (AP) — A comedian whose only political experience consists of playing a president on TV appeared headed for a landslide victory in Ukraine's real-life presidential election...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTS:  Mexican troops disarmed American soldiers on US side of border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/mexican-troops-drew-weapons-on-american-soldiers-on-u-s-side-of-the-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed Mexican troops disarmed two United States soldiers while they were on the American side of the border, U.S. defense officials have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK porn block will completely BAN some adult sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8898716/uk-porn-block-banned-websites-over-18/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN’S upcoming “porn block” could see some adult websites banned for all Brits – even if they’re older than 18. The block is designed to prevent minors accessing XXX web…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400+ INJURED...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sri-lanka-blast/bombs-kill-more-than-200-in-sri-lankan-churches-hotels-on-easter-sunday-idUSKCN1RX038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 people were killed and at least 450 injured in bomb blasts that ri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West Selling $50 Church Socks at  Coachella... </title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/kanye-west-coachella-socks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood stains Jesus statue in Sri Lanka...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/55d93daed99c4f76baf7deec1bce5c72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLOMBO, Sri Lanka (AP) — More than 200 people were killed and hundreds more wounded in eight bomb blasts that rocked churches and luxury hotels in Sri Lanka on Easter Sunday — the deadliest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banks fight to hire criminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/small-time-crimes-a-dealbreaker-for-banking-jobs-11555851720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past decade, hundreds of people with criminal records have asked the government to let them work at a bank—with more than 40% of requests rejected or unresolved. The banking industry wants to change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last Kennedy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/04/representative-joe-kennedy-said-no-presidential-race/587401/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of Democratic power brokers wanted Representative Joe Kennedy to run for president. He consulted with family members and said no.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KKK leader's wife admits to killing husband...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/wife-of-missouri-kkk-leader-admits-killing-him-claims-son/article_7e56913c-a366-547f-bdb3-1b186117692d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malissa Ancona said her son helped clean up the crime scene and dump the body of her husband, Frank Ancona Jr. He was the imperial wizard of the Traditionalist American</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA woman who berated man wearing MAGA hat reported missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/california-woman-who-harassed-man-wearing-maga-hat-reported-missing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who sparked a national uproar after berating a 74-year-old man wearing a “Make America Great Again" cap at a San Francisco-area coffee shop earlier this month was reported missing Friday, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Amendment 'sanctuary' movement expands...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-second-amendment-sanctuary-county-movement-illinois-20190416-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a town hall meeting this month, Edwards became the 64th Illinois county to declare itself a “Second Amendment sanctuary county,” in which law enforcement has publicly declared it won’t pursue arrests against otherwise legal gun owners who fail to comply with new gun legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter Critics Rage Against Machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/scooter-critics-rage-against-the-machines-11555844400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber and Lyft have dipped their toes into the scooter-sharing business, but they may be cannibalizing their ride-sharing core.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd attacks leader of Turkish opposition party...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-election-attack/leader-of-turkish-opposition-party-safe-after-crowd-attacks-him-idUSKCN1RX0CO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of Turkey's main opposition party was attacked by several shouti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope during Easter vigil: Reject 'glitter of wealth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/20/pope-easter-vatican-glitter-wealth-1283780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Sin seduces; it promises things easy and quick, prosperity and success, but leaves behind only solitude and death,” he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For millennials, climate change clock ticks louder than biological one...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/some-millennials-climate-change-clock-ticks-louder-biological-one-n993331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I had this internal struggle: ‘Do I really want to bring a child into this world?’” a Seattle 29-year-old said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Methodists edge toward breakup over LGBT policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/religion/united-methodists-edge-toward-breakup-over-lgbt-policies-n996741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under one scenario, many centrists and liberals would leave en masse to form a new denomination — a potentially complex endeavor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage after protesters urge police suicides...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d1114da81614882907167a924463937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — With French police suicides on the rise, officials are expressing shock and anger after some yellow vest protesters encouraged police to kill themselves. Radical protesters have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broke Roger Stone Speaking for Money at Strip Club...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/broke-roger-stone-is-speaking-for-money-at-a-strip-club</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s pal is destitute paying to defend against charges he lied about WikiLeaks. Now he’s being hounded by an antifa who doesn't want him and the Proud Boys in town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden camera found in women's bathroom aboard Navy ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/military/hidden-camera-found-women-s-bathroom-aboard-navy-ship-n996446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Navy spokesperson confirmed that NCIS is investigating the device found aboard the USS Arlington, currently in port in Greece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher charged with hiring hitman to kill student after molestation accusation...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksdk.com/article/news/investigations/teacher-charged-with-hiring-hitman-to-kill-student-after-molestation-accusation-pleads-not-guilty/63-c5eeab38-7825-41b7-b969-2907ab1d1f1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksdk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A St. Louis teacher with HIV is accused of taking a student out of class and molesting him. Three years later, police say the teacher tried to hire a hit man to kill the child and his family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts killing music or just wasting our time?</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/entertainment/article/Are-podcasts-killing-music-or-just-wasting-our-13775490.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm about to kick a hornet's nest - and if this were a podcast, you would now hear the crunch of a boot perforating a hive, followed by the intensifying hum of inconvenienced hornets. But, fortunately, this isn't a podcast, so my punt shall remain silent, and here it is: I'm against podcasts.  I think they're tedious and samey and sedative, and when I'm feeling especially cranky, I consider them an enemy of music. Most podcasts are conversations for people to eavesdrop on - recorded talk that precludes real-life talk about real life with zombie talk about podcasts. Also, I like music. With all of the world's unheard songs beckoning us with their endless mystery, why would anyone choose to waste their precious listening hours on a podcast?  Asking that question makes me feel very alone. In a March cover story, New York Magazine called the podcast "the most significant and exciting cultural innovation of the new century," offering lots of boffo numbers to back it up. First, there were those 340 million downloads of "Serial," the true-crime investigative blockbuster that made "podcast" a household word back in 2014. Then there was that $230 million transaction in February, when Spotify bought the podcast network Gimlet Media, foreshadowing juicier deals to come. And now there are well over a half-million podcasts currently in circulation, with new ones sprouting each day.  This is a serious new form, and it's generating serious money - so instead of treating podcasts as a convenient way to feel smarter, let's take them seriously. Let's measure their worth by truly listening.  Like it or not, they're invading a soundworld near you. The marquee names of podcasting - "Pod Save America," "The Joe Budden Podcast," "Terrible, Thanks for Asking" and many others - are currently appearing on actual marquees, bringing their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atheist prayers can be barred by House chaplain...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/hoh/house-chaplain-not-allow-atheist-prayers-federal-appeals-court-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House of Representatives chaplain scored a legal victory when a federal appeals court ruled he could bar an atheist from offering a secular prayer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulance that hit pothole may have saved patient's life...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/ambulance-hitting-pothole-may-have-saved-patient-s-life-doctors-say/27215034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The force of striking the pothole seemed to reset the man's rapid heartbeat to a normal rhythm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico warns of 'deep concern' over armed groups on U.S. border...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-mexico-border/mexico-warns-of-deep-concern-over-armed-groups-on-u-s-border-idUSKCN1RW0N6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico said on Saturday it had "deep concern" about armed groups that ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger attacks zoo keeper after 'error' brought two together...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kansas-zoo-idUSKCN1RW0J7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare Sumatran tiger attacked a worker at the Topeka Zoo in Kansas on Saturday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia orders urgent review after spate of dingo attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190421-australia-orders-urgent-review-after-spate-dingo-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia orders urgent review after spate of dingo attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke seen for miles as SPACEX Crew Dragon suffers anomaly at Cape Canaveral...</title>
      <link>https://www.floridatoday.com/story/tech/science/space/2019/04/20/smoke-seen-miles-spacex-crew-dragon-suffers-anomaly-cape-canaveral/3531086002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.floridatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SpaceX Crew Dragon capsule suffered an anomaly during a routine test fire at Cape Canaveral Air Force Station, the 45th Space Wing confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Umpire body slams fan who runs on baseball field...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8da832aede36492185ed2b53a6da4518</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — When a fan ran on the field during the Blue Jays-Athletics game, he got tossed by umpire Jeff Nelson. Quite literally, actually. Nelson put a swift end to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVT SHUTS SOCIAL MEDIA SITES...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2019-04-21/sri-lanka-government-declares-curfew-shuts-down-access-to-major-social-media-sites</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400+ INJURED...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8907637/sri-lanka-colombo-easter-tourists-seven-dead-bombs-death-toll-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITS are believed to be among 156 killed in an Easter Sunday terror attack on eight churches and five-star hotels in Sri Lanka today. Nearly 500 are thought to have been injured when blasts ripped…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 EXPLOSIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2019/apr/21/sri-lanka-explosions-dozens-killed-and-hundreds-injured-in-church-and-hotel-blasts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many more injured as explosions hit three hotels and three churches in and around Colombo as well as at Batticaloa in the east of the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates demur on pursuing Trump post-White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/news/nationworld/ct-2020-democratic-presidential-hopefuls-trump-investigations-20190420-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democratic contenders for president aren't saying whether they would re-open investigations into Trump if they were to oust him in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100+ DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/six-explosions-hit-sri-lanka-on-easter-sunday-11699701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 100 people have been killed and more than 400 injured following six simultaneous blasts across Sri Lanka, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASTER SUNDAY ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8907637/colombo-attacks-explosions-sri-lanka-hotels-churches-easter-sunday-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPLOSIONS ripped through three five-star hotels and three churches in Sri Lanka today, reportedly killing 52 and injuring 280 others. Tourists are feared to be among those hurt after blasts at the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI ARRESTS LEADER OF GROUP STOPPING ILLEGALS IN NEW MEXICO</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-militia/fbi-arrests-leader-of-armed-group-stopping-migrants-in-new-mexico-idUSKCN1RW0O5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI on Saturday said it had arrested Larry Hopkins, the leader of an armed g...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds hurt as blasts hit Sri Lanka churches, hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-6944119/Hundreds-hurt-blasts-hit-Sri-Lanka-churches-hotels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A string of blasts hit high-end hotels and churches in Sri Lanka on Sunday, injuring hundreds of people as worshippers attended Easter services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump brushes off Romney criticism, points to loss in 2012...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-brushes-off-romneys-criticism-232500380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. Mitt Romney says he's "sickened" by the dishonesty the Russia investigation found in the Trump White House, but the president fires back that Romney should have put the same energy into running for president in 2012 that the Utah Republican has tapped in criticizing</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
