<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/hillary-clinton-chokes-up-as-she-reads-parts-of-the-victory-speech-she-hoped-to-deliver-in-2016/3440944/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, Hillary Clinton is sharing the speech she would have made if she had won the 2016 presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plumber who found cash and checks in toilet wall of Joel Osteen's church is rewarded $20,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/plumber-who-found-cash-and-checks-in-toilet-wall-of-joel-osteen-e2-80-99s-church-is-rewarded-2420000/ar-AARC9aK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary delivers victory speech that never was...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/for-the-first-time-hillary-clinton-publicly-delivers-the-victory-speech-she-would-have-given-in-2016/ar-AARCvuA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packs of thieves targeting San Fran area cannabis businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/oakland-cannabis-business-hit-twice-in-back-to-back-burglaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oakland marijuana delivery service is the latest in the Bay Area's cannabis industry to be hit by a gang of thieves. They struck Presto Canna in the city's Fruitvale neighborhood, not once, but twice this week, in back to back days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smollett Jury Goes Home With No Verdict As Prosecutors Claiming 'Overwhelming' Proof Of Faked Attack...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/jussie-smollett-verdict-jury-trial-hate-crime-empire-1234887442/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though prosecutors said there was “overwhelming” evidence that Jussie Smollett staged an assault on himself in late January 2019, there will be no verdict today in the ex-Empire star’s trial. After…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Failure Revealed In Secret CDC Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/danvergano/covid-test-false-positive-failure-cdc-documents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigation records obtained by BuzzFeed News show how one of the most pivotal mistakes of the pandemic fell on an overburdened CDC lab with only three full-time employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancun tourists flee beach after 5 on jet skis open fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4233704/tourists-flee-holiday-hotspot-gunmen-jet-skis-open-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOURISTS scrambled for cover after gunfire broke out on a beach at the family-friendly Mexican resort in Cancun. Five attackers pulled up to the beach outside the four-star Oasis Palm hotel on jet …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Married in the Metaverse...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/08/getting-married-in-the-metaverse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traci and Dave Gagnon met in the cloud, so it only made sense that their wedding took place in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERIES MAY NEVER BE SOLVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4233002/ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-relationship-pregnancy-ranch-frozen-penis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell and Jeffrey Epstein’s strange relationship has been in the spotlight during her sex trafficking and abuse trial. One of the mysteries that’s emerged is a claim by one of Max…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians outraged by sperm-smuggling drama film...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/palestinians-outraged-by-sperm-smuggling-drama-film-688186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:   Prosecution Fumbling Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/12/the-prosecution-is-fumbling-its-case-against-ghislaine-maxwell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say they plan to rest their case against Jeffrey Epstein’s associate by week’s end—a shocking move from a team that appears to have failed on a number of other fronts already.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George W. Bush victim of Havana Syndrome?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10288759/George-W-Bush-Havana-Syndrome-G-8-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An intriguing new report on Wednesday suggests that former President George W. Bush could have been a victim of Havana Syndrome when he fell ill at a G8 conference in Germany in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coffee crisis in Central America fuels record exodus north...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coffee-crisis-central-america-fuels-120809292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four sons of María Bonilla and Esteban Funes all embarked on the treacherous journey north, one of them aged 10, preferring the life of an unauthorized migrant in America to a coffee farmer in Central America. Coffee doesn't pay for many of the hundreds of thousands of Central American farmers who produce the delicate arabica beans for the world's finest grounds. Increasingly, they are giving up, becoming part of a broader migrant flow to the U.S.-Mexico border that U.S. data shows has hit a record high this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of camels barred from 'beauty' contest over Botox...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2021/12/8/dozens-of-camels-barred-from-saudi-beauty-contest-over-botox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organisers say they will impose strict penalties on ‘manipulators’ as they attempt to halt ‘all acts of tampering’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury begins deliberations in Smollett case...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/08/jury-begins-deliberating-in-jussie-smollett-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors in the Jussie Smollett trial began deliberating Wednesday over whether he staged a race-hate attack on himself and then lied to cops about being the victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alt-Jihad' Rising On Socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/alt-jihad-rising-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The playbook of the “alt-right” is guiding a new generation of fringe jihadists, showing just how complicated extremism is about to become online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Moves Step Closer to Geoengineering Oceans...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/were-a-step-closer-to-geoengineering-the-oceans-1848179300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Academy of Sciences released a major report chronicling six techniques to turn the oceans into carbon dioxide vacuums.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Man Has Watched Hundreds of Executions. Now He's Next...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93ba3a/oklahoma-executions-bigler-stouffer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bigler Jobe Stouffer has spent 36 years on death row in Oklahoma and witnessed 133 executions. Now, it's his turn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends account providing updates...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/twitter-account-ghislaine-maxwell-trial-suspended</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Twitter account that closely monitored the trial of former Jeffrey Epstein partner Ghislaine Maxwell Epstein was suspended on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE:  Extramarital sex sins NOT that 'serious'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/08/pope-says-extramarital-sex-sins-arent-that-serious/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Sins of the flesh are not the most serious,” the 84-year-old religious leader said. Top transgressions instead include pride and hatred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest lab-grown steak unveiled...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/dec/08/worlds-largest-lab-grown-steak-unveiled-by-israeli-firm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MeaTech 3D created the 4oz steak using 3D printing with real bovine cells that mature into muscle and fat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person pulled from car submerged at brink of Niagara Falls...</title>
      <link>https://buffalonews.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/person-pulled-from-car-submerged-at-brink-of-niagara-falls/article_0d083f24-5850-11ec-b1d6-ff1659596882.html#tracking-source=home-top-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;buffalonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dark-colored compact vehicle was roughly 100 feet from the brink and about 30 feet from the edge of land in the park. It was mostly submerged in the river</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems begin souring on mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/west-wing-playbook/2021/12/07/dems-begin-souring-on-vaccine-mandates-495358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary SOBS as she reads '16 victory speech that never was...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10288375/Hillary-Clinton-gets-tearful-reads-speech-given-won-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton revealed the victory speech she would have given had she won that year, and admitted she did not even bother to write a concession speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How US Military Could Mobilize If Russia Invades Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2021/12/08/how-us-military-could-mobilize-if-russia-invades-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. paratroopers landing in the Baltics, Army cavalry and artillerymen convoying in from Germany and an armored brigade massing its forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Top Gun' Training Aims to Keep China at Bay...</title>
      <link>https://insidesources.com/can-top-gun-training-give-u-s-taiwan-leverage-to-keep-china-at-bay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;insidesources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was an image that got the Pentagon’s attention: Satellite photos of targets shaped like an American aircraft carrier and at least two Arleigh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California to be abortion sanctuary if Roe overturned...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-plans-to-be-abortion-sanctuary-if-Roe-16685072.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — With more than two dozen states poised to ban abortion if the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland PM sorry for clubbing after virus contact...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59577371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanna Marin went on a night out on Saturday, hours after her foreign minister had tested positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods announces return to golf...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/08/tiger-woods-announces-golf-return-10-months-after-horrific-car-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods announced Wednesday that he will participate in the upcoming PNC Championship with son Charlie, less than a year after a horrific car wreck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.2 million quit jobs in October...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2021/12/08/october-employees-quitting-jolts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high quits numbers are a reflection of what is perhaps the most worker friendly climate in decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels Hiring Kids to Be Hitmen...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/jgmpmy/mexico-drug-cartels-recruit-children-to-kill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trend of children and teens being recruited to kill by the cartels is widespread in Mexico, and the government is struggling to prevent or stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell gives Epstein foot massage in never-before-seen pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4229772/ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-foot-massage-relationship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CREEPY pictures have emerged showing Ghislaine Maxwell giving Jeffrey Epstein a foot massage. The never-before-seen images reveal the intimate relationship between the 59-year-old socialite and the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Hollywood wants to become Amsterdam of far West...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/west-hollywood-wants-to-become-amsterdam-of-the-far-west-jay-z-seems-to-approve/ar-AARBIb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of 40 quakes in 24 hours causing buzz in northwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/08/weather/earthquake-swarm-oregon/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of North America's most active fault lines sprung to life on Tuesday after a swarm of more than 40 earthquakes -- ranging from a magnitude 3.5 to 5.8 -- rattled off the coast of Oregon, catching the attention and concern of millions in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Tiniest Camera -- Size Of Grain Of Salt!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/tiniest-camera-grain-of-salt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of tiny devices could cover the whole surface of a smartphone to become one giant camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BLOOD IN LA: Brazen assault in middle of day leaves boy dead, neighborhood shaken...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/brazen-assault-in-the-middle-of-the-day-leaves-a-boy-dead-a-neighborhood-shaken/ar-AARBAyg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing arguments set in Smollett trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/jussie-smollett-entertainment-lifestyle-arts-and-entertainment-crime-644f875e61b3ea9c7e8eefd1c227bf91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Closing arguments are scheduled for Wednesday morning in the case against former “Empire” actor Jussie Smollett, who is accused of staging a racist, anti-gay attack against himself in downtown Chicago to get publicity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK BRINGING BACK 'DRACONIAN' RESTRICTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4228357/boris-johnson-plan-b-today-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson is poised to announce Plan B restrictions TODAY that will require Brits to work from home and use vaccine passports imminently. Government sources told The Sun that the tough measures…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Is 'Top Contender' for Correction, Money Managers Say...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-top-contender-correction-money-050001481.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- By many counts, 2021 was the year cryptocurrencies were finally embraced by institutions. Now those same money-managers say the asset class is ripe for a big selloff next year. Most Read from BloombergThe World’s Relentless Demand for Chips Turns Deadly in MalaysiaSand and Soldiers Mix as Troops Move In to Protect Cancun TouristsEven in the Metaverse, Not All Identities Are Created EqualThe $300 Billion Plan to Bring Green Power to China’s MegacitiesMeet the New Climate Refugee in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scholz becomes first new German chancellor in 16 years...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/584848-scholz-becomes-first-new-german-chancellor-in-16-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olaf Scholz became the first new German chancellor in 16 years on Wednesday, succeeding Angela Merkel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives prepare new push for constitutional convention...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/584835-conservatives-prepare-new-push-for-constitutional-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — Conservative lawmakers will mount a new push to call a constitutional convention aimed at creating a balanced budget amendment and establishing term limits for members of Congress in an effort to rein in what they see as a runaway federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate poised to pass resolution to nullify Biden vax mandate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/584825-senate-poised-to-pass-resolution-to-nullify-biden-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate is expected to vote as soon as Wednesday to nullify President Biden’s vaccine mandate for large employers, giving Republicans a big symbolic victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER: THREE SHOTS NECESSARY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/08/health/pfizer-omicron-vaccine-data/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary lab studies show two doses of the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine may not provide sufficient protection against the Omicron coronavirus variant, but three doses are able to neutralize it, the companies said in a news release on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Faces Tory Fury Again, This Time Over Lockdown Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/boris-johnson-faces-tory-fury-again-this-time-over-a-lockdown-party-1.1692769</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson’s government was plunged into further turmoil at a critical time for his ruling Conservatives and in the fight against Covid-19, after a video emerged showing key aides joking about a Downing Street Christmas party when such gatherings were banned last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway caps indoor gatherings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-europe-ee281cbd3dab88ea212b976a16330923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — The Norwegian government is introducing a 10-person limit for gatherings at private homes to counter an uptick in COVID-19 cases, although the number will be increased to 20 on Christmas and New Year's eves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Christmas tree set on fire in Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/fox-news-christmas-tree-on-fire-tyrus-nypd-new-york/11310845/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic video shows the 50 foot tree on Sixth Avenue going up in flames. The suspect is identified as 49-year-old Craig Tamanaha, who is homeless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin says he never pulled trigger. Experts skeptical...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Baldwin-says-he-never-pulled-the-trigger-Experts-16684156.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor dressed in drag for HBO show. Blowback led to him relieved of duties...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-pastor-dressed-in-drag-for-an-HBO-show-The-16684147.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a coifed pink wig, varnished acrylic nails, platform boots and a sparkling, fringed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian girl stabs Israeli woman in Jerusalem in new wave of lone wolf attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/palestinian-girl-stabs-israeli-woman-in-jerusalem-in-new-wave-of-lone-wolf-attacks/ar-AARBcgT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese billionaire launches into space, plans cash giveaways, zero-gravity haircut...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/japanese-billionaire-launches-into-space-plans-cash-giveaways-and-a-zero-gravity-haircut/ar-AARBp1E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Possessed' woman undergoes nine-hour exorcism after she attacked priest...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10287425/Possessed-woman-28-undergoes-nine-hour-exorcism-attacked-Italian-priest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 28-year-old woman was accompanied by her family members to the Church of Saint Mary of Mount Berico in Vicenza, northern Italy, at around 11am on Sunday for confession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis proposes plan to fight rising seas without any 'left-wing stuff'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-gov-desantis-proposes-plan-232500861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Gov. Ron DeSantis announced a series of steps to defend Florida against rising sea levels Tuesday, even as he denounced the use of the term “global warming” as a “pretext to do a bunch of left-wing things.” The governor submitted 76 projects to the state Legislature to improve drainage, raise sea walls and take other steps to fight flooding across the state. The state ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan doctor begs for more help as state tops covid hospitalization peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/doctors-call-arms-rejoin-us-110137712.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Michigan broke the pandemic record for COVID-19 hospitalizations, a critical care doctor issued an urgent plea for more help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partisan bickering could doom efforts to regulate social media companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/12/07/partisan-bickering-could-doom-efforts-to-regulate-social-media-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans and Democrats tried putting differences aside to regulate social media firms, but they have returned to old partisan corners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meadows on track for contempt of Congress charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/12/07/meadows-on-track-for-contempt-of-congress-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House Chief of Staff Mark Meadows has stopped cooperating with the Jan. 6 select panel and faces contempt of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some people actually paying to get 'lost' on vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/some-people-are-actually-paying-to-get-e2-80-98lost-e2-80-99-on-vacation/ar-AARzUFF?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court poised to further open door for taxpayer funding of religious schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-poised-to-further-open-the-door-for-taxpayer-funding-of-religious-schools/ar-AARzf13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers felt pressure to destroy covid data in Florida, report claims...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uf-researchers-felt-pressure-destroy-032700797.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fear of upsetting state officials is pervasive among faculty at the University of Florida, to the point that race-related references have been edited out of course materials and researchers felt pressure to destroy COVID-19 data, according to a report released Monday by a Faculty Senate committee. The six-person panel was convened three weeks ago to investigate academic freedom issues after ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
