<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Saga Threatens to Blow Up 2020 Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-whistleblower-saga-threatens-to-blow-up-2020-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two reports on Thursday night say the conversation in the complaint involved Ukraine, the country that the president’s close lawyer has turned to in looking for dirt on Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Military to present Trump with several options on Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4d4ce92397ba44a68bedd60edb2aee36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattress salesman rescues 120 people...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/462301-houston-mattress-salesman-rescues-about-120-people-from-imelda-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Houston furniture salesman reportedly rescued more than 100 people from flooding caused by Tropical Storm Imelda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican cartel girl assassins bathe in blood of victims, have sex with corpses...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9954708/el-chapo-kim-k-female-assassins-mexico-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH her red hair flowing over her shoulders, pretty Juana looks like any other young woman in her 20s – apart from the fact she’s holding a machine gun. Though she may have an innocent face,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Journalists to be tested on loyalty to Xi...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/sep/20/chinese-journalists-to-be-tested-on-loyalty-to-xi-jinping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exam will test journalists on president’s teachings on socialism and propaganda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery 'craft' explodes over Area 51...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mystery-craft-explodes-over-area-20082582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A renowned conspiracy theorist said the photos could show a black project spy plane that uses alien technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA emails reveal how agency didn't see large, 'sneaky' near-miss asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7485763/Internal-NASA-emails-reveal-missed-asteroid-skimmed-Earth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internal emails have revealed the US space agency was caught by surprise by the asteroid named '2019 OK' which passed Earth on July 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien enthusiasts descend on Nevada desert near secretive base...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7480385/Nevada-desert-towns-prep-possible-Storm-Area-51-influx.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a thousand tourists have already descended upon the tiny towns of Rachel and Hiko - which have a combined population of just 175 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of Unaccompanied Alien Children Entering USA Highest in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/melanie-arter/hhs-number-unaccompanied-minors-entering-us-reached-highest-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of unaccompanied children (UACs) entering the United States during fiscal year 2019 has grown to levels never seen before, Jonathan Hayes, director of the HHS’s Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR), told Congress on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BULLARD: Rate cut too small!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/20/feds-james-bullard-says-cutting-rates-by-a-bigger-half-percentage-point-would-have-been-more-appropriate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Bullard said he dissented on this week's Fed decision to lower rates by a quarter percentage point because he didn't think the cut was big enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,200 'burned out' nurses walk off job in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/university-of-chicago-nurse-strike-2200-nurses-walk-off-job-today-2019-09-20-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nurses strike after contract talks with the hospital broke down this week amid a dispute over staffing levels and pay raises</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellison: UBER 'worthless'; 'App cat could have written'...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/larry-ellison-says-uber-wework-are-almost-worthless-barrons-2019-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire cofounder or Oracle who is on Tesla's board isn't a fan of WeWork either, he told a group of entrepreneurs at his San Francisco home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Emergency in 13 Counties...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-09-19-tropical-depression-imelda-impacts-southeast-texas-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how Imelda is impacting parts of Texas and Louisiana along the Gulf coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-ray shows how vaping left teen lungs caked with hardened oil...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/09/19/shocking-x-ray-shows-how-vaping-left-teens-lungs-caked-with-hardened-oil-10775166/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;19 year-old Anthony Mayo has the lungs of a 60 year-old who has been smoking two packets of cigarettes a day all their adult life, doctors told his father Keith</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN Flight Cancelled Over Concerns About Muslim Passengers...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/09/19/american-airlines-flight-dallas-cancelled-concerns-about-muslim-passengers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Texas Muslim said American Airlines cancelled his flight Saturday because the flight crew didn't feel comfortable with him and his Muslim friend on the plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No crowds as iPhone 11 hits stores in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone-china-idUSKBN1W515K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's latest iPhone 11 range hit stores in China on Friday, with short qu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deeper danger of deepfakes: Powerless people...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ny-oped-the-real-deepfake-danger-20190920-mnu6w7xbdzgklgfr7ibmq6bcne-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the last year, news coverage of deepfakes — counterfeit videos that make it seem as though people are doing or saying something they actually aren’t doing or saying — has positioned them as dangerous to democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE FED PUMPING IN CASH CRUNCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2019/09/19/repo-madness-heads-into-day-4-another-75-billion-liquidity-drop-from-ny-fed-coming-friday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed's life support for the short-term funding market will continue on Friday. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER closes thousands of fake news accounts worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/twitter-closes-thousands-fake-news-accounts-worldwide-000942848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter said Friday it has closed down thousands of accounts across the world for spreading fake news as well as pro-government propaganda, including in places like the United Arab Emirates, China and Spain. Accounts coming from China seeking to sow discord among protesters in Hong Kong were closed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NFL teams battle QB crisis...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/no-country-old-men-nfl-teams-battle-qb-010322274--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Roethlisberger is out for the season, Drew Brees faces an extended injury layoff, and Eli Manning has been benched. The opening weeks of the 2018/2019 NFL campaign are making a persuasive argument that the league is no country for old men. After just two rounds, no fewer than five of the league</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Blasts Refs For 'Ridiculous Penalties'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/19/tom-brady-tweets-ridiculous-penalties-thursday-night-football/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The QB took to his Twitter account -- which is generally reserved for dad jokes and pump-up videos -- to vent about penalties in the Titans-Jaguars game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The wearable chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/shortcuts/2019/sep/19/the-wearable-lex-chair-lets-you-sit-where-you-want-but-will-it-catch-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of aluminium legs that you strap to your bum could be the solution for people who find there are not enough chairs in the world. As long as they don’t mind looking ridiculous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
American struggles with medical bills foreign concept in other countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/americans-struggles-with-medical-bills-are-a-foreign-concept-in/article_c412fecf-22e5-5edc-9e52-2925b9702a88.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GORINCHEM, Netherlands — In France, a visit to the doctor typically costs the equivalent of $1.12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen 'womanizer' portrayal of Mossad agent slammed by family...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7483209/Sacha-Baron-Cohens-portrayal-Israels-Mossad-agent-Netflix-drama-blasted-family.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eli Cohen's family have hit out at the new Netflix mini series about the Mossad agent's life undercover behind enemy lines in Syria saying the flamboyant womaniser isn't the man they knew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio pulls plug on sputtering presidential bid...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/20/bill-de-blasio-pulls-the-plug-on-his-sputtering-presidential-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio finally pulled the plug on his ill-fated presidential bid that failed to draw more than 1 percent support in national polls — but brought plenty of ire from New Yorkers w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schoolchildren hit streets in vast global climate strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/students-demand-change-vast-global-climate-strike-082628597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast crowds of children skipped school Friday to join a global strike against climate change, heeding the rallying cry of teen activist Greta Thunberg and demanding adults act to stop environmental disaster. It was expected to be the biggest protest ever against the threat posed to the planet by climate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With lines and blackouts, Cubans suffer fuel crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/queues-blackouts-cubans-suffer-fuel-crisis-060245703.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ernesto Mirabal gave up a night's sleep for a few gallons of gas at a Havana service station, where lining up for five hours has become the norm during a severe fuel shortage on the Communist-run island. Since President Miguel Diaz-Canel's shock announcement on September 11 that the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Oil Trader Causes $320 Million Loss...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mitsubishi-unit-expects-320-million-071334064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mitsubishi Corp. said a rogue oil trader at its Singapore unit lost $320 million in unauthorized transactions disguised as legitimate hedges for customers.The employee, a Chinese national working at Petro-Diamond Singapore Pte, has been fired and reported to police, Mitsubishi said in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most common antidepressant barely relieves symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/09/19/common-antidepressant-barely-helps-improve-depression-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most commonly prescribed antidepressant barely relieves symptoms of modern depression, a major study reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Hand Sanitizer Not Effective Against Flu; Takes 4 Mins Rubbing To Kill...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/flu-season-alert-hand-sanitizer-not-very-effective-against-virus-strain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new study, it took nearly four minutes of exposure to hand sanitizer to completely deactivate the flu virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Brown Accuser Says Sent Her 'Intimidating' Text Messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/2019/09/19/antonio-brown-accuser-text-messages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Antonio Brown accuser says she received “intimidating” text messages from the Patriots receiver, and has asked the NFL to act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOME DEPOT, LOWE'S ACCUSED OF SCANNING MILLIONS OF FACES...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/home-depot-and-lowes-accused-of-scanning-millions-of-customers-faces_09192019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper performs with Boris Johnson 'decapitated head'...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/article/mercury-prize-slowthai-boris-johnson-dummy-head-brexit-prime-minister-9112981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret FBI Subpoenas Scoop Up Personal Data From Scores of Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/20/secret-f-b-i-subpoenas-scoop-up-personal-data-from-scores-of-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - The F.B.I. has used secret subpoenas to obtain personal data from far more companies than previously disclosed, newly released documents show.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT: State dinner in White House Rose Garden...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7484459/Melania-Trump-uses-Australias-national-colors-set-stage-glamorous-state-dinner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's national colors of green and gold set the theme for Friday night's state dinner in the Rose Garden of the White House, picked by first lady Melania Trump to honor the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Admits He Asked Ukraine to Investigate Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/462277-giuliani-says-of-course-he-asked-ukraine-to-look-into-biden-seconds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's personal attorney Rudy Giuliani gave conflicting answers in an interview on CNN on Thursday night as to whether he asked Ukraine to look into former Vice President Joe Biden, saying at one point "of course I did."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unshackled Trump finally gets the presidency he always wanted...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/19/trump-presidency-aides-white-house-1502041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No longer hemmed in by aides, Trump has bent the presidency into the mold of the Trump Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/gtconway3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien enthusiasts descend on Nevada desert near secretive base...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/local-nevada/officials-say-theyre-ready-for-whatever-comes-from-area-51-events-1852066/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials looking over a pair of Storm Area 51 festivals still don’t know what to expect as the first day of events is set to kick off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man electrocuted, drowns trying to rescue horse...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/national-international/Its-Bad-Water-Rescues-Begin-as-Imelda-Soaks-East-Texas-560786191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The slow-churning remnants of Tropical Storm Imelda dangerously flooded parts of Texas and Louisiana on Thursday, scrambling rescue crews and volunteers with boats to reach scores of stranded drivers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Admits He Asked Ukraine to Investigate Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/must-watch-giuliani-says-he-asked-ukraine-to-probe-biden-seconds-after-denying-it-in-trainwreck-cnn-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani says he asked Ukraine to investigate Joe Biden seconds after denying it in trainwreck CNN interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLT suspends production of AR-15 for civilian market...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fbdf5e5f6d654332bbedfaffe3663154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — Gun-maker Colt is suspending its production of rifles for the civilian market including the popular AR-15, the company said Thursday in a shift it attributed to changes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48f63d46490a409ca20aecc1c4fdf573</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News from The Associated Press, the definitive source for independent journalism from every corner of the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS DRENCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Slow-Moving-Tropical-Depression-Imelda-Brings-Over-30-Inches-Rain-Texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devastating flooding unfolded across far southeast Texas late Wednesday night and spread into the Houston area on Thursday morning, as Tropical Depression Imelda continued to plague the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHISTLE-BLOWER DRAMA HITS WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/whistle-blower-s-complaint-is-said-to-involve-multiple-acts-by-trump/ar-AAHxDU9?li=AA30Nm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore officials pitched on putting three surveillance planes in sky at once, covering most of city...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/crime/bs-md-ci-cr-surveillance-pitch-20190919-dkurugpjdretrjzcevzlc7eabu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City officials are being pitched on putting not one but three surveillance planes into the skies above Baltimore, according to emails obtained by The Baltimore Sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TILLERSON: Netanyahu 'played' Trump with misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/middle-east-north-africa/462205-tillerson-netanyahu-played-trump-with</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Secretary of State Rex Tillerson said during a Tuesday interview with a panel of Harvard professors that Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu “played” President Trump numerous times,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States Warn Residents About Mosquito-Borne Illness That Has Killed 5...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/uptick-rare-mosquito-borne-virus-us-states-65704252</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US deaths and illnesses from rare mosquito-borne disease are up, officials say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police respond to apparent suicide at FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/19/police-respond-to-apparent-suicide-at-facebook-headquarters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Menlo Park Police Department on Thursday said it responded to an apparent suicide at Facebook's headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston hit with 3 FEET of rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/imelda-triggers-widespread-flooding-across-southeastern-texas/535882</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarosa visits Michael Cohen in prison, takes role of 'personal adviser'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/09/19/omarosa-visits-michael-cohen-in-prison-has-taken-on-role-of-personal-adviser-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“She apparently has taken on the role of his personal advisor/coach,” a source told Page Six.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: Demi Moore's 'CORPORATE ANIMALS' One of Worst Movies Ever...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/09/crporate-animals-review-demi-moore-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although she does not get top billing, Moore is the central focus, surrounded by a cast of amateurs who are unknown for a very good reason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil soars again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asian-markets-mixed-fed-leaves-traders-seeking-more-041912266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices shot higher Thursday on fresh supply concerns in the Middle East, while on most markets stocks climbed after the US Federal Reserve's decision to cut interest rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 tropical storms whirling at once set record...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/09/19/hurricanes-tropical-storms-atlantic-pacific-set-record-kiko-humberto-jerry-imelda-mario-lorena/2373241001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's hurricane season, but this is ridiculous. The six storms whirling this week in the Atlantic and Pacific set a record, forecasters reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snorkelers caught in rare shark 'feeding frenzy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/nation/article/Hawaii-snorkelers-caught-rare-shark-feeding-14452577.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people on a snorkeling tour in Oahu suffered from bite wounds and scratches after sharks circled them in a "feeding frenzy," according to Hawaii News Now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA kicks out Cuban diplomats over alleged 'influence operations'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-cuba-un/u-s-kicks-out-two-members-of-cubas-mission-to-u-n-over-alleged-influence-operations-idUSKBN1W42W2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Thursday ordered the expulsion from the United State...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd '500-year rainfall' in 2 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/2nd-500-year-rainfall-in-2-years-will-cause-6-billion-to-8-billion-in-damages-accuweather-predicts/537250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW MANY MORE?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/19/justin-trudeau-leaves-open-possibility-of-more-blackface-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Justin Trudeau offered a fresh apology to his fellow Canadians on Thursday over his blackface and “brownface” scandal — and left open the possibility that more photos of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaping illness count tops 500, but cause remains unknown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/38ff7532f98a42dabfa980b142033c7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — More than 500 people have been diagnosed with vaping-related breathing illnesses, but the cause remains unknown, U.S. health officials said Thursday. Meanwhile, the Food and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah Scout Looked for NYC Attack Targets: Feds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/investigations/Hezbollah-Scout-Attack-Targets-in-NYC-Boston-560797451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scout for the militant group Hezbollah was looking at locations for attacks in New York and Boston and sending target information back to leadership in Lebanon, federal prosecutors said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Canada lost 3 billion birds since 1970...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/u-s-canada-have-lost-3-billion-birds-scientists-say-ncna1055961</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It's an empty feeling in your stomach that these same birds that you grew up with just aren't there anymore.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANG: Eliminate Car Ownership...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/yang-well-eliminate-car-ownership-to-fight-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Andrew Yang said the United States may have to eliminate private car ownership to combat climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi mocks Trump's 'mind'...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7483051/Pelosi-uses-air-quotes-discuss-whats-Trumps-mind-gun-background-checks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asked what features of gun reform she thinks the president is stuck on, Pelosi told reporters: 'You want me to tell you what goes on in the president's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How senators invest in firms they regulate...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/sep/19/us-senators-investments-conflict-of-interest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis of financial disclosure data shows 51 senators and their spouses have as much as $96m invested in corporate stocks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America Over Simon Cowell? 'GOT TALENT' Ratings Fall To All-Time Low...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/09/kodi-lee-americas-got-talent-finale-low-ratings-masterchef-big-brother-nbc-1202738572/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kodi Lee took the big prize last night as the winner of America’s Got Talent’s 14th season, but there wasn’t much of a victory dance for the Simon Cowell show or NBC. With a 1.5 rating among adults…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS DRENCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/news/news/news/2019-09-19-tropical-depression-imelda-impacts-southeast-texas-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic in sky: DELTA flight plunges nearly 30,000 feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/panic-in-the-sky-delta-flight-from-atlanta-plunges-nearly-30-000-feet/987851866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Delta Air Lines pilot had to make a rapid, controlled decent of nearly 30,000 feet after getting an alarm on an Atlanta flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: War on D*ck Pics Begins...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/sep/19/its-a-violation-the-war-on-unwanted-dick-pics-has-begun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legislators and tech companies are finally working to protect women from receiving unwanted sexually explicit images online – will it work?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dem donor Ed Buck arrested after third man overdoses at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ed-buck-charged-after-third-man-overdoses-at-his-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In court papers, prosecutors said the wealthy activist is predator whose sexual fetish is injecting his victims with methamphetamine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six U.S. cities among most surveilled places in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.routefifty.com/public-safety/2019/09/six-us-cities-make-list-most-surveilled-places-world/159983/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.routefifty.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report found that CCTV surveillance is increasing in certain areas of the U.S., with one city government watching its citizens from 35,000 cameras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House stops announcing calls with foreign leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/24/politics/foreign-leaders-call-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House has suspended the practice of publishing public summaries of President Donald Trump's phone calls with world leaders, two sources with knowledge of the situation tell CNN, bringing an end to a common exercise from Republican and Democratic administrations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS testing drone delivery with FEDEXGOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/19/walgreens-to-test-drone-delivery-service-with-fedex-and-alphabets-wing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pilot program will deliver food and beverage, over-the-counter medications and other items within minutes, the company said. Prescription deliveries will not be available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Welcome Journalists to China Propaganda Workshop...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/09/19/china-launches-belt-and-road-news-network-workshop-to-indoctrinate-journalists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China launched a workshop under its Belt and Road News Network (BRNN) aimed at promoting propaganda about its infrastructure initiative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Pumps $75 Billion Into Financial System Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2019/09/19/fed-pumps-75-billion-into-financial-system-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve Bank of New York once again stepped into the money market to supply additional liquidity on Thursday morning. The N.Y. Fed injected | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: 89-Year-Old Woman Brutally Beaten Inside NYC Apartment...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/09/19/elderly-woman-robbed-in-east-village/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said the victim had been saving up to buy a tombstone for her late husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  What is mystery object approaching from interstellar space? </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9962068/mystery-object-approaching-us-from-interstellar-space-could-be-alien-spacecraft-top-scientist-admits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS object hurtling towards our Solar System may be an alien spacecraft. That’s the shock claim made by one space scientist, who has exclusively revealed to The Sun that our incoming…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to shoot down planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9951469/saudi-arabia-attack-donald-trump-plans-for-military-strike-iran-tehran-shoot-down-us-planes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump is drawing up a hit-list as he hatches plans to clobber Iran following the attacks on the world’s largest oil plant in Saudi Arabia.  The US President is said to have been given a “men…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Roasts LGBT Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/pete-buttigieg-cant-even-read-the-lgbt-media-anymore-its-all-too-gay-not-gay-enough-wrong-kind-of-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg said on a radio interview that he doesn't read LGBT-centered media anymore, saying it makes him feel like he can't be himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW HER NOMINATION TO LOSE?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/matt-drudge-predicts-this-2020-dem-has-the-nomination-to-lose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iconic conservative blogger Matt Drudge suggested who he thought was going to ultimately become the Democratic nominee in 2020 on Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUSTIN, IS THAT YOU?</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5680759/justin-trudeau-brownface-photo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trudeau apologized after TIME published a photo from the party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia detains shaman on mission to 'banish' president...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-detains-shaman-mission-banish-putin-084137836.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian police on Thursday said they had detained a Siberian shaman walking to Moscow on a mission to drive out President Vladimir Putin who he describes as a "demon". Police in the eastern Siberian region of Buryatia said they had detained the shaman, Alexander Gabyshev, on a highway near</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The crowds, the momentum, the issues...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-steve-bannon-i-dont-agree-matt-drudge-sen-warren-just-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'You’re going to have populist nationalism versus populist socialism'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  Party Polarization at Record...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/266906/trump-job-approval-ties-party-polarization-record.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gallup's latest update on President Trump's approval rating finds 43% of Americans approving of the job he is doing, but with a record-tying 86-point gap in Republicans' and Democrats' ratings of him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Nursing aide tried to perform sex act on male patient getting annual physical...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/florida-nursing-assistant-nabbed-185069</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 19--While conducting a physical exam, a Florida nursing assistant “opened his mouth and placed it around" the penis of his patient, according to police who arrested the health care worker o</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
