<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Amid delta surge, confusion again reigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Amid-delta-surge-confusion-again-reigns-16376462.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, IDAHO - Ben Lemons, an elementary school principal, received a coronavirus vaccine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov Threatens to WithHold Salaries...</title>
      <link>https://npr.org/2021/08/09/1026299001/florida-governor-desantis-school-superintendent-salary-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis ratcheted up a confrontation with school superintendents on Monday, saying anyone who defies his ban on mask mandates might lose a paycheck. Teachers and staff wouldn't be punished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China hold large-scale joint military drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810082158-s7pg3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-CHINA/DRILLS (TV):Russia, China hold large-scale joint military drills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women filmmakers denounce cinema prize for Depp...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-europe-arts-and-entertainment-9b1b8b4ab954f19552c3240e53edc39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain's leading group of women filmmakers on Tuesday condemned the San Sebastian film festival’s decision to award Johnny Depp its highest honor, saying it gave the international event a bad name after a British judge ruled last year that allegations of domestic violence against the actor were “substantially correct".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Sell Fast, Homeowners Making Mansions Move-In Ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/corcoran-ceo-pamela-liebman-interview-which-houses-selling-fast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To Sell Fast, Homeowners Are Making Their Mansions Move-In Ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals parceling out beds, hunting for doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/delta-strains-hospitals-across-u-s-as-unvaccinated-fill-icus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta Strains Hospitals Across U.S. as Unvaccinated Fill ICUs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN fears erasure of human rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810111411-58tfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX):WRAPUP 1-Taliban tighten control of Afghan north as UN fears erasure of human rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job openings record 10.1 million...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-4c614d89c69b4afd3504a4d92dd574f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. employers posted a record 10.1 million job openings in June, another sign that the job market and economy are bouncing back briskly from last year's coronavirus shutdowns. Job openings rose from 9.5 million in May, the Labor Department reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Deliberately Left Deadly Variant Out of Press Briefings During Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/tokyo-deliberately-left-deadly-new-lambda-covid-variant-out-of-press-briefings-during-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even after a Lambda case was conclusively identified at the airport, the government omitted the findings from two press releases, reluctant to raise alarms during the Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk slammed over plan to put satellite ad billboard in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-slammed-over-spacex-24725021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plans announced earlier this week would see SpaceX team up with Geometric Energy Corporation on its CubeSat project and launch the ad billboard into Earth's orbit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS CRYPTO CRACKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/change-to-crypto-provision-in-infrastructure-bill-blocked/ar-AAN7B3r?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A change to cryptocurrency reporting rules in the infrastructure bill was blocked in the Senate Monday, leaving language for broad oversight of virtual currencies still in the legislation that’s set to pass the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/storminfo/06L_tracks_latest.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tropicaltidbits.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/refresh/AL062021_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/233154_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor Who Said Donald Would Be Back in Office Says He Was Inaugurated in March...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/pro-trump-pastor-who-said-trump-would-be-back-in-office-in-june-now-says-he-was-inaugurated-in-march/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right-wing Pastor Jeff Jansen has baselessly claimed that he knows "for a fact" that former President Donald Trump was inaugurated on March 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World 'nowhere near end of pandemic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/09/covid-epidemiologist-larry-brilliant-on-delta-variant-vaccinations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The delta variant of Covid-19 is extremely contagious, noted epidemiologist Larry Brilliant. Relatively few worldwide have gotten the coronavirus vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm watches issued for Caribbean islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/developing-tropical-system-is-one-for-the-us-to-watch/996147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been more than a month since any tropical activity has remotely approached the U.S., but a budding threat could track toward Florida or the Gulf of Mexico, AccuWeather meteorologist say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools go against DeSantis, require masks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-education-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-a24acbc39533b222a580548ae3422298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The superintendent of the school district in Florida’s capital said Monday that he will require students to wear masks amid an increase in COVID-19 hospitalizations fueled by the delta variant, defying the governor’s attempts to block schools from imposing such a mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas reports new record for hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arkansas-coronavirus-pandemic-7ed21edba1069f6c57e07c42540021fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas on Monday set a new record for the number of people in the state hospitalized because of COVID-19 as its coronavirus surge continued. The state reported its COVID-19 hospitalizations rose by 103, its biggest one-day increase, to 1,376.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>911 LONE STAR:  APPEAL FOR OUT OF STATE COVID HELP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-education-coronavirus-pandemic-368eb9eb57b1d3b1a473d4414c42a522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Greg Abbott appealed for out-of-state help Monday to fight the third wave of COVID-19 in Texas. The request came as a county-owned hospital in Houston raised tents to accommodate their COVID-19 overflow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Olympics Viewership Plummeted 42% From Rio...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tokyo-olympics-ratings-viewers-down-rio-2016/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Olympics came one year late and were watched by 42% fewer viewers than the Rio games in 2016, according to Nielsen and Adobe data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine enthusiasts getting extra shots without FDA approval...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/covid-19-boosters-some-in-us-getting-extra-shot-without-fda-approval</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An untold number of Americans have managed to get COVID-19 booster shots even though the U.S. government hasn't approved them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man vows to defy judge's 'crazy' order to get dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9877299/Ohio-man-ordered-judge-COVID-19-vaccine-two-year-probation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio Judge Christopher Wagner ordered Brandon Rutherford on Wednesday to get a Covid vaccine as part of a condition of probation for his felony conviction on fentanyl possession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew sued in New York for sex assault...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/09/prince-andrew-may-be-sued-in-new-york-by-virginia-roberts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein accuser Virginia Roberts Giuffre may file a lawsuit against Prince Andrew this week in New York court, accusing him of “improper sexual violations,” her lawyer said in a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pediatrician warns: 'Not your grandfather's Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/live-updates/covid-delta-variant/?id=79359387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is facing a COVID-19 surge this summer as the more contagious delta variant spreads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Host Criticizes FOXNEWS: 'Not Acceptable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/this-is-not-acceptable-fox-news-host-dan-bongino-rips-fox-news-for-editing-trump-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan Bongino faced the wrath of his supporters after a clip of his Fox News interview with President Donald Trump was edited to remove false claims about the 2020 election. In an interview that aired on Fox News Saturday night, Trump told Bongino that the 2020 election he lost to Joe Biden was “fake.” While […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 more women contacted AG with allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/09/two-more-women-contacted-ag-with-allegations-against-cuomo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two more women approached the state Attorney General’s Office with allegations against Gov. Andrew Cuomo after Letitia James released her sexual harassment report against him last week, The P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant sucking joy out of back-to-school...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/delta-variant-sucking-joy-back-120001605.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of a back-to-normal back-to-school, the coronavirus casts new shadows over the return to full-time, in-person schooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant-Based Fish Rattling Seafood Industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/plant-based-fish-is-rattling-the-multibillion-dollar-seafood-industry/ar-AAMYzVU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beyond and Impossible showed the potential for plant-based proteins. Now tomatoes are coming for tuna</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Budget Includes Green Card Giveaway, Mass Amnesty...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/dem-budget-includes-green-card-giveaway-mass-amnesty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new budget proposal from Senate Democrats will dramatically increase the number of available green cards and include amnesty for illegal immigrants, according to an official fact sheet on the $3.5 trillion budget circulated by leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likely 'JEOPARDY!' successor defends himself on allegations he mistreated colleagues...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/09/media/mike-richards-jeopardy-host-controversy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Richards, who is in line to become the new host of "Jeopardy!," is defending himself against allegations that he mistreated colleagues at another game show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The animals changed by human contact...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210805-the-animals-changed-by-proximity-to-humans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not just domestication that has changed animals – simply sharing their environment with humans has radically altered the behaviour of some species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Denies Britney Spears' Request To Toss Father Off Conservatorship...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/britney-spears-conservatorship-latest-jamie-spears-court-filings-1234810638/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 12:46 PM: Britney Spears won’t get an earlier chance to try to chuck her father off of her restrictive conservatorship. In a tactical victory for Jamie Spears over his daughter&amp;#8217…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads everywhere, but don't seem to be helping...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/Gavin-Newsom-recall-ad-Republicans-candidate-Calif-16370247.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it time for Newsom to change up his ad strategy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids struggle with long haul...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/coronavirus/2021/08/09/this-is-really-scary-kids-struggle-with-long-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lingering physical, mental, and neurological symptoms are affecting children as well as adults, including many who had mild reactions to the initial coronavirus infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's pass now required in restaurants, trains...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-france-coronavirus-pandemic-655d8451d7494f8663ce2072e64cf7a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France took a big step Monday into a post-pandemic future by requiring people to show a QR code proving they have a special virus pass before they can enjoy restaurants and cafes or travel across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment committee to finish evidence review within 'several weeks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/09/cuomo-impeachment-committee-expects-to-finish-reviewing-evidence-within-several-weeks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The committee responsible for determining whether to impeach New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo expects to finish reviewing evidence within weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will gyms go way of arcades, movie rental stores?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-movie-rental-54a8021207d37650b9d96e55236553e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOLEDO, Ohio (AP) — Going to the gym was always part of Kari Hamra’s routine until last year’s government-ordered shutdowns forced her to replace the workouts with daily rides on her Peloton stationary bike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Billionaire Leon Black Flew Russian Model to Meet Jeffrey Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/08/billionaire-leon-black-flew-russian-model-to-meet-jeffrey-epstein-new-legal-filing-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to former Russian model Guzel Ganieva’s suit, Black referenced Epstein’s proclivity for “very young girls,” and once flew her to Florida against her will “to satisfy the sex needs of Epstein, his ‘best friend.’”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Force wary of taking over UFO mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/09/space-force-ufo-military-mission-502843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newest branch is among a number of military and intelligence organizations in the running to take over the investigation of unexplained aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters try to storm BBC studios in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3440034/anti-vaccine-protesters-storm-bbc-studios-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-vaccine protesters have attempted to storm studios where the BBC and ITV film as they clash with police during a rally in London. Footage shows crowds of people shouting and pushing back on co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada reopens its border for jabbed US visitors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-canada-business-health-travel-f2a37189b8c7ac90dddec1514a7f3fa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DERBY LINE, Vermont (AP) — Canada lifted its prohibition on Americans crossing the border to shop, vacation or visit on Monday while the United States is maintaining similar restrictions for Canadians, part of a bumpy return to normalcy from COVID-19 travel bans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldiers training in NYC for 'America's worst day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3440758/soldiers-training-americas-worst-day-nuclear-bio-attacks-ballistic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOLDIERS are in training for “America’s worst day” amid fears of a nuclear or biological attack and ballistic threats. The Army’s Task Force 46 were coached on how to respond to a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Tower Bridge stuck open...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/london-tower-bridge-stuck-scli-intl-gbr/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A technical fault has left world-famous London landmark Tower Bridge stuck open on Monday afternoon, with cars and pedestrians unable to cross.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to require for all troops by Sept. 15...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-vaccine-us-military-requirement-pentagon-3975940c732352f72e41f6e34a3a2669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Pentagon will require members of the U.S. military to get the COVID-19 vaccine by Sept. 15, according to a memo obtained by The Associated Press. That deadline could be pushed up if the vaccine receives final FDA approval or infection rates continue to rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows people trapped in elevator as floodwaters rise in Omaha...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/omaha-flooding-man-stuck-on-elevator-with-floodwater-flood-in-nebraska-tony-luu/10938754/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the time the elevator doors opened, the water was neck deep. "I was swimming out," Tony Luu said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mile-driven tax pilot program tucked into infrastructure bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/5/mile-driven-tax-pilot-program-tucked-12-trillion-i/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House’s $1.2 trillion infrastructure package includes a pilot program for a national mile-driven tax, contradicting President Biden’s previous dismissal of the policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Riddled With Inaccuracies...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/08/08/review-jennifer-hudson-gives-an-oscar-worthy-performance-as-aretha-franklin-in-respect-but-movie-is-full-of-alternative-facts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can’t say whether or not Aretha Franklin really handpicked Jennifer Hudson to play her in her biopic, but she certainly was persuaded to in time by friends and advisors. It was a wise choic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dixie Fire now SECOND LARGEST n CA history...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/fires/article253350538.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of structures have already been destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek Inferno: Thousands flee as apocalyptic flames rage 'like horror movie'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/greek-wildfires-thousands-flee-apocalyptic-24716990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze on the island of Evia erupted into several fronts, tearing through thousands of acres of forest across its northern region, forcing the evacuation of dozens of villages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PUMPING NEW MAGA MERCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/politics/trump-reveals-new-maga-hat-design-says-he-designed-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As opposed to the classic red cap with “MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN” in white letters slapped on the front, the new cap says the abbreviated “MAGA” in white letters outlined in yellow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharmaceutical firms rake in billions...</title>
      <link>https://today.rtl.lu/news/business-and-tech/a/1768290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;today.rtl.lu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time's Up leader steps down after criticism about ties to gov...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/roberta-kaplan-times-up-resigns-f549dee46459e588797e1199376d632b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Time’s Up leader Roberta Kaplan resigned Monday over fallout from her work advising Gov. Andrew Cuomo’s administration when the first allegations of sexual harassment were made against him last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal workers intercept suspicious letter to pope...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-religion-6acc98769c57f4c2960210324b2069fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Law enforcement in Milan is investigating the source of an envelope containing three bullets addressed to the pope, Italian paramilitary police said Monday. The suspicious envelope was intercepted by postal employees overnight at a mail sorting facility in a Milan suburb, according to the carabinieri provincial command in Milan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake jab cards worry college officials...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-education-fake-vaccination-cards-8c4ca2b4d54434c2fc022b34087df8cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN LUIS OBISPO, Calif. (AP) — As the delta variant of the coronavirus sweeps across the United States, a growing number of colleges and universities are requiring proof of COVID-19 vaccination for students to attend in-person classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery plane returns to Michigan airspace...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2021-08-08/mysterious-plane-returns-michigan-airspace-2495780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A previous owner of the plane, Fabian Bello of Journey Aviation in Boca Raton, Fla., said the plane, which left Michigan late last summer, was conducting “atmospheric research” for commercial — not military — applications. The repeated flights in the same location were made to achieve consistent results, Bello said. Consistent results for what, however, remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite, surfing and virtual burning man: Diplo's pandemic year...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210809-fortnite-surfing-and-virtual-burning-man-diplo-s-pandemic-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fortnite, surfing and virtual burning man: Diplo's pandemic year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon chief under fire for withholding info about deadly Kenya attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pentagon-chief-under-fire-for-withholding-16374262.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustrated lawmakers are pressuring Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin for information about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Dangerous Consequences of Russia Space Screwups...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/inside-dangerous-consequences-russia-space-155722559.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kirill Kudryavtsev/Getty A space capsule with a hole in it. A rocket that failed 31 miles over Earth’s surface. An orbital lab with misfiring thrusters.That’s the short list of the most dramatic mishaps involving the International Space Station in the last three years. The missteps have one thing in common: They all involve Russian spacecraft traveling to, or already attached to, the station—or station modules that recently arrived from Earth.There was a time, 60 years ago, when the Soviet Union</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest 'beaten to death by refugee he welcomed into community'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3439530/priest-stabbed-death-refugee-welcomed-freed-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIEST was beaten to death by refugee he welcomed into his community despite being on bail for torching a Cathedral, say investigators. The 40-year-old suspect is said to have confessed to killin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban-exile community worries and mobilizes to support loved ones on island...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cuban-exile-community-worries-and-mobilizes-to-support-loved-ones-on-the-island/ar-AAN6rmG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many here have few details on relatives, friends detained after the latest protests across Cuba.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama at 60: Feet on dance floor, eyes on future...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/article/Obama-at-60-Feet-on-the-dance-floor-eyes-on-the-16374027.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday Barack Obama celebrated his 60th birthday on Martha's Vineyard, at his $11.75...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ leaks pics of bday bash...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/08/dj-posts-pics-of-obamas-birthday-party-before-being-forced-to-delete-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manager TJ Chapman gave his Instagram followers an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at President Barack Obama’s 60th birthday party at Martha’s Vineyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin warns of 'catastrophe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/09/austin-catastrophe-epicenter-again-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City implores residents to stay home, mask up and get vaccinated as ICU capacity in hospitals dwindles to single digits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican megadonors flock to Tim Scott, building 2024 buzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/09/tim-scott-mega-millions-fundraising-502764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oracle's Larry Ellison is the biggest name in a group of major Republican donors sending big money to South Carolina's Scott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia contends with Confederate names on side streets...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/virginia-9206a44094a86f8b212bc9b4aff5fe5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McLEAN, Va. (AP) — It came as a surprise to Mottrom Drive resident Beau Fitzpatrick that he lives on a street named for a Confederate soldier. “Really? I always assumed it was named for an apple, or apple juice,” he said, referring to the Mott's brand of apple products.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
