<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>OFFERS $80 MILLION FOR TRUMP'S HEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2020/01/huge-breaking-news-iranian-regime-offers-80-million-for-president-donald-trumps-head-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Navy deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/01/04/britain-sends-warships-persian-gulf-protect-citizens-wake-qassim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Royal Navy was on Saturday night deployed in the Persian Gulf to &amp;quot;take all necessary steps to protect our ships and citizens&amp;quot; in the wake of Donald Trump's decision to assassinate Iran's top general Qassim Soleimani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani mixed White House role, personal cybersecurity business...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/Rudy-Giuliani-mixed-White-House-role-personal-14949921.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani’s mixing of his business interests, closeness with President Trump and involvement in government actions involving Ukraine is the subject of much attention as the impeachment case against the president moves toward the Senate. But a Chronicle investigation has found that Giuliani’s blurring of White House and personal business didn’t start with Ukraine. It began in 2017 when Giuliani was named as a White House adviser in an area where he had limited experience but was trying to build a clientele: cybersecurity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi parliament passes resolution to end foreign troop presence...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200105141444-bjkfk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/PARLIAMENT-RESOLUTION (URGENT):Iraqi parliament passes resolution to end foreign troop presence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi parliament meets to discuss withdrawal of US troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenational.ae/world/mena/iraqi-parliament-meets-to-discuss-withdrawal-of-us-troops-1.960145</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenational.ae&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraq's parliament held an extraordinary session on Sunday with Prime Minister Adel Abdul Mahdi in attendance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters thought she was talking to Greta Thunberg. It was actually trolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Rep-Maxine-Waters-thought-she-was-talking-to-14950261.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The call starts innocently enough: Rep. Maxine Waters, D-Calif., warmly greets the voices on the line, whom a staffer identifies as Greta Thunberg and her father, Svante. They share a laugh about Waters's nickname, "Auntie Maxine." The congresswoman praises her young caller for her climate change activism.  "You have made quite a big, big, big, big thunder on this issue. I am really, really very proud of you and the work that you're doing," Waters is heard saying.  The congresswoman and her staff thought they had connected with Thunberg, the 17-year-old Swedish climate activist who was recently named Time magazine's "Person of the Year." In reality, two 30-something Russians, Vladimir "Vovan" Kuznetsov and Alexei "Lexus" Stolyarov, were on the other end of the line. The duo describe themselves as comedians and pranksters, but they are widely suspected of having ties to the Russian government.  Audio from the call with Waters was posted to the pair's YouTube page on Thursday, along with a cartoon animating the approximately 10-minute interaction as part of their comedy video series called "Stars Save the Earth."  It's unclear when exactly the call took place. Waters' office did not respond to questions seeking details about how the call was arranged or whether her office has screening or security protocols for phone calls. Waters waved off the incident on Saturday, telling The Washington Post in an email statement:  "This was just another stupid prank by the same Russian operatives who have targeted many U.S. elected officials, including Rep. Adam B. Schiff, Sen. Lindsey O. Graham, Sen. Mitch McConnell, and late-Senator John McCain, and international heads of state such as Emmanuel Macron. The end."  But security experts warn that what's being passed off as prank-call mischief is really Russian misinformation meant to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens to attack White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7853703/Iran-threatens-attack-White-House-crushing-powerful-retaliation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has threatened to attack the White House in response to President Donald Trump's threat to strike 52 Iranian targets. 'We have the power,' said Iranian MP Abolfazl Abutorabi,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 dead, 60 injured in massive crash on PA Turnpike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b2bfea36577246521f22967102993de8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENSBURG, Pa. (AP) — At least five people were killed and dozens were injured in a crash early Sunday involving multiple vehicles on the Pennsylvania Turnpike, a transportation official said....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu, in apparent stumble, calls Israel 'nuclear power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-netanyahu-nuclear-idUSKBN1Z40CS?taid=5e11d33648fe97000144aa9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an apparent slip of the tongue on Sunday, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small cracks in Republican unity on trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/politics/small-cracks-have-appeared-in-gop-unity-on-impeachment-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pbs.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For now, Republicans are holding the line behind Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell’s position that they should start the trial and hear arguments from House prosecutors and Trump’s defense team before deciding what to do. But small cracks in GOP unity have appeared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escalating U.S.-Iran tensions scramble politics of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/escalating-us-iran-tensions-scramble-the-politics-of-trumps-impeachment/ar-BBYB4bv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain 'must be ready' for looming war...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/britain-must-ready-looming-iran-21217332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Admiral Lord West said it would be “very difficult” for Britain to stay out of a fresh conflict in the Middle East amid tensions between Iran and the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condemns Trump as 'terrorist in suit'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200105092357-uhs3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 1-Iran condemns Trump as 'terrorist in a suit' after attack threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady says retirement 'pretty unlikely'; Free agent for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28424771/tom-brady-says-retirement-pretty-unlikely-patriots-exit-playoffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots quarterback Tom Brady said it was "pretty unlikely" that he would retire this offseason, before adding it was "hopefully unlikely" after the team's 20-13 loss to the visiting Titans on Saturday night in the wild-card round of the AFC playoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Death to America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/us-iran-soleimani-tensions-live-intl-01-05-20/h_6a85a53149579c7cedb252b3b616085a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US is sending thousands of additional troops to the Middle East as tensions grow following the killing of Iran's top general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military confirms terror attack on US base in Kenya...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/us-military-confirms-terror-attack-us-base-kenya/story?id=68075337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. military acknowledges terror attack on U.S. base in Kenya</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soleimani body taken on unprecedented public mournings tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/5/qassem-soleimani-body-tours-iran-public-mournings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This marks the first time Iran honored a single man with a multi-city ceremony. Not even Khomeini received such a processional with his death in 1989.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows charred koala, kangaroo remains; Billion animals feared dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10673494/australia-fires-billion-animals-feared-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEARTBREAKING footage shows the charred remains of dead koalas and kangaroos – as experts fear the devastating Australian wildfires have killed a BILLION animals. A horrific video shows the c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  DOUBTS AT PENTAGON...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/nationworld/ct-nw-nyt-trump-decision-to-kill-soleimani-20200105-we7fksvu25farhbbb2wkwv3zfm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pentagon officials often offer improbable options to presidents to make other possibilities appear more palatable. https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/04/us/politics/trump-suleimani.html</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburb soars to 120&amp;#176;... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7852649/8-000-koalas-perish-bushfires-sweeping-Australia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of dead koalas is equal to a third of their population in New South Wales. Ecologists say the animal may have to be reclassified as an endangered species as it disappears from areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARR: Trump ordered the strike, and came down to dinner cool, collected...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2020/01/03/howie-carr-president-trump-ordered-the-strike-and-came-down-to-dinner-cool-collected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was just another evening at Mar a Lago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ERA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/sports/patriots/2020/01/04/derrick-henry-tennessee-run-over-eliminate-punchless-patriots/201YEIyFeKDMtDQtCPPInM/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bruising back finished with 182 yards on 34 carries, and New England was held without a point in the second half.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Brady will definitely play next season just not sure where...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/patriots/news/brady-will-absolutely-play-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It appears Tom Brady's time in the NFL will extend past the 2019 season, whether or not he loses on Wild-Card Weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood prepares to toast winners at GLOBES...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-prepares-toast-winners-golden-globes-013553940.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood's biggest party, the Golden Globes, kicks off the showbiz awards season Sunday, with streaming giant Netflix expected to be popping champagne corks through the night. Victory at the Globes ensures key momentum for the Oscars, which are a little more than a month away. Netflix and its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Pneumonia Outbreak Spurs WHO Action as Mystery Lingers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-pneumonia-outbreak-spurs-action-081026836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A mysterious lung infection in the central Chinese city of Wuhan is being monitored by the World Health Organization, which said it’s in active communication with its counterparts in China, where an investigation is underway to determine the cause.The United Nations agency activated its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solidarity March to Cross Brooklyn Bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/jewish-solidarity-march-to-cross-brooklyn-bridge-sunday/2254799/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a sign of unity, thousands of marchers are expected to cross the Brooklyn Bridge on Sunday morning in support of the Jewish community currently at the center of recent attacks. The “No Hate, No Fear Solidarity March” will lead members of the local Jewish community and its allies to Foley Square, the starting location of the march. The march…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Pentagon Was Duped by Contractors Using Shell Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/how-the-pentagon-was-duped-by-contractors-using-shell-companies/ar-BBYBYqp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid tech turmoil, celebration at global electronics show...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amid-tech-turmoil-celebration-global-electronics-show-012107156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Consumer Electronics Show opening Tuesday offers a chance to showcase the newest and shiniest gadgetry, looking past the turmoil engulfing the global technology industry. The annual Las Vegas gathering with more than 4,500 exhibitors brings out about 175,000 attendees searching for innovations of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could America re-start draft?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Could-the-strike-on-an-Iranian-general-trigger-a-14950144.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the hours since the Trump administration announced that the high-ranking Iranian commander Qasem Soleimani had been killed in a U.S. airstrike, Americans wondered: Does this mean war?  And for young people, there was a follow-up: Would I have to go?  The impact of President Donald Trump's decision to order a strike against Soleimani has yet to be seen, it has turned up the heat on America's already tense relationship with Iran, a country the president has portrayed as one of America's most dangerous adversaries. Google searches for terms such as "conscription", "Selective Service" and "Iran" spiked, according to Trends data, as youthful social media users on platforms like TikTok and Instagram dealt with this collective political anxiety the best way they knew how: by spinning out endless memes about getting drafted in a hypothetical, but seemingly imminent, World War III.  On Friday, the website for the Selective Service, a federal agency tasked with maintaining a database of adult men who could be called upon should a crisis require a draft, experienced technical difficulties as people flooded the site.  The draft was suspended in 1973 because of intense public and political opposition to the Vietnam War, and Congress and the president would have to pass legislation to bring it back, should an emergency call for it. But America still keeps a database of all young men who could be called upon should the draft ever return.  Every year, millions of young, adult men are required by law to register with the Selective Service, "a relatively low-cost insurance policy for our nation," as the agency puts it.  If you're a male residing in the United States between ages 18 and 25, you are required by law to register for the Selective Service. The mandate applies whether you're a U.S. citizen, immigrant, or undocumented...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial fence revives battle over marijuana dispensaries near churches...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/communities/san-diego/story/2020-01-04/controversial-fence-revives-battle-over-marijuana-dispensaries-near-churches</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applicant built fence to skirt San Diego's 1,000-foot separation rule</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  DOUBTS AT PENTAGON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/04/us/politics/trump-suleimani.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While senior officials argue the drone strike was warranted to prevent future attacks, some in the administration remain skeptical about the rationale for the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE ON... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/gamecenter/2020010401/2019/POST18/titans@patriots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow the Tennessee Titans vs. New England Patriots on Saturday, January 4, 2020. Watch the live drive chart and real-time highlights, get stats and game insights, and discover how to watch the game and buy tickets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Lawyer: Accuser 'Has Spent Entire Life Acting for Living'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/weinstein-attorney-says-annabella-sciorra-spent-an-entire-life-acting-a-living-1266409</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The public's biggest misconceptions come from the assumptions that have been made through the help of media," Weinstein wrote in an email interview with CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PARASITE' Named Best By National Society of Film Critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/national-society-film-critics-winners-2020-list-full-1266375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other major wins went to Antonio Banderas for his lead role in 'Pain and Glory' and Mary Kay Place for her lead role in 'Diane.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Iran' launches cyber-attack on US govt website; 'We're always ready'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-iran-launches-cyber-attack-21216337  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group claiming to be working on behalf of the Iranian government has hacked a US government website where they plastered sinister warnings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP HAS 52</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75944e42ccc66ac08ee5122e080d7f33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — President Donald Trump issued a stark warning to Iran on Saturday, threatening to hit dozens of targets in the Islamic Republic “very fast and very hard” if it...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
