<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Looters ransack San Francisco NEIMAN MARCUS in broad daylight...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/san-francisco-looters-neiman-marcus-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looters were captured on video Monday ransacking a Neiman Marcus in San Francisco as thefts continue to plague businesses in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>125 test positive at Texas church camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article252591403.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is a reminder that COVID-19 is still here and we have to take precautions,” the health director said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANDATES AT WORK?</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/workplace/interest-in-vaccine-mandates-rising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Google and Amazon won’t make employees get vaccinated before returning to the office. But some other big tech companies are starting to show interest in vax mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital nomads embraced work-life flexibility. Now their offices want them back...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/office-life-beckons-again-pandemic-s-digital-nomads-weigh-benefits-n1273000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 opened up the possibility of a nomadic lifestyle to entirely new groups of people. Now, many of them don't want to go back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buyers shun older buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/condo-buyers-shun-older-buildings-after-surfside-collapse/ar-AALPV5D?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. – The collapse of the Champlain condo building in Surfside could reverberate through the real estate market in South Florida for months to come, real estate experts say. The red-hot condo market could cool as buyers might hesitate to buy in older buildings, worried that the buildings have put off maintenance and that mammoth repair bills could be coming, brokers say. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM ELSA FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/live-news/live-follow-tropical-storm-elsa-updates/975544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Southeast puts together its final preparations and as Tropical Storm Elsa closes in on the Florida peninsula, follow along here for the latest updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Monroe, dead 59 years, still counterfeiter's best friend...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/marilyn-monroe-dead-59-years-is-a-counterfeiter-s-best-friend/article_4b4abcaa-84ac-5f3c-8fe7-d960386712ef.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly six decades after her death, Marilyn Monroe is still a popular choice for mugs, T-shirts, jewelry and other products using her name — even illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Sydney lockdown EXTENDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9761217/Coronavirus-Australia-Sydney-lockdown-extended-July-16-schools-closed-masks-stay.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Sydneysiders will endure another week of lockdown, with restrictions extended until at least July 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparks fly as musical film 'ANNETTE' geeks out festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210706-sparks-fly-as-musical-film-annette-geeks-out-cannes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sparks fly as musical film 'Annette' geeks out Cannes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Rash of Unexplained Deaths at Fort Hood...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/inside-the-rash-of-unexplained-deaths-at-fort-hood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of people were killed, died by suicide, or went missing from the Texas military base last year alone. What is behind the violence and tragedy at Fort Hood?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 79, McConnell contemplating legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/07/mitch-mcconnell-power-senate/619350/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At age 79, Mitch McConnell is contemplating his legacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin war dogs parachute into battle from 13,000ft...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3227010/putin-war-dogs-parachute-battle-13000ft-russian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BONKERS footage has emerged showing Russian army pooches parachuting into battle zones from heights of 13,000ft. Vladimir Putin’s crack team of canine warriors can be seen being hurled out of plane…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI reveals 'exact location aliens hiding'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3222902/ai-location-aliens-hiding-civilisations-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have identified the place where aliens are most likely lurking in the Milky Way. Using computer simulations, the US team determined that the mysterious centre of our galaxy represents ou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moguls Ready for Deals and Corporate Drama at Sun Valley Conference...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/sun-valley-allen-co-conference-discovery-warnermedia-1235012189/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If ever there was a year for the Allen &amp; Co. conference to be a fertile ground for dealmaking among the titans of tech and media, it’s this one. The entertainment industry is in an everyone’s-t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Soil. No Growing Seasons. Just Add Water and Technology...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/06/no-soil-no-growing-seasons-just-add-water-and-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOREHEAD, Ky. — In this pretty town on the edge of coal country, a high-tech greenhouse so large it could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly To Host Daily Talk Show For SIRIUSXM...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/megyn-kelly-siriusxm-talk-show-1234786686/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly has signed with SiriusXM to host a daily talk show, taking her podcast to the satellite network’s Triumph channel starting on Sept. 7. The former Fox News host will headline The M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan troops filmed surrendering...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9760119/20-000-Tajikistan-troops-ordered-border-stop-Afghanistan-soldiers-fleeing-Taliban.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Austin Scott Miller, commander of US and Nato troops in Afghanistan, said he was shocked by how quickly the Afghan National Army had surrendered to the resurgent jihadists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lambda: 'World's most transmissible strain' spreading in 31 countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9759677/Coronavirus-Australia-Covid-19-strain-Lambda-infectious-Delta-variant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lambda variant was detected in a traveller undergoing hotel quarantine in New South Wales, Australia, in April, according to the national genomics database AusTrakka.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black bears, with disease that makes fearless, swim alongside beachgoers in Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9758035/Black-bears-play-water-sun-Lake-Tahoe-surrounded-stunned-beachgoers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large adult black bear and her three cubs visited a South Lake Tahoe beach last weekend to escape the heat while beachgoers watched in shock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man went on racist rant, gave out address and said come 'see me.' 100 protesters did...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-man-who-went-on-a-racist-rant-gave-out-his-address-and-said-come-see-me-more-than-100-protesters-did/ar-AALPc5r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Jersey man was later arrested as protesters gathered outside of his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horn-wearing 'shaman.' Cowboy evangelist. For some, Capitol riot was Christian revolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-horn-wearing-shaman-A-cowboy-evangelist-For-16295334.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late last month, one of the accused Jan. 6 Capitol insurrectionists told a D.C. judge...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel blocks law that keeps out Palestinian spouses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-israel-religion-business-government-and-politics-f99c3aff0368bde00eef634ef42fde7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel’s parliament early on Tuesday failed to renew a law that bars Arab citizens from extending citizenship or residency rights to spouses from the occupied West Bank and Gaza, in a tight vote that raised doubts about the viability of the country’s new coalition government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER restricts account of academic who mocked China leader...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-business-technology-3741dcfb1c2eb11f17280c9ed8c06fc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — A New Zealand academic says Twitter temporarily restricted her account after she mocked Chinese President Xi Jinping. University of Canterbury Professor Anne-Marie Brady is an expert on China's attempts to exert political influence around the world and has been an outspoken critic of its ruling Communist Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Streets Erupt Into '12 Hours Of Non-Stop Chaos'; Homicides, Shootings...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/07/05/oakland-july-4-sideshow-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fourth of July reeled into "12 hours of non-stop chaos" Sunday night with several victims wounded by celebratory gunfire, a homicide and a massive sideshow marred by gunfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Tokyo Olympics approach, covid worries rise in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/africa-japan-tokyo-2020-tokyo-olympics-olympic-games-9fbd360e4524dca0b25140e60ebda389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The pressure of hosting an Olympics during a still-active pandemic is beginning to show in Japan. The games begin July 23, with organizers determined they will go on, even with a reduced number of spectators or possibly none at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Will China Rule World? Maybe Never...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/china-rule-world-maybe-never-210013340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- When will China overtake the U.S. to become the world’s biggest economy?Few questions are more consequential, whether it’s for executives wondering where long-term profits will come from, investors weighing the dollar’s status as global reserve currency, or generals strategizing over geopolitical flashpoints.In Beijing, where they’ve just been celebrating the 100th anniversary of the Chinese Communist Party, leaders are doing their best to present the baton-change as imminent and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban advance accelerating...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-taliban-advance-is-accelerating/ar-AALOBkg </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate firefighter takes engine on joyride, crashes and injures self...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/inmate-firefighter-takes-engine-on-joyride-in-california-crashes-and-injures-himself/article_0dc150be-3418-5bf2-bec8-eaec4077b220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate firefighter stole a fire truck while fighting a vegetation fire in Gold Country outside Sacramento, California, and took it on a joyride before crashing and injuring himself, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Soil. No Growing Seasons. Just Add Water and Technology....</title>
      <link>https://www.365newslive.com/2021/07/06/no-soil-no-growing-seasons-just-add-water-and-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.365newslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOREHEAD, Ky. — On this fairly city on the sting of coal nation, a high-tech greenhouse so massive it might cowl 50 soccer fields glows with the pinks and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Resurrected MGM. AMAZON Bought Studio. Now What?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/06/they-resurrected-mgm-amazon-bought-the-studio-now-what/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Thomas Anderson and Michael De Luca are film geeks with a shared history. As a studio executive, Mr. De</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah's Great Salt Lake Near 170-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/great-salt-lake-air-quality-lakes-wildlife-lifestyle-1adae582035c7f1b03f2a5cb57c0dda8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — The silvery blue waters of the Great Salt Lake sprawl across the Utah desert, having covered an area nearly the size of Delaware for much of history. For years, though, the largest natural lake west of the Mississippi River has been shrinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Should We Sell?' After Collapse, Hot Florida Market Faces Uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/06/should-we-sell-after-collapse-hot-florida-market-faces-uncertainty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. — Ines Mason bought the 14th-floor condo, perched on an island in Biscayne Bay, five years ago as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Jose has highest share of superrich residents in world!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-u-s-city-has-the-highest-share-of-superrich-residents-in-the-world-its-not-san-francisco-new-york-or-seattle-11625247163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global population of people worth $30 million or more grew by 1.7% in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As corona probe deepens, Bolsonaro increasingly threatened by corruption scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/As-coronavirus-probe-deepens-Bolsonaro-16294592.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO - For months, the congressional probe into Brazil's lax coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX yet to discover a great film director, says Cannes chief...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netflix-yet-discover-great-film-185518206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix and the other streaming giants have yet to discover one great director, the head of the Cannes film festival said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORMER FOX PRESIDENT TURNS ON 'NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/former-murdoch-exec-fox-news-052129970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos via GettyRupert Murdoch, whom I served for seven years, has many business and journalistic achievements. He owes himself a better legacy than a news channel that no reasonable person would believe.It was my great honor to join Rupert, Barry Diller (who now is the chairman of IAC, The Daily Beast’s parent company), Jamie Kellner and many others in the early days of Fox Broadcasting Company, the network that’s the home to The Simpsons and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measures in England Become 'Matters of Personal Choice'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-government-and-politics-650b09e7babe362e1777606e6b1a369b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain plans to scrap laws requiring face masks and social distancing later this month, Prime Minister Boris Johnson confirmed Monday, even as he acknowledged that lifting the restrictions will drive surging coronavirus cases higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE GROWS ON ANTI-VAXXERS</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-07-compulsory-jabs-pressure-anti-vaxxers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of countries and territories around the world are forcing people, often in specific sectors, to be vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As condo crashed down, they escaped through smoke and ruin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/surfside-building-collapse-71a19269343a1172f0c5bf782373a175</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Alfredo Lopez and his wife Marian were asleep when the first thundering blast jolted them awake. Moments later, a second boom, much louder than the first, shook the bed on the sixth floor of their Miami apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout continues from biggest global ransomware attack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-government-and-politics-technology-business-88c51d8041b1afdd42fa9f571c3de446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — The single biggest ransomware attack yet continued to bite Monday as more details emerged on how a Russia-linked gang breached the exploited software company. The criminals essentially used a tool that helps protect against malware to spread it globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada FINALLY reopening border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/canada-lifestyle-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-health-2b873761884d6aed7b7088a15fefb654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Pandemic restrictions on travel between Canada and the U.S. began to loosen Monday for some Canadians, and Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said plans to totally reopen the border would be announced over the next few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tribe becomes key water player with drought aid to Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arizona-science-government-and-politics-business-environment-and-nature-3d27c894e028629e87a14d7a41ddd5db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLAGSTAFF, Ariz. (AP) — For thousands of years, an Arizona tribe relied on the Colorado River's natural flooding patterns to farm. Later, it hand-dug ditches and canals to route water to fields. Now, gravity sends the river water from the north end of the Colorado River Indian Tribes reservation through 19th century canals to sustain alfalfa, cotton, wheat, onions and potatoes, mainly by flooding the fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S1t90INfeGY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to boost birth rate by adopting Nordic position?</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/week-asia/economics/article/3136991/can-china-boost-its-birth-rate-adopting-nordic-position</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As China drops its two-child limit to increase its birth rate, experts are hoping it can learn from Scandinavian countries that boosted fertility with pro-family policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emhoff carves out path as first second gentleman...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/561441-doug-emhoff-carves-out-path-as-first-second-gentleman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doug Emhoff has spent the first six months of the Biden administration carving out his role as the first second gentleman of the United States, traversing across the country to promote coronavirus vaccines and extend support to small businesses.&amp;n</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In final days, Khashoggi juggled secret wife and fiancee...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/he-gave-nobody-a-full-view-of-his-life-in-his-final-days-jamal-khashoggi-juggled-a-secret-wife-in-the-us-and-a-fiance-in-turkey-090031920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Khashoggi had a penchant to be secretive about much of his life. “If somebody sits across from you when you’re interviewing people about Jamal and tells you that Jamal told them everything, they are 100 percent lying to you,” said one friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA left Afghan airfield at night, didn't tell new commander...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bagram-afghanistan-airfield-us-troops-f3614828364f567593251aaaa167e623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGRAM, Afghanistan (AP) — The U.S. left Afghanistan's Bagram Airfield after nearly 20 years by shutting off the electricity and slipping away in the night without notifying the base's new Afghan commander, who discovered the Americans' departure more than two hours after they left, Afghan military officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like zoo animals': Eats alone at 'roped-off table' at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/like-zoo-animals-donald-and-melania-trump-eat-alone-at-a-roped-off-table-at-a-mar-a-lago-restaurant-book-says/ar-AALNMQC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They are like a newly married couple: every night is a wedding at which they spend their dinner greeting friends and wellwishers," Michael Wolff wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large fire reported near Tehran, background unclear...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/large-fire-reported-near-tehran-background-unclear-report-672964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire broke out in Karaj, south of Tehran, the city where an alleged attack targeted a nuclear facility reportedly used to produce centrifuges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists clone cow to produce lactose-free milk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9757939/Russian-scientists-clone-cow-edit-genes-remove-protein-causes-lactose-intolerance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in Moscow have cloned a cow whose milk doesn't contain the protein that causes lactose intolerance in humans. Born in April 2020, the calf is healthy with a normal reproductive cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inked Mummies, Linking Tattoo Artists With Their Ancestors...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/05/inked-mummies-linking-tattoo-artists-with-their-ancestors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1970s, hunters stumbled upon eight 500-year-old bodies preserved by the Arctic climate near Qilakitsoq, an abandoned Inuit settlement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthy 13-year-old dies 3 days after receiving PFIZER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9756975/CDC-launches-investigation-healthy-boy-dies-three-days-receiving-second-Covid-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jacob Clynick, a 13-year-old from Michigan has died in his sleep three days after receiving his second Coronavirus vaccine, prompting an investigation by the Centers for Disease Control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-day week 'overwhelming success' in Iceland...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-57724779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The majority of workers in Iceland now look set to move to shorter hours for the same pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANNES COVID CONFUSION: FESTIVAL GOERS MUST SPIT IN TUBE...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/cannes-covid-saliva-tests-1235011802/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday afternoon, Olivia Wilson had arrived from her home in Tennessee to the Cannes Film Festival, where she’ll be working as an intern at the American Pavilion. But before she got to enjoy the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE, MICROSOFT end 5-year cease-fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/google-and-microsoft-end-their-5-year-cease-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The old nonaggression pact between Google and Microsoft, forged at the time by two new CEOs wanting a fresh start on a formerly acrimonious relationship, had already been fraying before it lapsed in April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moguls, Deals, Vests: Look Inside 'Summer Camp For Billionaires'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/05/1012587989/moguls-deals-and-patagonia-vests-a-look-inside-summer-camp-for-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's Mark Zuckerberg is expected to attend. So is Apple's Tim Cook. A look inside the Sun Valley conference for top media and tech moguls organized by a little known investment firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts want to re-normalize mask-wearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/should-fully-vaccinated-people-continue-wear-masks-experts-weigh-n1272890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Do whatever it takes for Covid to go away," one doctor said. That includes continuing to wear a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain restricts nightlife as virus surges among young...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-spain-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-c03dead9ceedeb6f1e3e563d8cea2a68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Faced with soaring numbers of new coronavirus infections among unvaccinated young people, some Spanish regions are reinstating curbs on nightlife only weeks after dropping them. Fearing that the surging contagion could strain health care services as stressed employees try to go on summer holidays, health officials in several parts of the country are also rushing to get COVID-19 vaccine shots to people under 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever AI drone swarm in battle to hunt down, blitz terrorists...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3222879/israel-first-ever-drone-swarm-hamas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL used the first ever drone swarm deployed in battle to hunt down Hamas terrorists, it was reported. The drones have no human input but instead link together using artificial intelligence to s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'animal slaughter festivals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3222148/animal-slaughter-festival-world-yulin-dog-meat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of dogs were brutally killed as part of the Yulin Dog Meat Festival last month – but the controversial event is far from the only one around the world. Animal rights activists and celebri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How lizard venom inspired promising weight loss drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/22553793/gila-monster-lizard-venom-inspired-obesity-drug-semaglutide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Semaglutide is the start of a new chapter in obesity treatments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran forever dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/essays/article/End-of-the-Golden-Gate-book-review-16281983.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As San Franciscans, we’ll always be looking over our shoulders at Austin and Portland...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Neighborhood runs for cover as U-HAUL full of fireworks explodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article252579913.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three people were injured in the explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compulsory jabs: Pressure grows on anti-vaxxers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nursinginpractice.com/covid-19/government-to-consult-soon-on-compulsory-covid-jabs-for-healthcare-staff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nursinginpractice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A public consultation on making Covid-19 and flu jabs compulsory for patient-facing staff across all healthcare settings will be launched ‘shortly’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa suffers record number of cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/south-africas-coronavirus-cases-surge-160236823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa's resurgence of COVID-19 is setting record numbers of new daily cases, centered in Johannesburg and driven by the delta variant, health officials said Sunday. More than 26,000 new cases were reported on Saturday, up from 24,000 the previous day, according to the National Institute for Communicable Diseases, surpassing the highest number of new cases in previous waves and quickly bringing many hospitals to capacity. More than 13,800 COVID-19 patients are currently in South African hospitals where some facilities are canceling elective surgeries to free up beds and health care workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel data 'preliminary signal' Delta variant can bypass vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-07-israel-preliminary-delta-variant-bypass.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising coronavirus cases in Israel, where most residents are inoculated with the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine, offer "a preliminary signal" the vaccine may be less effective in preventing mild illness from the Delta variant, a top expert said Monday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
