<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>President to restrict aid to Central American governments, set new conditions for money...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/biden-to-restrict-us-aid-to-central-american-governments-set-new-conditions-for-money/article_9d1aa0d7-9ee0-5933-8747-17839c3c3c37.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Weeks after earmarking $4 billion in U.S. aid for Central America, the Biden administration is fine-tuning its plans and sharply limiting how much money will go directly to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU debating declaration of LBGT 'freedom zone'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/542506-eu-debating-declaration-of-lbgt-freedom-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Parliament on Wednesday is set to debate a resolution that would declare the European Union’s 27 member countries a “freedom zone” for LGBTQ people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body Of NJ Man Missing Since January Found Under Melting Mound Of Snow...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/andrew-fraioli-wyckoff-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-year-old Andrew Fraioli was last seen leaving his parents' Wyckoff home during the snow storm on Jan. 31.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals 'close to collapse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-56342303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts fear Brazil's variants may slow down pandemic recovery, as intensive care units there fill up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANDA EXPRESS Employee Claims Told To Strip Down To Underwear, Hug Co-Worker During 'Team-Building' Seminar...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/panda-express-harassment-battery-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Panda Express employee is suing the company and a seminar academy connected to the employer for alleged disturbing behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Politics Is the New Religion...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2021/04/america-politics-religion/618072/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As faith has declined, ideological intensity has risen. Will the quest for secular redemption doom the American idea?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Florida Market Red Hot, Realtors 'Never Busier'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/08/south-floridas-real-estate-market-red-hot-a-year-into-covid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Florida is seeing a crush of new housing buyers. So much so, it has created a seller’s market with many sellers getting top dollar. People from all over the Northeast in high-tax areas are making an effort to make South Florida their new home, but it’s not easy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palace response fails to end anger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-race-and-ethnicity-prince-harry-royalty-london-583ad5a3fc14367b21f04cf31769af7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Buckingham Palace’s statement on Prince Harry and Meghan’s allegations or racism and mistreatment has failed to quiet the controversy, with some observers criticizing the royal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'BS Artists' Most Likely To Get Duped Themselves!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/you-can-bs-bser-people-who-mislead-most-likely-to-fall-for-bull/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors add the typical BSer is also likely to fall victim to fake news headlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle Made Formal Complaint to Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/meghan-markle-complaint-itv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duchess of Sussex Meghan Markle reportedly filed a formal complaint to ITV after Piers Morgan effectively said everything Markle revealed to Oprah Winfrey was a lie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Woke Crowd' Will Be Disappointed If Think I'm 'Cancelled'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/piers-morgan-free-speech-hero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Good Morning Britain anchor Piers Morgan offered no regrets as he spoke about his resignation from the program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil posts new record of 1,972 deaths in day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210309211737-o0cdx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (URGENT):Brazil posts new record of 1,972 COVID-19 deaths in a day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Long-Dismissed Forgery Actually Oldest Known Biblical Manuscript?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/10/is-a-long-dismissed-forgery-actually-the-oldest-known-biblical-manuscript/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1883, a Jerusalem antiquities dealer named Moses Wilhelm Shapira announced the discovery of a remarkable artifact: 15 manuscript fragments,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 DAYS IN</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/542449-bidens-50-day-mark-to-coincide-with-relief-bill-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will mark the 50th day of his presidency Wednesday on the verge of his first significant legislative accomplishment as the House moves to pass his $1.9 trillion coronavirus relief plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLL THE DICE: Vegas casinos placing bets on NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/09/vegas-casinos-could-be-coming-to-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three large casino companies are jockeying over a rare opportunity to bring a piece of the Las Vegas Strip to the Big Apple, The Post has learned.  Wynn Resorts, Bally’s Corp. and Las Vegas Sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT: Calls Duchess accusations 'diatribe of bilge'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/piers-morgan-stands-by-meghan-comments-after-leaving-good-morning-britain-12241501</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His comments on Good Morning Britain sparked 41,000 complaints and an Ofcom investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US narrows in on organized extremists in Capitol siege probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-washington-elections-only-on-ap-8e6ddb336b23d1813b18e8932f321e40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As members of the Oath Keepers paramilitary group shouldered their way through the mob and up the steps to the U.S. Capitol, their plans for Jan. 6 were clear, authorities say. “Arrest this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After pandemic year, weary world looks back -- and forward...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-us-news-pandemics-health-north-carolina-c6274a112a7bec56b0298e395d2a7bc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one has been untouched. Not the Michigan woman who awakened one morning, her wife dead by her side. Not the domestic worker in Mozambique, her livelihood threatened by the virus. Not the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Tish James Holds His Future In Her Hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/03/11/tish-james-andrew-cuomo-investigation-new-york-attorney-general-474381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s attorney general was long regarded as the governor’s close ally. Then came a bruising report on Covid-19 deaths, and the rest could be history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A price tag on trauma? College town weighs Black reparations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-massachusetts-c54f6419bf59017ab28956d35981a55e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMHERST, Mass. (AP) — Professor Edwin Driver arrived in Amherst in 1948 as one of the first Black teachers hired at a flagship state university in the country. But the 23-year-old sociology...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royals' comments raise race issue in Commonwealth nations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-africa-cape-town-prince-harry-south-africa-17bb61007686b4e22d819df2fc4a955b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE TOWN, South Africa (AP) — In countries with historic ties to Britain, allegations by Prince Harry and Meghan that an unnamed member of the royal family had “concerns” over how dark their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden first 50 days: Where he stands on key promises...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-biden-cabinet-climate-climate-change-immigration-d40e38b8125d1ab2b98661c9ba919238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden laid out an ambitious agenda for his first 100 days in office, promising swift action on everything from climate change to immigration reform to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo faces NEW sex harassment allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/news/article/Cuomo-faces-new-allegation-of-sexual-harassment-16011424.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sixth woman has leveled allegations of sexually inappropriate conduct against Gov....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirt-cheap flights offered as airlines rebuild battered networks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/dirt-cheap-flights-offered-as-airlines-rebuild-battered-networks/ar-BB1epRND?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dirt-cheap fares are popping up from airlines brave enough to expand or start out amid the Covid crisis, as they try to eke out sales and get a jump on competitors that have pared back operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6th woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9343825/Sixth-woman-accuses-Gov-Cuomo-sexual-harassment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The female aide claimed New York Gov Andrew Cuomo touched her inappropriately during an encounter at his executive mansion last year when she had been summoned for work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump doubles down on calls to donate directly to him, NOT to RNC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/542432-trump-doubles-down-on-calls-to-donate-directly-to-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump doubled down on his calls for Republicans to donate to his leadership PAC rather than the GOP amid a growing feud over the party's use of his name and likeness in its fundraising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Flashes Warning to Big Tech as Antitrust Team Takes Shape...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-flashes-warning-big-tech-193848166.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden’s plan to put two progressive antitrust scholars in top positions signals an aggressive approach to combating corporate consolidation and monopoly power, especially that wielded by technology giants such as Alphabet Inc.’s Google and Facebook Inc.Biden’s team is vetting Lina Khan, a Columbia Law School professor who specializes in antitrust law, to serve as a member of the Federal Trade Commission, according to people familiar with the matter. Last week, he named another Columbia law professor, Timothy Wu, to join the National Economic Council as a special assistant on technology and competition policy.Together Khan and Wu could push the Biden administration to broaden an ongoing assault on the tech industry that started under former President Donald Trump. Wu is in a position to influence legislation that could upend the business practices of tech and other large companies. If confirmed, Khan would likely pressure the FTC to pursue an investigation of Amazon.com Inc. that began under Trump and write rules that tighten regulation of the tech industry.In addition, they would be able to influence how competition policy is applied to industries across the economy. Many antitrust experts are pushing for a broad rethinking of competition policy amid growing recognition that the U.S. has failed to tackle the power of dominant companies in numerous industries, including airlines, mobile-phone and internet services and agriculture.Both Khan and Wu have been outspoken advocates for vigorous antitrust enforcement against U.S. tech companies. They are part of a group of antitrust thinkers who argue that the current playbook for policing mergers and anti-competitive conduct has fallen short and want to return antitrust policy to its early 20th-century roots -- when regulators went after monopolies in railroads and oil.“It’s a major step,” said William Kovacic, a professor at the George Washington University Law School and a former FTC commissioner. “It’s another sign of the extraordinary success that the advocates of transformation have had in changing the debate and changing the policy-making context. Just extraordinary. I don’t even think they foresaw that this would happen five years ago.”While Wu and Khan will be influential, Biden has yet to nominate people for the most important antitrust positions -- the chair of the FTC and the head of the Justice Department’s antitrust division, who will oversee the case brought against Google last year and will decide whether to bring additional cases against tech companies. The division is investigating Apple Inc. over App Store practices.Kovacic said the choice of who will lead the Justice Department’s antitrust division is crucial. “Is that more of a traditionalist? Or Is there going to be a deliberate effort here to create a debate, create tension?” he said.In her early thirties, Khan already has served in influential roles as an adviser to regulators and lawmakers, having burst onto the antitrust scene with a groundbreaking analysis of Amazon published in 2017. That paper cast the online retail behemoth as a harmful monopoly that’s destroying small businesses.In her paper, Khan painstakingly built a case that Amazon employs practices that should provoke a rethink of antitrust enforcement in the U.S.“The company has positioned itself at the center of e-commerce and now serves as essential infrastructure for a host of other businesses that depend upon it,” she wrote. “Elements of the firm’s structure and conduct pose anticompetitive concerns -- yet it has escaped antitrust scrutiny.”The FBI is conducting a background check on Khan, which is routine for political nominees, according to a person familiar with the matter. The White House and Khan didn’t respond to requests for comment. Politico reported earlier on the plan to nominate Khan.The Khan and Wu appointments come as the internet platforms are facing a reckoning in Washington that could transform the industry. The FTC is already seeking to break up Facebook, and Khan could be instrumental in shaping a potential case against Amazon. Wu is likely to have a say over legislation that could put guardrails on how tech companies operate. Lawmakers are considering reforms to antitrust law that would make it harder for tech companies to buy rivals and are developing proposals to impose rules to protect the privacy of users and change liability protections that the companies prize.“This is not good for the platforms,” said Herb Hovenkamp, an antitrust law professor at the University of Pennsylvania. “There’s clearly not going to be any let up from the Trump administration to the Biden administration.”The American Economic Liberties Project, an anti-monopoly group closely aligned with Khan’s point of view, said Biden must appoint aggressive enforcers to the Justice Department and the other open FTC seat.“The Biden-Harris administration needs to turn the page on the ideology and policies that brought us to the brink,” Sarah Miller, the group’s executive director, said in a statement.Khan would take over one of five seats on the FTC, which is being run by Acting Chairwoman Rebecca Kelly Slaughter. While enforcement decisions require a majority vote, the chair of the agency wields significant power.Khan and Wu advocate a new view of antitrust enforcement that upends the framework the U.S. has been using to assess antitrust harm for decades. Often called the “New Brandeis School” after former Supreme Court Justice Louis Brandeis, proponents of this approach want to recast merger analysis by focusing not just on price increases but also on stagnant wages, innovation, income inequality and privacy rights.“With the nomination of Lina Khan, the Biden administration has signaled that antitrust enforcement and important competition policy changes will be a high priority,” said Charlotte Slaiman, competition policy director at Public Knowledge. “Khan has already had an incredible impact, pushing the competition policy discussion in the right direction with her work.”Defenders of the tech industry criticized Khan’s pending selection. The Information Technology and Innovation Foundation, which is funded by companies including Google, Facebook and Amazon, said Khan’s “antitrust populism threatens to derail traditional enforcement of antitrust laws.”“Her writings and opinions reveal a strong preference for smaller, less efficient, less innovative rivals at the expense of objective and principled enforcement of antitrust laws,” Aurelien Portuese, ITIF’s director of antitrust and innovation policy, said in a statement. “In a time of intense competition with China’s rising economic and technological power, the self-inflicted harm of Khan’s brand of antitrust populism will harm U.S. companies and consumers to the benefit of foreign rivals.Republican Senator Mike Lee of Utah, who sits on the Judiciary Committee’s antitrust panel, called Khan’s likely nomination “deeply concerning” and described her views on antitrust “wildly out of step with a prudent approach to the law.”“Nominating Ms. Khan would signal that President Biden intends to put ideology and politics ahead of competent antitrust enforcement,” Lee said in a statement.The nominations underscore that Biden is abandoning the antitrust playbook of the Obama administration, which took a largely hands-off approach to enforcement in the technology sector.While Barack Obama’s Justice Department stopped several high-profile mergers, it approved others that were criticized as worsening competition, such as the tie-up of American Airlines Group Inc. and US Airways. The FTC under Obama approved Facebook’s acquisitions of Instagram and WhatsApp and closed an investigation of Google into its search operations in 2013 without any action.Khan recently served as an aide to FTC Commissioner Rohit Chopra and did stints at the New America Foundation and its spin-off, the Open Markets Institute. She was also counsel to the House Judiciary Committee’s antitrust panel, which conducted a 16-month investigation into tech companies that determined that the biggest internet platforms have all abused their gatekeeper power over the digital economy. The panel, led by Rhode Island Democrat David Cicilline, is preparing to introduce legislation to reform antitrust laws.The committee’s report recommended a series of far-reaching antitrust reforms, including a measure that would prohibit a dominant tech platform from operating in competition with the firms dependent on it -- much the way banking laws once barred large lenders from acquiring insurers, real estate firms, and other non-banking companies. The committee also recommended restrictions on acquisitions by dominant firms.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL HE BOUNCE BACK AGAIN?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/mar/09/its-the-end-of-the-piers-show-for-the-man-who-never-knew-when-to-stop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: being ‘ghosted’ by Meghan may be behind the harsh words that cost the presenter his Good Morning Britain job</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's name will NOT appear on checks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/542371-bidens-name-will-not-appear-on-stimulus-checks-white-house-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Jen Psaki said Tuesday that President Biden’s name will not appear on stimulus checks that will be sent to many Americans after the $1.9 trillion coronavirus relief bill is passed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS LEGEND ROGER MUDD DEAD AT 93...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Roger-Mudd-a-probing-TV-journalist-and-network-16013034.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Mudd, a longtime CBS News political correspondent who reported on the Pentagon's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigated by  Media Regulator...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/global/meghan-markle-ofcom-investigation-1234925557/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. media regulator Ofcom has launched an investigation after more than 41,000 people wrote in to complain about ITV’s “Good Morning Britain” host Piers Morgan’s comments o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quits UK talk show...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/03/09/piers-morgan-leaving-uk-talk-show-amid-meghan-markle-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famed TV host Piers Morgan quit “Good Morning Britain” on Tuesday‚ just hours after his co-star confronted him over relentless criticism of Meghan Markle. “Following disc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BUZZFEED Cuts 47 HUFFPOST Jobs After Acquisition...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/09/buzzfeed-takes-buzzsaw-to-newly-acquired-huffpost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just three weeks after finalizing a deal to buy HuffPost, Jonah Peretti’s BuzzFeed is taking a buzzsaw to the left-leaning news and culture site. BuzzFeed on Tuesday said it made a series of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars Eyeing Union Station In Los Angeles As Venue...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/academy-awards-2021-ceremony-union-station-los-angeles-93rd-oscars-1234710352/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Deadline hears that the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences is seriously considering locating the 93rd Academy Awards at Union Station, the cavernous main railway station in Los …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miseducation of America's Elites: Rich parents organize in secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/the-miseducation-of-americas-elites</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Affluent parents, terrified of running afoul of the new orthodoxy in their children’s private schools, organize in secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Breach 150,000 Live Feeds; Exposing TESLA, Jails, Hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hackers-breach-thousands-security-cameras-213219424.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A group of hackers say they breached a massive trove of security-camera data collected by Silicon Valley startup Verkada Inc., gaining access to live feeds of 150,000 surveillance cameras inside hospitals, companies, police departments, prisons and schools.Companies whose footage was exposed include carmaker Tesla Inc. and software provider Cloudflare Inc. In addition, hackers were able to view video from inside women’s health clinics, psychiatric hospitals and the offices of Verkada itself. Some of the cameras, including in hospitals, use facial-recognition technology to identify and categorize people captured on the footage. The hackers say they also have access to the full video archive of all Verkada customers.In a video seen by Bloomberg, a Verkada camera inside Florida hospital Halifax Health showed what appeared to be eight hospital staffers tackling a man and pinning him to a bed. Halifax Health is featured on Verkada’s public-facing website in a case study entitled: “How a Florida Healthcare Provider Easily Updated and Deployed a Scalable HIPAA Compliant Security System.”Another video, shot inside a Tesla warehouse in Shanghai, shows workers on an assembly line. The hackers said they obtained access to 222 cameras in Tesla factories and warehouses.The data breach was carried out by an international hacker collective and intended to show the pervasiveness of video surveillance and the ease with which systems could be broken into, said Tillie Kottmann, one of the hackers who claimed credit for breaching San Mateo, California-based Verkada. Kottmann, who uses they/them pronouns, previously claimed credit for hacking chipmaker Intel Corp. and carmaker Nissan Motor Co. Kottmann said their reasons for hacking are “lots of curiosity, fighting for freedom of information and against intellectual property, a huge dose of anti-capitalism, a hint of anarchism -- and it’s also just too much fun not to do it.”“We have disabled all internal administrator accounts to prevent any unauthorized access,” a Verkada representative said in a statement. “Our internal security team and external security firm are investigating the scale and scope of this potential issue.”A person with knowledge of the matter said Verkada’s chief information security officer, an internal team and an external security firm are investigating the incident. The company is working to notify customers and set up a support line to address questions, said the person, who requested anonymity to discuss an ongoing investigation.Representatives of Tesla, Cloudflare and other companies identified in this story didn’t immediately respond to requests for comment. Representatives of the jails, hospitals and schools named in this article either declined to comment or didn’t immediately respond to requests for comment.A video seen by Bloomberg shows officers in a police station in Stoughton, Massachusetts, questioning a man in handcuffs. The hackers say they also gained access to the security cameras of Sandy Hook Elementary School in Newtown, Connecticut, where a gunman killed more than 20 people in 2012.Also available to the hackers were 330 security cameras inside the Madison County Jail in Huntsville, Alabama. Verkada offers a feature called “People Analytics,” which lets a customer “search and filter based on many different attributes, including gender traits, clothing color, and even a person’s face,” according to a Verkada blog post. Images seen by Bloomberg show that the cameras inside the jail, some of which are hidden inside vents, thermostats and defibrillators, track inmates and correctional staff using the facial-recognition technology. The hackers say they were able to access live feeds and archived video, in some cases including audio, of interviews between police officers and criminal suspects, all in the high-definition resolution known as 4K.Kottmann said their group was able to obtain “root” access on the cameras, meaning they could use the cameras to execute their own code. That access could, in some instances, allow them to pivot and obtain access to the broader corporate network of Verkada’s customers, or hijack the cameras and use them as a platform to launch future hacks. Obtaining this degree of access to the camera didn’t require any additional hacking, as it was a built-in feature, Kottmann said.The hackers’ methods were unsophisticated: they gained access to Verkada through a “Super Admin” account, allowing them to peer into the cameras of all of its customers. Kottmann says they found a user name and password for an administrator account publicly exposed on the internet. After Bloomberg contacted Verkada, the hackers lost access to the video feeds and archives, Kottmann said.The hackers say they were able to peer into multiple locations of the luxury gym chain Equinox. At Wadley Regional Medical Center, a hospital in Texarkana, Texas, hackers say they looked through Verkada cameras pointed at nine ICU beds. Hackers also say they watched cameras at Tempe St. Luke’s Hospital, in Arizona, and were also able to see a detailed record of who used Verkada access control cards to open certain doors, and when they did so. A representative of Wadley declined to comment.The hack “exposes just how broadly we’re being surveilled, and how little care is put into at least securing the platforms used to do so, pursuing nothing but profit,” Kottmann said. “It’s just wild how I can just see the things we always knew are happening, but we never got to see.” Kottman said they gained access to Verkada’s system on Monday morning.Verkada, founded in 2016, sells security cameras that customers can access and manage through the web. In January 2020, it raised $80 million in venture capital funding, valuing the company at $1.6 billion. Among the investors was Sequoia Capital, one of Silicon Valley’s oldest firms.Kottmann calls the hacking collective “Advanced Persistent Threat 69420,” a light-hearted reference to the designations cybersecurity firms give to state sponsored hacking groups and criminal cybergangs.In October 2020, Verkada fired three employees after reports surfaced that workers had used its cameras to take pictures of female colleagues inside the Verkada office and make sexually explicit jokes about them. Verkada CEO Filip Kaliszan said in a statement to Vice at the time that the company “terminated the three individuals who instigated this incident, engaged in egregious behavior targeting coworkers, or neglected to report the behavior despite their obligations as managers.”Kottmann said they were able to download the entire list of thousands of Verkada customers, as well as the company’s balance sheet, which lists assets and liabilities. As a closely held company, Verkada does not publish its financial statements. Kottman said hackers watched through the camera of a Verkada employee who had set one of the cameras up inside his home. One of the saved clips from the camera shows the employee completing a puzzle with his family.“If you are a company who has purchased this network of cameras and you are putting them in sensitive places, you may not have the expectation that in addition to being watched by your security team that there is some admin at the camera company who is also watching,” said Eva Galperin, director of cybersecurity at the Electronic Frontier Foundation, who was briefed on the breach by Bloomberg.Inside Arizona’s Graham County detention facility, which has 17 cameras, videos are given titles by the center’s staff and saved to a Verkada account. One video, filmed in the “Commons Area,” is titled “ROUNDHOUSE KICK OOPSIE.” A video filed inside the “Rear Cell Block” is called “SELLERS SNIFFING/KISSING WILLARD???” Another video, filmed inside “Drunk Tank Exterior” is titled “AUTUMN BUMPS HIS OWN HEAD.” Two videos filmed from “Back Cell” are titled “STARE OFF - DONT BLINK!” and “LANCASTER LOSES BLANKET.”The hackers also obtained access to Verkada cameras in Cloudflare offices in San Francisco, Austin, London and New York. The cameras at Cloudflare’s headquarters rely on facial recognition, according to images seen by Bloomberg.Security cameras and facial-recognition technology are often used inside corporate offices and factories to protect proprietary information and guard against an insider threat, said the EFF’s Galperin.“There are many legitimate reasons to have surveillance inside of a company,” Galperin added. “The most important part is to have the informed consent of your employees. Usually this is done inside the employee handbook, which no one reads.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrested journalist pleaded with officer: 'This is my job'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrea-sahouri-trial-fe036a8663c704b7669ce5a91f504e20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — An Iowa journalist covering a protest for racial justice was temporarily blinded after a police officer shot pepper spray at her and then jailed despite telling him...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire NV Dem Party Quits After Democratic Socialists Win Every Seat...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/03/08/nevada-democratic-party-dsa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The battle between insurgent progressives in Nevada and the Harry Reid machine began building in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOV:  'Not Aware Of Any Other Claim'...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/09/ana-liss-andrew-cuomo-accusations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a conference call with reporters on Tuesday afternoon, Cuomo was asked about the new allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER MUDD DEAD AT 93...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/television-roger-mudd-jim-lehrer-tv-news-virginia-e44bb30f564c30d10713e4116ce01755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Mudd, the longtime political correspondent and anchor for NBC and CBS who once stumped Sen. Edward Kennedy by simply asking why he wanted to be president, has died. He was 93. CBS News...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER MUDD DEAD AT 93...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/obituaries/roger-mudd-dead/2021/03/09/78ddf308-8117-11eb-9ca6-54e187ee4939_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a top Washington reporter for CBS and NBC, Mr. Mudd changed political fortunes with his direct questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA ALL-STAR GAME GETS RECORD LOW RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/03/09/nba-all-star-game-record-low-tv-ratings-tnt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TV ratings are in for the NBA All-Star Game, and the numbers are brutal. The game averaged a record low 5.94 million viewers on TNT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vet claims he lived in Philly stadium for 3 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/the-secret-apartment-vet-stadium-20210309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I was like a kid with a Willy Wonka golden ticket."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas gov signs near-total abortion ban into law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-arkansas-legislation-courts-asa-hutchinson-24ca79cb9b416f81d9152f54881c7a74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas Gov. Asa Hutchinson on Tuesday signed into law legislation banning nearly all abortions in the state, a sweeping measure that supporters hope will force the U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI still can't find suspect who planted bombs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/fbi-releases-new-video-suspect-planting-bombs-capitol-riot-n1260293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery of the two devices outside the separate DNC and RNC offices pulled dozens of police away from their usual posts before the riot unfolded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Rep's suit pits 1st Amendment against revenge-porn law...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/former-rep-katie-hills-lawsuit-pits-1st-amendment-against-californias-revenge-porn-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publication of private, intimate pictures of former Rep. Katie Hill that drove her to resign from office will be contested in court this week in an argument that pits the 1st Amendmen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter Asks If Pooch Will Be 'Euthanized'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/well-that-got-dark-reporter-asks-jen-psaki-if-bidens-dog-will-be-euthanized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things took a dark turn when a reporter asked White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki if First Dog Major Biden will be euthanized over a recent incident that resulted in an injury to a member of the White House staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand to sequester foreign tourists on yachts...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/thailand-to-sequester-foreign-tourists-on-yachts-poor-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union of 2 great houses -- Windsors and Celebrities -- complete...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishtimes.com/culture/tv-radio-web/harry-and-meghan-the-union-of-two-great-houses-the-windsors-and-the-celebrities-is-complete-1.4504502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Freyne: After Harry and Meghan, the monarchy looks archaic and racist. Well duh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge ends hearing because assault suspect attends from victim's home...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox2detroit.com/news/michigan-judge-cancels-bond-of-assault-suspect-who-attended-virtual-hearing-from-victims-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox2detroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michigan judge told a defendant his bond was canceled after the courtroom learned the assault suspect was attending a virtual hearing where the accuser was living, creating a potentially dangerous situation for the victim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring home prices set off alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/08/soaring-home-prices-alarm-policymakers-474433</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last time the U.S. saw such skyrocketing home prices, the ensuing crash brought down the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitamin D supplements may offer no Covid benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/09/vitamin-d-supplements-may-offer-no-covid-benefits-data-suggests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two studies fail to find evidence to support claims supplements protect against coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEEN VOGUE employees protest new editor over anti-Asian tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2021/mar/09/teen-vogue-alexi-mccammond-tweets-employees-letter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staffers sent letter to Condé Nast after racist tweets written by Alexi McCammond 10 years ago resurfaced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BUZZFEED Cuts 47 HUFFPOST Jobs After Acquisition...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/buzzfeed-huffpost-layoffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed announced last November it would acquire HuffPost in a deal with Verizon Media that went through in February</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN: 'RECOLLECTIONS MAY VARY BUT WE TAKE THEM VERY SERIOUSLY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14283067/royal-family-respond-meghan-harry-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE “saddened” Queen today responded to Meghan Markle’s race claims in her bombshell interview, saying: “Some recollections may vary”. Her Majesty finally responded to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY+ pulls 'DUMBO', 'PETER PAN', 'THE ARISTOCATS' for 'racist' stereotypes...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2479490/disney-pulls-iconic-movies-dumbo-the-aristocats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISNEY+ has stripped its kid’s menus of classic movies like Dumbo, The Aristocats and Peter Pan because of their “racist” stereotypes. Settings on the streaming site’s app will prevent children und…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleared for takeoff? World eyes 'health passports'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210309-cleared-for-takeoff-world-eyes-health-passports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cleared for takeoff? World eyes 'health passports'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskless UBER Passengers Assault, Cough On, Pepper Spray Driver...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/08/video-maskless-uber-passengers-assault-cough-on-pepper-spray-driver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Uber driver in San Francisco was assaulted and coughed-upon by a woman riding with two other women after he refused them service for not wearing masks, in an attack the driver captured on video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL star slammed for killing huge gator then posing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/14280662/nfl-wyatt-teller-alligator-hunting-backlash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star Wyatt Teller has received a fierce backlash from animal rights activists after he shot, killed and then posed with a 10-foot long alligator. The Cleveland Browns guard, 26, was captured on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>42% Now Consider Themselves Germaphobes!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-curse-many-americans-consider-themselves-germaphobes-over-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find constantly stressing over safety is getting old fast for Americans -- as the world enters year two of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only one New York governor has ever been impeached. Some lawmakers hope Cuomo will be second...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/only-one-new-york-governor-has-ever-been-impeached-some-n1260048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo has been besieged by bipartisan calls to resign or be impeached over dual scandals that have rocked his administration in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD DOG:  Major sent home to Delaware after biting incident...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/08/politics/president-joe-biden-white-house-dogs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two German Shepherds belonging to President Joe Biden and first lady Jill Biden were returned to the Biden family home in Delaware last week after aggressive behavior at the White House involving Major Biden, two sources with knowledge tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA ISSUES HEALTH PASSPORT</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14285224/china-issues-world-first-covid-vaccine-passport-and-plans-to-accept-other-countries-passes-soon-in-boost-for-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has issued what’s thought to be the world’s first Covid vaccine passport. In a boost to international travel, Beijing also plans to accept other countries’ vaccine health ce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINATED RECLAIM THEIR LIVES</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210309095717-w8o28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-SENIORS (PIX):After year of isolation, vaccinated older Americans start to reclaim their lives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palace silence on Harry, Meghan allegations adds to furor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/buckingham-palace-meghan-harry-interview-allegations-c1f78e3d617595fcb0534fbaa8f298ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Racism. Bullying. Insensitivity. Prince Harry and Meghan’s allegations of ill treatment by Britain's royal household are so serious that some observers say Buckingham Palace’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psych eval ordered for man caught having sex with stuffed animals inside TARGET...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/olaf-psych-eval-376215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 8--A judge today ordered a psychological evaluation to help determine the competency of a Florida Man charged with having sexual contact with a pair of large stuffed animals at a Target store,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York prosecutors investigating Trump Chicago skyscraper loan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/08/politics/trump-chicago-subpoena/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney's office subpoenaed documents from an investment company that loaned the Trump Organization millions of dollars for its Chicago skyscraper in a sign that the investigation into the former president's finances continues to expand, according to people familiar with the investigation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
