<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>IDF defends strike on Gaza media building, noting Hamas assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/idf-defends-strike-on-gaza-media-building-noting-hamas-pij-assets-in-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showed USA 'smoking gun'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-showed-us-smoking-gun-on-hamas-in-ap-office-tower-officials-say-668303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We showed them the smoking gun proving Hamas worked out of that building,” a senior diplomatic source said. “I understand they found the explanation satisfactory."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATT TO MERGE WARNERCNNTBSHBO WITH DISCOVERY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/17/att-to-combine-warnermedia-and-discovery-assets-to-create-a-new-standalone-company.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If approved by regulators, the deal effectively reverses AT&amp;T's years-long plan to combine content and distribution in a vertically integrated company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charging 589% Interest Is Booming Business...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2021-payday-loan-lenders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Payday lenders had record profits in 2020 while many Americans were barely getting by during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyprus 'devil' song aims to set Eurovision ablaze...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cyprus-devil-song-aims-set-174505161.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyprus rarely causes a splash at the Eurovision song contest but controversy over its entry "El Diablo" (The Devil) and a fiery rendition by Greek singer Elena Tsagrinou are drawing attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They're Vaccinated and Keeping Masks On, Maybe Forever...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/17/theyre-vaccinated-and-keeping-their-masks-on-maybe-forever-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whenever Joe Glickman heads out for groceries, he places an N95 mask over his face and tugs a cloth mask</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100 Million Bet on Cross-Country Restaurant Delivery...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/17/a-100-million-bet-on-cross-country-restaurant-delivery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the pandemic started last spring, Di Fara, one of New York City’s storied pizza joints, had the same question</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was banned from having guns after Capitol riot arrest. Then he shot mountain lion...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-was-banned-from-having-guns-after-his-capitol-riot-arrest-then-he-shot-a-mountain-lion-feds-say/ar-BB1gOCFn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Montgomery, 41, was released from custody and allowed to return to Colorado, where he shot and killed a mountain lion despite being barred from using guns, federal prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designed for disaster: These homes can withstand Cat 5 hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/designed-for-disaster-these-homes-can-withstand-a-category-5-hurricane/ar-BB1gN1Er </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines May Start Weighing Passengers At Gate...</title>
      <link>https://viewfromthewing.com/u-s-airlines-may-start-weighing-passengers-at-the-gate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;viewfromthewing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. airlines may need to start weighing passengers in order to comply with FAA rules. For safety reasons, carriers need to calculate an aircraft's weight and balance, and it has to be within allowable limits for the plane. However the assumptions they've been using for passengers are outdated. Americans are getting fatter, and the federal government wants airlines to find out how much fatter their passengers have gotten, at least for smaller aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More parents pick home-schooling...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/553140-more-parents-pick-homeschooling-after-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus lockdowns prompted a rise in home-schooling as parents' attitudes have shifted positively toward home education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Working 55 hours a week increases risk of death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/working-55-hours-week-increases-090630959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Working more than 55 hours a week increases the risk of death from heart disease and stroke, according to a United Nations study out Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller prosecutor says Trump could be imprisoned in FL if indicted in NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/mueller-prosecutor-trump-imprisoned-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump could end up stuck in Florida if he is indicted in New York and there is resistance to him being extradited, according to a top prosecutor in Robert Mueller's special counsel investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry &amp; Meghan grilled over deal with company that sells 'racist' skin whitening cream...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2896778/meghan-markle-prince-harry-procter-gamble-skin-whitening-cream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN Markle and Prince Harry are facing questions over their deal with Procter &amp; Gamble as it sells what campaigners say is a “racist” skin-whitening cream. The Duke and Duchess o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens left hanging for hours on broken roller coaster!</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/nation-world/national/article251453613.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There were a lot of kids on there that were really terrified.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why does it seem like there are more homeless on streets?</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/homelessness/story/2021-05-15/homeless-on-the-street-appear-growing-in-numbers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Encampments have cropped up across county, but it's unclear if population is increasing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC chief says any vaccine mandates will be set locally...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-chief-says-any-us-vaccine-mandates-to-be-set-locally/ar-BB1gNmTq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Any mandates in the U.S. to require people to be vaccinated against Covid-19 will be set at the local level by companies and institutions such as colleges, the head of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said. “It may very well be that local businesses, local jurisdictions, will work towards vaccine mandates,” CDC Director Rochelle Walensky said on NBC’s “Meet the Press.” “That is going to be locally driven and not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not funny: NBC has no comedies on fall schedule for first time in 50 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/nbc-2021-22-schedule-1234953502/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC is loading up its fall 2021 schedule with so much drama, it’s not funny. Literally: For the first time in at least 50 years, the network will start a season with no half-hour comedies on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein Gave Advice?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-gave-bill-gates-advice-on-how-to-end-toxic-marriage-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person who attended meetings at Epstein’s townhouse says Gates enjoyed holding court there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY DWARFED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/att-discovery-merger-038e7857-3051-4b37-accd-c21e6cf9b9c4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A potential merger could the companies to better compete with entertainment giants like Disney and Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL POUNDS HARDER</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210516213257-p1760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (TV, PIX):Israel-Gaza fighting enters its second week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convoy drives through London shouting 'f**k the Jews, rape their daughters'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/05/16/convoy-drives-through-london-shouting-fk-the-jews-rape-their-daughters-14590888/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Vile, criminal hatred like this must not be tolerated.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zaslav to RUN IT ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/att-discovery-in-talks-1234954038/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T is in talks with Discovery, Inc. to merge its media business with the sprawling television company, The Hollywood Reporter has confirmed. Bloomberg, which was the first to report the news …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATT TO MERGE WARNERCNNTBSHBO WITH DISCOVERY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/16/att-in-advanced-talks-to-merge-warnermedia-with-discovery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T and Discovery will announce a deal to merge Discovery and WarnerMedia as soon as tomorrow, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGHEST-EVER RATE OF ROCKET ATTACKS</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/middle-east/israel-faces-highest-ever-rate-of-rocket-attacks-army</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Monday, armed groups in Gaza have fired about 3,000 rockets towards Israel. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who didn't invent Flamin' Hot CHEETOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/smallbusiness/the-man-who-didnt-invent-flamin-hot-cheetos/ar-BB1gMYd1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Montañez has for years told a story of how he dreamed up Flamin' Hot Cheetos while working as a Frito-Lay janitor. The archival record, former employees and Frito-Lay itself say otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK mulls lockdowns to curb Indian variant...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/hancock-doesnt-rule-out-local-lockdowns-for-bolton-and-blackburn-due-to-indian-variant-12307876</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The health secretary tells Sky News he won't "rule out further action" as the India variant becomes dominant in some parts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks use Earth's magnetic field as GPS, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fl-state-wire-sharks-science-environment-and-nature-abf97cf60bb15f7fbf3bfed74671e398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Sharks use the Earth's magnetic field as a sort of natural GPS to navigate journeys that take them great distances across the world's oceans, scientists have found. Researchers said their marine laboratory experiments with a small species of shark confirm long-held speculation that sharks use magnetic fields as aids to navigation — behavior observed in other marine animals such as sea turtles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Jabs in the Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-super-coronavirus-vaccine-could-be-in-your-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more pathogens like the one that causes COVID-19. That’s why a team of scientists began work on what you might call a “super-vaccine.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Clapton blasts vaccine safety 'propaganda'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9583109/Eric-Clapton-hits-propaganda-vaccine-safety.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary guitarist Eric Clapton, a lockdown sceptic, said his hands and feet became 'useless' - prompting fears he would never play again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey making calls as he weighs TX gov run...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/16/matthew-mcconaughey-texas-governor-run-488536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s a beloved home-state star, but pundits are skeptical that the acclaimed actor has a chance at unseating Republican Gov. Greg Abbott.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No alternative to passports, says airport boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-57108969</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubai is the world's busiest airport and its boss says vaccine passports will get us flying again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China lands on Mars in major advance for space ambitions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-technology-business-science-e1c1d0679aa78a8cc79c04a4d1375322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China landed a spacecraft on Mars for the first time on Saturday, a technically challenging feat more difficult than a moon landing, in the latest step forward for its ambitious goals in space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware a national security threat, big business -- and wreaking havoc...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ransomware-is-a-national-security-threat-and-a-big-business-and-it-s-wreaking-havoc/ar-BB1gLSP7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 2,400 health care facilities, schools and governments in the United States were hit by ransomware attacks last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 3 Dead Prostitutes Triggered Wild Satanic Panic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-dead-prostitutes-triggered-wild-074213822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EpixThe Satanic Panic of the ’80s and early ’90s was fueled by wild stories about ritualistic killings, human and animal sacrifices, and pledges of allegiance to dark demonic lords. Most of those claims turned out to be tall tales, but that doesn’t mean they didn’t result in criminal justice system convictions. One such example involved the nightmare that befell Fall River, Massachusetts, (the birthplace of Lizzie Borden) in1979-1980, when three young prostitutes were found bound, bludgeoned to death, and, in one instance, horribly mutilated. Though the victims were all killed in a strikingly similar manner, police didn’t investigate them as the work of a single fiend. And in the case of the third slaying, they decided that the perpetrator’s motivation had less to do with personal impulses than with getting in good with a higher power: Satan.Premiering on Epix May 16, the Jason Blum-produced Fall River revisits this tumultuous episode in traditional docuseries fashion, employing archival photos and videos, newly recorded interviews, graphical flourishes, and unnecessary dramatic recreations to try to assemble a puzzle whose pieces, decades later, don’t quite fit. Director James Buddy Day’s four-part docuseries begins with the Oct. 13, 1979, murder of 17-year-old prostitute Doreen Levesque, who was found under a high school’s bleachers with her head brutally caved in by a blunt object. At the time of Doreen’s death, there was a turf war in the area between two rival pimps: notorious Carl Drew and 17-year-old Robin Murphy. The latter was dating a prostitute named Karen Marsden, who said that she was present at Doreen’s murder, which had been carried out by Carl. Karen, however, refused to outright finger Carl to the cops, and on Feb. 9, 1980, she was found murdered in Freetown-Fall River State Forest. Horrific: D.C. Sniper Boasts of Post-Shooting Sex ‘High’ With Accomplice in New DocLike Doreen, Karen had also been bludgeoned to death with a rock. And thanks to Robin’s testimony, police soon came to believe that Karen was the victim of a Satanic ritual orchestrated by Drew, in which he forced Robin to kill her girlfriend, perform oral sex on her corpse, and decapitate her so he could kick her head around the woods.This was a bombshell accusation, and it eventually led to Robin pleading guilty to second-degree murder in exchange for testimony against Carl, who received a life sentence for his mastermind role in the affair. Fall River’s recap of these events is bolstered by a thorough contextualization of Fall River’s street culture, where prostitutes and drug addicts operated out in the open mere blocks away from the police station, and where officers frequently plied informants with booze and drugs. To detectives Alan Silvia and Thomas Joaquim (both of whom participate throughout), it was clear that Carl was this milieu’s de facto “Satan,” and while they knew that Robin was a formidable figure not to be messed with, they were sure that Carl was the culprit they sought.Fall River, however, isn’t so sure about that. As the series lays out, there was no physical evidence against Carl, much less any real proof about Satanism; the only thing linking him to Karen’s murder was the eyewitness testimony of Robin, their driver Carol Fletcher, and Carl’s prostitute-girlfriend Leah Johnson, who revealed that Carl gifted her Karen’s ring shortly after the crime. More problematic still, in later years, all three of these women recanted their statements—most explosively Robin, who admitted at a 2004 parole hearing that she had made the entire Satanic story up. As if that weren’t enough to muddy the waters, Robin was also involved in a third homicide, in November 1979: that of Barbara Raposa, who was killed by Andy Maltais, a notorious pedophile who’d been terrorizing pre-teen girls for years, including Robin beginning when she was 11.Everyone who had any role in this tangled saga (and is still alive) participates in Fall River, including Carl. Yet clarity remains constantly out of reach. The fact that Robin was told about (or related in some way to) three different murders, ostensibly committed by three different men, that all were executed according to the same M.O., makes her look mighty suspicious. It also suggests that there was a serial predator on the loose—thus potentially exonerating Carl, who comes across as a shady and violent pimp but not, in the final tally, the man who ended Karen and Doreen’s lives. Day’s docuseries ultimately makes a compelling argument that there was one monster responsible for this reign of terror: Andy Maltais, because he knew all three victims; they were bound-and-bludgeoned in a manner that aligned with his kinky proclivities; and he had a motive to kill Karen, whom he might have wanted to silence before she exposed him as Doreen’s attacker.It’s a nice theory that makes more sense than any of the show’s other hypotheses. Unfortunately, though, Day doesn’t quite come up with explanations for all of the case’s outstanding questions. Chief among them has to do with Robin, who states that she lied to the cops in order to make sure Andy was convicted of Barbara’s murder, but who also supposedly lied to cover up Andy’s possible involvement in her girlfriend Karen’s killing in order to implicate Carl. Why Robin would have done that, or accepted jail time for a second-degree murder charge if she was totally innocent—and when there was no evidence linking her to Karen’s death—is similarly baffling, and contributes to an air of impenetrable confusion that Fall River is forced to embrace, to both haunting and frustrating effect, as it speeds toward a finale full of additional wannabe-explosive revelations.There’s at least one apparent miscarriage of justice to be found in Day’s docuseries, but by its closing installment, one gets the sense that there may be more story here to tell—especially in light of Carl’s ongoing efforts to secure a new trial. The abruptness of Fall River’s ending goes hand-in-hand with a formal approach that’s conventional at best and rickety at worst, undermined by cheesy chapter headings featuring scary devil-ish book illustrations. Nonetheless, as a mystery marked by inextricably knotted-up untruths, it’s a non-fiction work that’s been well-designed to spark heated debate and incite further inquiry—as well as, perhaps, beget a sequel.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Being Falsely Accused of Exchanging Money for Naughty Favors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/matt-gaetz-jokingly-compares-sex-trafficking-scandal-to-earmarks-at-ohio-rally-im-being-falsely-accused-of-exchanging-money-for-naughty-favors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz’s (R-FL) “wingman” may have signed a plea agreement in the federal case that is broadly rumored to involve Gaetz, but the possibility of pending criminal prosecution didn’t seem to put a damper on the Florida Congressman’s mood Saturday, as he spoke to a crowd of Trumplican faithful in Strongsville, Ohio, even cracking […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From gas to chicken: Supply chain woes bring soaring prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/15/business/supply-chain-price-increases/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Used cars, homes, lumber, gas and chicken: What do they all have in common? They're all getting more expensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100 million NJ deli fires wrestling coach CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/15/100-million-new-jersey-deli-company-fires-ceo-paul-morina.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hometown International has a massive stock market capitalization despite owning just a small New Jersey deli.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
