<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Legal marijuana industry had banner year in 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/legal-marijuana-industry-had-banner-2018-060708442--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — The last year was a 12-month champagne toast for the legal marijuana industry as the global market exploded and cannabis pushed its way further into the financial and cultural mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Winter Be Cold? Depends Which FARMERS' ALAMANAC You Read...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/will-winter-be-nasty-or-nice-depends-which-farmers-almanac-you-read-11545929300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dueling weather forecasts confound fans of longtime rivals the Old Farmer’s Almanac and the Farmers’ Almanac; ‘I don’t know what to believe’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks of Hollywood Gnawing on 'GREEN BOOK'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/whats-wrong-with-green-book-11545949461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film about a white chauffeur traveling with black pianist Don Shirley in the Jim Crow South is facing contemporary criticisms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Urged to Move as Indonesian Volcano Erupts Frequently...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/residents-urged-to-move-as-indonesian-volcano-erupts-frequently-11545991850</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A volcano that triggered a deadly tsunami was erupting nearly every minute, blowing ash more than a mile skyward, and authorities said they would urge survivors to permanently move away from the shorelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-Editing Experiment Loses Track of Patients, Alarming Inventors...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinese-gene-editing-experiment-loses-track-of-patients-alarming-technologys-inventors-11545994801 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gene-editing trial in China lost touch with cancer patients whose DNA was altered, alarming some Western scientists who say subjects should be monitored for many years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller collected 'nude selfie' as evidence in Russia probe, attorney claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/27/robert-mueller-collected-nude-selfie-evidence-conc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller is leaving no stone unturned in his quest for evidence of Russian collusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASS MIGRANT RELEASE CONTINUES; THOUSANDS MORE?</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2018/12/27/18157515/immigrant-families-detention-border-children-deaths-ice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But with border nonprofits already stretched to capacity, many families will probably end up dropped off en masse at bus stations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cow escapes cattle truck to slaughterhouse, bolts toward freedom...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/12/28/cow-escapes-slaughterhouse-truck-paterson-nj-video/2430077002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly all on-duty police officers in Paterson, New Jersey, were deployed to wrestle the cow off of a highway as shown in video clips from the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depression, anxiety, withdrawal: The Hell of trying to quit vaping...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/12/27/quitting-vaping-e-cigarette-addiction-nicotine-withdrawal-depression-anxiety-headaches/2388272002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;E-cigarettes were introduced to help smokers quit. But for those trying to quit vaping, nicotine withdrawal can be 'hell'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA' Dominating Critics' Awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/2018-critics-awards-roma-dominates-star-is-born-black-panther/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 30 groups declaring their favorites, Alfonso Cuarón's drama has won as many best-picture awards as the next five rivals combined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinky sex scene leaves mystery series viewers vomiting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/8073395/abc-murders-kinky-sex-scene-heels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIEWERS of last night’s ABC Murders were left feeling queasy after a S&amp;M kinky sex scene. Fans claim they had to cover their eyes and ‘were nearly sick’ as Thora Grey dug her …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmonaut insists hole in space station drilled from INSIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8067766/russian-cosmonaut-hole-iss-drilled-from-inside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS hole found on the International Space Station (ISS) was in fact drilled from inside the orbiting lab. That’s according to Russian cosmonaut Sergey Prokopyev, who investigated the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots to FEEL human touch with new 'smart skin'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8030636/sex-robots-feel-human-touch-smart-skin/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEX robots will soon be able to ‘feel’ a human’s touch with a new ‘smart skin’ making cyber love more realistic, an expert has told The Sun Online. The TouchYou is the lates…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom kills 'tyrant' son, slices off penis, cuts body into pieces...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8073208/oap-mum-killed-son-frying-pan-sliced-corpse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 63-YEAR-OLD grandmother killed her “tyrant” son by hitting him over the head with a large frying pan, before using a power saw to cut his body into more than 70 pieces. The Russian woman, named o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAST TURNS NYC BLUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8072400/new-york-sky-lights-eerie-blue-glow-explosion-power-plant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE sky above New York was lit up by an eerie blue glow that could be seen across the city after a huge power plant explosion last night. Electricity was cut off for thousands while the busy La Gua…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey claims 'sex attack' was consensual...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8066178/kevin-spacey-lawyer-claims-sex-attacker-accuser-allowed-grope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TEENAGE boy who accused Kevin Spacey of sexually assaulting him allowed the actor to grope him during a boozy lunch, the star’s lawyers claim. Spacey’s legal team went to court last w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby born with three hands worshipped as god...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelondoneconomic.com/news/world-news/baby-girl-born-with-three-hands-is-worshipped-as-a-god/27/12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelondoneconomic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The infant girl has a third hand growing out of the side of her left hand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rough year for 'universal basic income' experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612640/universal-basic-income-had-a-rough-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the biggest and most promising experiments were plagued by delays and shutdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's African debt-trap: Beijing prepares to seize Kenya port...</title>
      <link>https://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3605624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.taiwannews.com.tw&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO FILTER: Can Armie Hammer still get away with saying whatever wants?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/As-Armie-Hammer-becomes-more-famous-can-he-still-13493376.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Armie Hammer is sitting in a hotel room, in the middle of telling a story, when his publicist coughs. Loudly. Hammer stops talking and turns to look at her. "What?" he asks, grinning innocently. "What?" He's not sharing a particularly controversial anecdote - it's one he told before on "Conan," about how he got so worn down during the 14-month press tour for "Call Me By Your Name" that he refused to wear anything but tracksuits. But the cough may be a signal for "Armie, please stop talking." Or "Armie, please don't say anything that will make my job harder." The need for a signal wouldn't be a surprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhunt for Illegal Accused of Killing Cop...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article223621665.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newman police officer Ronil Singh was killed by a man who is in the United States illegally, and investigators believe the suspect is still in Stanislaus County, California, authorities said in a news conference Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli general, polling closest to Netanyahu, joins election race...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election-gantz/israeli-ex-general-polling-closest-to-netanyahu-joins-2019-election-race-idUSKCN1OQ14E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Israeli armed forces chief who opinion polls show poses the toughest ch...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash-strapped Cuba plans fresh austerity measures as finances worsen...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-economy/reality-bites-cuba-plans-more-austerity-as-finances-worsen-idUSKCN1OR0VN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cash-strapped Cuba plans fresh austerity measures and will pressure the sluggish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Secret Rulebook for Political Speech...</title>
      <link>