<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside secure village, where athletes forced to eat alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3121750/inside-tokyo-covid-olympic-village/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO is a city full of famous buildings and iconic architecture. And its Olympic and Paralympic Village comes across as a homely, if slightly sterile, home for athletes that will descend upon it n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fans sues town for $25M after being told to remove MAGA flags from car...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3119621/trump-supporter-sues-town-for-25m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DIE-HARD Trump fan is suing a Long Island town for $25million after being ordered to take MAGA flags off his car. Michael Wasserman claims Long Beach authorities are trying to “silence̶…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST TRANS OLYMPIAN!</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/sport/tokyo-olympics-kiwi-weightlifter-laurel-hubbard-to-become-first-transgender-athlete-to-compete-at-the-games/DM7ZUGW3HQ2IDL6O7OSAXT3YJU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurel Hubbard will make history at the Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK GAMES:  Olympian tests positive for virus upon arrival in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ugandan-olympian-tests-positive-for-virus-upon-arrival-in-japan-the-first-detection-as-athletes-head-to-tokyo/ar-AALfAsS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uganda’s team was reportedly all vaccinated with AstraZeneca and tested negative for the virus before departure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disappearance of circus from American life leaves us lonelier...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-the-disappearance-of-the-circus-from-american-life-leaves-us-lonelier/ar-AALeIis?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Circuses made entertainment a community event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen suffers disappointment in French elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210620-far-right-leader-le-pen-suffers-first-round-disappointment-in-france-s-regional-elections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party of France's far-right leader Marine Le Pen performed weaker than expected in the first round of regional elections Sunday, in a vote marked by record levels of abstention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  One killed in 'tragic accident' as truck hit Florida Pride parade...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/one-killed-truck-hits-crowd-022637693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One man was killed and another injured in what US authorities said Sunday was a "tragic accident" at a Pride parade in Florida where a pickup truck driver unintentionally accelerated, striking pedestrians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Counting Enters New Era as Threat Shifts Away from Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/lifestyle/coronavirus/covid-counting-enters-new-era-as-threat-shifts-away-from-cases/ar-AALeYID</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST CRUISE IN YEAR SETS SAIL OUT OF MIAMI</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/first-us-cruise-in-15-months-set-to-sail-as-restrictions-ease/ar-AALforp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guests lined up to board Royal Caribbean Cruises Ltd.’s Freedom of the Seas on Sunday, marking the first cruise from a U.S. port since the pandemic suspended operations 15 months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROJECT LIBERTY:  Real Estate Mogul Has $100 Million Plan to 'Save the Internet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/a-real-estate-mogul-has-a-24100-million-plan-to-save-the-internet/ar-AALfdW1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank McCourt wants to build a blockchain-based alternative to Facebook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,000 women being monitored after reporting period problems following vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3120109/vaccine-watchdog-monitoring-women-period-problems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE vaccine watchdog is “closely monitoring” 4,000 women who have reported period problems after getting their Covid jab. A change in menstrual cycle is not included on the list of pote…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Israel on verge of new covid outbreak?..</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/is-israel-on-the-verge-of-a-new-covid-19-outbreak-671558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel Health Ministry official says to 'remain calm' amongst worries of a possible future coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand names trans athlete to women's Olympics weightlifting team...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210620211050-scgha</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLYMPICS-2020/WEIGHTLIFITING (URGENT):New Zealand names transgender athlete Hubbard to women's Tokyo Olympics weightlifting team</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic-delayed surgeries share blame for blood shortage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-business-coronavirus-pandemic-health-20353f0a14431ef99f913c2220091015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Some New England hospitals are delaying or rescheduling surgeries because of a shortage of blood donations during the pandemic. “We haven’t seen anything like this in about 30 or 40 years at least,” Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  Iran's nuclear power plant undergoes emergency shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-europe-entertainment-business-6729095cdbc15443c6135142e2d755e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran’s sole nuclear power plant has undergone an unexplained temporary emergency shutdown, state TV reported on Sunday. An official from state electric company Tavanir, Gholamali Rakhshanimehr, said on a talk show that the Bushehr plant shutdown began on Saturday and would last "for three to four days.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials: Deadly Pride parade crash appears unintentional...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-music-eae400f8ef28e9a1f97019e2ed01caf5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — A member of a men’s chorus group unintentionally slammed into fellow chorists at the start of a Pride parade in South Florida, killing one member of the group and seriously injuring another, the group's director said Sunday, correcting initial speculation that it was a hate crime directed at the gay community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver rams cyclists in AZ race, critically injuring 6...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arizona-sports-bcaa4de628461416c92f181764ca8618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Bicyclist Tony Quinones had only just shaken hands with a fellow cyclist and wished him good luck in this weekend's community race in an Arizona mountain town when a truck sped into a crowd of bike riders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 children killed after crash in drenched Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/alabama-crash-interstate-65-claudette-girls-tropical-weather-6c1105ca3a0d1a80c1e516a0e1e4213a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Eight children in a van from a youth home for abused or neglected children were killed in a fiery multi-vehicle crash on a wet interstate that also killed a man and his baby in another vehicle, the most devastating blow from a tropical depression that claimed 12 lives in Alabama as it caused flash floods and spurred tornadoes that destroyed dozens of homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 children killed after crash in drenched Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3121026/alabama-crash-kills-nine-children-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HORROR crash led to the deaths of nine children and one adult in Butler County, Alabama over the weekend. The crash — which took place on Saturday in a storm-plagued Alabama — likely occurred whe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUCK ACCIDENT OR TERROR?</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/police-1-dead-1-hospitalized-after-truck-hits-pedestrians-at-stonewall-pride-parade-driver-in-custody/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILTON MANORS, FLA. (WSVN) - A night of celebration turned into a night of tragedy when, police said, a truck driver ran over two pedestrians...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicles hydroplaned... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/floods-environment-and-nature-6c1105ca3a0d1a80c1e516a0e1e4213a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Tropical Depression Claudette claimed 12 lives in Alabama as the storm swept across the southeastern U.S., causing flash flooding and spurring tornadoes that destroyed dozens of homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Italygate' conspiracy pushed by firms led by woman who falsely claimed $30 million mansion was hers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/italygate-election-conspiracy-theory-was-pushed-by-two-firms-led-by-woman-who-also-falsely-claimed-30-million-mansion-was-hers/ar-AALdLiW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two firms led by Virginia business executive Michele Roosevelt Edwards promoted outlandish claims that an Italian defense contractor conspired with CIA officials to switch votes from Trump to Biden using satellite technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARLEY'S new HOG's: 'Electrification is given'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/20/electrification-is-a-given-harley-ceo-on-future-of-riding-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harley-Davidson is up under new CEO Jochen Zeitz and he says the brand's success will come down to 'desirability' and, for some consumers, that means electric.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver rams cyclists in AZ race, critically injuring 6...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/az-state-wire-arizona-police-abbe4e51dcb7de54b4e90f49a419fd19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOW LOW, Ariz. (AP) — A driver in a pickup truck plowed into bicyclists during a community road race in Arizona on Saturday, critically injuring several riders before police chased the driver and shot him outside a nearby hardware store, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most premature baby celebrates 1st birthday -- after beating 0% survival odds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/19/us/worlds-most-premature-baby-birthday-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A baby born weighing less than a pound has beaten the odds and celebrated his first birthday, becoming the most premature baby to survive, according to Guinness World Records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESAME introduces family with two gay dads...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2021/06/sesame-street-introduces-family-with-two-gay-dads-during-pride-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are some new faces on “Sesame Street” and they’re bringing a new layer of diversity to the decades-old children’s show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Animals Different from All the Rest...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/blue-animals-are-different-from-all-the-rest/ar-AALeR2B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the colors we see on creatures such as blue jays and poison-dart frogs aren’t created by pigments at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS: Olympian tests positive in Tokyo...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/uganda-olympian-covid-positive-tokyo-6bbb9fed-fdd4-406d-9873-073934dbb2e0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unidentified athlete during a screening at a Tokyo airport, per NHK TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Butcher of Tehran'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/israel-says-raisi-most-extreme-president-yet-671493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lapid: His election should prompt renewed determination to immediately halt Iran’s nuclear program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Confusion: Investor wakes up 'trillionaire' -- but can't cash out...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/crypto-currency-confusion-georgia-man-wakes-up-a-trillionaire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRILLION-DOLLAR DILEMMA: Imagine going to sleep as an average, hard-working American only to wake up in the morning a trillionaire. It may have happened to one Georgia man this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$500 universal basic income payments tested in NY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-travel-health-coronavirus-pandemic-a8d5fc984ec98ac21cfb2fe380b10713</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annette Steele isn't destitute or unemployed. But for a year she'll be receiving $500 per month in no-strings-attached payments as part of an experimental universal basic income program in upstate New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China gives 1 billionth dose...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210620-china-gives-one-billionth-covid-shot-as-brazil-toll-hits-milestone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China gives one-billionth Covid shot as Brazil toll hits milestone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businesses beg Congress for ANOTHER bailout...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/19/businesses-lobby-billions-pandemic-aid-495171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plea comes even after Congress appropriated more than $1 trillion over the past year to support smaller employers through forgivable loans and grants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Count on Needing Booster Shot, WHO Scientist Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/don-t-count-on-needing-a-covid-booster-shot-who-scientist-says/ar-AALdX5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As some governments and pharmaceutical officials prepare for Covid booster shots targeting more-infectious virus variants, health authorities say it’s too early to tell if they will be required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ cop shoots suspect who struck multiple cyclists with vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/19/us/arizona-suspect-shot-struck-cyclists/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Show Low, Arizona, on Saturday shot a suspect who they say struck multiple cyclists with a vehicle during a bicycle race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports betting brings stunningly low amount of money to DC...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/06/the-stunningly-low-amount-of-money-sports-betting-has-brought-dc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tax revenue windfall from legalized sports betting has yet to become reality in D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia embraces USA -- and pays price with China...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/australia-embraces-u-s-pays-price-china-trade-war-hits-n1270458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Beijing and Washington target each other's economic and military ambitions in a cycle of escalating tensions, some in Australia worry their country could pay the price for being caught between the two geopolitical foes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing market on fire. Fed keeps adding gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/19/business/inflation-housing-market-federal-reserve/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bidding wars. All-cash offers. Homes selling for $1 million over asking. The housing boom has officially reached the ridiculous stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  2 mushrooms a day halves cancer risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/health-wellness/article/3135636/eating-two-mushrooms-day-could-lower-cancer-risk-45-cent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who incorporate mushrooms in their daily diet lower their risk of getting cancer, analysis suggests. Mushrooms are high in antioxidants and contain chemical components thought to boost immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Spawns Tornadoes, Heavy Rains to South...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/tropical-storm-claudette-spawns-tornadoes-and-brings-heavy-rains-to-the-south/ar-AALd9uz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Claudette, the third named storm of the Atlantic hurricane season, formed in the Gulf of Mexico and brought “copious rainfall” of five to 10 inches across the Mississippi Delta and Gulf Coast before being downgraded to a tropical depression on Saturday, forecasters said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia accused of 'excessive, unnecessary' secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-australia-15029370cec301172244fe168b4b9dd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Australia’s suppression of information seen as pivotal to a free and open media is at the center of accusations that the country has become one of the world’s most secretive democracies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruel, Twisted Discoveries at Germany's Stonehenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-cruel-and-twisted-discoveries-at-germany-s-stonehenge/ar-AALedt0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you think of Stonehenge what do you think of? England? Druids? Partygoers celebrating the solstice? A unique piece of ancient heritage?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOORDASH app crashes leaving drivers stuck with orders... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/doordash-app-temporarily-crashes-company-working-to-resolve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DoorDash company leaders said they're having difficulties with their app Saturday after frustration mounted on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUCK 'TERROR'</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/06/19/2-people-hit-by-truck-at-pride-parade-in-wilton-manors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two people were run over by a pickup truck as the LGBTQ Pride parade in Wilton Manors was just getting started around 7 p.m. Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit sex guide on Norwegian public television causes stir...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9700987/Explicit-sex-guide-Norwegian-public-television-causes-stir.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING -- EXPLICIT CONTENT: Public broadcaster NRK offered a guide of 60 different positions, with models simulating sexual positions including 'the squeezing koala' and 'spaghetti'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE KILLED</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/mayor-1-dead-1-hospitalized-after-truck-hits-pedestrians-at-stonewall-pride-parade-driver-in-custody/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILTON MANORS, FLA. (WSVN) - One person has died and another has been taken to the hospital after they were run over by a truck...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIDE SCARE SOUTH FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fl-state-wire-florida-8ba2e46151a5592ed0e54c004cbedf85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILTON MANORS, Fla. (AP) — A driver slammed into spectators Saturday at the start of a Pride parade in South Florida, injuring at least two people. Fort Lauderdale Mayor Dean Trantalis confirmed the crash occurred Saturday evening at the Stonewall Pride Parade in the nearby city of Wilton Manors, WSVN-TV reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Square becomes no-go zone after dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9704729/The-rotten-core-Big-Apple-iconic-Washington-Square-Park-no-zone-locals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com spoke to park visitors after a woman was trampled by terrified crowds trying to flee a man armed with a large knife and a taser during a late-night rave at the Manhattan landmark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  As king, Charles will not let grandson Archie be prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9704475/Prince-Charles-wont-let-Archie-prince-plans-slim-monarchy-save-costs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heir to the throne has made it clear that Harry and Meghan's son will have no place among frontline Royals as he plans a slimmed-down Monarchy after he becomes King.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addiction treatment had failed. Could brain surgery save him?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Addiction-treatment-had-failed-Could-brain-16260047.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MORGANTOWN, W.Va. - After nearly two decades of hardcore drug addiction - after overdoses...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French police battle party-goers at curfew-busting rave...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/several-hurt-french-police-break-182529476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five police officers were injured in western France as they broke up a 1,500-strong illegal rave, authorities said Saturday, with one party-goer losing a hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Downtown Chicago emerges from pandemic --  hobbled by crime wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/downtown-chicago-emerges-pandemic-hobbled-011618733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Businesses in downtown Chicago that survived the pandemic-related economic slump and two spasms of looting last summer should be ecstatic with Monday's reopening of America's third-largest city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Turns Into Test Case Endgame...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/britain-turns-into-test-case-for-covid-endgame/ar-AALdGLM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson has promised no more delays to lifting restrictions, yet cases are surging and more deaths are inevitable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Says it Sent 'Completely Normal' Vaccines to Palestinians...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/israel-says-it-sent-completely-normal-vaccines-to-palestinians/article_8047d6ed-63d6-52c4-865b-0deaeec9a5f1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel — The first batch of Pfizer vaccines Israel sent to the Palestinian Authority on Friday as part of a larger swap deal was “completely normal” and identical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe goes to church day after challenge from bishops on abortion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-goes-church-day-challenge-224324432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden went to church Saturday in his hometown a day after US Roman Catholic bishops issued a challenge to him over his support for abortion rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City shuts down classes again, enters higher risk tier...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210619165131-1hkfj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/MEXICO (PIX):Mexico City shuts down classes again, enters higher COVID-19 risk tier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck plows into crowd at Pride Parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/3118900/two-run-over-truck-man-florida-pride/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN is in custody after he allegedly ran over two people during a Pride march in Florida on Saturday, according to local reports. The horrifying incident unfolded during the Stonewall Pride in Wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Heckled With Boos and Cries of 'Traitor' at Evangelical Conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/mike-pence-gets-heckled-at-faith-freedom-coalition-summit-with-boos-and-cries-of-traitor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence owes a great deal of his political career to support from evangelical conservatives, and Friday’s Faith &amp; Freedom Coalition Summit has been home turf for him for years. But the Republican base is still very devoted to former President Donald Trump, and Pence’s apostasy on Jan. 6 — refusing to oppose […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Nikki Haley's road to White House start in Jerusalem?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/does-nikki-haleys-road-to-the-white-house-start-in-jerusalem-671276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Israel should not be fighting alone," said the former-US ambassador to the UN on a solidarity mission to Israel's rocket-ravaged south.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom assaulted by aggressive homeless on Oakland street...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2021/06/18/chp-gov-newsom-assaulted-by-aggressive-person-in-oakland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of TV news and newspaper reporters nearby heard the commotion. All they could see was the governor’s security detail detaining a man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman claims she's in love with alien after UFO abduction...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/woman-says-shes-fallen-alien-24356799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Abbie Bela claims she has fallen for an alien after being abducted by a UFO from her bedroom window this month. The actress, who is in her 30s, says her ET paramour is her “soul mate” – and better than any earthling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang unloads on rival and media in raw, late-night interview...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/nyc-mayoral-race-andrew-evelyn-yang-blast-eric-adams.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Brazil tops 500,000 deaths, protests against president Bolsonaro...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brazil-coronavirus-pandemic-health-bb2f9632be7a8a484d35d4e7fb642406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Anti-government protesters took to the streets in more than a score of cities across Brazil on Saturday as the nation's confirmed death toll from COVID-19 soared past half a million — a tragedy many critics blame on President Jair Bolsonaro's attempt to minimize the disease.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
