<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Buttigieg has been surprise of Dem field. Where does he go next? </title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Buttigieg-has-been-the-surprise-of-the-Democratic-13782776.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Bend, Indiana Mayor Pete Buttigieg is on a trajectory that few people would have imagined when he first formed his presidential exploratory committee. His poise and thoughtfulness have produced accolades on Twitter and cable TV that must make him blush at times. But his performance has made him the surprise factor in the Democratic nomination race.  What happens as the campaign moves ahead is the interesting question. History is an uncertain guide but still worth examining as Buttigieg tries to capitalize on the attention he has gotten. Is he a genuine breakthrough candidate, whose rise to prominence shatters both barriers and expectations? Or is he like some candidates of the past, who found a following within a segment of their party's electorate - or the attention of the media - but could not move beyond it?  Several past candidates come to mind in trying to assess the Buttigieg phenomenon. One is Barack Obama. Another is former New Jersey senator Bill Bradley. A third is former Arizona governor Bruce Babbitt. All had their moments. All were the subject of favorable and sometimes gushing media coverage. Only Obama went on to become both his party's nominee and president of the United States.  Obama is the candidate anyone like Buttigieg would like to become: a history-maker, an outsider who shook the system, a political meteor who flashed across the nation's screens but didn't burn out. Obama's 2004 keynote speech to the Democratic National Convention turned him into an overnight political celebrity. By the time he announced his candidacy for president more than two years later (and after election to the U.S. Senate), he was already destined to become the most serious challenger to Hillary Clinton for the 2008 Democratic nomination.  Buttigieg's rise has been far more condensed - and limited. He formed his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest unsolved mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/04/20/mueller-report-left-some-perplexing-trump-russia-questions-unanswered/3521806002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mueller's report was brimming with details about Donald Trump's White House but it left some of the probe's most perplexing questions unanswered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Armed civilians detaining migrants at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/04/19/united-constitutional-patroits-armed-group-detaining-migrants-texas-nm-border/3523457002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Constitutional Patriots is patrolling the border area, armed with weapons and searching for migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLEFACEBOOKAMAZONAPPLE employees donating to Warren -- even though she wants to break up big tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/04/19/elizabeth-warren-president-tech-campaign-donations-berine-sanders-kamala-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren is getting some surprising financial support from the employees of the big tech companies she wants to slice and dice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow vest anger burns in France, fueled by Notre Dame fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fd877004c7b942568fe8d95a1229e180</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French yellow vest protesters set fires Saturday along a march through Paris to drive home their message to a government they believe is ignoring the poor: that rebuilding the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real reasons why New Yorkers fleeing city...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/20/the-real-reasons-why-new-yorkers-are-fleeing-the-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;True story: My wife and I both are former residents of New York City, and on a recent business trip there she was taking a nostalgic walk through the Upper West Side on a lovely fall day, talking t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna 'MEDELLIN' Flops...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/04/19/pop-charts-madonnas-comeback-fizzles-as-medellin-with-columbian-singer-maluma-flops-on-itunes-gets-no-streaming-love-on-spotify</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna had a big build up for “Medellin” single this past Wednesday. She premiered it at noon with Zane Lowe on Apple’s Beats 1 Radio like it was the second coming. The song turn…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal dispute drove end of probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.oakridger.com/zz/news/20190420/how-legal-dispute-drove-end-of-special-counsels-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oakridger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel ended his investigation last month, pointedly choosing not to reach a conclusion about whether the president had obstructed justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Venezuela in flames, ChinaRussia seeking claims in rubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-soured-relations-in-Latin-America-China-13782596.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Venezuela in flames, China and Russia are seeking claims in the rubble.  But the United States has been caught flat-footed, and the Pentagon is struggling to develop ways to blunt the countries' influence in Latin America since President Donald Trump has antagonized and distanced himself from nations in the Western Hemisphere.  Defense officials have sought non-force options to deter China and Russia in Venezuela, CNN reported this week, through a mix of humanitarian missions and more training in Latin America led by U.S. Southern Command, the Pentagon arm that oversees a sixth of the world's land mass.  Yet experts said those efforts and others are in opposition to pressure and rhetoric from the White House, which has made significant demands to Latin American nations to curb migration and drug trafficking without offering much in return - all while ceding influence and support that Russia, and particularly China, have been happy to take over.  "The Trump administration's policy has supercharged China's increased presence in the region," said Benjamin Gedan, former National Security Council official under the Obama administration and a senior adviser to the Latin American program at the Wilson Center, a Washington think tank. "It's entirely counterproductive."  For years, China and Russia have sought more influence in the Western Hemisphere, but are increasingly emboldened to bolster their economic and security positions in South America, Central America and the Caribbean.  China has pledged to invest $250 billion there and reach half a trillion dollars in trade, while Russia has taken root to antagonize the United States and demonstrate its might. Both have invested billions in Venezuela, though some experts have questioned Russia's true prominence and focus on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOTAL BULLSH*T'</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cf496df553ea4b15a232c5adaa1a2936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is lashing out at current and former aides who cooperated with special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation, insisting the deeply unflattering picture...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake news? Mueller isn't buying it...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/06c88719c3634e66a15adbbc658978b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump and his team love to deride unfavorable stories as "fake news," but it's clear from Robert Mueller's report that the special counsel isn't buying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't Afford Surgery? In China, Millions Chip In Half Penny to Cover You...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cant-afford-surgery-in-china-millions-chip-in-half-a-penny-to-cover-you-11555772400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a girl in Shanghai suffered brain damage after falling off a bunk bed, millions of strangers across China helped foot her surgical bills. Crowdfunded medical coverage, offered by fintech startups, could fill gaps in the country’s health insurance sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 1 In 5 Children Suffers From Mental Health Disorder...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/one-in-five-children-suffers-from-mental-health-disorder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in five children suffer from a mental health disorder -- with notable increases in depression and anxiety over the past 30 years -- yet less than one-third have had contact with a mental healthcare provider, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists create 'living' machines that eat, grow -- and evolve...</title>
      <link>https://thenextweb.com/robots/2019/04/19/cornell-scientists-create-living-machines-that-eat-grow-and-evolve/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenextweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The field of robotics is going through a renaissance thanks to advances in machine learning and sensor technology. Each generation of robot is engineered with greater mechanical complexity and smarter operating software than the last. But what if, instead of painstakingly designing and engineering a robot, you could just tear open a packet of primordial …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome for migrants cools in Mexican town weary of caravans...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190420145232-6ogk1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO (PIX, TV):Welcome for migrants cools in Mexican town weary of caravans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Church' to offer 'miracle cure' despite FDA warnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/apr/19/church-group-to-hold-washington-event-despite-fda-warnings-against-miracle-cure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group to hold ‘effective alternative healing’ event in Washington state in which they peddle a ‘sacrament’ known to be industrial cleaner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are worst 25 jobs in America?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/04/20/the-worst-jobs-in-america/39364439/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dislike your job? These 25 are considered the worst occupations in the U.S. for factors such as lack of job security, danger, low pay and stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot anchor in Russia sparks 'propaganda' controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/russian-news-anchor-robot-sparks-propaganda-controversy-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian news channel has reportedly started using a robot to anchor some of its newscast - but not everyone is impressed. ‘Alex,’ which was built by and based on Promobot co-founder Alexei Yuzhakov, has started reporting stories on Rossiya 24 about agriculture and nuclear technology among other topics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 campaign trail runs through churches in SCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e3cd6d9a08c94ca59a1a427e6517cfd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) — By now, most Democratic presidential candidates have polished their stump speeches. But when they're in South Carolina, they may need to add in a sermon. In a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 things media got wrong...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/19/top-10-things-the-media-got-wrong-about-collusion-and-obstruction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prestige press has some explaining to do — for subjecting the nation to a long, cruel ordeal named “collusion” and “obstruction.” Almost two years and millions of column inches later, special c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving? The Kids Are So Over It...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/driving-the-kids-are-so-over-it-11555732810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a challenge for Detroit, teens put off getting their licenses and buying cars. About a quarter of 16-year-olds had a driver’s license in 2017, a sharp decline from nearly half in 1983.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Tom Ford, Fragrant Vegan Vampire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/20/style/tom-ford-maureen-dowd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a designer known for sex and excess became a devoted family man — and C.F.D.A. chief!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Should White Man Be Face of Dem Party?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/should-a-white-man-be-the-face-of-the-democratic-party-in-2020/ar-BBW7KnG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious life of James McCord, Watergate burglar whose death went unnoticed for 2 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/obituaries/la-me-james-mccord-watergate-breakin-dead-20190419-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As shadowy in death and he was in life, James McCord died at 93 — two years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Power Gets Booster Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/presidential-power-gets-a-booster-shot-no-matter-mueller-s-view</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential Power Gets a Booster Shot, No Matter Mueller's View</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand marijuana festival has visitors on a high...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thailand-marijuana-festival-visitors-high-083609076.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Buddhist monk fishes out a vial of cannabis oil from his robe and puts a drop under his tongue -- one of many people flocking to a weed festival in northeastern Thailand, where excitement is building over a medical marijuana boom. Thailand became the first country in Southeast Asia to legalise marijuana</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Pressured...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pelosi-pressured-progressives-demand-impeachment-80000574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin pop has US grooving more and more in Spanish...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/latin-pop-us-grooving-more-more-spanish-010456904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just two years after the lilting mega-hit "Despacito" captivated the globe, Latin stars are cementing their place in the US mainstream, moving beyond scoring a one-off smash to headline festivals and permeate the charts. An unprecedented number of Spanish-language acts are performing at this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FATHER WHO GAVE BIRTH:  TRANS MAN'S STORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/video/2019/apr/02/seahorse-exclusive-trailer-for-new-documentary-about-the-dad-who-gave-birth-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the trailer for Seahorse, a new Guardian-produced feature-length documentary, about one trans man’s pioneering quest to fulfil an age-old desire: to start his own family. The is the story of the dad who gave birth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL:  Ebola worker shot dead at hospital in eastern DR Congo...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ebola-worker-killed-hospital-eastern-dr-congo-181745813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health worker fighting an Ebola outbreak in DR Congo was shot dead Friday in an attack on a hospital in the eastern city of Butembo, the World Health Organization said. The WHO said that Dr. Richard Valery Mouzoko Kiboung, an epidemiologist it had deployed to help rein in the Ebola outbreak, was killed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 40 Years, C-SPAN Founder Signs Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/after-40-years-c-spans-founder-signs-off-11555713751?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Lamb, the man who put Congress on live television, reflects on the results and explains why the Supreme Court ought to be next.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
