<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Selling fake social media popularity is very big business...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/14/selling-fake-social-media-popularity-is-a-very-big-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internet has brought new meaning to the old adage, “Don’t believe everything you read.” From fake news and fake Twitter accounts to fake Instagram followers and fake Amazon reviews, the online …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE DOC READY TO SCORCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/michael-moore-f-k-hope-seriously-f-k-hope-trump-will-be-last-president-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-Trump filmmaker Michael Moore (Screenshot) “F—k hope,” because it’s “the lazy way out,” liberal activist filmmaker Michael Moore says in an interview promoting his new anti-Trump film, “Fahrenheit 11/9,” which opens in theaters on September 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Agents 'Sickened' By Containers With Tea, Soap; Hazmat Team Brought In...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/08/14/mysterious-liquids-make-tsa-officers-ill-at-orlando-international-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials at Orlando International Airport say four security officers fell ill after checking the contents of oversized containers holding unknown liquids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weed-killing chemical linked to cancer found in children's breakfast foods...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/glyphosate-roundup-chemical-found-in-childrens-breakfast-foods/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;31 out of 45 tested products had glyphosate levels higher than what some scientists consider safe for children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant Reality Star Found Dead on Street Without Pants...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2018/08/14/lyric-mchenry-found-dead-on-new-york-sidewalk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 26-year-old produced and co-starred on the series "EJNYC."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Russian satellite's behaviour raises alarm in US...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-45194333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official says "there is no way to verify" what object is and whether or not it may pose a danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oral sex, then holy water...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/report-pennsylvania-priests-abused-over-1-000-children-042935265.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "real number" of abused children and abusive priests might be higher since some secret church records were lost and some victims never came forward, the grand jury said. U.S. bishops adopted sweeping reforms in 2002 when clergy abuse became a national crisis for the church, including stricter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unwanted dogs left on own in Iowa forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/15/57-unwanted-dogs-dumped-iowa-forest/995933002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 30 dogs were found in an south-central Iowa forest after they were left there by owners who didn't want them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves Accuser Shopping Tell-All Memoir...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/leslie-moonves-accuser-christine-peters-shopping-tell-all-memoir-1134765 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say the 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days' producer is pitching a memoir titled 'Hollywood Granola: My Life With Nuts and Flakes,' which will chronicle a "cautionary tale about the hard work behind the scenes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman born in 1905 oldest living person in USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article216678160.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Hester Ford was researching her year of birth with her family, she came across census data that might indicate Ford might have been born in 1904, making her 114 years old and the oldest living person in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studios Gamble on Franco, Affleck Projects Post-#MeToo Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/studios-gamble-james-franco-casey-affleck-projects-metoo-claims-1134941 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many of Hollywood’s accused men aren't finding new work easily, some are keeping the jobs they have — which brings unique risks for their business partners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARREY RETURNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/jim-carreys-reluctant-return-hollywood-1134623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first extensive profile in years, the one-time $20 million-a-movie star and current political cartoonist opens up about his disappearance, his personal pain, his outrage and why he's returning to the spotlight with Showtime's 'Kidding': "My plan was not to join Hollywood. It was to destroy it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's hottest export? Sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/aug/15/americas-hottest-export-sperm-fertility</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American and a Danish company dominate the global sperm market – and both claim their supply is biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Republican Seats Join Toss Up Column?</title>
      <link>https://www.cookpolitical.com/analysis/house/house-overview/house-three-more-gop-seats-join-toss-column</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cookpolitical.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Republicans, the 2018 House playing field is a lot like a game of Whack-a-Mole: everywhere they turn, new problems keep popping up in surprising places. In January, we rated 20 GOP-held seats as Toss Ups or worse, including three leaning towards Democrats. With today's changes, we now rate 37 GOP-held seats as Toss Ups or worse, including ten leaning towards Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT: Retail sales increase strongly...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/15/us-retail-sales-july-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. retail sales were forecast to edged up 0.1 percent in July, after climbing 0.5 percent a month earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night of firsts as Dems pick diverse slate of nominees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c134320bf194096a66d93616e0b0680/Night-of-firsts-as-Democrats-pick-diverse-slate-of-nominees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — In a night of firsts, Democrats in Vermont's primary chose the nation's first transgender gubernatorial nominee. In Minnesota, they picked a woman who would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where does pay go furthest?  Duluth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/where-in-the-u-s-does-your-pay-go-furthest-try-duluth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to where you live, big salaries don't always deliver the biggest bang for your buck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals scrap surgeries, Venezuelans forgo showers as taps run dry...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180815120014-zxwh0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-WATER/ (PIX, TV):Hospitals scrap surgeries, Venezuelans forgo showers as taps run dry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muja the alligator still alive and snapping in his 80s...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180815110007-tdpgs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SERBIA-ALIGATOR/ (PIX, TV):Muja the alligator still alive and snapping in his 80s at Belgrade Zoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: More than 600 birds removed from home...</title>
      <link>https://myfox28columbus.com/news/local/columbus-humane-closes-tuesday-to-handle-large-animal-cruelty-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;myfox28columbus.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Columbus Humane was closed Tuesday to handle a large animal cruelty investigation involving around 600 birds at a home.The organization said all animal support center appointments will continue, but new adoption pickups will need to be rescheduled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden under doctor's orders not to travel...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/news/joe-biden-falls-ill-wont-campaign-for-dems-at-illinois-state-fair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president had been scheduled to take part in Thursday’s Illinois State Fair Democrat Day to help bolster support for state candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Punk Rock Frontman Jumps Off Stage, Attacks Trump Supporter In Middle Of Concert...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/08/14/social-distortion-lead-singer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Hildebrand of Galt says the attack happened at a Social Distortion concert at the Ace of Spades in Midtown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive candidates bounce back in key Midwest races...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/progressive-candidates-bounce-back-gop-eyes-midwest-races/story?id=57183800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates in Minnesota and Vermont made history Tuesday night, while a former GOP presidential candidate's comeback bid fell short in a key gubernatorial race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somali-American nears new historic mark with primary win...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/somali-american-nears-new-historic-mark-with-primary-win/490894121/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's first Somali-American state legislator is poised to set the same historic mark in Congress after winning a crowded Democratic primary in Minnesota to replace Rep. Keith Ellison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing arguments in explosive Manafort trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/lawyers-begin-closing-arguments-explosive-manafort-trial-055211909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers will begin closing arguments Wednesday in the explosive trial of former Donald Trump campaign chief Paul Manafort, after which the veteran political operative's fate will rest with the jury. After hearing some 20 witnesses for prosecutors describe how Manafort allegedly evaded taxes on millions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Twelve Apostles' help migrants cross Mexico...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180815-twelve-apostles-help-migrants-cross-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buddhist monk master resigns after sexual misconduct allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-harassment-religion/buddhist-monk-master-in-china-resigns-after-sexual-misconduct-allegations-idUSKBN1L00HR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of China's highest-ranking Buddhist monks quit as the head of the country's Buddhist association on Wednesday after facing a government investigation over accusations of sexual misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Probe Seen Pushing Past Trump-Demanded September 1 Deadline...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/15/mueller-probe-seen-pushing-past-trump-demanded-sept-1-deadline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller Probe Seen Pushing Past Trump-Demanded September 1 Deadline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ dominance of gossip dwindles...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/08/15/harvey-levin-is-casting-the-tmz-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Levin Is Casting the TMZ Primary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUTERTE: Thinking of stepping down because I'm tired...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/15/philippine-president-duterte-won-t-stop-talking-about-quitting </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines' Duterte Won't Stop Talking About Quitting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rejects appeal for American pastor's release from detention...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/08/15/court-rejects-appeal-for-american-pastors-release-from-detention-turkish-media-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ankara rejected the U.S.' appeal for an American pastor's release from detention Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran rolls out 'Poop Patrol' to keep sidewalks clean...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/heatherknight/article/It-s-no-laughing-matter-SF-forming-Poop-13153517.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a city where filthy sidewalks are many residents’ No. 1 complaint, City Hall has come up with a new way to deal with No. 2. It sounds like silly elementary school banter, but it’s real. San Francisco is about to launch the Poop Patrol. In about a month, a team of five Public Works staffers will begin patrolling the alleys around Polk Street and other hot spots in a vehicle equipped with a steam cleaner. They’ll begin their shifts in the afternoon, as the city starts losing its sheen from overnight cleaning. The Poop Patrol’s mission? To spot and clean piles of feces before anybody complains about them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEINFELD: Jokes Are Not Real Life; TWITTER is Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/15/magazine/jerry-seinfeld-says-jokes-are-not-real-life.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian on offensive humor, why Twitter is hell and the best joke in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER blocks Alex Jones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/15/twitter-suspends-alex-jones.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has suspended right-wing media personality Alex Jones for violating its policies, according to a Tuesday report. Jones will be blocked from posting on Twitter for seven days, Dow Jones reported citing the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study: Wealthy people cheat more...</title>
      <link>https://www.columbian.com/news/2018/aug/14/study-wealthy-people-cheat-more-than-others/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.columbian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is it about money that makes people do bad things?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER blocks Alex Jones...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/401879-twitter-blocks-alex-jones-from-tweeting-for-a-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has blocked right-wing conspiracy theorist Alex Jones from tweeting on his personal account for one week after one of his posts violated the platform’s policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F**k Donald Trump' Rapper Booted from AMERICAN Flight, Claims Racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/08/14/american-airlines-rapper-yg-from-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines claims it removed rapper YG from a flight Monday because he was drunk, but the rapper claims it is all about racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles outbreak 21 states...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/health/cdc-monitoring-measles-outbreak-in-21-states-including-north-carolina-/3957136/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Tuesday afternoon that 107 people from 21 states, including North Carolina, have reported contracting the measles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The bohemian world of Venice Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/gallery/2018/aug/14/venice-beach-photos-dotan-saguy-bohemian-world-in-pictures </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Disneyland, Venice Beach is the second largest tourist attraction in southern California and over a three-year period, photographer Dotan Saguy captured the artists, body builders, musicians, vendors and homeless people who made up the diverse community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boys and girls will share restroom in Kansas City...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/article216439305.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Kansas City school district has gender-neutral restrooms in two new elementary schools and some renovated areas at a high school and sixth-grade centers. Toilets are in floor-to-ceiling door stalls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of food pushes 2.3 million to flee Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180814-lack-food-pushes-23mn-flee-venezuela-un</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California paying inmates $1 an hour to fight wildfires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/california-is-paying-inmates-1-an-hour-to-fight-wildfires.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are over 2,000 volunteer inmate firefighters battling the blaze in Northern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHOOL'S BACK!  Notorious college students keep dressing up in blackface, Nazi costumes...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/14/notorious-college-students-keep-dressing-up-in-blackface-nazi-costumes/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Happy Hanukkah from Auschwitz!!” reads the image caption. The photo, taken at an event organized and hosted at the elite St. Mark’s residential college, features two recent students from the Unive…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANS WINS IN VT; HISTORIC RUN FOR GOV.</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/christine-hallquist-becomes-first-transgender-gubernatorial-nominee-in-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She beat out three contenders in Vermont’s Democratic primary on Tuesday and will face incumbent Phil Scott in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots IMPROVE marriages?</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6060627/Sex-robots-IMPROVE-marriages-letting-spouses-focus-companionship-expert-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a professor at the University of British Columbia, sexbots could improve marriages by making husbands and wives focus more on love and parenting, instead of sexual compatibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka's quiet success...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/401862-pavlich-ivanka-trumps-quiet-success </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks ago Ivanka Trump announced the end to her clothing company, citing conflicts of interest and plans to stay in Washington, D.C., long term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Pushes Apps Toward Subscription Model Behind the Scenes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thisisinsider.com/apple-secret-meeting-developers-new-york-subscriptions-app-store-2018-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thisisinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BI Prime: Apple is trying to change the business model of the App Store from in-app purchases and paid apps to software-as-a-service. To help kickstart this, in 2017 it held a secret conference and encouraged developers to experiment with raising the prices of their software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average American 'takes less holiday time than Medieval peasant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7017447/average-american-holiday-medieval-economist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE average American takes less work holiday than a medieval peasant. US is the only advanced country with no national vacation policy whatsoever, plus has a culture of working long hours. Many Ame…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY:  Ailing UNIVISION Hit With $2M Suit Over Shell Game Purchase Of 'THE ONION'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/univision-lawsuit-the-onion-purchase-financial-advisors-vince-sadusky-1202445561/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Univision, now run by CEO Vince Sadusky, may be trying to trim costs and staff to stay competitive, but the purchase and possible sale of its brand The Onion could result in a whole new set of tear…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate TV ad: I'll vote against Pelosi!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/democratic-house-candidate-kathy-manning-airs-tv-ad-saying-she-wont-back-pelosi-for-speaker/2018/08/14/ed829a20-a004-11e8-93e3-24d1703d2a7a_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year of Republican attack ads against Pelosi, the N.C. lawyer became the latest candidate to announce that she will not support Democrats’ longtime House leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directors tell Musk to stop tweeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/14/business/dealbook/tesla-board-musk-tweets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla’s board of directors has hired multiple outside law firms, and a number of board members and Tesla employees have urged Mr. Musk to stop posting on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Kobach wins gov nomination after rival concedes...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansas.com/news/politics-government/article216702595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kansas Secretary of State Kris Kobach will advance to face Democrat Laura Kelly and independent candidate Greg Orman in the general election for Kansas governor in November. Gov. Jeff Colyer conceded Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts on TESLA; Hit with another fraud suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/tesla-hit-with-new-lawsuit-alleging-elon-musk-manipulated-stock-price-2018-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla is facing another class-action lawsuit accusing CEO Elon Musk of manipulating the company's stock price. A complaint filed on Monday alleges that some investors purchased Tesla stock "at artificially inflated prices and suffered significant losses and damages."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep space gamma ray bursts have mysterious time-reversing effect...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6060269/Gamma-ray-bursts-deep-space-mysterious-time-reversing-effect.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research headed up by the College of Charleston in South Carolina has studied mysterious bursts of high-energy that appear to defy time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEARL JAM Poster Praises Dem, Depicts Dead Trump...</title>
      <link>http://newstalkkgvo.com/missoula-pearl-jam-poster-praises-jon-tester-features-dead-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newstalkkgvo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A poster promoting the band Pearl Jam's August 13 concert in Missoula is being described as reprehensible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President, McConnell Reshape Courts With Little Fanfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/with-little-fanfare-trump-and-mcconnell-reshape-the-nations-circuit-courts/2018/08/14/10610028-9fcd-11e8-93e3-24d1703d2a7a_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican-led Senate has installed 24 appellate court judges since January 2017 and is poised to confirm two more this week, a record for a president’s first two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200+ Newspapers Plan 'Coordinated' Editorials -- But Will They Listen?</title>
      <link>https://www.poynter.org/news/200-newspapers-will-write-pro-journalism-editorials-will-they-also-listen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.poynter.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Asexual' Hot Identity in Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/california/2018/08/14/asexual-is-new-sexual-identity-in-bay-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new sexual identity has surfaced in the Bay Area, known as "asexual," among those who do not have sexual attraction to other people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town mulls 'eau de lion poo' to scare invading deer...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dutch-mull-eau-lion-dung-scare-off-pesky-173044546.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dutch seaside town overrun by fallow deer is mulling plans to diffuse the smell of lion manure to keep them at bay and stop them invading streets and parks. Situated in the North Sea dunes just west of Amsterdam, Zandvoort has over the past decade been invaded by thousands of the boisterous bucks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver tests positive -- for every possible drug in test by cops...</title>
      <link>http://www.euronews.com/2018/08/14/spanish-driver-tests-positive-on-all-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police stopped a car in northeastern Spain after its driver proved positive for all drugs in the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China tears down Jesus posters, replaces with Xi images...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7015374/china-rips-down-jesus-posters-replaced-president-xi-jinping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has taken extreme measures to wipe out all traces of Christianity in the country, by tearing down posters of Jesus and replacing them with images of President Xi Jinping. The country’s ruling…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivor describes plunging 160 FEET...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7016476/genoa-bridge-collapse-italy-footballer-survivor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Italian footballer has revealed how he fell 160 feet when he was driving over the doomed bridge in Genoa which collapsed today killing at least 35. The Ponte Morandi road on the A10 motorway in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST BLACK SPEAKER? CLYBURN CHAMPIONS 'TRANSFORMING' PARTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article216593000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If he became speaker of the House, U.S. Rep. Jim Clyburn of South Carolina says he would be a “transitional” leader who would “transform” Democrats. A movement is growing for Clyburn to run for the job if Democrats win the majority in the U.S. House and Nancy Pelosi steps aside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles first in US to install subway body scanners...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/la-become-first-us-install-161917486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles' subway will become the first mass transit system in the U.S. to install body scanners that screen passengers for weapons and explosives, officials said Tuesday. The deployment of the portable scanners, which project waves to do full-body screenings of passengers walking through a station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez claims have fact-checkers working overtime...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/14/ocasio-cortez-claims-have-fact-checkers-working-overtime.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York congressional candidate Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has excited the liberal base with her media blitz touting Medicare-for-all, the elimination of ICE and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-day weeks in full effect for Colorado school district...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/education/four-day-school-weeks-in-full-effect-for-school-district-27j/73-583765384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elementary schoolers and kindergartners had one more day of summer break due to the district's new four-day week schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-secret conditions, no tunnel for El Chapo trial...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/14/el-chapo-wont-be-tunneling-to-court-during-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman will stand trial in Brooklyn, a judge ruled Tuesday. Defense attorneys for the drug kingpin had tried to convince Brooklyn federal Judge Brian Cogan that he sh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Madam: 'Leading questions' made me feel sick...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/kristin-davis-talks-about-russia-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman known as the &amp;quot;Manhattan Madam&amp;quot; for once running a high-end prostitution ring in New York City says she was bullied by Robert Mueller&amp;#39;s team when she was forced to testify in front of a grand jury in connection with the Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  NEW YORK Magazine Owner Explores Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-magazine-owner-explores-possible-sale-1534264090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publisher of New York magazine, Vulture and The Cut is reviewing strategic options including a possible sale, the latest media outlet to consider consolidation in a tough marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile asks Vatican for information on cases...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180814200458-kr4kc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILE-ABUSE/VATICAN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Chile asks Vatican for information on sex abuse cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan says Turkey will boycott US electronics...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180814101313-nzpia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TURKEY-CURRENCY/ (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Erdogan says Turkey will boycott US electronics, lira steadies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA chief: Domestic surveillance program 'makes awful lot of sense'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tsa-administrator-david-pekoske-says-quiet-skies-domestic-surveillance-program-makes-an-awful-lot-of-sense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Quiet Skies" program has been criticized for tracking American citizens not suspected of any crimes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 1,000 victims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/301822e3d7a04b0b88a1c40738c4a513/Report-identifies-more-than-1,000-victims-of-priest-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — More than 1,000 children — and possibly many more — were molested by hundreds of Roman Catholic priests in six Pennsylvania dioceses, while seni</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFOWARS SITE HIT WITH ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.newswars.com/infowars-com-site-goes-down-amid-big-tech-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newswars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comes as social media giants try to silence political speech ahead of midterms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER founders sue for billions claiming company 'robbed' them of stock...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/barry-dillers-iac-sued-by-tinder-founders-2-billion-1134767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former CEO Sean Rad alleges that Tinder's parent companies intentionally undervalued the popular dating app to deny early employees billions in stock options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulated financial information...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/tinder-founders-sue-iac-claiming-company-robbed-them-of-stock-options.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plaintiffs in the case filed in New York State Supreme Court in Manhattan include Tinder's founders Sean Rad, Justin Mateen and Jonathan Badeen, as well as three current senior executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK REVIEW: 'A new peak in disgrace'...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/books/2018/08/14/omarosa-memoir-review/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the 'Fire and Fury' sequel you never wanted: the 2018 tell-all in its purest, saddest form</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranians Impersonating Americans On TWITTER...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/13/iranians-fake-american-twitter/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'But after all we are not American'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK threatens media:  'Work with us or die'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7014408/facebook-threatens-press-saying-work-with-us-or-end-up-in-a-hospice/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK has been accused of threatening media firms into working with them by saying their businesses would end up “in a hospice” if they didn’t. Campbell Brown, Facebook’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's laser cannon;  Kremlin's plans to 'wipe out satellites'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1003268/russia-news-military-laser-cannon-vladimir-putin-us-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US has branded Russia’s plans to build a laser cannon capable of wiping out international satellites as EVIL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER Founders Seek Billions Against Parent Company, Allege Sex Harassment Cover-Up...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/breaking-tinder-founders-seek-billions-against-parent-company-allege-sexual-harassment-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Palestinian Congressional Candidate Gets Physical With Jewish Journalist at Political Event...</title>
      <link>https://bigleaguepolitics.com/palestinian-congressional-candidate-assaults-jewish-journalist-at-political-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bigleaguepolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She claims Trump knew in advance that WIKILEAKS was publishing Hillary emails...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6060473/Omarosa-claims-Trump-knew-advance-Wikileaks-publishing-Hillary-Clintons-emails.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omarosa Manigault Newman claimed in a new interview that President Trump 'absolutely' knew about hacked Hillary Clinton emails in advance of publication in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodeo bull escapes stockyards, runs loose in Oklahoma City...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rodeo-bull-escapes-stockyards-runs-loose-oklahoma-city-185148310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — A rodeo bull broke free from the Oklahoma City Stockyards late Monday, charging through city streets and chasing people, including one person who jumped into a river to escape the animal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian cops drop 'masculinity' requirement...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/brazilian-cops-drop-masculinity-requirement-175952287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sao Paulo (AFP) - Police candidates in southern Brazil are now free to get in touch with their softer side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>35 DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7011626/genoa-bridge-collapse-italy-motorway-morandi-latest-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT LEAST 35 people – including a baby – died today after a major tourist motorway bridge collapsed during a “violent” lightning storm in Italy. Firefighters say cars and tru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Now Spying on American Soil...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/chinese-police-are-spying-on-uighurson-american-soil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is compiling a global registry of its ethnic minorities who have fled persecution, threatening to detain the families of those who don’t comply. The message: Nowhere is safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  'Mega-Round' Investors Shower Start-Ups With Millions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/14/technology/venture-capital-mega-round.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Start-ups raising $100 million or more from investors used to be a rarity. Now, this scale of fund raising is commonplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unlikely Activists Who Took On Silicon Valley -- and Won...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/14/magazine/facebook-google-privacy-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook and Google made billions mining personal data, and fought off anyone who threatened to stop them. Then came a challenge in their own backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300+ 'Predator Priests' Named In PA Grand Jury Report...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/08/14/pennsylvania-diocese-sex-abuse-grand-jury-report-released/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-awaited state grand jury report into sexual abuse in six Pennsylvania dioceses, including Pittsburgh and Greensburg, has finally been released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Injuries Reported Following Studio City Explosion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/LAFD-Responding-to-Studio-City-Explosion-490836201.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Fire Department responded Tuesday morning to a reported explosion in a Studio City neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radioactive sheep shed light on secret nuke test...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/14/radioactive-sheep-shed-light-on-secret-nuclear-weapons-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly discovered data from radioactive sheep provides strong evidence that a mysterious “double flash” detected almost 39 years ago near a remote island group was a nuclear explosion. Ever since th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Hops Fence at LA Zoo, Spanks Hippo...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/08/13/hippo-spanking-video-los-angeles-zoo-lapd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He might have done it for the 'Gram, but now a man who crossed a barricade guarding a hippopotamus enclosure at the Los Angeles Zoo is looking at potential trespassing charges after he was filmed spanking one of the animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100K Cello Found in LA Bush...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/california/100K-Cello-Found-in-Bush-Downtown-490763911.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $100,000 cello was found in a bush downtown after it was reported stolen for a few days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein now accused of sex trafficking......</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/08/14/harvey-weinstein-accused-of-being-a-sex-trafficker-in-new-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit was filed by aspiring British actress Kadian Noble claiming that the “Shakespeare In Love” producer violated federal laws against sex trafficking when he lured her to his Ca…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of child who died in 'exorcism' expected resurrection...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6057933/Family-child-died-ritualistic-exorcism-expected-resurrected.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The little boy's father Siraj Ibn Wahhaj, along with one of his wives Jany Leveille, two sisters and a brother-in-law are accused of training children at the camp to use firearms 'to commit school shootings.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Silent...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/14/dnc-keith-ellison-domestic-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Total silence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS:  Sleep deprivation fuels loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/08/14/sleep-deprivation-fuels-loneliness-tired-people-socially-repellent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sleep deprivation is fuelling the loneliness epidemic because overly-tired people are less sociable, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANAFORT WON'T MOUNT DEFENSE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/manafort-attorneys-opt-skip-defense-proceed-closing-arguments/story?id=57168855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for Paul Manafort, the former Trump campaign chairman who is on trial for financial crimes, will not present a defense of their client, ABC News has learned.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
