<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VERIZON phone outages across East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/verizon-sees-phone-outages-across-u-s-east-coast/ar-AAUCKHp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VP Harris to visit Poland, Romania...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Live-updates-Fire-at-Ukraine-nuclear-plant-16976507.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest developments on the Russia-Ukraine war:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen. Milley Personally Delivers Javelins, Stingers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/04/as-russia-pounds-ukraine-nato-countries-rush-in-javelins-and-stingers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEAR UKRAINE’S BORDER — Some 14 wide-bodied aircraft transported a bristling array of Javelin antitank missiles, rocket launchers, guns and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone enthusiasts sign up to repel forces...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-technology-business-europe-47dfea7579cedfe65a70296eb0188212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In better times, Ukrainian drone enthusiasts flew their gadgets into the sky to photograph weddings, fertilize soybean fields or race other drones for fun. Now some are risking their lives by forming a volunteer drone force to help their country repel the Russian invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN YANKS BROADCAST</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-cnn-to-stop-broadcasting-in-russia-will-continue-to-monitor-the-situation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia amid the invasion of Ukraine, according to a tweet from CNN senior media reporter Oliver Darcy. Darcy tweeted that a CNN spokesperson has said that the cable network "will stop broadcasting in Russia while we continue to evaluate the situation and our next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKY NEWS' harrowing account of violent ambush...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/sky-news-teams-harrowing-account-of-their-violent-ambush-in-ukraine-this-week-12557585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, near Kyiv, chief correspondent Stuart Ramsay and his team were attacked. Camera operator Richie Mockler took two rounds to his body armour, Stuart was wounded. Their experience illustrates the scale of the mayhem and violence as Russia's invasion enters a new and deadlier phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO MORE top commanders killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/politics/17847821/two-more-russian-top-commanders-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO more of Vladimir Putin’s top military chiefs have been killed after personally charging to the battlefield to rescue their stalled invasion. As well as sniping General Andrei Su…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Incapable of Complex Operations?</title>
      <link>https://rusi.org/explore-our-research/publications/rusi-defence-systems/russian-air-force-actually-incapable-complex-air-operations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rusi.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a week into the Russian invasion of Ukraine, the Russian Air Force has yet to commence large-scale operations. Inactivity in the first few days could be ascribed to various factors, but the continued absence of major air operations now raises serious capability questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS defense reporter challenges war comments on air...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-arts-and-entertainment-army-tucker-carlson-europe-7d0f7212e07ecb8657f3e94b851710db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fox News national security correspondent Jennifer Griffin couldn't hold back when following a retired U.S. Army colonel on the air recently, saying she barely had time to correct all of his “distortions.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Deer may have passed Covid to person...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/article/first-potential-case-of-deer-to-human-covid-transmission-found</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus is widely circulating in white-tailed deer. Until now, no humans are known to have been infected by deer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Lessons in Humanity From Malfunctioning Robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/lessons-in-humanity-from-a-malfunctioning-robot/ar-AAUCPKL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Tall People At Greater Risk Of Colon Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/tall-risk-for-colorectal-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists report tall adults have a greater risk of developing colorectal cancer or malignant colon polyps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Protectionism Spreading as Hungary Bans Grain Exports...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/governments-step-protect-food-supplies-162829874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Governments around the world are taking steps to safeguard domestic food supplies after Russia’s invasion of Ukraine roiled trade and sent prices of key staples soaring.Most Read from BloombergRussian Forces Occupy Site of Nuclear Plant as Fire ContainedUkraine Update: Russian Troops Occupy Nuclear Plant SiteUkraine Update: Russia Blocks Facebook as Media Crackdown WidensRussia’s Rating Cut to Junk; Talks on Tap: Ukraine UpdateWall Street Is Pouncing on Russia’s Cheap Corporate De</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War images he doesn't want his people to see...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/ukraine-war-pictures-vladimir-putin-26384495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING GRAPHIC IMAGES – President Vladimir Putin is drastically altering the picture of the war in Ukraine to Russian civilians, according to a Norwegian international affairs researcher</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P Dow Jones will drop Russian stocks from indices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/04/sp-dow-is-removing-all-russia-stocks-from-indices-stripping-country-of-emerging-market-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;S&amp;P Dow Jones Indices said Friday it is removing all stocks listed and/or domiciled in Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterinarian Shortage Hits Crisis Levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pet-care-lures-private-equity-5b72f26d-2d54-4d62-92f0-5ef3584d7ce8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID pet boom is unleashing more opportunities for investment across the burgeoning veterinary care industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On eve of D.C. arrival, 'Freedom Convoy' picks up more cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/convoy-picks-cars-anti-ukraine-talking-points-ahead-washington-arrival-rcna18716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American offshoot of the “Freedom Convoy” is staging in Hagerstown, Maryland, on Friday and ramping up for its final protest somewhere in Washington, D.C., on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA BANS FACEBOOK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/04/russia-blocks-access-to-facebook.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook previously said it refused to comply with Russia's request to stop labeling or fact-checking state-affiliated media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida poised to limit abortions as Supremes mull Roe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-us-supreme-court-health-florida-ron-desantis-b94e54a0da65afede67582a867afebfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Gov. Ron DeSantis is expected to sign a 15-week abortion ban into law after Florida's legislature joined the trend of Republican-led states anticipating a U.S. Supreme Court decision that could sharply limit abortion rights in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Biden and Alone in Rural America...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/03/04/pennsylvania-rural-democrats-trump-neighbors-00008915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rural Democrats suffer in silence, abandoned by a party that they fear has stopped fighting to win the places where they live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-year-old sneaks on to plane, travels 1,700 miles before anyone notices...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/nation/2022/03/9-year-old-sneaks-on-to-plane-travels-nearly-1700-miles-before-anyone-notices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm not even mad. That's amazing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approval Surges 8 Points Following State of Union...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/new-poll-biden-approval-surges-8-points-following-state-of-the-union-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's approval surged 8 points in one poll following his State of the Union speech, and other data indicate the potential for a wider polling bounce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC halts work in Russia over 'fake news' jail terms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220304-bbc-halts-work-in-russia-over-fake-news-jail-terms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BBC announced Friday that it was halting its journalists' work in Russia after lawmakers moved to impose harsh jail terms for publishing "fake news" about the army as part of efforts to muffle di…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIANS SEIZE NUKE PLANT</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/russia-ukraine-nuclear-plant-shelling-fire-invasion-putin-rcna18685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze at the Zaporizhzhia plant, in Ukraine’s southeast, was extinguished early Friday but not before it spread fears of catastrophic fallout across the continent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTS:  Russian troops raping Ukrainian women...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4822326/russian-troops-accused-of-raping-numerous-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN troops have been accused of raping “numerous” women as they rampage through Ukrainian cities. As the war rages on for a ninth day, Ukraine’s foreign minister Dmytro Kuleba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton to Resume Leadership Summits Put on Hold Since 2016...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/bill-clinton-to-host-leadership-summit-for-first-time-since-2016/ar-AAUC33z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky survives 3 assassination attempts...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/volodymyr-zelensky-survives-3-kremlin-26386610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of 400 mercenaries from the Kremlin-backed Wagner group and Chechen special forces were reportedly sent to Ukraine up to five weeks ago to 'decapitate' the Ukrainian government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bronx Bishop uses rap to draw faithful...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/finding-faith-bronx-bishop-breaking-barriers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Auxiliary Bishop Joseph Espaillat is not only the youngest Bishop in the U.S., but he is the first Dominican to reach that rank as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions doses of covid vax dumped as demand plummets...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/covid-vaccine-demand-falls-states-left-with-huge-stockpiles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the demand to get vaccines collapses in many areas, states are scrambling to use doses before they expire. From some of the least vaccinated states (Indiana and North Dakota) to some of the most vaccinated states (New Jersey and Vermont), health departments are trying to find providers that can use them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA rolls out program that sends mental health workers to 911 calls...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/la-city-county-roll-pilot-130040228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles announces launch of mental health response teams</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  HYPER-PARTICAN HELLSCAPE OF USA...</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/state-of-disunion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What cancer hecklers, "USA!" chanters, George Packer, and Ray Charles tell us about our country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Facing Child Porn Charges In Texas Over 'CUTIES'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/netflix-cuties-child-porn-charges-lawsuit-texas-1234970827/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Backed against the wall, Netflix wants a Texas District Attorney stopped from hitting the streamer with child pornography charges over the coming-of-age drama Cuties. “Netflix brings this Com…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Sidesteps Calls to Take a Stand on Florida's 'Dont Say Gay' Bill Despite Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-dont-say-gay-bill-response-statement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The biggest impact we can have in creating a more inclusive world is through the inspiring content we produce," Disney said in response to protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUMAN JUNK POLLUTES MOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/now-we-re-just-throwing-trash-at-the-moon/ar-AAUCdbU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The agent and the comic: Fight for Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/volodymyr-zelensky-tells-putin-im-26382843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an address to the Russian leader, the Ukraine president Volodymyr Zelensky urged Putin to "get off our land" amid claims a convoy of Russian military vehicles outside Kyiv has hardly moved in three days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He 'Was Responsible' for Capitol Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/breaking-bill-barr-tells-lester-holt-that-trump-was-responsible-for-jan-6th-capitol-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Barr revealed to Lester Holt that he believes former President Donald Trump was responsible for the attack on the Capitol on January 6th.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN'S ROBO-BALLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/vladimir-putins-war-gadget-robo-26387894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has a lot of high-tech military gadgets up its sleeve, but one in particular stands out - high-tech 'robo-balls' which can be used to grab secret intel from urban warzones around the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia accused of nuclear terrorism as world looks on aghast...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2642730?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin was denounced for his “recklessness” after Ukraine said that Russian forces attacked a nuclear power plant, raising the stakes in the nine-day-old war and prompting calls for an even more robust response to the Kremlin’s aggression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unprecedented killing': Deadliest season for Yellowstone wolves...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/2022/03/04/yellowstone-wolves-hunting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spike in wolf hunting around Yellowstone National Park has made this area the center of a political controversy over how to manage the predator across the West. The issue is also dividing neighbors and relatives who live at the park's edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iguana killers: Hunts around S Florida backyards become tourist attraction...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/iguana-killers-hunts-around-south-florida-backyards-become-a-tourist-attraction/article_c60d8dc7-8fa4-5284-855a-5a487c00c01a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Standing in a boat in suburban Fort Lauderdale, Chris Whitaker aimed a .25-caliber air rifle at a large green iguana on a canal bank and squeezed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia business ties to West took 30 years to build, week to shatter...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russias-business-ties-to-the-west-took-30-years-to-build-and-one-week-to-shatter/ar-AAUBSrl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court reinstates death sentence for Boston Marathon bomber...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/04/supreme-court-reinstates-death-sentence-for-boston-marathon-bomber-dzhokhar-tsarnaev.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United State Supreme Cour reinstated the death penalty sentence imposed on Boston Marathon bomber Dzhokhar Tsarnaev.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA city, county roll out pilot program that sends mental health workers to 911 calls...</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/news/la-city-county-roll-pilot-130040656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles announces launch of mental health response teams</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin actions trigger long-buried fears of nuclear war for generations of Americans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putins-actions-trigger-long-buried-133058950.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Old anxieties came flooding back last week as the Russian president launched a massive military invasion of Ukraine, while warning potential foes who intervened of "consequences greater than any you have ever faced in history."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Women Taking Up Arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjbndq/ukrainian-women-soldiers-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women have played a vital role in Ukraine’s national defense since 2014, as the number of female recruits has grown in response to Russian aggression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EUPHORIA' Crew, Actors Speak Out Against 'Toxic' Production...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/euphoria-season-2-crew-and-background-actors-speak-out-against-sam-levinsons-toxic-production</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources reveal that Season 2’s shoot was hellish, resulting in background actors “dropping like flies,” a number of alleged SAG-AFTRA violations, and a union rep being sent to set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA: Academy Infighting Mounting Over Oscars Categories Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/oscars-infighting-over-excluding-categories-1235103324/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hollywood Reporter's awards columnist Scott Feinberg provides an update on the firestorm over the decision to present eight awards prior to the live Oscars telecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Roger Stone tapes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/596850-new-evidence-details-roger-stones-efforts-against-2020-electionwapo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New video evidence from a documentary in the making about Roger Stone offers new details about his involvement in efforts to undermine the results of the 2020 presidential election,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan leaders try to calm fears over Ukraine invasion but citizens worry their island will be next...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/taiwans-leaders-try-to-calm-fears-over-ukraine-invasion-but-citizens-worry-their-island-will-be-next/ar-AAUBDWa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO WARNS WILL GET WORSE</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/russia-ukraine-power-plant-fire-war-news-latest-vladimir-putin-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the U.S. accuses Russia of a "war crime" with its attack on a nuclear power plant, NATO makes a "painful decision" to reject Ukraine's calls for a no-fly zone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk warns may be spying on Starlink internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4820166/elon-musk-starlink-satellites-russia-spying-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has warned Ukrainians using his emergency satellite internet that there is a “high” chance Russia will try to spy on them. The billionaire donated a truck load of dishes to th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public executions?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4818364/vladimir-putin-ukraine-public-executions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN spooks have reportedly drawn up plans to carry out public executions in Ukrainian cities. The Federal Security Service, Russia’s intelligence agency, is said to be ready to carry out summar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused of Nuclear 'Terrorism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/russia-accused-of-nuclear-terrorism-as-world-looks-on-aghast-1.1732470</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin was denounced for his “recklessness” after Ukraine said that Russian forces attacked a nuclear power plant, raising the stakes in the nine-day-old war and prompting calls for an even more robust response to the Kremlin’s aggression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton to Resume Leadership Summits Put on Hold Since 2016...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bill-clinton-to-resume-leadership-summits-put-on-hold-since-2016-1.1732430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Bill Clinton plans to convene his signature gathering of business, government and philanthropic leaders in New York this September, according to a letter sent Friday to supporters of his charitable foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London's Billionaire Playground Challenged by Reality of War...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/london-billionaire-playground-challenged-reality-093020335.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergRussian Forces Occupy Site of Nuclear Plant as Fire ContainedUkraine Update: Russian Troops Occupy Nuclear Plant SiteRussia’s Rating Cut to Junk; Talks on Tap: Ukraine UpdateGerman Authorities Said to Deny Seizing Usmanov YachtResignation Sets In as Russians Face Their New Economic RealityFrom King Constantine II of Greece and Saudi Arabia’s Sheikh Yamani to Russian billionaire Roman Abramovich, London’s mansions and penthouses have been a preferred haven f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Roger Stone tapes...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/interactive/2022/roger-stone-documentary-capitol-riot-trump-election/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCKET SMASHES MOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-60596449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Moon's far side should now have a new crater after being hit by a large chunk of space junk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tearful goodbyes at train station...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-europe-d9216cfa7cac9ec25ef47f0121c4a4a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — A woman crouches down in the doorway of a blue and yellow train at a station in Kyiv, Ukraine's embattled capital city. Her husband stands on the platform below and cranes his neck up for a kiss that both hope will not be their last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates leaving gangs, stripping tats for jobs, better lives...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-chicago-gangs-76872f04ab5b651fddbd29de108946aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEATON, Ill. (AP) — Under penalty of a beating or death, Erik Eck pledged at age 13 to adhere to the Latin Kings' first rule: “Once a King, always a King.” Tattoos that bedeck his entire body express his fealty forever to one of the largest gangs in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine refugees 1.2 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenationalnews.com/world/europe/2022/03/04/ukraines-refugees-un-map-shows-12million-have-fled-and-where-they-are-heading/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UN fears more than 4 million will eventually leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky invokes Judaism to rally support for Ukrainian cause...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220304-zelensky-invokes-judaism-to-rally-support-for-ukrainian-cause</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With online posts in Hebrew and appeals to Jews to "cry out" in response to Russia's invasion, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has invoked his faith to rally support for his embattled country.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin backs jail time for 'fake' news...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220304-russia-backs-jail-time-for-fake-army-news-restricts-media-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian lawmakers moved Friday to impose harsh jail terms for publishing "fake news" about the army, which a senior lawmaker said will apply to foreigners too, as Moscow moves to muffle dissent over…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A.'s most extravagant mansion sells for less than half list price...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/l-most-extravagant-mansion-sells-003823146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of construction, a foreclosure and a bankruptcy, the Bel-Air mega-mansion known as The One has sold at auction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail carrier allegedly beat turkey to death. Was it self-defense?</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/a-california-mail-carrier-allegedly-beat-a-turkey-to-death-was-it-self-defense/article_e0ac3ca7-1dff-5695-875d-43a7604e03b2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — California wildlife authorities and the U.S. Postal Service are investigating reports that a mail carrier beat a wild turkey to death in Sacramento County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe awakens to Russian threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Europe-awakens-to-the-Russian-threat-16976696.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Russian money, energy and military strength held Europe in thrall. But as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Glass Of Wine WIth Dinner Slashes Diabetes Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/wine-with-dinner-diabetes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Tulane University report that drinking wine with dinner could actually help stave off diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rheumatoid arthritis drug could be lifesaver for severely ill COVID patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-covid-rheumatoid-arthritis-drug-reduces-death-coronavirus-severe-illness-20220304-sa3fyxptfnef7oj6bpsgrkueem-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anti-inflammatory drug normally used for rheumatoid arthritis could turn out to be a lifesaver for people hospitalized with COVID, a large clinical trial indicates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills store admits to using safe deposit boxes to launder drug money...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/beverly-hills-store-pleads-guilty-to-laundering-drug-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The store's owners admitted to recruiting drug traffickers as customers and subsequently running their money through the business, a.k.a. "cleaning" the currency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>275 grave stones vandalized at TX cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/about-275-grave-stones-vandalized-at-texas-cemetery/article_105cb9cf-739e-5312-bf2b-cf7f21f14fd1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 275 grave stones at the century-old Waxahachie City Cemetery — just south of Dallas — were vandalized earlier this week, including the gravesite of one of the city’s first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham blowback after calling for Putin assassination...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Lindsey-Graham-hit-with-bipartisan-blowback-after-16976764.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., was sharply criticized by fellow lawmakers on both sides of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The agent and the comic: Putin, Zelensky in fight for Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220304-the-agent-and-the-comic-putin-zelensky-in-fight-for-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One is a former comic actor who became president in 2019 as a political novice. The other a one-time KGB agent now in power for over two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians pack trains into Finland...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220304-russians-pack-trains-into-finland-as-sanctions-bite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's one of the few remaining routes from Russia to the EU: trains to Finland are packed with Russians fearful that now is their last chance to escape the impact of Western sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do You Hide 500-Foot Yacht?</title>
      <link>https://techilive.in/where-do-you-hide-a-500-foot-yacht-asking-for-an-oligarch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techilive.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s one thing to stuff cash under your mattress or move millions into an offshore bank account. Hiding a mega-yacht from multiple governments and a global mob of private citizens is a bit more tricky. To intensify sanctions on Russia and further throttle the finances of the Kremlin’s uber-wealthy allies, the Biden administration this week […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee getting closer to ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2022/03/03/jan-6-committee-work-shifts-into-new-gear-getting-closer-to-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jan. 6 select committee has stated it has a “good-faith belief” that former President Donald Trump may have committed criminal acts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: $807 million in oligarch yachts seized...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4817890/vladimir-putins-cronies-have-superyachts-seized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN billionaire Alisher Usmanov was slapped on Britain’s sanctions list last night as Vladimir Putin’s cronies had their beloved superyachts seized. Usmanov, who has been bankrolling Everton FC…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rage met by revulsion -- first Jan. 6 trial shows family, nation torn by The Don...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Rage-met-by-revulsion-first-Jan-6-trial-shows-16976509.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A father's runaway political rage and his son's revulsion at lawlessness enthralled a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peer pressure ending mask usage in schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Peer-pressure-is-ending-mask-usage-in-schools-16976598.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chelsea Ellingson hopes that her children keep masks in their backpacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS rushes to hire 10,000 workers but giant backlog to persist...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/IRS-rushes-to-hire-10-000-workers-but-giant-16976309.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Internal Revenue Service plans to hire 10,000 employees in a push to cut...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine flagship sunk to avoid capture by Russian troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.pravda.com.ua/eng/news/2022/03/4/7328077/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pravda.com.ua&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hetman Sahaidachny flagship of the Ukrainian Navy has been sunk to prevent the Russian occupying forces from using it, including for sabotage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New evidence shows Trump was told many times there was no voter fraud -- but kept saying it anyway...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/New-evidence-shows-Trump-was-told-many-times-16975783.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A data expert for former President Donald Trump's campaign told him bluntly not long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EUROPE AT RISK'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10575179/Russian-troops-fire-Ukrainian-civilians-protecting-Europes-largest-nuclear-plant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson led a chorus of condemnation this morning over Russia's attack on the Zaporizhzhia nuclear plant in southern Ukraine overnight, which sparked a fire the burned for several hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'BATMAN' SET FOR $100+ MILLION OPENING...</title>
      <link>https://www.boxofficemojo.com/article/ed3748725764/?ref_=bo_ne_nl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Humans Will Live In Metaverse Soon', Claims Zuckerberg. What About Reality?</title>
      <link>https://in.mashable.com/tech/28254/humans-will-live-in-metaverse-soon-claims-mark-zuckerberg-what-about-reality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meta intends to spend the next five to ten years creating an immersive virtual environment that includes fragrance, touch, and sound to allow users to lose themselves in virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACE JUNK SET TO SMASH MOON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-science-business-china-moon-7044a26d9b4b43dc44e961c250186f26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The moon is about to get walloped by 3 tons of space junk, a punch that will carve out a crater that could fit several semitractor-trailers. The leftover rocket will smash into the far side of the moon at 5,800 mph (9,300 kph) on Friday, away from telescopes’ prying eyes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
