<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UK to ban junk food advertising online...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/jun/23/uk-to-ban-junk-food-advertising-online-and-before-9pm-on-tv-from-2023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prohibition of adverts for products high in fat, salt and sugar could cost broadcasters more than £200m annually in revenue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I WAS WHACKD'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3145281/john-mcafee-suicide-whackd-tattoo-didnt-kill-himself-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHN McAfee had a “Whackd” tattoo and once claimed that if he was ever found dead by suicide that he did not kill himself. He posted a picture of the tattoo in a 2019 tweet in which he …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation into deaths of girls found in Florida canal focuses on woman with Bible...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/investigation-into-deaths-of-girls-found-in-florida-canal-focuses-on-woman-with-bible/ar-AALmEJ5?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAUDERHILL, Fla. — The day after two girls’ bodies were discovered in a canal, police canvassed the Lauderhill neighborhood across the water asking for information about a woman whose behavior was so alarming, she was detained by officers and sent away in an ambulance. The woman appears to be at the center of the investigation Wednesday. According to neighbors interviewed by the South Florida ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All UK arrivals in EU should be quarantined, says Merkel...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1453728/Angela-Merkel-news-Covid-quarantine-UK-EU-arrivals-travel-latest-Germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANGELA MERKEL has cracked down on Britain and insisted visitors from the UK arriving in the European Union should isolate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAX EVASION;  CRYPTO FRAUD</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/john-mcafee-found-dead-after-spanish-court-oks-extradition-for-tax-crimes-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antivirus software company founder John McAfee was found dead in a Spanish jail Wednesday after a court approved his extradition to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC FINDS MORE HEART INFLAMMATION AFTER VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/cdc-reports-more-than-1200-cases-of-rare-heart-inflammation-after-covid-vaccine-shots.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is still a rare event," Dr. Tom Shimabukuro said at the meeting. For both vaccines combined, there were 12.6 heart inflammation cases per million doses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second 'Oath Keepers' pleads guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/06/23/nation/second-alleged-oath-keepers-member-us-capitol-during-insurrection-pleads-guilty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graydon Young’s plea was one of three on Wednesday by defendants charged in the Capitol breach as prosecutors seek to build momentum on nearly 500 federal cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPANISH PRISON 'SUICIDE'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/23/john-mcafee-dies-by-suicide-inside-prison-in-barcelona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McAfee, the founder of a antivirus software company, was arrested in October of last year and awaiting extradition when he was found dead, police sources told the newspaper El Pais.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes rule for foul-mouthed cheerleader in student free speech case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/supreme-court-cursing-cheerleader-first-amendment-981374cd3adc0e73274d7d33c29a9e0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the case of the cursing cheerleader, the Supreme Court notched a victory for the free speech rights of students Wednesday, siding with a high school student whose vulgar social media post got her kicked off the junior varsity squad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCAFEE DEAD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/john-mcafee-dead-spain-prison-extradition-c39cc0f375a975946fb83b60cc2bf3d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — John McAfee, the creator of McAfee antivirus software, was found dead in his jail cell near Barcelona in an apparent suicide Wednesday, hours after a Spanish court approved his extradition to the United States to face tax charges punishable by decades in prison, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAfee's INSTAGRAM posts 'Q' pic AFTER his death...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3146043/john-mcafee-death-qanon-conspiracy-instagram/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHN McAfee’s Instagram account posted a mysterious “Q” just minutes after his jail “suicide” death was reported. The antivirus pioneer reportedly killed himself after…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famity 'won't let her get married or have babies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3145981/britney-spears-wants-marry-have-baby-blocked-abusive-conservatorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears said she wants to marry and take out her IUD to have another baby. However, the 39-year-old claimed she is unable to grow her family because her “conservator won’t let he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 1% of Americans have 16 times more wealth than bottom 50%!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/how-much-wealth-top-1percent-of-americans-have.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top 1% of Americans control $41.52 trillion, according to the Federal Reserve. That's roughly 16 times more wealth than the bottom 50%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY DEMANDS FREEDOM...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/britney-spears-speaks-court-hearing-conservatorship-los-angeles-1234780358/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I would honestly like to be able to sue my family,” Britney Spears said Wednesday via telephone to a downtown Los Angeles courtroom during a hearing over her on her longtime and restrictive conser…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaks Her Silence During Hearing: 'Want to Sue My Family'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/britney-spears-speaks-out-at-conservatorship-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears finally spoke out about her conservatorship during a Wednesday, June 23, hearing — read more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This conservatorship is abusive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/snyde/ny-britney-spears-slams-conservatorship-at-hearing-20210623-vheianzm3bfi5frhr4yzx5w5pu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears slammed her conservatorship during an emotional and unprecedented court hearing Wednesday, telling her judge she feels “enslaved” by the stringent structure and wants to get married and have a baby with her boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY ASKS FOR FREEDOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Spears-set-to-make-rare-remarks-to-16266946.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Britney Spears asked a judge Wednesday to end court conservatorship...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No jail time in 1st riot sentence; Oath Keeper pleads guilty...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-capitol-siege-government-and-politics-87122373383f8d3f3c9f0b2ba3fa57d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indiana woman on Wednesday became the first defendant to be sentenced in the Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol and avoided time behind bars, while a member of the Oath Keepers extremist group pleaded guilty in a conspiracy case and agreed to cooperate with prosecutors in a major step forward for the massive investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE CHINESE PROPAGANDA CAMPAIGN...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/how-china-uses-youtube-and-twitter-to-spread-its-propaganda-version-of-life-for-uyghurs-in-xinjiang</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of videos of Uyghurs denying abuses against their community are showing up on Twitter and YouTube. They’re part of an elaborate influence campaign by Chinese officials to counter reports of human rights violations in Xinjiang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE legal worries grow as long-dormant French case moves ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/france-legal-action-case-apple-app-store-developers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of French startups joins a case that could change the way the tech giant runs its App Store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX POLL: McConaughey 'most favorable'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/politics/1001887/matthew-mcconaughey-has-the-best-favorability-numbers-of-any-potential-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NRA President Duped Into Delivering Fake Graduation Speech to Empty Chairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-former-nra-president-duped-by-parkland-parents-into-delivering-fake-graduation-speech-to-empty-chairs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NRA president David Keene accepted an invitation to address what he thought was going to be its graduating class of 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans form group on 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-business-climate-climate-change-e1f0f572a7b5841bb6141456776bafec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Utah Rep. John Curtis says he's tired of hearing that Republicans — his party colleagues — don't care about climate change or slowing global warming. A former Provo mayor who has served in Congress since 2017, Curtis says Republicans can push for serious climate solutions while holding fast to conservative values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhunt for escaped con captivates Brazil, terrifies town...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/manhunt-for-escaped-con-captivates-brazil-terrifies-town/ar-AALmx2J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looks like a scene straight out of Hollywood: hundreds of police sweep the countryside looking in vain for an escaped convict, search dogs scampering as helicopters and drones hover overhead. But the massive manhunt under way for Lazaro Barbosa, a twice-escaped inmate and suspect in a quadruple murder, is all too real for the small Brazilian town of Cocalzinho de Goias. Barbosa, 32, has become the most-wanted criminal in Brazil since June 9,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY confirms 'god of mischief' bisexual...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/news/1001883/loki-director-says-it-was-very-important-to-confirm-the-character-is-bisexual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT APPROVED EXTRADITION TO USA</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9718567/Antivirus-pioneer-John-McAfee-dies-bars-suspected-suicide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McAfee was found dead this afternoon in his cell in Brians 2 Prison in Barcelona, with officials saying that the early investigation points to a suicide, Spanish newspapers reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Greek bishops doused with acid in 'act of revenge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3144454/seven-greek-bishops-acid-revenge-priest-kicked-out-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIEST has been arrested after throwing acid on seven bishops who were attending a disciplinary hearing against him. The shocking attack that took place at an Athens monastery has left three of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOPPING: COMCAST EYES VIACOMCBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/viacomcbs-roku-shares-jump-on-report-that-comcast-is-considering-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comcast chief Brian Roberts is exploring new options for the company's push into streaming, according to The Wall Street Journal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jabs linked to 4 different skin reactions...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15370614/covid-vaccine-linked-skin-reactions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID vaccines are essential to beat the virus – but they can cause side effects after having the jab. These are mostly nothing to be concerned about, but can cause discomfort. 🔵 Read our cor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JILL JEERED!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3142111/jill-biden-booed-nashville-tennessee-vaccination-rates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JILL Biden received boos on stage in Nashville on Tuesday as she slammed Tennessee’s low vaccination rate and insisted “you’re booing yourselves.” The First Lady was visiting a pop-up vaccine site …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE CHINESE PROPAGANDA CAMPAIGN...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2021/06/22/technology/xinjiang-uyghurs-china-propaganda.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of videos posted look like unfiltered glimpses of life for Uyghurs, but taken together, the videos begin to reveal clues of a broader influence campaign orchestrated by the Chinese government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Money Paying for Traffic Fines...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/california-bailout-money-is-paying-for-traffic-fines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is expected to extend their eviction moratorium, while simultaneously using borrowed government money to subsidize the landlords they are hurting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Little Hedge Fund Taking Down Big Oil...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/23/the-little-hedge-fund-taking-down-big-oil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. On the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face-Tracking Ad Tablets in Back of UBERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dbyvz/this-company-is-putting-face-tracking-ad-tablets-in-the-back-of-ubers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As drivers struggle to make ends meet, companies are eager to take advantage of the situation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA yoga, wellness and spirituality community's QAnon problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-06-23/covid-adds-to-california-yoga-wellness-qanon-problem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A world that has long embraced love, light and acceptance is now making room for something else: QAnon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUBWAY tuna sandwiches found to contain no tuna DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/lab-tests-no-tuna-subway-sandwiches</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Times lab tests found no real tuna in Subway sandwiches following lawsuit claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Ending Platform Monopolies Act'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/apple-apps-google-search-amazon-basics-drastic-changes-bipartisan-house-antitrust-bill-jayapal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new antitrust bill aimed at reducing conflicts of interest on online marketplaces could drastically decrease Big Tech companies giving preference to their own products and services and potentially even break up the tech giants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns of 'explosive' surge ...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/06/23/russia-warns-of-explosive-virus-surge-a74317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citing increases in cases in all regions, Deputy Prime Minister Tatiana Golikova called for stronger restrictive measures and more inoculations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French tycoon stirs resistance with right-wing media shake-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.indopremier.com/ipotnews/newsDetail.php?news_id=1521203&amp;group_news=ALLNEWS&amp;news_date=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indopremier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb-targeting cat burglar suspects go on trial in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/celeb-targeting-cat-burglar-suspects-145446244.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gang of cat burglars accused of scaling buildings to steal millions in jewellery, fashion items and other valuables from the rich and famous, including Paris Saint-Germain football star Thiago Silva, went on trial in the French capital on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Berners-Lee defends auction of NFT representing web's source code...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jun/23/tim-berners-lee-defends-auction-nft-web-source-code</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creator of the world wide web says digital asset is ‘totally aligned with the values of the web’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists identify 29 planets where aliens could observe Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/23/scientists-identify-29-planets-where-aliens-could-observe-earth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers estimate 29 habitable planets are positioned to see Earth transit and intercept human broadcasts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sometimes necessary to protect superfluous in order to preserve necessary'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-sides-with-high-school-cheerleader-in-free-speech-dispute-over-profane-snapchat-rant/ar-AALmcTu?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court ruled 8 to 1 that the punishment was too severe, although it declined to say schools never have a role in disciplining students for off-campus speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Flies Over Times Square On Hoverboard; NYPD Investigating...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/man-flying-a-hoverboard-stuns-spectators-in-times-square-67856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunter Kowald says he got permission to fly the aircraft beforehand: "I spent years on this thing to make this happen, at least to do it safely and properly."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insults fly in rainbow row ahead of Germany-Hungary Euro 2020 clash...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/germany-turns-rainbow-coloured-protest-095711805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU leaders and Hungary traded barbs over Budapest's anti-LGBTQ law on Wednesday as Germany staged a defiant display of rainbows following UEFA's refusal to light Munich's Euro 2020 stadium in rainbow colours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain court agrees to extradite McAfee founder to USA; Wanted for tax evasion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spain-court-agrees-extradite-mcafee-144932343.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's National Court said Wednesday it had approved the extradition of antivirus software pioneer John McAfee to the United States where he is wanted for tax evasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist wins Buffalo primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/socalist-candiate-buffalo-victory-9f1e74c4-55ae-4eeb-86c8-59cdab5c497d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India Walton's win is likely to precede a general election victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are TWITTER trolls mentally ill?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/06/are-twitter-trolls-mentally-ill/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A disproportionate amount of bad online behaviour stems from psychological issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S GIVING OUT SHOTS!</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/06/22/mcdonalds-partnering-cdph-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some local McDonald’s restaurants are working with the Department of Public Health to give out free vaccines with a menu item.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nature bites back: Animals push human boundaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210622-nature-bites-back-animals-push-human-boundaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nature bites back: Animals push human boundaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40 cows escape slaughterhouse, 1 charges family...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ca-state-wire-los-angeles-business-c0200f2e265f514d9bb475f576bc4f8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PICO RIVERA, Calif. (AP) — Forty cows escaped a slaughterhouse and ended up in a Los Angeles suburb where one was killed after charging a family, authorities said Wednesday. The cows were reported running loose on the streets of Pico Rivera around 7:30 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shielding Scott Rudin: How Super-Producer Avoided Answering for Abusive Behavior for Decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/scott-rudin-abusive-behavior-1234972177/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In September 2019, Eric Emauni was rolling calls when his boss, Scott Rudin, ordered him to get media mogul Barry Diller on the line. Immediately. So the assistant did just that. The only problem w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope meets Spider-Man at weekly audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210623-pope-francis-meets-spider-man-at-weekly-audience</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis meets Spider-Man at weekly audience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook called Pelosi with 'warning' about antitrust bills...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/news/1001852/tim-cook-reportedly-called-pelosi-to-deliver-a-warning-about-congress-antitrust-bills</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump clash ahead: DeSantis positions self as Republican future...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/559787-with-a-direct-mail-piece-ron-desantis-positions-himself-as-gops-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mailer proves that DeSantis is a brilliant player, positioning himself as the GOP’s future while only lightly kissing the ring of his “creator.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIANA BONES: Harrison Ford Injures Shoulder Rehearsing Fight Scene...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/harrison-ford-indiana-jones-5-injures-shoulder-rehearsing-fight-scene-production-shoot-around-recovery-1234780040/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Harrison Ford hurt himself rehearsing a fight scene in Indiana Jones 5, sources tell Deadline.  The extent of his injury wasn’t immediately known, but it involves his shoulder. Dir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Redneck Rave' descends into chaos: Man has throat slit, another impaled, woman choked...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9716847/Redneck-Rave-Kentucky-descends-chaos-48-people-charged.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of people attended the five-day Redneck Rave festival at Blue Holler Offroad Park in the small town of Mammoth Cave, 90 miles south of Louisville, last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents arrested as school board meeting descends into violence over trans rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9715305/Loudoun-County-Virginia-school-board-CUTS-public-comment-transgender-policies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;County residents arrived early to pack the auditorium as 259 residents signed up to speak before debates became so heated at least two men were arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SEXY BEASTS' trailer reveals new NETFLIX dating show...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/sexy-beasts-trailer-reveals-new-netflix-dating-show-and-you-kinda-just-have-to-see-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You couldn't make it up. Except that's exactly what they've done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKEA Juneteenth menu with watermelon, fried chicken sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/22/ikea-juneteenth-menu-of-watermelon-fried-chicken-sparks-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attempt to honor Juneteenth has intensely backfired for one Georgia Ikea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiji spike 'wake-up call' for Pacific Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/covid-19-fiji-spike-wake-up-call-red-cross-15073418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Red Cross called for faster vaccine rollouts in vulnerable Pacific island nations Wednesday as a record Covid-19 surge threatens to overload ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark sightings, attacks up and down East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/resilience/natural-disasters/559594-shark-sightings-and-attacks-up-and-down-east</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;None have been fatal so far this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD Prof Says 'Alien Craft' May Have Dropped Sensors...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/harvard-alien-spacecraft-sensors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"But rather than simply wonder about possible scenarios, we should collect better scientific data and clarify the nature of UAP."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was preparing for 'civil war,' feds say. Now he faces up to 30 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-was-preparing-for-a-coming-civil-war-feds-say-now-he-faces-up-to-30-years-in-prison/ar-AALlx25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Miller, an extremist known for spewing racist and anti-Semitic rhetoric on social media, pleaded guilty Tuesday after the FBI found ammunition and an unregistered firearm in his Florida home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials, the Wealthiest Generation?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/millennials-the-wealthiest-generation-believe-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials, the Wealthiest Generation? Believe It</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Space Travel Company Offering Flights -- on Balloons!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/how-can-i-go-to-space-space-perspective-balloons-launch-2024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Space Travel Company Is Offering Cheaper, Safer Flights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia 'fires warning shots, drops bombs near Royal Navy in Black Sea'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15369390/russia-warning-shots-royal-navy-black-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN vessel fired warning shots British warships while a fighter jet dropped “warning bombs”, Vladimir Putin’s defence ministry has claimed. Moscow has alleged the Russian sh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffett gives away another $4.1 billion, resigns as trustee at Gates Foundation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/warren-buffett-gives-away-another-4point1-billion-resigns-as-trustee-at-gates-foundation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Trump talked of COVID killing Bolton...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-john-bolton-covid-nightmare-scenario-6c34e67a-3872-449e-b927-8fa89b829061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Nightmare Scenario" by Damian Paletta and Yasmeen Abutaleb is out next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rembrandt's Damaged Masterpiece Whole Again -- With AI's Help...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/23/rembrandts-damaged-masterpiece-is-whole-again-with-a-i-s-help/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMSTERDAM — Rembrandt’s “The Night Watch” has been a national icon in the Netherlands ever since it was painted in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of birds dying from mystery illness across several states...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-birds-dying-mystery-illness-south-midwest-20210623-sibvwcxdjzfuhasz7o3vvuxcpu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are befuddled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo shapes up to be No-Fun Olympics with many rules, tests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tokyo-2020-tokyo-olympics-olympic-games-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-b0c7951989b4b0b61ddde7f8ec9c8429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The Tokyo Olympics, already delayed by the pandemic, are not looking like much fun: Not for athletes. Not for fans. And not for the Japanese public. They are caught between concerns about the coronavirus at a time when few are vaccinated on one side and politicians who hope to save face by holding the games and the International Olympic Committee with billions of dollars on the line on the other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SABOTAGE' AT NUKE FACILITY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-sabotage-business-media-995879deee39e4511fd756a6444d4f6c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iranian authorities have thwarted what they called a “sabotage attack” targeting a civilian nuclear facility near the country's capital, Iranian media reported Wednesday, as details about the incident remained scarce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliwa wins Republican NYC mayor primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/primary-day-2021-curtis-sliwa-wins-republican-mayoral-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guardian Angels founder Curtis Sliwa has won the Republican mayoral primary in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore police chief calls for more 'boots on ground'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/559750-baltimore-police-chief-calls-for-more-boots-on-the-ground-to-handle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore Police Commissioner Michael Harrison said Tuesday that he would like to see more “boots on the ground” and additional funding for his department amid a surge in violent crime in cities across the country.&amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 29% of Mississippians vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/two-covid-nations-delta-variant-threatens-sections-of-the-country-where-vaccination-rates-lag-212540696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emergence of the Delta variant could mean that while communities with high vaccination rates continue to return to normal, states where vaccinations lag could suddenly find themselves thrust into a new wave of infections and deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS:  Pandemic INCREASED trust in media...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-increased-trust-media-report-230104613.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has helped rebuild a little of the confidence lost in the media, and pushed news companies even more towards digital, according to the annual Reuters Institute report published Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal experts worldwide draw up 'historic' definition of ecocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/jun/22/legal-experts-worldwide-draw-up-historic-definition-of-ecocide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Draft law is intended to prosecute offences against the environment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden pitches shots for reluctant arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jill-biden-pitches-shots-for-reluctant-arms-in-trump-country/ar-AALjRTY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First lady Jill Biden traveled to the U.S. Deep South on Tuesday to encourage Covid-19 vaccinations, as the White House seeks to combat widespread hesitance to get shots in areas that are politically hostile to the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian soldier imprisoned for showing photos of testicle swastika tattoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/austrian-soldier-imprisoned-for-showing-photos-of-testicle-swastika-tattoo-671688</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The soldier said he had been very drunk when he got the swastika tattoo earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2021 covid deaths already top 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/covid-19s-global-death-toll-this-year-has-already-surpassed-2020s-count</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a drop in COVID-19 hospitalizations, cases and deaths in much of the developed world, the death toll this year has already eclipsed the total count for 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers take first step toward Big Tech regulation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-lawmakers-first-step-toward-012159187.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US lawmakers take a first step toward regulating Big Tech on Wednesday with a vote on a series of bills with potentially massive implications for large online platforms and consumers who use them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC  to review heart problems among teens...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-experts-review-heart-problems-011518309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A panel of experts convened by the top US health agency will hold a meeting Wednesday to review data surrounding more than 300 confirmed cases of heart muscle inflammation among adolescents and young adults after receiving mRNA Covid vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKE CONTROL OF 92 DOMAINS!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/notices-iran-linked-websites-seized-185255419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI (Reuters) -The U.S. Justice Department said on Tuesday it seized 36 Iranian-linked websites, many of them associated with either disinformation activities or violent organizations, taking them offline for violating U.S. sanctions. Several of the sites were back online within hours with new domain addresses. "Today, pursuant to court orders, the United States seized 33 websites used by the Iranian Islamic Radio and Television Union (IRTVU) and three websites operated by Kata’ib Hizballah (KH), in violation of U.S. sanctions," the department said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis taste future with lab-grown chicken 'food revolution'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israelis-taste-future-lab-grown-153024189.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looks like chicken and tastes like chicken, but diners in Israel are tucking into laboratory-grown "meat" that scientists claim is an environmentally friendly way to feed the world's growing population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFOWAR:  FEDS SEIZE NEWS SITES IN IRAN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/iran-middle-east-03e651ff86918c871d9e1baaa5e30e37</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — American authorities seized a range of Iran’s state-linked news website domains they accused of spreading disinformation, the U.S. Justice Department said Tuesday, a move that appeared to be a far-reaching crackdown on Iranian media amid heightened tensions between the two countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China condemns latest U.S. warship transit of Taiwan Strait...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-warship-transits-taiwan-strait-001356953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING/TAIPEI (Reuters) -China condemned the United States on Wednesday as the region's greatest security "risk creator" after a U.S. warship again sailed through the sensitive waterway that separates Taiwan from China. The U.S. Navy's 7th Fleet said the Arleigh Burke-class guided missile destroyer USS Curtis Wilbur conducted a "routine Taiwan Strait transit" on Tuesday in accordance with international law. "The ship's transit through the Taiwan Strait demonstrates the U.S. commitment to a free and open Indo-Pacific."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand reports new daily record of covid deaths...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/thailand-reports-daily-record-51-011926590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thailand reported on Wednesday a new daily record of 51 COVID-19 fatalities, bringing total deaths to 1,744 since the pandemic started last year. The country, grappling with its third and most deadly outbreak, also reported 3,174 new infections, bringing total confirmed cases to 228,539. More than 85% of new cases and deaths came after April this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand on edge after virus-infected Australian visits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-zealand-australia-lifestyle-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-aeacc7186bb1e25dc90538460a7330ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — After enjoying nearly four months without any community transmission of the coronavirus, New Zealanders were on edge Wednesday after health authorities said an infectious traveler from Australia had visited over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS BAILOUT AIRPORTS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-ea5072c5f9c7397a8b01a4876abaccbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Airports around the country will share $8 billion in federal grants to help them recover from the pandemic, which caused a steep drop in air travel and a loss of revenue that airports expect from airlines and passengers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi to create special panel to probe Jan. 6 attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-government-and-politics-b05ca57ac271dc25f1739505357028ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is signaling that she is poised to create a new committee to investigate the Jan. 6 insurrection at the Capitol, pushing closer to a partisan investigation of the attack after Senate Republicans blocked the creation of an independent probe.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
