<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CNN: Experts urge country shut down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/26/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus deaths in the US topped 1,000 four days in a row last week amid ongoing debates on the return of school and mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea scrambles to contain 'first' case...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/26/north-korea-scrambles-contain-first-coronavirus-ca/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un placed the city of Kaesong near the border with South Korea under total lockdown after a person was found there with suspected COVID-19 symptoms, saying “the vicious virus” may have entered the country, state media reported Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12% STILL Don't Wash Hands After Using Public Bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/living-dangerously-adults-still-dont-wash-hands-after-using-public-bathroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey reveals that 12% of British adults still regularly use the bathroom, both public and private, without washing their hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN +5 IN AZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/poll-biden-leads-trump-battleground-arizona-n1234888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presumptive nominee is up five points in a new NBC News/Marist poll while Democrats also enjoy double-digit lead in state's Senate contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>+12 MI...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/26/politics/cnn-poll-biden-trump-florida-arizona-michigan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 100 days remaining until Election Day, voters in three critical battleground states swing in former Vice President Joe Biden's way, according to new Arizona, Florida and Michigan CNN polls conducted by SSRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Arab country acquires new Chinese missile system...</title>
      <link>https://www.almasdarnews.com/article/first-arab-country-acquires-new-chinese-missile-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.almasdarnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT, LEBANON (9:30 A.M.) - China has started exporting the third generation of their Red Arrow-12 anti-tank systems, also known as the HJ-12. According</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sledding Athletes Taking Their Lives. Did Crashes Damage Their Brains?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/26/sledding-athletes-are-taking-their-lives-did-high-speed-crashes-damage-their-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Matthew Futterman On May 3, Pavle Jovanovic, a former bobsledder, rigged a chain to a crane he and his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Really Is Spying On You -- For China...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2020/07/25/beware-tiktok-really-is-spying-on-you-new-security-report-update-trump-pompeo-china-warning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new security report has just been published, adding substance to the U.S. threats being made against China's social media sensation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Trump Supporter Gunned Down In Drive-By Shooting In Milwaukee...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2020/07/25/black-trump-supporter-killed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating whether there was a political motive in the crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wages of Woke: How to get rich peddling 'white fragility'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/culture/the-wages-of-woke-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Robin DiAngelo, the bestselling author of White Fragility, claims to believe in accountability. DiAngelo used to list the “racial justice” organizations she donates to as part of her extensive “accountability statement,” including a monthly “land rent” paid to the Native American tribe which used to occupy Seattle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAVENS Player Alleged Victim Of Repeated Domestic Abuse By Girlfriend...</title>
      <link>https://247sports.com/Article/Baltimore-Ravens-Alabama-football-DJ-Fluker-domestic-violence-victim-149516199/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;247sports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courthouse set ablaze as 'Wall of Moms' protest intensifies in Oakland...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/26/courthouse-set-ablaze-wall-moms-protest-intensifie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters in California set fire to a courthouse, damaged a police station and assaulted officers after a peaceful demonstration intensified late Saturday, Oakland police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin says Russian Navy to get hypersonic nuke strike weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-navy-day-parade-putin-idUSKCN24R0CJ?taid=5f1d5fdd31fdfb000144d967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Sunday the Russian Navy would be armed with hypersonic nuclear strike weapons and underwater nuclear drones, which the defence ministry said were in their final phase of testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One shot dead during march in Austin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8560753/Cops-declare-Seattle-protest-riot-youth-detention-center-goes-flames.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A protester was shot and killed in a shooting at a protest in Texas Saturday night as tensions flared across America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosives, rocks thrown at police in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/25/us/seattle-protest-riot/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle protesters threw large rocks, bottles, fireworks and other explosives at officers Saturday, police said. Others set fire to a portable trailer and a construction site, police said in a series of tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 days until Election Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/07/26/100-days-out-heres-what-defined-2020-election-and-what-expect/5467900002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 100 days out from the general election, impeachment, coronavirus and systemic racism have dominated voters' minds. Here's what to expect next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain outbreak drives European fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53539015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its Catalonia region closes its nightlife as other nations eye increases in new infections warily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasa Mars rover: Meteorite to head home to Red Planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-53491555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Perseverance robot will take Martian rock with it when it launches from Earth on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richmond dump truck set on fire outside police HQ...</title>
      <link>https://richmond.com/news/local/police-use-chemical-agents-flash-bangs-to-disperse-crowd-outside-rpd-headquarters-after-city-dump/article_11b30f19-e70a-51f9-8e1d-ef53a1a4ba3e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 1:20 a.m.: The Richmond Fire Department responded to the Chipotle Mexican Grill on the 800 block of W. Grace St. early Sunday morning where flames could be seen coming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEEP DRIVES THROUGH CO PROTESTERS</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/07/25/protesters-block-interstate-225-injured-car-drives-through-crowd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aurora police are investigating a shooting on Interstate 225 after a vehicle drove through protesters marching on the highway Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to unveil obesity plan after Boris Johnson's near-death...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/uk-unveil-obesity-plan-pms-near-death-experience-090319401.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson is set to roll out a £10 million anti-obesity campaign, including junk food advert bans, following his own brush with death that he partly blamed on his weight. Johnson will announce his "Better Health" campaign on Monday, which is expected to include encouraging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah Shutting Down O MAGAZINE After 20 Years with Embattled HEARST...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/26/oprah-shutting-down-o-magazine-print-edition-after-20-years-with-embattled-hearst-publications</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O stands for Oprah and for over. The Oprah magazine, called O, is apparently over. Begun twenty years ago in print, and 10 years ago digitally, there are reports that O will cease print operations …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA:  More than 1,000 deaths for 5th day in row...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/coronavirus-updates-hundreds-texas-bar-owners-pledge-defiance/story?id=71982262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The novel coronavirus pandemic has now killed more than 643,000 people worldwide and over 15.9 million people across the globe have been diagnosed with COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPPOSING ARMED MILITIAS CONVERGE IN LOUISVILLE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8559841/Black-militia-members-brandish-guns-demanding-charges-against-cops-linked-Breonna-Taylors-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The simultaneous demonstrations in Louisville by 'Not F*****g Around Coaltion' and the right-wing 'Three Percenters' are taking place a day after scores were arrested on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public losing faith in govts, says survey...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/virus-surges-worldwide-public-loses-faith-authorities-092641725.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey released Saturday showed governments are fast losing support for their handling of the coronavirus pandemic, as health officials recorded a surge of more than 280,000 new cases globally two days in a row. Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro, widely criticised for his handling of the crisis there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mysterious seeds from China sent to dozens of people in multiple states...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/nation-world/national/article244479272.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. sidelined scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Coronavirus-ravaged-Florida-as-Ron-DeSantis-15434450.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. - As Florida became a global epicenter of the coronavirus, Gov. Ron DeSantis held one meeting this month with his top public health official, Scott Rivkees, according to the governor's schedule. His health department has sidelined scientists, halting briefings last month with disease specialists and telling the experts there was not sufficient personnel from the state to continue participating.  "I never received information about what happened with my ideas or results," said Thomas Hladish, a University of Florida research scientist whose regular calls with the health department ended June 29. "But I did hear the governor say the models were wrong about everything."  DeSantis, a Republican, this month traveled to Miami to hold a roundtable with South Florida mayors, whose region had emerged as a novel coronavirus hot spot. But the Republican mayor of Hialeah was shut out, weeks after saying the governor "hasn't done much" for a city disproportionately affected by the virus.  As the virus spread out of control in Florida, decision-making became increasingly shaped by politics and divorced from scientific evidence according to interviews with 64 current and former state and administration officials, health administrators, epidemiologists, political operatives and hospital executives. The crisis in Florida, these observers say, has revealed the shortcomings of a response built on shifting metrics, influenced by a small group of advisers and tethered at every stage to the Trump administration, which has no unified plan for addressing the national health emergency but has pushed for states to reopen.  DeSantis relies primarily on the advice of his wife, Casey, a former television reporter and host, and his chief of staff, Shane Strum, a former hospital executive, according to multiple Republican...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Church Defies State Lockdown To Resume In-Person Assembly...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/compliance-would-be-disobedience-prominent-california-church-defies-state-lockdown-to-resume-in-person-assembly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pastor and elders of a prominent evangelical church in California issued a statement on Friday explaining why they will no longer comply with the state&amp;#8217;s mandate ordering them to refrain from in-person gatherings. John F. MacArthur, the 81-year-old senior pastor of Grace Community Church in Sun Valley, California, also claimed that the state had [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gig Economy Compromised Our Immune System...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gig-economy-compromised-immune-system-000048670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- There’s nothing arbitrary about an epidemic.While each disease is the product of a chain of accidental genetic shifts, the process that turns a novel infection into a devastating outbreak is as much social as biological. The vast majority of new conditions will die out before they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPPOSING ARMED MILITIAS CONVERGE IN LOUISVILLE</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/local/2020/07/25/louisville-protests-nfac-three-percenters-expected-demonstrate/3288198001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFAC, which is a Black militia that stands for "Not F**king Around Coalition," said it is coming to demand justice for Breonna Taylor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINCLAIR pulls show featuring Fauci conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/25/media/sinclair-pulls-fauci-conspiracy-segment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sinclair Broadcast Group said Saturday it will postpone and rework a segment it planned to air this weekend that suggested Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation's top infectious disease expert, was responsible for the creation of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign told to STOP using Reagan to raise money...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/RNC-Trump-campaign-told-to-stop-using-President-15434408.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ronald Reagan Presidential Foundation and Institute formally asked the Trump campaign and the Republican National Committee to stop using the 40th president's name and image to raise money.  The request came in response to a fundraising appeal sent from the Trump Make America Great Again Committee, a joint effort of the Trump campaign and the RNC, offering two commemorative coins, one engraved with Reagan's image and the other with that of President Donald Trump to anyone who donates $45 or more for Trump's reelection. The email was "signed" by Trump.  Melissa Giller, the Reagan Foundation's chief marketing officer, told Washington Post columnist Karen Tumulty that the request to cease sales of the coins was made by phone to the RNC last week. Giller said the RNC agreed "within seconds" to stop using Reagan to solicit funds for Trump's reelection.  The foundation, which runs the Reagan Presidential Library near Los Angeles, was provided sole rights of the use of Reagan and his wife's names and images. While the foundation can't stop every time the Reagans' likenesses are used, it claims the right to stop groups from using them for political or commercial gain.  Giller told Tumulty that although the RNC agreed to the demand, there are likely coins that were already sold and many people saw the fundraising email that suggests an association between the 40th and 45th presidents, which might require further legal action.  Frederick J. Ryan Jr., who chairs the Reagan Foundation board, is also publisher and CEO of The Washington Post.  RNC communications director Michael Ahrens said in an emailed statement to The Post that the foundation's "objection came as a surprise" but that it would "stop emailing this fundraising solicitation as a courtesy."  Trump has often invoked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STANDOFF WITH FEDS IN PORTLAND CONTINUES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9c7992fc9cd4062ccf32f616cb5bb7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Federal agents again repeatedly fired tear gas to break up rowdy protests in Portland, Oregon, that continued into the early morning Saturday as demonstrations that have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIOT SEATTLE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9149f66e43442eb04df4932932b7bcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Seattle police declared a riot Saturday following large demonstrations in the city's Capitol Hill neighborhood and deployed flash bangs and pepper spray to try to clear an area near...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient teeth show that epidemics began much further back in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Ancient-teeth-show-that-epidemics-began-much-15434108.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the novel coronavirus pandemic reshapes lives and entire economies, historians tell us this is not the first time. The earliest written records of tiny infectious organisms overhauling human societies stretch back as far as the Plague of Justinian in A.D. 541, which is thought to have killed up to 50 million people, or even the earlier Antonine Plague in A.D. 165, which left 5 million dead, a substantial portion of the world then.  Now, paleogenomics - a nascent field that studies DNA in remnants of ancient teeth - is rewriting the first chapter of humanity's entanglement with disease to thousands of years older than originally thought. The growing evidence suggests that these first epidemics forced societies to make epoch-defining transformations.  "In the case of covid-19 [the disease caused by the coronavirus], we see similar processes, but we are watching it unfold in real time," said Anne Stone, regents professor in the School of Human Evolution and Social Change at Arizona State University, whose focus is anthropological genetics. She also has studied evidence of tuberculosis in ancient DNA.  Paleogenomics, which adapts high-end medical tools similar to some now being used to track the coronavirus, has amounted to a "revolution" in understanding disease history, says Maria Spyrou, a microbiologist at the Max Planck Institute in Germany.  "This is one of the things that we can now start saying," said Spyrou, adding that where historical records are lacking, DNA evidence offers the possibility of filling in gaps, sometimes in surprising ways.  "One of them is plague," Spyrou said. "Until 2015, we thought that plague was maybe a 3,000-year-old disease."  Scientists and archaeologists now believe, however, that the plague bacteria, which caused the medieval Black Death that killed up to half of Europe's population,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he 'often' regrets his tweets and retweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1196623/donald-trump-regrets-tweets-dave-portnoy-barstool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump said he often regrets what he posts on Twitter as he revealed that he may never tweet again come November. In a revealing interview with Dave Portnoy of Barstool Sports on Thursday, Tr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP's pleas to RNC for financial help go unanswered... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/House-GOP-s-pleas-to-Republican-National-15433714.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Senior House Republicans are pleading with the deep-pocketed Republican National Committee and the Trump campaign to provide financial help as Democrats vastly outraise the GOP, but top campaign officials are so far declining to commit.  House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., has been prodding the RNC to write a check to the National Republican Congressional Committee - a request he has made multiple times. McCarthy specifically has asked Jared Kushner, President Trump's son-in-law and senior adviser, to make a financial commitment to the House GOP, according to several officials familiar with the discussions, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to freely describe private conversations.  But Kushner, who oversees such decisions and has a greater say than RNC Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel, has refused thus far, the officials say. While the Trump campaign and the RNC have brought in record amounts of money, some Trump officials see donating to the House as a wasteful investment as the GOP's chances of reclaiming the majority sharply deteriorate. Their decline in fortunes can largely be attributed to Trump's sagging support over his handling of the coronavirus pandemic and the sliding economy.  "The campaign just wants the money. . . . They don't care about the House - it's not their concern," one official close with the Trump campaign said. "When you've been working in politics for years, and you understand it's a team sport, you kind of look at these things a little differently. I don't think they see it that way."  Trump has been raking in unprecedented amounts of cash - though presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden outraised him the past two months. The president's fundraising committees and the RNC entered July with a whopping $295 million on hand, which is more than twice the $144 million that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infects your nose first...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article244473917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH CEO HILL GRILL SET FOR WEDNESDAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/25/big-tech-hearing-bezos-zuckerberg-381448</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first joint congressional appearance by the chief executives of the four powerful tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dilemma of Covid's Second Wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-dilemma-of-covid-19s-second-wave/ar-BB17aqJ2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump praises DeSantis' despite record deaths in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-praises-desantis-despite-record-covid-19-deaths-in-florida-canceled-gop-convention/ar-BB17byIu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus and mail-in voting will mean an accelerated 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article244467957.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA:  More than 1,000 deaths for fourth day in row...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/coronavirus-update-us-counts-more-than-1000-fatalities-for-a-fourth-straight-day-as-virus-spread-accelerates-in-south-and-west-2020-07-25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus illness COVID-19 claimed another 1,100 lives in the U.S. in a single day to push the death toll above 145,000 on Saturday, marking a fourth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regis Philbin Dies At 88...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/regis-philbin-iconic-tv-host-dead-at-88-138303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former 'Live! with Regis and Kelly' host's family released a statement following his death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston, Miami, other cities face mounting care worker shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Houston-Miami-other-cities-face-mounting-health-15433996.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortages of health care workers are worsening in Houston, Miami, Baton Rouge and other cities battling sustained covid-19 outbreaks, exhausting staffers and straining hospitals' ability to cope with spiking cases.  That need is especially dire for front-line nurses, respiratory therapists and others who play hands-on, bedside roles where one nurse is often required for each critically ill patient.  While many hospitals have devised ways to stretch material resources - converting surgery wards into specialized covid units and recycling masks and gowns - it is far more difficult to stretch the human workers needed to make the system function.  "At the end of the day, the capacity for critical care is a balance between the space, staff and stuff. And if you have a bottleneck in one, you can't take additional patients," said Mahshid Abir, a senior physician policy researcher at the RAND Corporation and director of the Acute Care Research Unit (ACRU) at the University of Michigan. "You have to have all three . . . You can't have a ventilator, but not a respiratory therapist."  "What this is going to do is it's going to cost lives, not just for covid patients, but for everyone else in the hospital," she warned.  The increasingly fraught situation reflects packed hospitals across large swaths of the country: More than 8,800 covid patients are hospitalized in Texas; Florida has more than 9,400; and at least 13 other states also have thousands of hospitalizations, according to data compiled by The Washington Post.  Facilities in several states, including Texas, South Carolina and Indiana, have in recent weeks reported shortages of such workers, according to federal planning documents viewed by The Post, pitting states and hospitals against one another to recruit staff.  On...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK REPORT:   DEMS COULD SWEEP IT ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/the-blue-wave-keeps-growing-d4d45832-d5f2-4d77-8fc8-20e6fe19a1cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right now, every measurable trend is going against Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK quarantines travellers from Spain in major blow to Europe's revival...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200725183049-n4hcl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-SPAIN (UPDATE 5, PIX):UPDATE 5-UK quarantines travellers from Spain in major blow to Europe's revival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WATCH HAWAII</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2020/07/25/breaking-news/douglas-remains-category-2-hurricane-overnight-as-it-heads-toward-hawaii-kauai-under-tropical-storm-watch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's richest looking to buy access to citizenship in safe havens...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-rich-are-looking-to-buy-access-to-covid-safe-havens/ar-BB16Y5PR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots that kill Covid in 10 minutes unleashed in hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/robots-kill-viruses-10-minutes-22415385</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The £71,000 roaming robots are the latest cutting edge technology to be employed by the frontline in the Covid-19 battle. The huge wheeling machines will be vital according to NHS nurses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local TV stations across nation to air Fauci conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/24/media/sinclair-fauci-conspiracy-bolling/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local television stations owned by the Sinclair Broadcast Group are set to air a conspiracy theory over the weekend that suggests Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation's top expert on infectious diseases, was responsible for the creation of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters follow his pandemic cues...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-coronavirus-cues-90af5c46-f341-426b-b115-d8e30eb6ca86.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans' shifts in thinking and behavior weren't immediate, often manifesting in a week or so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents fret over back-to-school decisions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2da549f1cbee9f90cca60751cd32871e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Claybourn is leaning toward sending his kindergarten daughter to in-person classes at a private school next month. Holly Davis’ sixth-grade daughter will learn online, though the family has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local TV stations across nation to air Fauci conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jul/25/sinclair-tv-stations-fauci-plandemic-conspiracy-theory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinclair stations to run interview with Plandemic researcher who claims infectious disease expert created the coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shut it down now:' Health experts call for 2nd lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/6334320/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 150 doctors endorsed an open letter to lawmakers, urging them to hit the restart button.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
