<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ZpFhwJ4eGM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALVIN KLEIN apologizes to LGBT community for ad of model kissing female robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2019/05/18/calvin-klein-apologizes-lgbt-community-bella-hadid-lil-miquela-kissing-ad/3718939002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Calvin Klein is apologizing after the fashion label came under fire for aÂ video campaign showing Bella Hadid kissing female robotÂ Lil Miquela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite Iranian force raids modeling agencies for 'promoting vulgarity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-fashion-arrests/elite-iranian-force-raids-modeling-agencies-for-promoting-vulgarity-idUSKCN1SO0EH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards force has raided three underground modeli...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope tells press: Church on your side; Denounces fake news...</title>
      <link>https://www.americamagazine.org/faith/2019/05/18/pope-francis-tells-press-church-your-side-denounces-fake-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.americamagazine.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“One of the first things that dictators do is to remove the freedom of the press,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I don't have to be 'angry' to win...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/444386-biden-at-campaign-kickoff-event-i-dont-have-to-be-angry-to-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden is touting a theme of unity and pushing back on those who may urge Democratic presidential candidates to be "angry" in their bid to take on President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger attacked in South Africa...</title>
      <link>https://sandtonchronicle.co.za/226372/watch-man-kicks-arnold-schwarzenegger-back-arnold-classic-africa-sandton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sandtonchronicle.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANDTON – The man ran up, jumped and kicked Schwarzenegger in the back and was then swiftly pinned down by security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirchner Roils Argentina With Surprise Bid for Vice-Presidency...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kirchner-roils-argentina-surprise-bid-141141755.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kirchner, 66, will run on the same ticket as Alberto Fernandez, her late husband’s former cabinet chief, she said in message broadcast Saturday on her official YouTube channel. “The overwhelming and unnecessary indebtedness of the country is starting to show the first symptoms of a reality that will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth about sex: We are not getting enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/may/18/truth-about-sex-we-are-not-getting-enough </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEREST, MOST CONTROVERSIAL YET?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/eurovision-2019-queerest-most-controversial-yet-n1007201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gay Muslim teen and BDSM anarchists will vie for this year's Eurovision Song Contest, as the competition's only trans and drag champions return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA TO ROCK EUROVISION...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitalspy.com/tv/reality-tv/a27513711/eurovision-2019-host-assi-azar-madonna-performance-unbelievable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitalspy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's an amazing show."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan military ready to slaughter US troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/779742/venezuela-united-states-maduro-weapons-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US issues warning to airlines flying over Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-issues-warning-airlines-flying-over-gulf-091628073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The advisory, which also covers airspace over the Gulf of Oman, comes amid rising tensions between the US and Iran. Washington has deployed an aircraft carrier group and B-52 bombers to the region against what it claims is an imminent threat from Tehran. President Donald Trump's administration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the Moon, people on Mars by 2033...or 2060</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/moon-people-mars-2033-2060-024224039.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dates fixed by the space agency are 2024 for the Moon and Mars in 2033, but according to experts and industry insiders, reaching the Red Planet by then is highly improbable barring a Herculean effort on the scale of the Apollo program in the 1960s. "The Moon is the proving ground for our eventual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden ramps up 2020 bid with wind at his back...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/joementum-biden-ramps-2020-bid-wind-back-061320503.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the one true known quantity in the Democratic nomination race, former vice president Joe Biden sits atop the pack of 2020 presidential contenders, relishing the prime position as he hosts a kickoff rally Saturday. No one knows whether the man who served as number two to popular Democratic president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going down: Brazil economic woes hit stocks, currency...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/going-down-brazil-economic-woes-hit-stocks-currency-023649668.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atrophying growth forecasts and waning confidence in President Jair Bolsonaro sent Brazil's stocks and currency to their lowest level of the year this week, as analysts warned of further falls. Since touching a record 100,000 points in mid-March, the Bovespa has fallen 10 percent and wiped out gains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILLEGALS FLOWN OUT OF TX TO EASE CROWDING</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/world/article-border-patrol-to-ease-overcrowding-by-flying-migrants-from-texas-to/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detroit, Miami, Buffalo and New York also considered as destinations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Texas man decapitated mother's body in apartment before fleeing, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/community/fort-worth/article230516319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS IN SOUTH FLORIDA AFTER DUMPING WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/immigration/article230536269.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump risks credibility with policy that veers between threats and inaction... </title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/05/17/analysis-trump-risks-credibility-with-his-policy-gyrations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has said there is no inconsistency in his administration’s messaging but that the image of incoherence can be useful. “At least Iran doesn’t know what to think, which at thi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmaker apologizes for using phrase 'consensual rape'... </title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/missouri-lawmaker-apologizes-for-using-term-consensual-rapes-abortion-bill-debate/YYPEvB11T22PPxoTyxh7MN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Missouri lawmaker walked back comments he made Friday during a debate over a restrictive anti-abor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri next on abortion ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c176d21d9a8946b9a8c126c179f8560d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. (AP) — Missouri's Republican-led House on Friday passed sweeping legislation designed to survive court challenges, which would ban abortions at eight weeks of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran tests 'America First' pledge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1097699ac34342f8b657325bcb580eb9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump won the White House pledging to wind down the nation's many foreign entanglements and put "America First." But as his administration in recent days has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELTON DEFENDS STRAIGHT ACTOR PLAYING LIFE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/9100258/elton-john-rocketman-taron-egerton-straight-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELTON JOHN has defended Rocketman star Taron Egerton over criticism that a straight actor should not play the gay icon – branding it “bulls**t”. The sobbing singer watched the movie for the first t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump aides try to quash tax hike rumors amid infrastructure talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/17/trump-tax-hike-rumors-infrastructure-1331703</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior advisers have repeatedly downplayed the possibility in private meetings with fiscal conservatives who are expressing alarm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller testimony off until at least June -- if EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/17/mueller-testimony-june-1331704</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerry Nadler had set a tentative May 23 deadline for Mueller to testify.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced to play long game...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b1005ff321144a58856cd1d43937dc03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — First came the sternly worded letters. Then the subpoenas. Now the votes to hold Trump administration officials in contempt of Congress. As House Democrats plod ahead...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio May Not Make Debate Stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/city-hall/story/2019/05/17/de-blasio-admits-first-debate-may-be-out-of-reach-1021938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As he kicked off his campaign here in the nation's first presidential selection state, the mayor said he has achieved one debate stage requirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Mueller, No McGahn: Fuming Dems Plot 'Extreme Measures'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/No-Mueller-no-McGahn-and-stalled-investigations-13854965.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - An increasing number of House Democrats are frustrated by their stalled investigations into President Donald Trump, with an uncooperative chief executive, their own leader's reluctance about impeachment and courts that could be slow to resolve the standoff.  Democrats have yet to hear from special counsel Robert Mueller III, who led the nearly two-year investigation into Russia interference in the 2016 election and possible involvement with the Trump campaign. Even with negotiations, the earliest Mueller could testify would be next month.  And any hopes of former White house counsel Donald McGahn facing a congressional panel on Tuesday are slim, as the White House moves to block all current and former aides from cooperating with congressional inquiries.  Weighing all options, Democrats have raised the specter of imposing fines or jailing people who ignore subpoenas, extreme measures that have prompted some legal experts to wonder whether Democrats have a strategy for this constitutional conflict.  A group of House Judiciary Committee Democrats privately have discussed ways to increase pressure on leadership to being impeachment proceedings despite House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's wariness, according to several Democrats who spoke on the condition of anonymity to freely discuss the plan.  "There's no doubt in my mind that we are all going to come to a point [where more has to be done] - including the speaker," said Rep. Marcia Fudge of Ohio, a senior Democrat. "We respect her leadership and we respect her strategic sense about how these things work, her political sense. But I think we're all getting to a point where we know something more has to be done."  The anxious search for next steps comes as Pelosi, D-Calif., has settled on a long-game approach and most Democrats have fallen in line. She has argued that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American cities moving into real-time facial surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/some-us-cities-moving-real-time-facial-surveillance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities apply facial-recognition programs to surveillance videos to identify subjects. Now, a report says Chicago and Detroit have purchased their own systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Judges Ignore Occupation of Journalist Who Had Home Raided By Cops?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/bayarea/article/Motion-Aims-To-Find-Out-If-Judges-Knew-Or-Ignored-13852762.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (BCN)  A free-speech advocacy group filed a motion in San Francisco Superior Court Thursday to unseal applications for search warrants obtained by police before they raided the home and office of a journalist last week.  Freelance stringer Bryan Carmody's home and office were raided May 10 in connection with an investigation into a leaked police report on the February death of San Francisco Public Defender Jeff Adachi.  According to the San Rafael-based First Amendment Coalition, they filed the motion on behalf of Carmody and with help from the Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press and the Northern California chapter of the Society of Professional Journalists.  The motion is set to be heard Tuesday morning at the Hall of Justice in Department 22.  Leaders of the coalition said the search warrants in this case should already be public because the warrants were executed.  In a statement, coalition executive director David Snyder said, "Our motion to unseal aims to answer one of the most disturbing mysteries of this case-how two judges separately issued warrants that allowed police to raid the home of a working journalist in order to reveal that journalist's source.  "This obvious and unlawful intrusion on press rights demands accountability and accountability starts with knowing the facts," Snyder said.  Coalition leaders said that in order for police to get a search warrant to seize property police must show that it's likely stolen or embezzled property will be found at the location.  In making their case to a judge, police should have told the judge that Carmody is a working journalist and the warrant should not have issued.  According to the coalition, the California Shield Law generally prevents...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fisherman dead after castrated by giant crocodile...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/fisherman-27-killed-after-huge-16159054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Nyamhanza from Harare, Zimbabwe was killed while he was fishing with his brother</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French reporters face jail for publishing secret govt doc...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/05/17/france-takes-unprecedented-action-against-reporters-who-published-secret-government-document/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists could face years in jail for handling a classified military document that revealed details about France’s involvement in the Yemen conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texting while walking could soon be crime in New York...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/politics/ny-senate-introduces-bill-to-ban-texting-while-walking/5302620/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new bill introduced by the State Senate would make it illegal for people to cross streets in the state with your eyes glued to your smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China armored vehicle launches swarms of killer drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9098437/china-armoured-truck-drones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHINESE defence firm has unveiled a terrifying new battle truck which can unleash a swarm of killer drones behind enemy lines. The armoured war machine – based on a Russian Tigr vehicle …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police find GRENADE in Goodwill donation bin -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.tcpalm.com/story/news/local/st-lucie-county/2019/05/16/grenade-goodwill-clears-out-port-st-lucie-store-bomb-squad-responds/3692317002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tcpalm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the second time in less than a year a grenade has been dropped off at a Port St. Lucie Goodwill store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-armed man sues cops after they handcuffed wrist to ankle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7041147/One-armed-man-sues-handcuffed-wrist-ankle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man with one arm whose wrist was cuffed to his ankle filed a federal lawsuit against the Sheriff's Department in Clay County, West Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Break up FACEBOOK? Vestager favors making share data instead...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1622036/break-up-facebook-eus-margrethe-vestager-favors-making-it-share-data-instead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Competition commissioner Margrethe Vestager doesn't think splitting up the giant social network is the best way to rein it in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin hails new 'science fiction' secret military lasers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff03960c48a6440bacc1c2512a7c197a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — President Vladimir Putin says that new types of laser weapons developed in Russia will significantly enhance the nation's military capability. Speaking during Friday's meeting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration rejects subpoena for Trump's tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/17/trump-administration-rejects-subpoena-tax-returns-1331481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Friday rejected a Democratic subpoena for President Donald Trump's tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Missouri closer to near-total abortion ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/article230523469.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Look At 'Trans Time Facility'...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/05/16/cryogenics-san-leandro-lab-frozen-second-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the stuff of science fiction and Hollywood movies. The promise: upon your death, your body is frozen until some future medical breakthrough restores you to full health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Gov in Louisiana breaks from party...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec2a8082c8ea429cbfa66cf21682cedf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — Nearly three decades ago, when Democratic Louisiana Gov. John Bel Edwards' wife was 20 weeks pregnant with their first child, a doctor discovered their daughter had spina...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  World's Best Hotel Rooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestravelguide/2019/05/15/worlds-best-hotel-rooms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forbes Travel Guide's compilation of the finest hotel accommodations around the globe—from Beverly Hills to Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 fires at MA Jewish Centers 'Intentionally Set'...</title>
      <link>https://news.vice.com/en_us/article/mb83ey/3-fires-at-jewish-centers-in-massachusetts-were-intentionally-set</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two were at a rabbi's house â€” and one at a nearby Jewish center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US ambassador to Germany returning $8M to treasury...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/17/rand-paul-richard-grenell-embassy-germany-1330271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ambassador to Germany wants a zero dollar increase for his embassy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Collapse Worst Outside of War in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/17/world/americas/venezuela-economy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Butchers have stopped selling meat cuts in favor of offal, fat shavings and cow hooves, the only animal protein many of their customers can afford.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicides rising among young girls...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/suicide-rates-are-rising-among-young-girls-study-finds-n1006911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s not just numbers. We’re seeing a trend. But we don’t have good information about what is driving this shift.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret messages in urine revealed Nazi medical experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/world-news/.premium.MAGAZINE-nazis-experimented-on-these-women-they-told-the-world-using-brilliant-code-1.7249737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter shot, killed in Mexican tourist resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-violence-idUSKCN1SM2BD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crime reporter has been shot and killed in the beach resort of Playa del Carme...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Allies Freak About New DNC Big...</title>
      <link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/chris-korge-dnc-finance-chair-affirms-neutrality-amid-bernie-sanders-allies-concerns_n_5cded67ee4b00735a91608a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Korge, the party organ’s new chief fundraiser, has criticized Sanders and is a donor to Kamala Harris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal reached to lift steel, aluminum tariffs on Canada, Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/17/us-to-announce-deal-to-lift-steel-and-aluminum-tariffs-on-canada-and-mexico-as-soon-as-today-sources.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deal would get rid of a key obstacle to passing updates to the North American Free Trade Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stockholm men push boundaries with synchronized swim...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/sync-swim-stockholm-men-push-boundaries-synchronised-swimming-160532041--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Balding, paunchy and unshaven, this group of Stockholm friends in their 40s are making waves: they&amp;#39;re pioneers of men&amp;#39;s team synchronised swimming, challenging stereotypes one aquatic pirouette at a time. On a recent May evening, these 18 amateur swimmers ran through their formations and underwater</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age Divide Defining Primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/05/joe-biden-winning-big-older-voters/589555/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s edge with older voters is his greatest asset so far in the race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy investigates GOOGLE for antitrust...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-italy/italys-watchdog-investigates-google-for-alleged-antitrust-abuse-idUSKCN1SN0KZ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy's competition watchdog said on Friday it had opened an investigation ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer sentiment surges to highest level in 15 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/17/consumer-sentiment-may-2019-preliminary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The optimistic consumer outlook was mostly recorded before U.S.-China trade deliberations soured earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED:  This Is The Story Tony Robbins Doesn't Want You To Read...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/janebradley/tony-robbins-self-help-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Robbins claims he has helped millions of fans overcome some of life’s darkest difficulties. But leaked records reveal he has used his fame to berate victims of rape and violence, while female former staffers and followers have accused him of inappropriate sexual advances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9,000 migrants released into USA in last 8 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/16/homeland-security-releases-9k-illegal-aliens-into-u-s-in-8-days-1-1k-released-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DHS has released about 9,000 border crossers and illegal aliens into the interior of the United States over the last eight days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart tech turns sinister in 'CHILD'S PLAY' reboot...</title>
      <link>https://sg.style.yahoo.com/smart-tech-turns-sinister-in-uk-trailer-for-the-childs-play-reboot-130534991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new UK trailer for the 'Child's Play' reboot features the Chucky doll using an onslaught of murderous smart technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Ohio State leaders knew about team doctor's abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8100ceaf06c44dc2a85bea4c5daff04f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — An Ohio State University team doctor who died years ago sexually abused at least 177 students over a period of decades so wantonly that students described his examinations as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author Herman Wouk dead at 103...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ee28153a1e54f52a516352171c7f41d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Herman Wouk, the versatile, Pulitzer Prize winning author of such million-selling novels as "The Caine Mutiny" and "The Winds of War" whose steady Jewish faith inspired his stories...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrians told to stop French kissing COWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9094938/austrians-told-stop-kissing-cows-bizarre-challenge-social-media-health-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SNOGGING cows – “with or without tongues” – is all the rage in Austria, endangering the animals and those smooching them, warn officials. The disturbing trend has been promoted by Swiss app Castl, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to Set Up 'Fake News Database'...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2019/05/16/russia-to-set-up-fake-news-database-a65613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Many Dems Exaggerated 'Mental Distress' After '16 Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/many-democrats-exaggerated-mental-distress-after-2016-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many registered Democrats who claimed they were suffering from mental distress after Donald Trump won the 2016 presidential election may have been embellishing a bit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S.-China trade war faces another superpower: AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Amazon-is-the-third-superpower-heightening-the-13853379.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LORTON, Va. - Maxsa Innovations, a small business selling electronic gadgets on the outskirts of Washington, was already reeling from the U.S.-China trade war when it realized it had a third superpower to manage: Amazon.  Maxsa, which manufactures many of its products in China, had to start paying 25 percent more to import some goods after the United States introduced tariffs on Chinese-made products last summer. Faced with higher costs, Maxsa says it managed to persuade several small U.S. retailers to pay roughly 20 percent more for the company's wares.  But its biggest customer, Amazon, drove a much harder bargain.  Amazon, which buys products from Maxsa and then sells them to consumers, initially rejected Maxsa's attempt to charge more for a laser-guided parking aid called Park Right, forcing Maxsa to cut off sales to the online retailer. (Amazon founder and chief executive Jeff Bezos owns The Washington Post.)  "Please do what you can to help get this through," Maxsa founder Skip West pleaded in a January email to Amazon, part of an exchange reviewed by The Washington Post. "I felt horrible turning down $18,000 in orders this week."  As President Donald Trump ramps up his trade war with China, other consumer-product companies report similar struggles getting big retailers to budge.  With the internet driving ruthless price competition among Amazon, Walmart, Home Depot and others, large retailers are loath to pay more or to raise their own prices. That leaves importers of Chinese goods caught between the trade war and Americans' quest for the best possible deal.  "Retailers are all about everyday low prices. They want to protect consumers, but they also want to protect their sales," said Jason Trice, president of Jasco Products, a lighting and electronics seller in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy spying on media through data technology...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/2019/05/17/secret-tracking-device-found-in-navy-email-to-navy-times-amid-leak-investigation-raises-legal-ethical-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It appears that the Navy sought to secretly extract data from the Navy Times computer network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colbert Brutally Mocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-colbert-cold-open-on-farmers-goes-from-mildly-amusing-to-seriously-dark-in-just-seconds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oddly dark, even sadistic take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FLYNN TAPES...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Judge-orders-public-release-of-what-Michael-Flynn-13852480.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A federal judge on Thursday ordered that prosecutors make public a transcript of a phone call that former national security adviser Michael Flynn tried hard to hide with a lie: his conversation with a Russian ambassador in late 2016.  U.S. District Judge Emmet Sullivan in Washington ordered the government also to provide a public transcript of a November 2017 voice mail involving Flynn. In that sensitive call, President Donald Trump's attorney left a message for Flynn's attorney reminding him of the president's fondness for Flynn at a time when Flynn was considering cooperating with federal investigators.  The transcripts, which the judge ordered be posted on a court website by May 31, would reveal conversations at the center of two major avenues of special counsel Robert Mueller III's investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 election. So far they have only been disclosed to the public in fragments in court filings and the Mueller report.  Sullivan also ordered that still-redacted portions of the Mueller report that relate to Flynn be given to the court and made public.  Sullivan's orders came very shortly after government prosecutors agreed to release some sealed records in Flynn's case. The release was in response to a motion filed with the court earlier this year by The Washington Post, which argued that the public deserved to know more about Flynn's role in key events and cooperation with investigators.  Flynn pleaded guilty in December 2017 to one felony count of making a false statement to FBI investigators about his contact with the ambassador and awaits sentencing.  The purpose of the phone calls, and the motives of the callers, have been hotly debated.  In the December 2016 call, Flynn urged that the Kremlin not get too riled up about U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showdown with Trump in PA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-2020-trump-biden-pennsylvania-20190517-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and Joe Biden are obsessed with each other and with Pennsylvania. The president and the former vice president are both headed there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Kroft to Retire from '60 MINS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/steve-kroft-retire-60-minutes-1211628</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The show's longest-tenured correspondent is known for his incisive interviews and impactful investigations. But he admits, "I'm not easy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesia Says Foiled Plot to Detonate Bombs via Wi-Fi...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7041149/ISIS-plot-detonate-bombs-remotely-using-WIFI-foiled-police-Indonesia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesian police said they arrested ISIS linked terror suspects, including some who planned to detonate bombs at political demonstrations when election results are announced next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deadline Day' For Baltimore Set By Ransomware Hackers...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/05/16/as-ransom-deadline-arrives-thursday-baltimore-city-continues-to-struggle-for-fix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crippling cybersecurity attack on Baltimore City enters its ninth day, as city officials continue to say they can't say much about the investigation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
