<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Memo in 1990s pollution case shows Warren in action as corporate consultant...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Memo-in-1990s-pollution-case-shows-Elizabeth-14894375.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The memo from then-Professor Elizabeth Warren was written on Harvard University law school letterhead, a symbol of gravitas for a scholar renowned as a champion for consumers victimized by predatory banks and other big businesses.  But on this occasion, Warren was not arguing on behalf of vulnerable families, nor was she offering the sort of stinging rebuke of corporate greed that would later define her political career. Rather, Warren was representing a large development company that was trying to avoid having to clean up a toxic waste site.  The memo, which Warren wrote in 1996, used legalistic and often dense language to argue that businesses faced the "risk of the unknown" from a growing threat of lawsuits, and that defended the company's right to "maximize its returns to its unpaid creditors and to survive as an employer."  "Environmental claims, product liability claims, and mass tort claims, for which we have currently only seen the tip of the iceberg, are multiplying against American businesses," wrote Warren, who, according to her campaign, was arguing that a different company should bear the cleanup costs.  The eight-page memo, which has not previously been reported, offers a rare glimpse of Warren in action during her past work as a corporate consultant - one whose arguments were at times out of step with the liberal presidential campaign she is running today.  Warren's compensation in the 1996 case was included in a summary released by her campaign late Sunday night showing that she had been paid about $2 million as a legal consultant during her time as a professor, most of it between 1995 and 2009.  But Warren, who has released 11 years of tax returns, has not disclosed her tax records from most of that time period. And her campaign has provided few details about her private legal business beyond short...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOBBS:  IT'S A WHITEWASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/lou-dobbs-doj-ig-report-a-whitewash-shows-the-deep-states-awesome-control-of-our-permanent-bureaucracy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Business' Lou Dobbs today reacted to the DOJ inspector general report by calling it "long-delayed and hardly worth the wait."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dozen feared dead, many missing in volcano blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7772591/White-Island-volcano-New-Zealands-eruption-leaves-dozens-Australians-feared-missing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 20 Australians including a Sydney family-of-four and a newlywed couple are listed as missing by the New Zealand Red Cross in the wake of the deadly White Island volcano eruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'Social Credit System' Used to Blacklist Foreign Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/12/09/china-uses-social-credit-system-control-domestic-foreign-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bloomberg News report on Sunday described how Communist China uses its “social credit system” to control not just citizens but corporations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWSUIT THREAT...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/clint-eastwood-lawsuit-richard-jewell-movie-warner-bros-atlanta-journal-constitution-1202805069/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros is more than willing to take on one of America’s largest newspapers over claims that portion of the Clint Eastwood directed Richard Jewell movie are defamatory. “The film is based on a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI DIRECTOR DEFENDS...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fbi-director-chris-wray-reacts-doj-watchdog-report/story?id=67605418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI Director Christopher Wray offered mixed reactions to a Justice Department watchdog report that uncovered "serious performance failures."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THEY CAN'T AGREE ON ANYTHING</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191209222918-j9it6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV):UPDATE 8-As Democrats close in on impeachment charges, Republicans cry foul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crossfire Hurricane' Turns Tornado...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/In-opening-Trump-campaign-investigation-FBI-felt-14894307.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The FBI had barely closed a politically volcanic investigation into Secretary of State Hillary Clinton's use of a private email server when it got a troubling tip about her rival's presidential campaign.  On July 28, 2016, the bureau received information from an Australian diplomat, who said a Donald Trump campaign aide had "suggested the Trump team had received some kind of suggestion from Russia" that Moscow could anonymously release damaging information about Clinton, according to the long-awaited Justice Department inspector general's report released Monday.  The tip, vague as it was, shook senior FBI officials, who were already investigating suspected Russian interference in the 2016 campaign, including the theft of emails from the Democratic National Committee. Three days later, the FBI took the momentous decision to open a counterintelligence investigation of a presidential campaign, as the election season entered the home stretch.  Almost ever since, the origin of that investigation has been a lens through which Trump's most ardent supporters and critics see his entire presidency. To the former camp, it is the original sin of a Deep State determined to prevent Trump's election on the basis of slim, if not outright fabricated evidence. To Trump's opponents, the investigation was the only possible response to the threat of a foreign adversary compromising the Republican presidential nominee's campaign.  The 434-page report by Inspector General Michael Horowitz will not settle the feud. It finds that the FBI's investigation, dubbed Crossfire Hurricane, was sufficiently predicated and largely confirms previous findings about the origins of the probe by special counsel Robert Mueller.  But it also questions officials' investigative decisions, notably about how they decided to secretly monitor the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetics-Based Dating App?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/epstein-funded-scientist-george-church-is-creating-a-genetics-based-dating-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard professor George Church says he wants to eliminate genetic diseases, but critics find his idea chilling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ON TO THE NEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/09/us/politics/trump-ig-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the time the Justice Department inspector general’s report was released, the president and his supporters had moved on in their effort to convince Americans of the enemies arrayed against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THEY CAN'T AGREE ON ANYTHING</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnn-analyst-calls-out-gop-conduct-at-hearing-didnt-even-defend-trump-just-played-game-of-distraction-and-disinformation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN Legal Analyst Susan Hennessey calls out GOP conduct at impeachment hearing: The Republicans played a 'game of distraction and, frankly, disinformation'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military bases increase security after shootings in Hawaii, Florida...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/473735-military-bases-increase-security-after-shootings-on-hawaii-and-florida-bases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Military bases are stepping up security following two shootings within the past two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARR:  MY IMPEACHMENT WAS BETTER...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/473708-chris-wallace-allegations-against-trump-far-broader-than-the-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Chris Wallace said Monday that the House impeachment inquiry includes "far broader" allegations against President Trump than were levied against former President Clinton, pointing out that the Democrats' case is based on matters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Watchdog Forces Barr To Scramble...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/muckraker/how-doj-watchdog-forced-barr-to-scramble-to-undermine-trump-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Bill Barr scrambled on Monday to keep a main anti-DOJ conspiracy theory going, after Justice Department Inspector General...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia reacts with anger after doping ban from Olympics, World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/russia-faces-sporting-ban-wada-meets-095603606--oly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Anti-Doping Agency on Monday banned Russia for four years from major global sporting events including the 2020 Tokyo Olympics and the 2022 World Cup in Qatar over manipulated doping data, prompting an angry response from President Vladimir Putin. WADA&amp;#39;s executive committee, meeting in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Moves to Center...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/boris-johnson-bad-day-health-195000630.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It was the kind of moment Boris Johnson has spent the entire U.K. election campaign trying to avoid. Confronted with a picture of a sick 4-year-old forced to sleep on the floor of a British hospital because of a shortage of beds, the prime minister looked away and tried to change the subject.As</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL worker swung machete at drive-through customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/news/20191209/taco-bell-worker-swung-machete-at-drive-through-customer-austin-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee at a South Austin Taco Bell is accused of swinging a machete at a customer in the drive-through lane over the weekend, according to court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY:  Truth is finally out... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-james-comey-the-truth-is-finally-out-the-fbi-fulfilled-its-mission/ar-BBY08vk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents were confiscating drugs and guns from luggage when rapper Juice Wrld suffered seizure...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/breaking/ct-juice-wrld-guards-arrested-20191209-sfhqe3cns5hsffhxskrhqfagl4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As authorities were going through his and his entourage’s luggage, the rapper “began convulsing (and) going into a seizure,” sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government deficit spikes another 12%... </title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/473755-deficit-spikes-12-percent-in-first-two-months-of-fiscal-year-cbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy on hospital floor dominates campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a6742889e9f1c0b8652d06ba94563864</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A 4-year-old boy in a Spider-Man top lying on a hospital floor took center stage Monday in Britain's election campaign, as the opposition painted his plight as a symptom of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain faces most history-shaping election since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7c2df941c2e2b3648f552efd2f2d0ca4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain is facing the most testing and significant period in its modern history since World War II. The polarized electorate now has a critical choice to make -- but it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops that defied Maduro have fled Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/779a723625d58303b7beff55ed85c4f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — For seven nerve-wracking months, they slept through the day in cramped quarters on cold floors, while spending their nights in prayer, keeping fit with dumbbells made from water jugs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned baby giraffe befriended by dog in Africa dies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c7b10c3cdcb9bab7711a1c8adef27bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — A baby giraffe that was befriended by a dog after he was abandoned in the wild has died, a South African animal orphanage said Friday. “Our team is heartbroken,” the orphanage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Argument Over Impeachment Turned Violent...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/impeachment-battery-bust-750138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 9--An argument about the impeachment hearings targeting Donald Trump turned violent Friday evening when a man allegedly shoved his 60-year-old girlfriend to the ground in the couple’s Florid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-BOEING manager says he warned company of problems prior to 737 crashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/former-boeing-manager-says-he-warned-company-problems-prior-737-n1098536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"For the first time in my life, I’m sorry to say that I’m hesitant about putting my family on a Boeing airplane," Ed Pierson wrote to a company executive before the first tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ERS Player Likes, Retweets Own Highlights -- During Game...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/2019/12/09/49ers-emmanuel-sanders-liked-retweeted-own-highlights-during-game-saints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco 49ers wide receiver Emmanuel Sanders is happy the team is playing at a high level. [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk whacks traffic pylon in 'Cybertruck'; Runs red light?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/elon-musk-tesla-cybertruck-video-driving/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the video where Tesla's CEO may have run a red light and check out the shocking amount of body roll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegan influencer eats meat for 30 days, says now feels healthier...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/09/vegan-influencer-eats-meat-for-30-days-shocks-fans-by-saying-shes-healthier-than-shes-felt-in-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, that’s a big change. A formerly vegan influencer revealed to her fans that she spent 30 days eating nothing but meat and animal products. She also revealed that the new diet had some surprisi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 2 women's trip to Florida strip club sparked constitutional bout...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/orange-county/os-ne-rachels-human-rights-ordinance-20191209-4greouwqafbx7nqi7k67zf7h3q-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On her weekly trips to an Orlando strip club, Brittney Smith noticed that one of the dancers looked very familiar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENGALS:  NFL looking into if PATS taped sideline...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28261318/bengals-nfl-looking-patriots-taped-sideline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cincinnati Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Monday that the NFL is investigating whether the New England Patriots were videotaping in the press box Sunday's game against the Cleveland Browns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK govt criticized for hiding details of AMAZON data deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/alexa-what-is-transparency-government-criticised-for-hiding-details-of-amazon-data-deal-11882241</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health Secretary Matt Hancock signed the deal giving Amazon access to NHS data, but the NHS is refusing to reveal on what terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents Trashed Clinton as 'Criminal', Celebrated Trump Winning Election...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/09/fbi-agent-new-jobs-2016-election-trump-hillary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the day after the 2016 election, a pro-Trump FBI agent texted another, saying that &amp;quot;shit just got real.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star athlete whose battle with ALS inspired 'Ice Bucket Challenge' dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/pete-frates-whose-battle-with-als-inspired-ice-bucket-challenge-dies-at-34/30171879</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Frates, whose battle with ALS inspired the "Ice Bucket Challenge" to raise millions of dollars for research and awareness of the disease, has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr condemns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/ag-barr-condemns-ig-report-s-finding-fbi-probe-trump-n1098451</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney general said the investigation was launched on the "thinnest of suspicions."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DYNASTY:  Grandson of late President Bush runs for Congress in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08f0a9a637debc8d1be04b53296b3f7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Pierce Bush, the grandson of former President George H.W. Bush, announced his candidacy Monday for a congressional seat in Texas, becoming the latest member of his famous...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scathing critique of FBI wiretap application...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/internal-justice-watchdog-finds-russia-probe-was-justified-not-biased-n1098161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Barr and a prosecutor he tapped to lead a separate review of the Russia probe immediately criticized the DOJ inspector general's findings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.justice.gov/storage/120919-examination.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.justice.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORGANSTANLEY layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/09/morgan-stanley-cutting-jobs-due-to-uncertain-environment-sources.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York-based Morgan Stanley had 60,532 employees as of September 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The surprising things stolen from luxury hotels...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/12/09/world/mattresses-stolen-luxury-hotels-intl-scli/index.html?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When checking out of a five-star hotel, thrifty travelers have been known to slip a few shower caps, mini-shampoos or even slippers into their suitcases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCHDOG: FBI's Russia probe justified, no bias found...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a734c40d142c8950f57ad4c8f8af565c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The FBI was justified in opening its investigation into ties between the Trump presidential campaign and Russia and did not act with political bias, despite “serious performance...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tested new rocket engine to provoke USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/73b6635438481b6fbe9451dfea49699d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — A day after North Korea said it had performed a “very important test” at its long-range rocket launch site, there is wide speculation that it involved a new engine for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANY MISTAKES...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191209173451-zfucj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-No political bias but many mistakes in FBI probe of Trump campaign - watchdog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SO LONG, BLACK ROCK:  CBS' Historic Headquarters to Be Sold...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cbs-black-rock-new-york-headquarters-be-sold-1260942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The office building, located at 51 West 52nd Street at the corner of Sixth Avenue, has served as CBS’ headquarters since it was completed in 1964.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causes of Wall Street cash crunch remains mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/09/bis-report-warns-of-ripple-of-problems-in-short-term-funding-markets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big banks and hedge funds helped fuel disruptions in the overnight lending markets a few months ago, the Bank of International Settlements said in a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nadler Fails to Swear in Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/12/09/nadler-failed-to-swear-in-witnesses-at-judiciary-impeachment-hearings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Nadler failed to swear in impeachment witnesses until after opening statements, letting Democrat Barry Berke make dubious claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WE VOTE BY FILM, NOT SEX'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/golden-globes-female-directors-shut-out-1203429629/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite gains in the number of films and TV shows helmed by women, female directors were completely shut out of the Golden Globes once again this year. The snub was immediately called out on social…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNARD GOLDBERG:  The only thing Trump has to fear in 2020 is Trump himself...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/473254-the-only-thing-trump-has-to-fear-in-2020-is-trump-himself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the president has to do is change his ways, turn himself into a new-and-improved Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi gets standing ovation at Kennedy Center Honors...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/473619-pelosi-gets-standing-ovation-at-kennedy-center-honors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) received a standing ovation at a Trump-less Kennedy Center Honors late Sunday, which largely stayed away from political talk but had moments that alluded to the tense partisan climate around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWSUIT THREAT...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/clint-eastwood-lawsuit-threat-richard-jewell-film-warner-bros-atlanta-journal-constitution-1202804529/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Jewell opens wide this week, but the Clint Eastwood directed film could find itself in court soon afterwards facing defamation charges if Atlanta’s leading newspaper doesn’t get…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O: It's surreal...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/news/michelle-obama-speaks-out-impeachment-proceedings-t169452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former first lady opened up about a number of issues in an exclusive interview with TODAY's Jenna Bush Hager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia banned from ALL global sport for 4 years over doping...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/football/10512594/russia-four-year-sport-ban-world-cup-olympics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA have been banned from all global sport, including the World Cup 2022 and 2020 Olympics, after being hit with FOUR-YEAR suspension over the recent doping scandals. The nation – who host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds Kentucky abortion law mandating ultrasounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/supreme-court-upholds-kentucky-abortion-law-mandating-ultrasounds-n1098181</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors must perform ultrasounds and have women listen to fetal heartbeats before performing abortions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparks outrage by flying 90 miles in plane instead of bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/boris-johnson-sparks-outrage-flying-21059449  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Prime Minister took a plane for around two-thirds of the 156-mile journey between Grimsby and Washington - weeks after allies claimed his general election manifesto would be the greenest in history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFOWARS Host Booted From Judiciary Committee After Protesting...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/reporter-arrested-after-calling-impeachment-hearings-a-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Owen Shroyer booked in Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CLEAR AND PRESENT DANGER'</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Lawyer-for-Democrats-calls-President-Trump-a-14892874.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A lawyer for Democrats on the House Intelligence Committee called President Trump "a clear and present danger" as he summarized the party's case for impeaching him for having abused his power and obstructed a congressional investigation into his conduct in Urkaine.  The testimony from Daniel Goldman came amid a crucial hearing at which lawyers for both Democrats and Republicans are making cases for and against impeachment. Earlier, Stephen Castor, a lawyer for Republicans called impeachment "baloney" and said Democrats had failed to make a compelling case.  At the heart of the Democrats' case is the allegation that Trump tried to leverage a White House meeting and military aid, sought by Ukraine to combat Russian military aggression, to pressure President Volodymyr Zelensky to launch an investigation of former vice president Joe Biden and his son Hunter Biden, as well as a probe of an unfounded theory that Kyiv conspired with Democrats to interfere in the 2016 presidential election.  Goldman, the top investigative counsel for the House Intelligence Committee, summarized the Democratic case for impeachment in his presentation.  "We are here today because Donald J. Trump, the 45th president of the United States, abused the power of his office, the American presidency, for his political and personal benefit," Goldman said. "As part of this scheme, President Trump applied increasing pressure on the president of Ukraine to publicly announce two investigations helpful to his personal reelection efforts."  He later added: "When faced with the opening of an official impeachment inquiry into his conduct, President Trump launched an unprecedented campaign of obstruction of Congress - ordering executive branch agencies and government officials to defy subpoenas for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTA NEWSPAPER DEMANDS DISCLAIMER ON EASTWOOD'S 'RICHARD JEWELL'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/clint-eastwood-richard-jewell-kathy-scruggs-1203429660/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlanta Journal-Constitution is asking Warner Bros. and the makers of “Richard Jewell” to release a statement acknowledging it took dramatic license when it portrayed journalist Kat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Gears Up for Most Divisive Election in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-election-campaign-enters-final-rounds-brexit-line-023320612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's election campaign entered its frenetic final straight Monday with Prime Minister Boris Johnson trying to lock in the votes needed to draw a line under years of arguments and paralysis over European Union membership. Johnson is hoping Thursday's poll hands his ruling Conservatives the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  More Americans Delaying Medical Treatment Due to Cost...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/269138/americans-delaying-medical-treatment-due-cost.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putting off treatment for a medical condition because of the cost is at a high ebb in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLOMON:  IG report lays out evidence FBI misled FISA court...</title>
      <link>https://johnsolomonreports.com/ig-report-provides-compelling-evidence-fbi-misled-fisa-court-in-russia-case-sources-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;johnsolomonreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERALDO SNAPS ON CNN: 'F*CK RUSSIA AND F*CK YOU'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/09/geraldo-rivera-cnn-fox-news-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geraldo Rivera got quite angry Sunday on Twitter over a CNN segment about Fox's alleged &amp;quot;Russia infatuation,&amp;quot; telling a critic &amp;quot;fuck you.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea calls Trump 'heedless and erratic old man' after tweets...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e45a5ea9fa921f9180c6d6d36223ec14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea insulted U.S. President Donald Trump again on Monday, calling him a “heedless and erratic old man” after he tweeted that North Korean leader Kim Jong Un...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: RAPPER JUICE WRLD ALLEGEDLY POPPED PILLS BEFORE SEIZURES... </title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/12/09/juice-wrld-private-jet-drugs-70-pounds-marijuana-arrests-feds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The private jet Juice WRLD flew to Chicago on was loaded down with 70 pounds of marijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans learned to smile 'to get sex' in prehistoric times, study claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10512223/humans-learned-to-smile-for-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SMILES were developed by ancient humans as a way to attract less-aggressive mates, according to a new study. A team of scientists is claiming that the kindness humans can show via facial expression…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art Basel Takes Another Crazy Turn With Epstein Graffiti...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/art-basel-takes-another-crazy-turn-with-jeffrey-epstein-graffiti</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exhibit wall that once held the $120,000 duct-taped banana was vandalized on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic priests beset by overwork, isolation, scandals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bcac665d78417b6acd0288ad8493f7dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICOPEE, Mass. (AP) — More than a century ago, waves of Catholic immigrants from Ireland, Poland and Quebec settled in Chicopee and other western Massachusetts mill towns, helping build churches,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFOWARS Host Booted From House Judiciary Committee After Protesting...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/infowars-host-booted-from-house-judiciary-committee-after-interrupting-impeachment-hearing-with-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee's second hearing on the Donald Trump impeachment inquiry was instantly derailed on Monday when a supporter of the president launched a protest at the start of the pr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodybuilder set to marry his sex robot girlfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/bodybuilder-set-marry-sex-robot-21055600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yuri Tolochko, from Kazakhstan, will marry his sex robot girlfriend Margo after paying for the doll to have plastic surgery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GAME OF THRONES' Fans Furious...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/tv-shows/2019/12/09/game-of-thrones-fans-furious-golden-globes-final-season-snub/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Game of Thrones fans were furious Monday morning to discover that the final season of the HBO [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Industry Suffers Steepest Drop in Ad Sales Since Recession...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tv-industry-suffers-steepest-drop-133000490.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global TV advertising sales fell almost 4% in 2019, the steepest drop since the depths of the economic recession in 2009, in the latest sign that advertisers are following viewers to the internet.Declines in TV viewership have suppressed the medium’s advertising dollars, according to research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Arrested For Driving Drunk On Highway -- On Horseback!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/12/08/drunken-man-arrested-after-injuring-horse-while-riding-it-on-dallas-highway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man has been arrested in downtown Dallas after witnesses say he was riding a horse — drunk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro Snubbed...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/12/golden-globe-snubs-nominations-surprises-game-of-thrones-robert-de-niro-female-directors-watchmen-the-politician-1202804345/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day perhaps the Hollywood Foreign Press Association will join the 21st century and realize they don’t need to announce the Golden Globes nominations before dawn anymore. However, that’s not tod…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Love for 'CATS'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e547f34fe0a07278d2e811b688646de3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Some Golden Globe nominations seemed like locks: Joaquin Phoenix, Tom Hanks, Adam Driver and Eddie Murphy. But others were shocks, like Lupita Nyong'o not getting a nomination for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials misled public about Afghan war, confidential docs reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/confidential-documents-reveal-us-officials-failed-to-tell-the-truth-about-the-war-in-afghanistan/ar-BBXY8l1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JOKER' Nabs Numerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/golden-globes-joker-nabs-4-2020-nominations-1260831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Warner Bros. film inspired by the Batman villain had a total of four nominations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley psychedelic wonder drug almost here...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90436824/silicon-valleys-psychedelic-wonder-drug-is-almost-here</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new startup called MindMed could have the key to providing the upsides of psychedelic drugs for both focus and addiction treatment—while cutting out the downsides of tripping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Fed Chairman Volcker Dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/09/paul-volcker-the-carter-reagan-fed-chairman-who-beat-inflation-dies-at-92.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As chairman of the Federal Reserve under Presidents Carter and Reagan, Paul Volcker helped tame inflation with 20% interest rates that also crunched American manufacturing, farming and real estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: Hearing on Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?467123-1/hearing-evidence-impeachment-inquiry&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee holds a hearing to hear evidence in the on-going impeachment inquiry against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only Male Directors...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/golden-globe-nominations-female-director-snub-1203429487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year distinguished by a record number of hit movies directed by women, from “Hustlers” to “The Farewell,” the Golden Globes once again nominated five men in the best directing category. No wom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast TV Shut Out...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/12/09/golden-globe-nominations-2020-globes-awards-nominees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations for the 77th Annual Golden Globe Awards were announced on Monday morning in Beverly Hills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/golden-globes-nominees-2020-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nominees for the 77th Golden Globes are coming our way, rapid-fire. What shows, movies and talent will be up for a trophy at next month's Golden Globes?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Play Sports For Sharper Mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/play-sports-for-sharper-mind-study-finds-athletes-have-healthier-brains-than-others/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An interesting new study conducted at Northwestern University is playing devil's advocate in the debate surrounding sports and brain health in athletes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first human composting site to open...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/funeral-green-burial-climate-change-environment-soil-composting-recompose-seattle-a9238896.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Big Wake-up Call': 'Giant UFO' Over California Seen 'by More Than 100 Witnesses'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/us/201912091077520365-a-big-wake-up-call-giant-ufo-over-california-reportedly-seen-by-more-than-100-witnesses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The object could have been taken for a drone or a skydiving vehicle, if not for a combination of facts: it didn’t move and emitted no sound whatsoever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible pardons loom for former Trump aides...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/09/possible-pardons-loom-former-trump-aides-078480</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s willingness to toss aside optics is giving hope to former aides and allies that the president might grant deeply controversial pardons in the coming months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commuters face 300-mile traffic jam as French strikes bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/09/france-strike-paris-sees-500-kilometers-of-traffic-jam-amid-protestsover-pension-reform.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French commuters experienced a chaotic journey getting to work on Monday as public sector workers entered a fifth consecutive day of nationwide strikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No signs of life'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/new-zealand-pm-people-unaccounted-for-as-volcano-erupts-11882051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists recently noticed an uptick in volcanic activity on White Island, prompting questions over why visitors were allowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary hearing sets stage for charges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4ed63e09b3cb2aa2119246194118470</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pushing ahead with articles of impeachment, the House Judiciary Committee convenes Monday to formally receive the investigative findings against President Donald Trump as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booed off  field by angry fans; Questions stacking up...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Questions-keep-stacking-up-against-Patriots-and-14891882.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. - Predicting the demise of the New England Patriots is a long-running parlor game that leaves no winners, only regret and fools. The onset of doom, for them, ends with trophies and parades, with Bill Belichick cracking his annual half-smile and Tom Brady somehow looking younger. Declaring the end of the Patriots is both pointless venture and folly.  But we also don't know what the end will look like, so we might not be able to identify it even when it happens in front of our eyes. What if the end looks like an impotent offense surrendering amid the strange sound of Gillette Stadium boos at halftime? What if it looks like Brady engulfed in the pocket and fuming on the sideline days after his father openly speculated in the local newspaper about his son's future? What if looks like undrafted rookie Jakobi Meyers running wide open across the middle and allowing a pinpoint pass to slip through his fingers? What if it looks like Brady sitting on his backside, a final pass having fluttered to the turf, as the visiting sideline erupts?  What if the end looks like Sunday evening?  The Patriots still hold a bye in the AFC playoffs, and they may yet win their seventh Super Bowl two months from now. If they do, they will think back to the first half of Sunday's 23-16 defeat and marvel at how they ever sailed so far ashore. In a rematch of last year's AFC championship game, the Kansas City Chiefs snapped the Patriots' 21-game home winning streak, playoffs included, and disabused anyone of the notion that the Patriots are presently a championship-caliber outfit.  The Patriots rebounded in the second half, and Brady threw a pass into the end zone with 1:06 left that could have given the Patriots a chance to tie or take the lead. If not for untimely officiating misadventures, New England may well have won. Then...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
