<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES PAGE ONE THURSDAY:  Men fight back after Saudi Arabia women allowed to drive...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/saudi-arabia-s-women-are-allowed-to-drive-but-not/article_59493d70-b8a7-5f7b-a4c0-de54149caef4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT — From the very first day 31-year-old Salma Barakati got behind the wheel of her car after Saudi Arabia lifted the ban on women driving, the men in her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem warns 'dangerously close'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/video/2018/08/01/durbin-trump-dangerously-close-to-obstruction-of-justice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday's broadcast of CNN's "Cuomo Primetime," Senate Minority Whip Dick Durbin (D-IL) stated President Trump is "dangerously close" to committing | Breitbart TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC urges Americans to stop washing, reusing condoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/health/cdc-urges-americans-to-stop-washing-reusing-condoms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention issued a reminder that some may laugh at. But apparently, it needs to be said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY: Election about impeachment or no impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/01/trump-lawyer-giuliani-says-midterms-will-answer-impeachment-question.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani said Wednesday the upcoming midterm elections will be a referendum on impeaching the president. If Democrats hold the majority in the House, there won't be enough votes to prevent impeachment proceedings, he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 518 inquires tied to potential outbreak from single CHIPOTLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/01/ohio-health-agency-gets-518-inquires-in-potential-chipotle-outbreak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Delaware General Health District said Wednesday that it had received a total of 518 inquiries — 95 emails and 423 calls — related to a possible outbreak stemming from a Chipotle in Powell, Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN ACOSTA: Trump Rally 'Felt Like We Weren't in America Anymore'... </title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/video/2018/08/01/acosta-on-facing-cnn-sucks-chant-at-trump-rally-it-felt-like-we-werent-in-america-anymore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wednesday, on HLN’s "S.E. Cupp Unfiltered," CNN Chief White House correspondent Jim Acosta said being shouted at by Trump supporters at a rally in Tampa, | Breitbart TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTRESS: If They Fire Mueller, We Take to Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/08/01/alyssa-milano-if-they-fire-mueller-we-take-to-the-streets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Alyssa Milano put out a call to the Resistance, warning of a revolt if Robert Mueller's investigation into the 2016 election is ended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor: Trump Will Be 'Most Pro-Black President in Our Lifetime'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/01/pastor-predicts-donald-trump-will-be-the-most-pro-black-president-in-our-lifetime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pastor Darrell Scott thanked Trump for helping inner-city communities, predicting he would be the “most pro-black president in our lifetime.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS BREWS WITH THE COMMUNISTS; PLANS 2,000 STORES WITH ALIBABA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/02/starbucks-ceo-confirms-alibaba-partnership-china-delivery-expansion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks CEO Kevin Johnson tells CNBC that the coffeemaker's just-announced partnership with Alibaba will, without a doubt, "be an accelerator for our business."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESSIONS SILENT AFTER TRUMP DEMAND</title>
      <link>http://www.vagazette.com/la-na-pol-trump-mueller-20180801-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vagazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump called on Atty. Gen. Jeff Sessions to “stop this Rigged Witch Hunt right now,” opening the president to further complaints that he is trying to obstruct the investigation into Russia’s election interference and his campaign’s possible complicity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Nervous As Military Choppers Buzz Over Pittsburgh For Days...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/08/01/military-choppers-pittsburgh-law-enforcement-tactical-training/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City officials say military helicopter drills have been in the works for over a year with the Department of Defense and other agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy-hunting foes sue to shut down Trump wildlife board...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180801203637-ocnpu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/WILDLIFE-LAWSUIT (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Trophy-hunting foes sue to shut down Trump wildlife board</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURLEY: Tweets NOT Crimes, But Could Be Costly...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2018/08/01/donald-trump-tweets-jeff-sessions-not-obstruction-justice-column/881960002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s inflammatory tweets are costly for his administration. But they shouldn't be used as the basis for a criminal allegation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAK DOUBLES DOWN: Stands by anthem comments despite backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/sports/nfl/dallas-cowboys/article215893955.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas Cowboys QB Dak Prescott has received a barrage of criticism on social media since his comments about standing for national anthem went viral last week. He has no regrets but says he was misunderstood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGHT IN TEX: BETO CLOSES IN ON CRUZ?</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/article215907475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll shows a single-digit lead for Republican Sen. Ted Cruz over Democratic challenger U.S. Rep. Beto O’Rourke of El Paso for Cruz’s U.S. Senate seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study Shows One Overheated Laptop Battery Could Down Airliner...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/01/study-shows-one-overheated-laptop-battery-could-down-an-airliner </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study Shows One Overheated Laptop Battery Could Down an Airliner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERRY BROWN:  Worse 'Since Civilization Emerged 10,000 Years Ago'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/news-and-politics/jerry-brown-fire-fueling-heat-worse-than-since-civilization-emerged-10000-years-ago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor said that steps to combat global warming&amp;nbsp;can still “shift the weather back to where it historically was" and dial back fire threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'OBSTRUCTION' QUESTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/special-counsel-mueller-president-obstruction-justice-sources/story?id=56973384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller wants to ask President Donald Trump about possible obstruction of justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor praises Trump as 'pro-black' at prison reform event...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/trump-talks-prison-reform-pastors-56972301 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was lauded by inner-city pastors, including one who said he may go down as the "most pro-black president" in recent history, during a White House roundtable on Wednesday that was focused on efforts to reform the prison system. Trump told the group, which included...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters faces questions on mailer money, daughter's 'enrichment'... </title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/01/maxine-waters-hit-with-fec-complaint-over-mailer-money.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Rep. Maxine Waters, one of the most outspoken members of the anti-Trump ‘resistance’ in Congress, is facing fresh questions about a longstanding controversy regarding how her campaign raises money and how those funds have flowed to her daughter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Farrakhan Blames 'Outside Forces' for NETFLIX Rejecting His Film...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/louis-farrakhan-asks-outside-forces-kept-film-off-netflix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New statement from Nation of Islam asks whether "opponents of truth" pressured Netflix to not stream the doc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seth Rogen Film Defends Putting Child Actor in Blackface...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/pop-culture/2018/08/seth-rogen-produced-film-company-defends-putting-child-actor-in-blackface</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The production company insists this is not an example of blackface, and darker makeup was used on the African-American stand-in to match skintones for lighting purposes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk apology to scorned analysts sends stock soaring...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/01/musk-s-apology-to-analysts-he-scorned-sends-tesla-stock-soaring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk's Apology to Analysts He Scorned Sends Tesla Stock Soaring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Naked man in 'chem-induced psychosis' hit by car after taking hostage at knifepoint...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-naked-man-20180801-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The naked suspect got hit by a car, ending the standoff after he got spooked by a hovering helicopter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstaining from alcohol heightens dementia risk?</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/abstaining-from-alcohol-heightens-dementia-risk-by-as-much-as-45-per-cent-survey-suggests-a3901891.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who drink more than the recommended alcohol limit and those who are teetotal are at a heightened risk of dementia, a new study suggests. Scientists examined data on more than 9,000 people who took part in the survey, which tracked the health of civil servants working in London. Abstinence was found to be associated with a staggering 45 per cent higher risk of dementia compared to those who consumed between one and 14 unites of alcohol a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at 'shoddy renovations' as Great Wall of China section collapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/997622/great-wall-of-china-collapsing-heavy-rainfall-renovation-wechat-shanxi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SECTION of the Great Wall of China has collapsed after recent heavy rains – with critics suggesting that recent renovation works which they believe had weakened its structure are partly to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium charging journalists to cover EU summits...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/blogs/on-media/2018/08/journalist-press-fee-belgium-criticized-for-charging-reporters-to-attend-eu-summits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazi flag hoisted at Wyoming park...</title>
      <link>https://trib.com/news/state-and-regional/nazi-flag-hoisted-in-laramie-park-police-department-investigating/article_9aef03f0-862d-51d2-ab74-b810837134d5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;trib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laramie Police found an American flag crumpled on the ground and a Nazi flag in its place on a city flagpole Monday, a police spokeswoman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee rages at 'Billionaire Bezos' after work injury forces her to live in car park...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6914589/amazon-employee-vickie-shannon-allen-49-posts-youtube-videos-claiming-she-now-lives-in-warehouse-car-park-after-being-injured-at-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ex-Amazon employee claims she ended up being evicted from her home and having to sleep at the warehouse car park after becoming injured at work and receiving no sick pay. Vickie Shannon Allen, 4…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON lobby group to battle Postal Service change...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-shippers-post-office/amazon-forms-u-s-postal-service-lobby-group-with-other-companies-idUSKBN1KM5X0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc and other retail and logistics companies said on Wednesday they had started a new group to lobby to keep the U.S. Postal Service's (USPS) package delivery services "reliable and affordable."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New telescope picks up mysterious space signal...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/new-radio-telescope-picks-up-mysterious-signal-from-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new observatory may have already found clues to one of the newest mysteries in astronomy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Trillion-Dollar Share Price: $207.05</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-08-01/apple-s-new-trillion-dollar-number-for-stock-price-is-207-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holding your breath for Apple Inc. to break $1 trillion? There’s a new magic number to fixate on. And it’s less than 3 percent away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need for speed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-08-01/manafort-judge-s-need-for-speed-jolts-prosecution-off-its-game</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. prosecutors want to tell a jury about Paul Manafort’s lavish lifestyle and spending habits to support their claim that he failed to pay taxes on offshore income and defrauded banks. The judge isn’t making it easy for them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAG ORDER: Judge duct-tapes robber's mouth shut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/court-justice/index.ssf/2018/07/cuyahoga_county_judge_orders_c_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Cuyahoga County judge ordered a convicted robber's mouth taped shut during his sentencing on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple struggle to find videographer to film wedding night sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.bristolpost.co.uk/news/local-news/couple-take-out-ad-looking-1849562</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bristolpost.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It will be their first night as married partners yet they want to introduce a third person into the bedroom - and no one they know is up for it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Ambient Church, sacred setting for radically meditative music...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/music/la-et-ms-0802-ambient-church-20180801-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popular New York concert series, which brings experimental composers into re-purposed churches, makes its L.A. debut with the analog synthesis pioneer Suzanne Ciani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: GROW YOUR OWN ORGANS BY 2023!?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/08/01/grow-your-own-organs-could-within-five-years-scientists-prove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grow-your-own organs could be available for desperately ill patients within five years, after scientists successfully transplanted bioengineered lungs into pigs for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug Sellers Tout GRINDR Safety: Don't Fear Dealer Battles...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/sex-drugs-popular-gay-dating-app-allows-users-find-more-n896081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite Grindr’s past efforts to address the selling and promoting of drugs on its app, those who use it say there’s still a robust market for illicit substances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resistance Builds to Canada 'Smart City'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/local-resistance-builds-to-googles-smart-city-in-toronto-1533135550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Alphabet project aimed at creating a “smart city” on Toronto’s waterfront is facing resistance from local officials who are worried about the development’s direction and how Google’s parent company will handle residents’ personal data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge scolds prosecutors, but uses intellect to their benefit...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/public-safety/he-has-torn-my-head-off-manafort-judge-known-for-being-tough/2018/07/31/f604e25a-6f28-11e8-afd5-778aca903bbe_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge T.S. Ellis has degrees from Princeton, Harvard and Oxford and 31 years on the bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Expected to Rest Case Next Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2018-08-01/the-latest-trump-wants-attorney-general-to-end-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffett Metric Points to Market Crash?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/this-favorite-warren-buffett-metric-tells-us-a-stock-market-crash-could-be-coming/ar-BBL7KZy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas sand dunes go from worthless to mega-valuable...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/energy/texas-sand-dunes-go-from-worthless-desert-to-mega-valuable-commodity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s how one company has turned a dusty wasteland into a high-valued commodity in the Permian Basin of Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP WARNS MUELLER</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/01/trump-urges-attorney-general-sessions-to-stop-mueller-probe-right-now.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump escalates his attacks on the Mueller's probe of Russian meddling in the 2016 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELLS SESSIONS TO 'END IT'</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-sessions-twitter-stop-rigged-witch-hunt/story?id=56962100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Wednesday made what appeared to be his most direct public call yet for Attorney General Jeff Sessions to shut down special counsel Robert Mueller's Russia investigation, but his personal attorney later described it as only Trump's "opinion." Trump took to Twitter to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AS THE PROBE TURNS!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6015393/Trump-tells-Jeff-Sessions-end-Russia-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Press Secretary Sarah Sanders said a morning tweet from the president demanding Sessions end the Mueller probe was not an official order but a simple statement of views which he has long held.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA to eliminate screening at smaller airports?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/01/politics/tsa-considering-eliminating-screening-at-smaller-airports/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TSA is considering eliminating passenger screening at more than 150 small and medium-sized airports, according to senior agency officials and internal documents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDE NAST selling 3 magazines...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/01/business/media/conde-nast-vogue-magazines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anna Wintour is staying, but the once-plush company behind Vogue and The New Yorker lost $120 million last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPERBOY: Michael Phelps World Record Broken By 10-Year-Old -- Named Clark Kent!</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/07/31/clark-kent-beats-michael-phelps-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clark Kent, a 10-year-old from California nicknamed "Superman," beat retired Olympic swimmer Michael Phelps' record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIULIANI TO MUELLER: 'PUT UP OR SHUT UP'...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/01/giuliani-to-mueller-put-up-or-shut-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'They should render their report'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Burqa Ban' comes into effect in Denmark amid protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/08/01/burqa-ban-comes-into-effect-denmark/878286002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who break the law for the first time can be fined $157, and repeat offenders face fines of up to $1,570, or six months in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sues MCDONALD'S, says employee drugged him...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2018/07/31/utah-man-is-suing-after/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachelle Walker was working on a client’s hair in her in-home salon when the mystifying texts from her husband appeared on her phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Depressed' Canine Won't Eat After 'Best Friend' Guinea Pig Dies...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/08/01/pup-mourns-guinea-pig-friend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dog's touching farewell to his best friend is breaking hearts on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALASKA AIRLINES panned after gay couple had to give up seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Alaska-faces-outrage-after-gay-couple-made-to-13122495.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) - Alaska Airlines faces outrage from people on social media after a gay couple had to give up seats on a New York City-Los Angeles flight to make room for a straight couple. The Seattle Times reports the couple accepted an apology Tuesday from the airline, which said there was a seating mistake not reflective of disrespect in Sunday's incident. David Cooley said he and his traveling companion were in their assigned seats when a gate agent asked his companion to give up his seat and move so another couple could sit together. Coley, owner of a popular upscale gay bar in the West Hollywood section of Los Angeles, recounted the incident in posts on Facebook and Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian to be charged after being hit by tractor-trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/pedestrian-charged-after-being-hit-tractor-trailer/FuDT0ZSCeH6YmginQViV8N/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;﻿A woman who was hospitalized after she stepped in front of a tractor-trailer in southwest Atlanta o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran readying massive military exercise in Persian Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/01/politics/us-iran-military-exercise-gulf/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's Islamic Revolutionary Guard forces are expected to begin a major exercise in the Persian Gulf as soon as within the next 48 hours that could be aimed at demonstrating their ability to shut down the Strait of Hormuz, according to two US officials directly familiar with the latest US assessment of IRGC troop movements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eiffel Tower shuts as workers strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/eiffel-tower-shuts-workers-strike-over-long-visitor-183809399.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staff at the Eiffel Tower walked out on strike on Wednesday in a dispute over lengthening queues at the Paris landmark, forcing it to close during the peak summer tourist season. Talks between the CGT trade union and the tower's management over a new access system - which according to workers was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CONGRATULATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.rushlimbaugh.com/daily/2018/08/01/president-trump-calls-the-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rushlimbaugh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PRESIDENT: This is your favorite president, and I think you are fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA SNUBS NEW DEM STAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/barack-obama-releases-list-of-dem-midterm-endorsements-see-if-you-can-spot-ocasio-cortez/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superbugs now becoming resistant to alcohol disinfectants...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/superbugs-now-becoming-resistant-alcohol-disinfectants-181456258.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multidrug-resistant "superbugs" that can cause dangerous infections in hospitals are becoming increasingly resistant to alcohol-based hand sanitizers and disinfectants designed to hold them at bay, scientists said. In a study of what the researchers described as a "new wave of superbugs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT HACKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.shacknews.com/article/106481/reddit-was-hacked-all-user-data-from-2007-earlier-accessed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shacknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Reddit team is cooperating with law enforcement and taking steps to further secure the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,400 elementary school teachers in NC flunk math exams...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/education/article215848065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of NC teachers have failed their math licensing exam, putting their jobs at risk, since North Carolina started paying Pearson testing company to administer the test. State officials say the new exam may be the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey punished over imprisonment of American pastor...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/01/trump-administration-to-sanction-turkish-officials-over-imprisonment-of-american-pastor-756896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brunson was arrested in October 2016 in Izmir, Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Island Rail Road train derails in Queens... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/01/lirr-train-derails-in-queens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long Island Rail Road train carrying about 500 passengers derailed in Queens on Wednesday afternoon, officials said. The 12:19 p.m. train from Penn Station to Port Washington derailed just as it …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing demand sees biggest drop in 2+ years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/01/housing-demand-sees-biggest-drop-in-more-than-2-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Housing demand has been very strong, but red-hot home prices, combined with higher mortgage rates, are finally taking their toll on affordability and demand. Housing demand in June fell by the biggest margin since April 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rappers brawl in Paris airport, disrupting flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-rappers-fight/french-rappers-brawl-in-paris-airport-disrupting-flights-idUSKBN1KM5NM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A punch-up between two rival French rappers that descended into a mass brawl in the departure lounge of Paris' Orly airport on Wednesday forced the brief closure of one terminal and caused flight delays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EBOLA OUTBREAK: Killer disease WARNING as fresh cases discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/997484/ebola-outbreak-dr-congo-ebola-outbreak-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Ebola virus outbreak has been confirmed in eastern Democratic Republic of Congo's North Kivu province, the country's Governor has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANISTON: Been 'treated worse' by women in Hollywood than men...</title>
      <link>https://www.instyle.com/news/jennifer-aniston-september-cover</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.instyle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“With all due respect, I’m not heartbroken.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOLSONCOORS brewing cannabis drinks...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/molson-coors-brewing-cannabis-drinks-canadian-market-151433003.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beer giant Molson Coors said Wednesday it is teaming up with a Canadian pot producer to develop cannabis-infused non-alcoholic beverages. The brewer behind popular brands such as Coors Light and Molson Canadian will have a majority stake (57.5 percent) in the standalone joint venture with medical marijuana</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged after freeing dogs from hot car...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkyc.com/article/news/local/cuyahoga-county/parma-man-cited-for-criminal-damage-after-rescuing-dogs-from-car/95-578778235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkyc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Parma man is facing charges after doing what he thought was a good deed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Wades Into Contentious Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-wades-into-high-stakes-primaries-for-young-progressives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator is getting more active in gubernatorial primaries for younger, more progressive candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary to executive produce TV drama with Spielberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/hillary-clinton-adapting-womans-hour-tv-steven-spielberg-1131291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amblin TV has optioned the rights to Elaine Weiss' 'The Woman's Hour: The Great Fight to Win the Vote," with the former secretary of state and first lady attached as an executive producer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES: Hollywood's First All-Asian Movie in 25 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/crazy-rich-asians-story-behind-rom-com-1130965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new film's creators turned down a "gigantic payday" at Netflix to ensure the first Asian-American-focused studio movie in 25 years would be seen in theaters and, if all goes well, reshape the Hollywood landscape: "The biggest stage with the biggest stakes — that's what we asked for."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President calls 'hoax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/paul-manafort-trial-bank-fraud-today-2018-08-01-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manafort trial enters day two after prosecutors painted Manafort as being "above the law"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Raid 'Occupy ICE' Protest In Sacramento, Clear Camp, Seize Gear...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/31/occupy-ice-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists say they were just protesting President Trump’s immigration policies, and claim what may have looked like a campsite is just part of their message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Heart Attack Victim Waits 43 Minutes For Ambulance After Calling 911...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/07/30/heart-attack-victim-waited-43-minutes-for-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State standards require fire departments to provide advance life support assistance within six minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENDLESS INFERNO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/it-just-goes-on-and-on-new-wildfires-erupt-in-scorched-northern-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest blazes spread with shocking speed through bone-dry forest and brush, prompting new evacuations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Dog Lick Causes Blood Infection, Man Has Both Legs Amputated...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/07/31/dog-lick-blood-infection-amputate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greg Manteufel contracted Capnocytophaga canimorsus, a bacteria found in dog saliva that can cause sepsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Pregnant Dolphin. A Fatal Gunshot. A Disturbing Trend...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/01/us/pregnant-dolphin-shot-reward.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case is the latest example of violence against dolphins in the northern Gulf of Mexico, which experts say is becoming increasingly common.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Board Pressed for Monnves Investigation Weeks Before Ronan Expose...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/les-moonves-cbs-investigation-board-letter-metoo-tipping-point-1131238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As sexual misconduct claims threaten to bring down the CBS CEO, industry insiders take sides and The Hollywood Reporter reveals a board letter that questioned why no action had been taken weeks before Ronan Farrow's bombshell investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Clinton, Steven Spielberg Bringing Women's Voting Drama to TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/hillary-clinton-adapting-womans-hour-tv-steven-spielberg-1131291  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amblin TV has optioned the rights to Elaine Weiss' 'The Woman's Hour: The Great Fight to Win the Vote," with the former secretary of state and first lady attached as an exec producer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY TWO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/01/politics/manafort-trial-day-two/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Day two of the Paul Manafort trial gets underway Wednesday with testimony expected from a Democratic consultant who worked on Ukrainian political campaigns and President Donald Trump attacking special counsel Robert Mueller and federal investigators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley records hottest month EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6916022/death-valley-hottest-place-earth-record-temperatures-monthly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEATH Valley in California recorded the hottest ever recorded month this July with an average of 108 degrees Fahrenheit (42C). The remarkable temperature broke the record clocked at the Furnace Cre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian-Flagged Vessel Returns Migrants To Libya...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/08/for-first-time-in-a-decade-italian-flagged-vessel-returns-migrants-to-libya-open-borders-activists-outraged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rock Band Flirts with German Taboos, and Finds Huge Following...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/01/arts/music/freiwild-germany.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frei.Wild has become one of the most popular bands in Germany. But critics say the group fosters anti-immigrant sentiment and right-wing nationalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica to change constitution to legalize taking away white farmers' land...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/434784-south-africa-amendemnt-land-expropriation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South African President Cyril Ramaphosa has said the ruling African National Congress must initiate a parliamentary process to enshrine in the constitution a proposed amendment, paving the way for land grabs without compensation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA EARNINGS: HIGH STAKES FOR MUSK...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/01/news/companies/tesla-earnings-walkup/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla will post its quarterly earnings Wednesday, and all eyes will be on the cash burn rate and clues about Model 3 demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem takeover could bring first black speaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/01/house-speaker-african-american-democrats-753177</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upheaval in the Democratic caucus could pave the way for a historic House leader — and some potential names are already being discussed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT: PRIVATE PAYROLLS BOOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/01/adp-private-payrolls-increase-by-219000-vs-185000-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private payrolls in the U.S. grew more than expected last month as companies get a boost from lower corporate taxes, ADP and Moody's Analytics said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden leads Trump in early match-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/01/biden-trump-2020-elections-752979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plurality of registered voters, 44 percent, said they’d choose Biden in the 2020 presidential election, while 37 percent of voters said they would vote for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Teen ripped out relative's eyes with his bare hands, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/01/teen-relatives-eyes-bare-hands/877266002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim was missing both eyes and multiple teeth when he was found by police. Mahad Aziz, an 18-year-old relative of the victim, is accused of using only his hands in the assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Minnesota, SDakota, Colorado Happiest States...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/minnesota-happiest-state-america-louisiana-least-happy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota may lack the glitzy allure of a New York or Los Angeles, but it beats out the rest of the nation when it comes to overall life satisfaction, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Slams 'Evangelist' USA as Pastor's Detention Roils Ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/01/erdogan-slams-evangelist-u-s-as-pastor-s-detention-roils-ties#gs.yGf_Cvo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Erdogan Slams ‘Evangelist’ U.S. as Pastor’s Detention Roils Ties</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bag rage' prompts backdown on plastic bag levy in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/australia-coles-supermarket-plastic-bag-levy-sparks-outrage-10579968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Dems try to catch some of Cortez lightning in a bottle...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/progressive-dems-try-catch-ocasio-cortezs-lightning-bottle-090017428.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston City Council member Ayanna Pressley, who is running for Congress,  on July 28 near Boston. SOMERVILLE, Mass. — On a sweltering July Saturday in this city a few miles west of Boston, Ayanna Pressley is making a pitch for change. Pressley, a member of the Boston City Council, is attempting to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope blasts supermarket of idols of money, drugs, vanity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/856e9f6923744957becec5efb840ddb7/Pope-blasts-%22supermarket-of-idols%22-of-money,-drugs,-vanity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis has returned from a month's vacation, blasting the "idols" of money, drugs and vanity that he said distract people from God and render them blind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation, gas prices, tariffs squeeze consumers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/78c2df3ec38449a493be1d467f2652aa/Inflation,-gas-prices,-tariffs-squeeze-consumers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price of a can of Coca-Cola? Likely going up. A package of Pampers? That too. Plane tickets? They also may be more expensive. These items and more may cost more in the coming months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cocaine use soars in richer households...</title>
      <link>http://www.itv.com/news/2018-08-01/cocaine-use-soars-in-richer-households/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burger on wheels: Saudis try once 'lowly' jobs as economy bites...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180801-burger-wheels-saudis-try-once-lowly-jobs-economy-bites</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Crew Killed in Africa Probed Mercenaries of 'Putin's Cook'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/01/tv-crew-killed-in-africa-probed-mercenaries-of-putin-s-cook#gs.6d3oZqU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV Crew Killed in Africa Probed Mercenaries of `Putin's Cook'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange May Be Ready to Take First Steps Into Different World...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/01/assange-may-be-ready-to-take-first-steps-into-a-different-world#gs.o4brozM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assange May Be Ready to Take First Steps Into a Different World</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE to Launch Censored Search Engine in China?</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/01/google-china-search-engine-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Search app that will "blacklist sensitive queries" could be launched in six to nine months, according to documents and people familiar with the plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson freed on bail after winning court battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6912226/tommy-robinson-freed-appeal-bail-contempt-of-court-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOMMY Robinson will today be freed from jail after winning his appeal for a contempt of court conviction. The English Defence League founder was sentenced to 13 months in prison after he broadcast …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders, Warren question whether Dem primary big enough for both of them...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/399795-sanders-warren-question-whether-dem-primary-is-big-enough-for-both-of-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Bernie Sanders debated whether or not to enter the 2016 presidential race, one of the first people he consulted was Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
