<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un Fourth Visit In Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/kim-jong-un-lands-in-china-for-his-fourth-visit-in-a-year-11546909773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean leader Kim Jong Un arrived in China—North Korea’s main backer, as he sends mixed signals to the U.S. about his willingness to give up his nuclear weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULLED OVER FOR SPEEDING ON WAY HOME...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/07/kevin-spacey-pulled-over-speeding-after-court-arraignment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Spacey walks out of court, and gets pulled over for speeding hours later. Seriously ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Biden Bid Most Divisive Thing For Field...</title>
      <link>https://www.esquire.com/news-politics/politics/a25782295/joe-biden-2020-democrats-divisive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.esquire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president's track record in Congress puts him on the wrong side of every issue that currently energizes his political party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Untested' Kamala Readies Publicity Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/07/politics/kamala-harris-new-book-tour/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a new memoir set to publish Tuesday, the 2020 spotlight shifts this week to Sen. Kamala Harris as she embarks on a book tour in advance of an expected presidential announcement this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive cultural extermination campaign against Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/global-opinions/china-has-launched-a-massive-campaign-of-cultural-extermination-against-the-uighurs/2019/01/07/efe03c9c-12a4-11e9-b6ad-9cfd62dbb0a8_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Vocational training” is basically just cultural extermination under a less-horrific name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON most valuable US company for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2019/01/07/amazon-tops-microsoft-as-most-valuable-us-company/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The repositioning has been triggered by mounting concerns that the Trump administration’s trade war with China and rising interest rates will bog down the worldwide economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Death Penalty for Scientist Who Created Gene-Edited Babies?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/chinese-scientist-who-created-crispr-babies-could-face-1831553751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British geneticist is worried that He Jiankui—the Chinese scientist responsible for the birth of genetically modified human twins—could face the death penalty for corruption and bribery charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO SOLO ROAD TRIP TO MEET VOTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/beto-orourke-plans-solo-road-trip-to-meet-democratic-voters-outside-texas-11546900932</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O’Rourke is asking aides to create an itinerary for a solo road trip outside Texas where he would ‘pop into places’ such as community colleges, as he considers whether to enter the 2020 Democratic presidential primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil gang rampage challenges Bolsonaro security strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-violence/brazil-gang-attacks-challenge-bolsonaros-security-strategy-idUSKCN1P11YS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Criminal gangs on a rampage in northeast Brazil are posing an early security tes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Promobot' struck, 'killed' by self-driving TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6566655/Oops-Autonomous-robot-struck-killed-self-driving-Tesla-Las-Vegas-ahead-CES.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla has found itself the cause of yet another self-driving car accident – and this time, its victim was a $2,000-per-day rentable humanoid robot. Promobot says the damage to its bot is likely irreparable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison commissaries offer AMAZON-like goods, rack up $17M sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/expo/news/g66l-2019/01/8e8ac092fe8811/oregons-prison-commissaries-of.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state operates its own version of big box stores for its inmate population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asks followers to help make bribery jokes...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Netanyahu-asks-Twitter-followers-Help-me-make-bribery-jokes-576643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In reference to the power-duo of Israeli television Rotem Sela and Assi Azar, a user claimed that Bribery without money is like the famous model and actress Sela having to work without the Azar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers grounded with dead body for 2 HOURS after passenger dies on board...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6566739/Plane-passengers-left-grounded-dead-body-TWO-HOURS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ANZ80 flight from Hong Kong was diverted to Cairns Airport at 2.30am on Monday morning after the man died due to an unknown medical emergency. It waited at Cairns for two hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Black Man Dies in Home of West Hollywood Dem Donor...</title>
      <link>https://www.advocate.com/crime/2019/1/07/another-black-man-has-died-home-democratic-donor-ed-buck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.advocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ski resort evacuated as heavy snow blankets...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/ski-resort-evacuated-thousands-stranded-142144984.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy snowfalls have left large areas of the Austrian and Bavarian Alps paralysed, with more than 2,000 people trapped in villages and ski resorts cut off from the outside world. Five people have been killed, and another two are missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 cops in 'love rectangle' stripped of guns so won't kill each other...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/07/4-cops-in-love-rectangle-stripped-of-guns-so-they-wouldnt-kill-each-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NYPD sergeant cheated on his cop girlfriend with a fellow officer — whose husband is also on the job — and the bosses took away all their guns so they wouldn’t kill each other,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows 'Sanctuary To All Who Seek It'...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/07/gavin-newsom-california-governor-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Jerry Brown is passing his title to fellow Democrat Gavin Newsom, who was sworn in Monday as California's 40th governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How China Flexes Political Muscle to Expand Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-china-flexes-its-political-muscle-to-expand-power-overseas-11546890449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secret discussions show how China uses its political and financial clout to bolster its position overseas, especially for its “Belt and Road” infrastructure project. Malaysian’s new leader has since put the deal on hold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Gov. Newsom immediately challenges Trump at inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/Gov-Gavin-Newsom-governor-inaugural-speech-brown-13514913.php?t=6c49ce5a9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO - Gavin Newsom took the oath as California's 40th governor Monday and instantly challenged President Trump, promising a "progressive, principled" administration that will counter "corruption and incompetence" in the White House. "It is up to us to renew the California dream for a new generation. And now more than ever, it is up to us to defend it," Newsom said. "But there is an administration in Washington hostile to California's values and interests." The former San Francisco mayor painted a picture of California as a virtual "nation-state," one that will push beyond the strictures proposed by the GOP leaders in Washington toward a more progressive future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Refunds To STILL Be Sent Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/07/white-house-official-says-tax-refunds-will-be-sent-out-despite-government-shutdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 12 percent of IRS staff are expected to continue working through a shutdown, according to the agency's plan, which means certain functions such as answering taxpayer questions would be curtailed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Draft Beto' effort builds momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/07/orourke-south-carolina-nevada-boost-1085236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O’Rourke is getting a significant lift in the early nominating states of South Carolina and Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vet issues alert as nasty dog virus sweeps UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1068363/dog-virus-warning-uk-dog-news-pet-illness-bacterial-infection-gastroenteritis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VET has warned dog owners of a painful bacteria infection spreading rapidly across the UK, urging pet lovers to take care of their animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic mushroom legalization gets closer in Denver...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/01/07/denver-magic-mushrooms-legalization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists who hope to make Denver the first U.S. city to decriminalize psychedelic mushrooms plan to turn in ballot petitions Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Kelly allegedly posts sex tapes of accuser to discredit rape claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6566331/R-Kelly-allegedly-posts-sex-tapes-accuser-site-launched-camp-discredit-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook page, whose name is not being revealed, was created on Sunday, and by Monday afternoon there was an announcement that video had been posted online of one accuser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 'dramatic statement,' Netanyahu says he was refused chance to confront accusers...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-january-7-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement authorities say investigations against PM were carried out 'professionally and thoroughly... only according to professional considerations'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Hearing Loss Linked To Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-hearing-loss-linked-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elderly people suffering from hearing loss are more likely to experience symptoms of depression, and the greater the degree of hearing loss, the more intense those symptoms are, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANS OVAL OFFICE ADDRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/breaking-trump-reportedly-seeking-to-address-the-nation-on-tuesday-night-but-networks-reluctant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripper Arrested After Threatening Mass Shooting At Club...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/01/06/florida-stripper-arrested-after-threatening-mass-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another arrest has been made following a shooting threat on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver admits murdering 6 between fares...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/07/uber-driver-admits-to-murdering-six-strangers-between-fares/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KALAMAZOO, Mich. — A man charged with killing six strangers between picking up rides for Uber pleaded guilty to murder on Monday in Michigan. Jason Dalton’s surprise move occurred as lawyers …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS SOAR...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/eagles-bears-ratings-nfl-wild-card-golden-globe-sunday-1202530563/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking until the final minutes like it may go into overtime and delay the start of the Golden Globes, last night’s NFL wild card playoff game between the Philadelphia Eagles and Chicago Bears was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu to make 'dramatic announcement'... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/82d4bc7a869947c886071bfef325fe70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu says he will deliver a "dramatic announcement" set to coincide with the evening news broadcast. Netanyahu said in statement on Twitter on Monday that he would broadcast a "special announcement to the press." The embattled prime minister's mysterious statement left even veteran political reporters baffled as to its nature. There was speculation it was related to investigations into alleged corruption by Netanyahu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home items getting creepier...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/12787de930564f2cbe8fadfdf63e2e7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — One day, finding an oven that just cooks food may be as tough as buying a TV that merely lets you change channels. Internet-connected "smarts" are creeping into cars, refrigerators, thermostats, toys and just about everything else in your home. CES 2019, the gadget show opening Tuesday in Las Vegas, will showcase many of these products, including an oven that coordinates your recipes and a toilet that flushes with a voice command. With every additional smart device in your home, companies are able to gather more details about your daily life. Some of that can be used to help advertisers target you — more precisely than they could with just the smartphone you carry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns against nationalism -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-diplomats/pope-francis-warns-of-resurgent-nationalism-urges-help-for-migrants-idUSKCN1P115Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis warned on Monday against a resurgence of nationalist and populist m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THURSDAY:  Trump to Visit Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-to-travel-to-southern-border-thursday-sarah-sanders-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump will travel to the U.S.-Mexico border on Thursday in a bid to highlight border security, as he presses Democrats for wall funding amid the protracted standoff that triggered a partial government shutdown now stretching into its 17th day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER CHANNEL Sued For Selling Data Of App Users...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/04/la-sues-weather-channel-illegally-selling-private-data-mobile-app-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The data was sold to at least 12 third party websites over the past 19 months, the complaint reads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain testing 'no-deal' scenario as Brexit vote nears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24342b039b64431193bac0d07f7415d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain is testing how its motorway and ferry system would handle a "no-deal" Brexit by sending a stream of trucks from a small local airport to the port of Dover — even as some legislators try to pressure the government to rule out the scenario. The tests began Monday morning and are intended to gauge how severe the disruption would be if Britain leaves the European Union on March 29 without an agreed-upon withdrawal deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney in Yankee cap arrested in series of violent NYC sex attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Attorney-Sex-Attack-Manhattan-Pattern-2014-Rashaun-Kelley--503995031.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney has been charged in three sex attacks that took place in Manhattan more than three years ago, the NYPD said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END:  Supreme Court Denies Review of Olivia De Havilland 'FEUD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/supreme-court-denies-review-olivia-de-havillands-feud-lawsuit-1174078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 102-year-old actress has lost her case over a series that she claimed depicted her falsely and unfairly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey Makes First Court Appearance... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-spacey-makes-first-court-appearance-alleged-sexual-assault-1173337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged victim was 18 at the time when he claims the actor assaulted him after getting him drunk at a restaurant on Nantucket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How solitary confinement drove young inmate to brink of insanity...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/how-solitary-confinement-drove-a-young-inmate-to-the-brink/article_62707aa1-d5ec-51cc-b41d-911f58c313cb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — With his mental state deteriorating as he sat in the crushing isolation of solitary confinement, a desperate inmate named Anthony Gay saw a temporary way out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player thinks Goodell plotting against Chargers...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/01/07/russell-okung-thinks-the-league-is-plotting-against-the-chargers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chargers had a chance to take the lead over the Ravens in December, when a holding penalty on Russell Okung backed them up, and they fumbled on the next play. The Chargers had a chance to kneel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAGA LOSES TO GA GA...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/movies/golden-globes-2019-a-star-is-born-snubbed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 76th annual Golden Globes were presented live on NBC at the Beverly Hilton in Beverly Hills, California, on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEYLAND sharply hikes prices; Most expensive pass $1,949!</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2019/01/07/disneyland-2019-ticket-prices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Lando Calrissian once griped: "This deal is getting worse all the time!" Disneyland announced it's significantly hiking its already…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'self-aware' vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cars/news/self-aware-car-launched-ces-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans of the sentient, singing trains in Philip Reeve's Rail Head science fiction tale will be disappointed with Delphi's somewhat overstated exhibit at this year's Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas, the &amp;quot;self-aware car&amp;quot;, although in reality it is much better than the usual sci-fi fantasy fare usually served up at this frenetic early-year event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to crash spacecraft into asteroid in mission to stop strike on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/751994/nasa-news-spaceship-crash-asteroid-deadly-strike-earth-dart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Biggest Bear Says Problems 'Likely to Worsen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/facebook-s-biggest-bear-says-problems-likely-to-worsen-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's Biggest Bear Says Problems â€˜Likely to Worsenâ€™Â in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smarts' creep into everyday products...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/12787de930564f2cbe8fadfdf63e2e7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — One day, finding an oven that just cooks food may be as tough as buying a TV that merely lets you click between channels. Internet-connected "smarts" are creeping into cars, refrigerators, thermostats, toys and just about everything else in your home. CES 2019, the gadget show opening Tuesday in Las Vegas, will showcase many of these products, including an oven that coordinates your recipes and a toilet that flushes with a voice command. With every additional smart device in your home, companies are able to gather more details about your daily life. Some of that can be used to help advertisers target you — more precisely than they could with just the smartphone you carry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Denies Ownership Of Syringes Found In Rectum During Jail Strip Search...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/contraband/syringe-story-stinks-482093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida Man denied ownership of three syringes removed from his rectum during a 4:30 AM strip search at a county jail, according to a criminal complaint. Cops arrested Wesley Scott, 40, early Frida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China confronts US with fury as destroyer sails through South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8136009/china-confronts-us-fury-missile-destroyer-beijing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has confronted the US with fury after it sent a missile destroyer through the disputed South China Sea in a direct challenge to Beijing. China responded by scrambling warships and aircraft to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Men face MORE discrimination than women...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6564767/Men-face-discrimination-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK, the US and Australia all discriminate against men more whereas Italy, Israel and China are harder environments for women, according to the study (stock).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant one-eyed cow worshipped 'as a GOD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6564981/Holy-cow-One-eyed-calf-worshipped-god-India.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The little cow, whose appearance is due to a birth defect, is being worshipped as a god by locals in the Bardhaman district of West Bengal, in eastern India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Fearing Murder By Her Saudi Family Livestreaming from Hotel in Thailand...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/saudi-woman-fleeing-abuse-says-shes-being-held-at-thai-airport-at-request-of-saudi-authorities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 18-year-old has appealed to human rights groups to save her from being sent home, where she says she faces possible “slaughter” by male relatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI tool used to catch people who lie to police...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/07/artificial-intelligence-tool-used-catch-people-lie-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British scientists have developed a new computer programme that can spot if someone has lied to police about being robbed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual leader 'Buddha boy' probed over disappearance of devotees...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190107-nepal-probes-buddha-boy-over-devotee-disappearances</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nepal probes 'Buddha boy' over devotee disappearances</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House may try to block release of Mueller findings...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/when-mueller-issues-report-trump-may-try-to-suppress-some-of-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller may submit his findings on Russian interference in the 2016 Trump campaign to the Justice Department as early as February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS CEO Reins In Predecessor's Ambitions: 'I'm Not Howard'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/starbucks-ceo-kevin-johnson-reins-in-predecessors-ambitions-im-not-howard-11546857001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Johnson, Starbucks Corp.’s new chief executive, is aiming to bring discipline and focus to the chain’s plans for new stores as it recovers from traffic declines at its signature coffee shops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey to Be Arraigned on Sex-Assault Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/kevin-spacey-to-be-arraigned-on-sexual-assault-allegations-11546857000 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The felony charge against the 59-year-old actor stems from an alleged sexual assault in 2016 involving an 18-year-old who worked as a busboy at a Nantucket, Mass., restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butterfly numbers plummet...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/01/07/monarch-butterfly-numbers-drop-86-california/2499761002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thatâ€™s bad news for a butterfly species whose numbers have already declined an estimated 97 percent since the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richer Americans Skipping SUVs for Station Wagons...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/richer-americans-are-skipping-suvs-for-station-wagons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S customers drove off in 212,000 brand spanking new station wagons last year, 29 percent more than they did five years earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jittery Wall St has lot ahead to be nervous about...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f8fc04ec030846d7a1af02c89596e2ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Welcome to the brave new world of investing, where every day in the stock market can feel like bedlam. Investors have been careening from fear to relief and back again as they react to morsels of news about the health of the economy and corporate profits, the global trade war and when the Federal Reserve will next raise interest rates. With each mood shift, stock prices have swung wildly. Unusually big moves — both up and down — have come at a frequency not seen in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CES 2019: APPLE plasters privacy ad on billboard...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-01-privacy-tech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is not among the exhibitors at the 2019 Consumer Electronics Show, but that didn't prevent the iPhone maker from sending a message to attendees on a large billboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun Use Surges in Europe, Where Firearms Are Rare...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/gun-use-surges-in-europe-where-firearms-are-rare-11546857000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gun ownership is rising across Europe, a continent that until recently faced far less gun crime and violence than much of the globe, driven in part by insecurity arising from terrorist attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot delivers freshly baked bread every 6 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/01/06/breadbot-delivers-freshly-baked-bread-every-six-minutes/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's hard to be taken seriously'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6563981/Lady-Gaga-cries-earns-Golden-Globe-says-hard-taken-seriously-woman-music.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 32-year-old multihyphenate accepted the Best Original Song trophy for her work on A Star Is Born smash hit Shallow at the 76th annual Golden Globes on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Parliament Gears Up for Crucial Brexit Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/british-parliament-gears-up-for-crucial-brexit-vote-11546779600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British lawmakers this week begin debating Prime Minister Theresa May’s Brexit plan before a critical vote she is widely expected to lose, heightening political and economic uncertainty as Britain’s withdrawal from the EU nears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ark of Covenant in Ethiopia?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/is-the-ark-of-the-covenant-in-ethiopia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Ethiopian lore, the Ark of the Covenant is hidden in a church in Aksum–a small city in the northern highlands–and guarded by a single monk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is hype about CBD, or cannabidiol, real? </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Is-the-hype-about-CBD-or-cannabidiol-real-13512076.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not that long ago, I would not have been able to tell you what the acronym "CBD" stood for, let alone what it was used for. CBD, or cannabidiol, is most commonly extracted from hemp, but it can also come from marijuana plants, which is why it is sometimes confused with its trippy chemical cousin THC. Unlike CBD, THC produces a high when smoked or eaten. Today, we are living in a CBD world, with tinctures, ointments and vaping oils popping up everywhere. Celebrities from Gwyneth Paltrow to Willie Nelson are CBD believers, and if you frequent the right coffee shops, you can even get a shot of cannabidiol in your latte.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren regains footing in Iowa blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/05/elizabeth-warren-iowa-democrats-2020-1082574</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts senator was the only major 2020 contender to rebuff the crucial state during the midterms. She’s now making up ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN SAYS HE'S BEST HOPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-sees-himself-as-democrats%E2%80%99-best-hope-in-2020-allies-say/ar-BBRTcPg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZIRINSKY FOR THE SAVE</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-cbs-news-zirinsky-20190106-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newsroom veteran and longtime "48 Hours" executive producer will take over the troubled division in March amid turbulent times for CBS and diminishing ratings for daily news programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's hard to be taken seriously'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6563681/Golden-Globes-2019-Winners-announced-film-television.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen biopic Bohemian Rhapsody surprised many as it finished off the night with a Best Motion Picture - Drama win over Bradley Cooper's critically acclaimed project on Sunday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Malone Troubling Message About 'Mental Stability'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/2019/01/06/post-malone-posts-troubling-message-mental-stability/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Post Malone tweeted a troubling message on Sunday morning, making fans fear he was not [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Michaels throws hands up at controversial call...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/06/al-michaels-throws-hands-up-at-controversial-call-nfl-just-making-it-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even Al Michaels couldn’t believe what he just saw as a bizarre Sunday of NFL officiating continued. On a second-down play late in the second quarter from the Eagles’ 35-yard line, Bears quar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuaron Champions Streaming...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/alfonso-cuaron-champions-netflix-streaming-limited-theatrical-model-as-roma-wins-two-golden-globes-1202529703/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tonight Netflix/Participant Media’s Roma won two key awards best director for Alfonso Cuarón and best foreign film, further solidifying its momentum this awards season. The film has been the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RHAPSODY' SURPRISE!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ac9bf6f45544160aecc88031ddd5528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards, being presented live Sunday at the Beverly Hilton Hotel in Beverly Hills, California (all times local): 8:15 p.m. "Bohemian Rhapsody" is the winner of the best film drama Golden Globe Award. The 20th Century Fox biopic that charts the rise of Freddie Mercury and Queen stars Rami Malek as Mercury and was directed by Bryan Singer. Moments earlier, star Malek won best actor in a film drama for his portrayal of Mercury. The film had a troubled production and was met with mediocre reviews, with the exception of high praise for Malek's performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court judge flees to USA, denounces Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/former-venezuela-supreme-court-judge-flees-to-u-s-denounces-maduro-idUSKCN1P00OU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Venezuelan Supreme Court Justice Christian Zerpa has fled to the United S...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline orders obese cabin crew: Lose weight or grounded...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/travel/travel-advice/flights/pakistan-international-airlines-tells-obese-cabin-crew-to-lose-weight-or-be-grounded/news-story/bd76c57083feb895fc67d5dbac110679</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pakistan International Airlines has allegedly instructed “obese” employees of its cabin crew to lose weight in the first six months of 2019 or risk losing their jobs, according to reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Bale credits Satan for inspiration...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/awards/christian-bale-credits-satan-inspiration-how-play-dick-cheney-vice-n955506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During his Golden Globes acceptance speech, Christian Bale credits Satan for inspiration on how to play Dick Cheney in "Vice"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zirinsky becomes first female chief...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/susan-zirinsky-replaces-david-rhodes-cbs-news-president-1203100853/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Rhodes will step down as president of CBS News after an eight-year tenure and will be replaced by veteran producer Susan Zirinsky, CBS announced Sunday night, a maneuver executives and anchor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man robs bank across from police station mins after release from jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/man-robbed-credit-union-across-the-street-from-wentzville-police/article_fcef4e8f-1e8a-5d3c-9659-990db9dbab99.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wentzville police said they discovered the man is also a suspect in bank robberies in Kansas and Texas, though he has not been charged in those cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX and chill no more as streaming gets complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/ny-news-netflix-streaming-complications-20190105-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Streaming TV may never again be as simple, or as affordable, as it is now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunger sparked by food shortages, hyperinflation overwhelms Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article223950330.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About one-third of Venezuelans are eating only one meal a day, due to the country’s economic collapse under Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro. Lack of food and hyperinflation are the leading causes of the hunger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist explores the '7th sense'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailypress.com/news/science/dp-nws-sigma-immune-brain-20190104-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailypress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;University of Virginia scientist explores what he calls the "seventh sense" — an enigmatic link between the immune system and brain disorders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions surface over 'secret court' hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2019/01/06/kevin-spacey-sex-assault-case-got-secret-hearing-but-his-lawyers-failed-derail/DxuHrbtsGpe4uz7exhdNcN/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Monday’s arraignment, the actor’s lawyers were given a special opportunity to have his case reviewed in a mini-trial-type setting where records are kept out of public view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy security as Egypt opens region's biggest cathedral...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46775842</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Sisi inaugurated the massive Coptic cathedral, a day after a bomb blast near a church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Fan Brutally Beats LA Fan In Stands...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/01/06/ravens-fan-can-be-seen-punching-chargers-fan-during-fight-in-stands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a tough loss for Baltimore Sunday and some Ravens fans didn't take well to a Chargers fan in the stands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Daughter beats mom, charges dad with knife after refuse to take to OUTBACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.wpbf.com/article/woman-arrested-after-attacking-parents-for-not-taking-her-to-outback/25742370</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wpbf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Lake Worth woman has been arrested for attacking her parents because they refused to take her to Outback restaurant Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are witches': Scandal divides parishes and politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-poland-church-abuse-insight/we-are-witches-clerical-abuse-scandal-divides-parishes-and-politics-in-poland-idUSKCN1P1024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Catholic priest of the Polish village of Kalinowka is serving three y...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKILEAKS warns press: 140 'defamatory' things not to say about Assange...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-ecuador-assange/wikileaks-tells-reporters-140-things-not-to-say-about-julian-assange-idUSKCN1P00NN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks on Sunday advised journalists not to report 140 different "false ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk soccer star arrested at airport for swearing blames sleeping pills...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/wayne-rooney-arrested-for-being-drunk-and-swearing-in-public-in-us-11600617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former England captain, who now plays for US team DC United, was charged in December.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
