<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump looks to make more history, this time with Putin...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/defense/393868-trump-looks-to-make-more-history-this-time-with-putin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh off a meeting with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un that saw history-making images plastered on screens around the globe, President Trump is zeroing on another headline-making summit — one with Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels meeting with prosecutors on Cohen cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jun/25/stormy-daniels-to-meet-prosecutors-on-michael-cohen-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interview with adult film actor about Donald Trump’s former personal attorney cancelled due to media attention</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buzz Aldrin Fights Family For Control of Space Legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/buzz-aldrin-fights-family-for-control-of-his-space-legacy-1529872576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former astronaut’s children say their father is in mental decline and are asking a Florida court to appoint them his guardians. He says they are after his business, and is suing for “elder exploitation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis Bad Boy Kyrgios In Hot Water for Simulating Sex Act With Water Bottle During Match...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/tennis-bad-boy-nick-kyrgios-fined-for-simulating-self-pleasure-with-a-water-bottle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-ELEVEN Ad Greets Tourists In Norway: 'Land of Chlamydia!' </title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.no/20180621/land-of-chlamydia-provocative-ad-greets-tourists-to-norway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.no&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An advertisement for condoms by convenience store 7-eleven has irked Norway’s tourist board with its message about venereal disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China takes spying to new heights with flock of robotic doves...</title>
      <link>http://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2152027/china-takes-surveillance-new-heights-flock-robotic-doves-do-they</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi-tech drones that look and move like real birds have already flown over restive Xinjiang region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator suffers cracked rib after colleague saves from choking...</title>
      <link>http://www.kmov.com/story/38496874/mccaskill-suffers-cracked-rib-after-colleague-saves-her-from-choking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kmov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Senator Claire McCaskill joked she would not be hugging people after suffering a broken rib at a Democratic caucus luncheon, thanks to her colleague.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Affair Between Reporter, Senate Aide Rattled DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/24/business/media/james-wolfe-ali-watkins-leaks-reporter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seizure of email records from a Times reporter alarmed First Amendment groups. Her relationship with an intelligence aide set off an ethical debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels to meet prosecutors in Michael Cohen probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Stormy-Daniels-to-meet-with-prosecutors-in-13022033.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels is scheduled Monday to be interviewed by prosecutors in the Southern District of New York, preparing for a potential grand jury appearance about a $130,000 payment from President Donald Trump's attorney Michael Cohen in exchange for her silence about an alleged affair with Trump, according to a source familiar with the investigation. Daniels and her attorney, Michael Avenatti, have been cooperating with prosecutors and provided documents about the payment, made shortly before the 2016 election, in response to a subpoena, said the source, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to provide the information about Monday's interview. A spokesman for the U.S. attorney and attorneys for Cohen declined to comment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author name nixed from major book award over 'stereotypical attitudes' in 'LITTLE HOUSE ON PRAIRIE'... </title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-ent-laura-ingalls-winder-stereotypical-attitudes-20180624-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The children’s division of the American Library Association voted Saturday to remove Laura Ingalls Wilder’s name from a major award based over how the “Little House on the Prairie” author portrayed minorities in her novels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris Fashion Week: Male wardrobe 'comprehensively feminized'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/boys-girls-learned-paris-fashion-week-212934732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Paris men's fashion week comes to an end Sunday we look at four things we learned from a packed and at times emotional six days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian rockers end Jay-Z, Beyonce No. 1 debut streak...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/australian-rockers-end-jay-z-beyonce-no-1-232948214.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian pop band 5 Seconds of Summer stunned Beyonce and Jay-Z by opening Sunday at the top of the US album chart, with the couple's surprise collaboration ending the superstars' streak of number one debuts. 5 Seconds of Summer had stepped up promotion of their album "Youngblood"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN WINS AGAIN...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180624203412-9ou8s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TURKEY-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 14, PIX, TV):UPDATE 14-Turkey's Erdogan claims election victory, opposition wary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Era of One-Man Rule...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/06/24/turkish-president-erdogan-claims-victory-expanded-powers-in-dual-elections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan appeared to win broadly expanded powers Sunday, as unofficial election results showed him garnering enough support to avoid a runoff -- although the opposition warned results were incomplete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FISH DEFICIT:  USA imports record levels of seafood...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-imported-more-seafood-2017-prior-141246717--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — The United States imported more seafood last year than at any point in its history, and the nation's trade deficit in the sector is growing, federal data show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders's midterm problems; Big test on Tuesday...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/24/us/politics/bernie-sanders-midterm-elections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While their goals like a higher minimum wage and “Medicare for All” have gained traction among Democrats, Senator Sanders and his allies have struggled to win elections or build support in conventional ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air defenses intercept missile above Saudi capital...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180624204043-irrj6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEMEN-SECURITY/SAUDI (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-Saudi air defences intercept missiles above capital - coalition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire police force detained in Mexico town where mayoral candidate killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/entire-police-force-detained-mexico-town-where-mayoral-214643267.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The whole police force in a Mexican town of Ocampo where a mayoral candidate was slain this week has been detained for an internal investigation, authorities said Sunday. "All of them are being interviewed to proceed as due under law in the event anyone has taken part in acts that violate the town</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of elite 'robocops' will protect Trump during UK visit amid 'terror attack' fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/978706/donald-trump-latest-uk-state-visit-police-officers-protect-us-president-terror-attack-fear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UP TO 10,000 police officers will be drafted in to protect the US President from mass protests and the threat of a terror attack when he visits the UK next month, it has been revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVANS-PRITCHARD: Financial system vulnerable as rising rates meet record debt... </title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/06/24/bis-fears-snapback-crunch-rising-rates-meet-record-global-debt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World debt ratios have spiralled to record levels during the era of super-easy money and markets are showing tell-tale signs of late-cycle excess, leaving the international financial system acutely vulnerable to a jump in borrowing costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can STARBUCKS be fixed?</title>
      <link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/06/21/news/companies/starbucks-strategy-johnson/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is experiencing some growing pains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: John McAfee Poisoned?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-06-23/john-mcafee-vows-revenge-enemies-who-tried-poison-me</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA 'not ready' for increasing level of deadly bug diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/24/health/bug-disease-preparedness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts warn that programs to fight deadly diseases carried by ticks and mosquitoes aren't equipped to do proper surveillance or prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIGGED: Police find car full of FORGED ballot papers......</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/978893/turkey-elections-latest-update-erdogan-Muharrem-Ince-result</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLICE in Turkey have arrested three people after sacks overflowing with sealed ballot papers were found in a car they were driving adding fuel to speculation today’s election was rigged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security employees warned of increased threats amid immigration uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/homeland-security-memo-today-increased-threats-2018-06-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A memo recommends numerous safety precautions, including not displaying work badge in public, be careful with public conversations and using caution on all social networks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria threatens to reinstate border checks...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5879471/Austrias-chancellor-says-ready-necessary-protect-borders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The threat from Chancellor Kurz (pictured) comes as more than half of the EU's leaders meet in Brussels today to grapple with a political crisis over migration that threatens to tear the bloc apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant owner who booted out White House press secretary took staff vote...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5878973/Owner-restaurant-booted-Sarah-Huckabee-Sanders-speaks-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Wilkinson, the owner of The Red Hen in Lexington, Virginia says she took a staff vote before asking the Press Secretary to leave her restaurant on Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air defenses intercept missile above Saudi capital...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180624180155-k67nd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEMEN-SECURITY/SAUDI (URGENT):Saudi air defences intercept missile above Saudi capital - state media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls of Senate Races Boost Republican Prospects for Retaining Control...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/polls-senate-races-boost-gop-164521302.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prospect of Republicans retaining control of the U.S. Senate are looking better, according to polls of races in Texas, Florida and Arizona by CBS News conducted by YouGov and published Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls of Senate Races Boost Republican Prospects for Retaining Control...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2018-06-24/polls-of-senate-races-boost-gop-prospects-for-retaining-control</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prospect of Republicans retaining control of the U.S. Senate are looking better, according to polls of races in Texas, Florida and Arizona by CBS News conducted by YouGov and published Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Illegals told they'll be reunited with children if they sign voluntary deportation order...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2018/06/24/kids-exchange-deportation-migrants-claim-they-were-promised-they-could/?utm_campaign=trib-social-buttons&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a detention center near Houston, an asylum seeker from Honduras said he agreed to sign a voluntary removal order from the U.S. after federal officials promised to reunite him with his 6-year-old daughter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  BORDER JUMPERS OUT WITH NO 'JUDGE OR COURT'</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-trump/trump-calls-for-deporting-illegal-immigrants-with-no-judges-or-court-cases-idUSKBN1JK0OL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said on Sunday that people who enter the United States illegally should be sent back to where they came from immediately without any judicial process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court poised to rule on Trump travel ban, other cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-immigration/supreme-court-poised-to-rule-on-trump-travel-ban-other-cases-idUSKBN1JK0F7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court, winding down its nine-month term, will issue rulings this week in its few remaining cases including a major one on the legality of President Donald Trump's ban on people from five Muslim-majority nations entering the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES ELECTION...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5879221/Polls-open-Turkeys-fiercely-fought-elections-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The elections will also usher in a powerful new executive presidency long sought by Erdogan and backed by a small majority of Turks in a 2017 referendum. Critics say it will erode democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN WINS AGAIN...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180624174552-0cwf3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TURKEY-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 10, PIX, TV):UPDATE 10-Erdogan, ruling AK Party build comfortable lead in Turkish elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roseanne Opens Up: 'I've Made Myself a Hate Magnet'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/roseanne-barr-opens-up-abc-firing-tearful-interview-ive-made-myself-a-hate-magnet-1122923 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a wide-ranging interview with spiritual adviser Rabbi Shmuley Boteach, the disgraced comedian addressed the current controversy stemming from a racist tweet she made weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  BORDER JUMPERS OUT WITH NO 'JUDGE OR COURT'</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-calls-deporting-illegal-immigrants-no-judges-court-152120701.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said on Sunday that people who enter the United States illegally should be sent back to where they came from immediately without any judicial process. Facing a public outcry and pressure even from within his Republican Party, Trump last week reversed his policy of separating migrant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men still bristle...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/saudi-men-still-bristle-women-driving-163831919.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Ayat Basma JEDDAH, Saudi Arabia (Reuters) - Amid the celebratory end of Saudi Arabia's ban on women driving on Sunday, some men expressed quiet disapproval of a change they fear will undermine the kingdom's deeply conservative Muslim identity. During our fathers' and grandfathers'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian minister tells foreign rescue ships to stop migrant pick-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/italian-minister-tells-foreign-rescue-ships-stop-migrant-165113035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy's far-right Interior Minister Matteo Salvini on Sunday told foreign charities to back off and let Libya take care of rescue operations in the Mediterranean. "Let the Libyan authorities do their work of rescue, recovery and return (of migrants) to their country, as they have been doing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN IN LEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkeys-erdogan-faces-poll-test-against-resurgent-opposition-023302424.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan was on Sunday leading a tightly-contested presidential election in a partial count as he seeks a new mandate in the face of a revitalised opposition and weakening economy. Turkish voters had for the first time cast ballots for both president and parliament in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Protests Spread Across Nation...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/portland-occupiers-shut-down-ice-office-steal-flag-replace-it-with-refugees-welcome-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protests are spreading to major cities across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  The strategic blunder of 'Trump-as-Hitler'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/393049-the-strategic-blunder-of-trump-as-hitler</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overwrought comparisons to the Nazis are both historically illiterate and an extreme strategic misstep for Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters orders MORE public harassment of Trump aides...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/maxine-waters-orders-more-public-harassment-of-trump-aides-god-is-on-our-side/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxine Waters wants more people to harass Trump administration officials in public spaces. The California Congresswoman went on a shouting rampage during a toy drive outside the Wilshire Federal Building on Saturday. After claiming Trump is”sacrificing our children,” referring to the illegal immigrant kids separated from their “parents” near the border, Waters again called for …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead bodies found at WALMART nationwide phenomenon...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/24/walmart-dead-bodies-nationwide-phenomenon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Unger was among the growing number of people around the country who drew their last breaths in Walmart parking lots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulldog wins World's Ugliest Dog...</title>
      <link>http://abc7news.com/pets-animals/bulldog-named-zsa-zsa-wins-worlds-ugliest-dog-contest/3642265/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zsa Zsa was crowned at the World's Ugliest Dog competition, an annual event at the Sonoma-Marin Fair in Petaluma, Calif. The bulldog and her owner, Megan Brainard, couldn't be happier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seth Rogen brags about refusing photo with Paul Ryan's kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/24/seth-rogen-refuses-take-photo-paul-ryans-kids-brag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Seth Rogen bragged on “The Late Show with Stephen Colbert” about how he refused to take a photo earlier this month with a couple of teenage fans — because they were the sons of House Speaker Paul Ryan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big tech directors skip shareholder meetings...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-technology-directors/waiting-for-peter-thiel-big-tech-directors-miss-shareholder-meetings-idUSKBN1JK0AC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some small investors who want to give a piece of their minds to big tech company directors are losing their only chance: many board members are skipping annual shareholder meetings. Companies that hold meetings online have some of the worst records for attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun industry sees banks as new threat to 2nd Amendment...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/gun-industry-sees-banks-threat-2nd-amendment-130134288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAINESVILLE, Ga. (AP) — In the wake of high-profile mass shootings, corporate America has been taking a stand against the firearms industry amid a lack of action by lawmakers on gun control. Payment processing firms are limiting transactions, Bank of America stopped providing financing to companies that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Median price for Bay Area home hits record-shattering $935,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/06/22/median-price-tag-for-a-bay-area-home-hits-a-record-shattering-935000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skyrocketing housing prices continued their upward climb in May, while the number of sales inched up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 injured when German apartment building explodes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/379787116e1d42009305b01cf23f8815</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Twenty-five people were injured, four of them severely, when an explosion destroyed an apartment building in the western German city of Wuppertal, police said Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of memes? Campaigners dismayed at EU internet ruling...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/end-memes-campaigners-dismayed-european-internet-ruling-n885726</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Article 13 of a new E.U. law would place responsibility for enforcing copyright onto platforms rather than individuals, with potentially big implications for internet culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man robs Vegas casinos by posing as delivery driver...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/man-accused-of-stealing-from-las-vegas-casinos-by-posing-as-delivery-driver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A criminal complaint accuses Danny Roy Salazar of burglarizing the Rio, Westgate and Caesars Palace between Jan. 13 and June 8 and stealing an assortment of items, including mattresses, televisions…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransom Demands, Frozen Computers: Hackers Hit Towns Across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ransom-demands-and-frozen-computers-hackers-hit-towns-across-the-u-s-1529838001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers are targeting small towns’ computer systems, with public-sector attacks appearing to be rising faster than those in the private sector. Online extortionists demand bitcoin ransom in return for decryption keys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida AG confronted at Mr. Rogers movie...</title>
      <link>http://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article213733494.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters confronted Florida Attorney General Pam Bondi at a showing of a documentary about children's TV host Fred Rogers, and they questioned her stands on immigration and health care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas sheriff refuses to help feds...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-texas-sheriff-child-migrants-20180621-story,amp.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The El Paso County sheriff prohibited his deputies from working off-duty at a temporary shelter housing migrant children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWNER:  MORAL DECISION...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/23/sarah-sanders-booted-so-restaurant-could-uphold-certain-standards-co-owner-says-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A co-owner of a restaurant that refused to serve White House press secretary Sarah Sanders on Friday reportedly cited morality and living up to certain standards,” as the reason why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea erasing most anti-USA propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/23/north-korea-erasing-most-anti-us-propaganda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nix the nuclear warheads, cue the doves. The North Korean government is erasing much of its anti-U.S. propaganda following dictator Kim Jong-un’s forays onto the world stage. Gone are the posters d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Hussein: Jordan's 23-year-old fresh-faced future ...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/prince-hussein-jordans-fast-rising-royal-heir-100824139.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Western-educated trainee helicopter pilot with a huge Instagram following, Jordan's 23-year-old Crown Prince Hussein bin Abdullah has emerged as the fresh-faced future of the desert kingdom's monarchy. The heir to the throne is hosting Britain's Prince William, 36, from Sunday for a visit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6c4fdff53c2c4c388a7add2f1f3654b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Turkey held high-stakes presidential and parliamentary elections on Sunday that could consolidate President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's grip on power or curtail h</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
