<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>COLDPLAY Chris Martin says lockdowns forced him to re-evaluate fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/may/07/coldplay-chris-martin-lockdowns-forced-re-evaluate-fame</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frontman says Covid pandemic means he has tried ‘to not attach too much to being a pop star’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Suspended Over Photos Showing Them Not Wearing Masks Off-Campus...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/07/umass-amherst-students-suspended-masks-outside-off-campus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three UMass Amherst students said they are not being treated fairly after they were suspended for not wearing masks at an off-campus outdoor event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild VIP Group-Sex Party About to Invade NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-wild-vip-group-sex-party-is-about-to-invade-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On May 15, SNCTM—an exclusive sex club—is set to host an 80-person bash in Downtown Manhattan. Masks are not optional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Internet Turned on Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/05/08/elon-musk-snl-saturday-night-live-host-internet-controversy-485781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unlikely, polarizing SNL hosting stint for the mogul reveals the boundaries and tensions of our ever-present culture wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did DeSantis violate First Amendment with FOXNEWS-only bill signing?</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/florida-politics/2021/05/07/did-desantis-violate-first-amendment-with-fox-news-only-bill-signing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts said the Florida governor likely ran afoul of the U.S. Constitution with his staged event in West Palm Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The origin story of Medina Spirit, Derby winner born on patch of Florida dirt and sold for $1,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/the-origin-story-of-medina-spirit-a-derby-winner-born-on-a-patch-of-florida-dirt-and-sold-for-241000/ar-BB1gvbQi </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In India's surge, religious gathering attended by millions helped spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/In-India-s-surge-a-religious-gathering-attended-16161841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI - As coronavirus cases in India shot upward last month, millions of people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney effort to turn Republicans from Trump threatens her ambitions. She says it's only beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Liz-Cheney-s-effort-to-turn-Republicans-from-16161868.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Liz Cheney had been arguing for months that Republicans had to face the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young causing Florida to have among highest hospital rates in country...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/younger-patients-causing-florida-to-have-among-the-highest-covid-hospital-rates-in-country/article_d0232b9b-f2ff-5a15-8236-702f84555174.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — As state and local officials drop mandates on COVID-19 restrictions, the virus continues to circulate throughout Florida, sending increasingly younger people to the hospital at rates that are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones? Lasers? New study suggests ways park service could clean Gateway Arch...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/drones-lasers-new-study-suggests-ways-park-service-could-clean-gateway-arch/article_349f30df-911e-5625-833d-d4f4301157f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS — The Gateway Arch gradually is losing some of its silver sheen, as a variety of forces — from salt to body oils to graffiti — take a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tried to track robbery victim by attaching iPhone to his car, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Florida-man-tried-to-track-his-robbery-victim-by-16161191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He'd been at the Millenia Mall in Orlando, Fla., for less than an hour when he allegedly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm as German anti-maskers co-opt Nazi resister Sophie Scholl...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210508-alarm-as-german-anti-maskers-co-opt-nazi-resister-sophie-scholl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alarm as German anti-maskers co-opt Nazi resister Sophie Scholl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese rocket debris set for uncontrolled plummet back to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210508-chinese-rocket-debris-set-for-uncontrolled-plummet-back-to-earth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Debris from parts of China’s Long March 5B rocket is set to crash down to Earth this weekend – but space agencies do not know when or where.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA and LaPierre's Fate Lies in Hands of TX Bankruptcy Judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-08/nra-and-lapierre-s-fate-lies-in-hands-of-texas-bankruptcy-judge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association, long a feared power broker, will learn its fate next week in a court ruling that could hobble the gun rights group and imperil the three-decade reign of its controversial boss, Wayne LaPierre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON warehouse employee dies at site of unionization drive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/07/amazon-employee-dies-at-bessemer-alabama-warehouse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon declined to share further details about the situation, noting that it was a personal medical incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Rachel Levine's Rise as Trans Issues Gain Prominence...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/this-is-politics-dr-rachel-levines-rise-as-transgender-issues-gain-prominence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Rachel Levine was not a particularly aggressive football player at the elite all-boys school she attended in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCAA Chief, Pressured by State Laws, Pushes to Let Athletes Cash In...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/n-c-a-a-chief-pressured-by-state-laws-pushes-to-let-athletes-cash-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORAL GABLES, Fla. — The University of Miami has long been able to make a glossy pitch to the students</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri House passes bill to create 'Rush Limbaugh Day'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/rush-limbaugh-michael-brown-8ff0013141d209410e4777035cdc913e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. (AP) — The Missouri House on Thursday voted in favor of creating “Rush Limbaugh Day.” The GOP-led House tacked the provision on another bill, which then passed the chamber...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Da Vinci 'Head of Bear' drawing seen fetching $16 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/da-vincis-head-bear-drawing-seen-fetching-up-16-mln-2021-05-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drawing of a bear's head by Leonardo da Vinci is seen fetching up to $16.7 million, potentially setting a record, when it heads to auction in July, Christie's said on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANS FIGHT SPLITS REPUBLICANS; New front in culture wars backfiring?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/06/transgender-athlete-laws-gop-484799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;States are considering an unprecedented number of bills targeting transgender women and girls who play sports, but Republican support for the measures is not universal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mogul Behind LA TIMES Says Papers Need Govt Aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/biotech-mogul-behind-la-times-says-papers-need-government-aid/ar-BB1gtRIe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of the Los Angeles Times is calling on the government to throw its support behind newspapers, saying the loss of advertising to tech companies and declining readership threaten local journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS SUPERYACHT SO BIG IT NEEDS 'SUPPORT YACHT' WITH HELIPAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.maxim.com/rides/jeff-bezos-megayacht-support-yacht-with-helipad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.maxim.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like a lot of divorced folks, billionaire Jeff Bezos is making some changes in his life. In February he stepped down as Amazon CEO, and Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Dogecoin whale owns $22 billion of cryptocurrency...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/currencies/news/single-dogecoin-whale-owns-22-billion-elon-musk-february-warning-2021-5-1030404506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last wild macaw in Rio lonely and looking for love...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-environment-and-nature-3632d009dc9f6929e4cf15a38fa58b00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Some have claimed she’s indulging a forbidden romance. More likely, loneliness compels her to seek company at Rio de Janeiro’s zoo. Either way, a blue-and-yellow macaw that zookeepers named Juliet is believed to be the only wild bird of its kind left in the Brazilian city where the birds once flew far and wide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBERATTACK SHUTS TOP U.S. PIPELINE</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/cyberattack-forces-a-shutdown-of-a-top-u-s-pipeline-operator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cyberattack forced the shutdown of one of the largest pipelines in the United States, in what appeared to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airborne Virus a Threat, CDC Acknowledges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/airborne-coronavirus-is-a-threat-the-c-d-c-acknowledges/ar-BB1gtRBD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal health officials on Friday updated public guidance about how the coronavirus spreads, emphasizing that transmission occurs by inhaling very fine respiratory droplets and aerosolized particles, as well as through contact with sprayed droplets or touching contaminated hands to one’s mouth, nose or eyes. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention now states explicitly — in large, bold lettering — that airborne virus can be inhaled even...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Bill to kill up to 90% of Idaho wolves signed by governor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-idaho-lifestyle-wolves-bills-f83cd2449975c977d167c0509bccab24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — Idaho Gov. Brad Little has signed into law a measure that could lead to killing 90% of the state’s 1,500 wolves in a move that was backed by hunters and the state's powerful ranching sector but heavily criticized by environmental advocates...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Children Who Grow Up Around Nature Less Likely To Have ADHD...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/children-green-spaces-adhd-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities brace for more...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/israel-braces-weekend-violence-after-spate-shootings-eviction-protests-n1266697</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t know what will happen with us if they kick the families out from the houses,” Yacoub Abu Arafa who is facing eviction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity stockpicker reveals Bill Hwang behind funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/ark-invest-ceo-wood-says-bill-hwang-provided-seed-capital-for-first-4-etfs--cnbc-2499924</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ark Invest CEO Wood says Bill Hwang provided seed capital for first 4 ETFs - CNBC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45,000 volunteer to kill 12 bison in national park...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210507-more-than-45-000-people-volunteer-to-kill-12-bison-in-us-national-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 45,000 people volunteer to kill 12 bison in US national park</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Video Shows Endangered Right Whales 'Hugging' In Cape Cod Bay...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/07/right-whales-hugging-video-cape-cod-bay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New drone footage shows an incredible encounter between endangered whales in Cape Cod Bay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY ending temperature checks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/walt-disney-world-universal-studios-end-temperature-checks-guests-n1266683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As temperature checks end, coronavirus safety measures such as face coverings and social distancing requirements will remain intact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHINGTONIAN staffers protest CEO's 'public threat' to return to in-person work...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/07/media/washingtonian-remote-work-culture/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staffers at the Washingtonian, a monthly DC-based magazine, are protesting Friday in response to their CEO's opposition of remote work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent clashes break out at Temple Mount... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/riots-break-out-at-temple-mount-667550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Police officers closed off Damascus Gate in the Old City in an attempt to regain control of the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians, Israel police clash at Al-Aqsa Mosque; 53 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-middle-east-west-bank-shootings-d5c6b1ed602844be69318bd1d1a334cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Palestinian worshippers clashed with Israeli police on Friday evening at Al-Aqsa Mosque in Jerusalem’s Old City as weeks-long tensions between Israel and the Palestinians over Jerusalem soared again...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World turns to China for vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/china/covid-the-world-turns-to-china-for-vaccines-after-india-us-stumble/articleshow/82451380.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China News: China’s reliability as a vaccine supplier is increasing its geopolitical clout at a time when the US and the EU have been slow confronting the global</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America burned out on news...</title>
      <link>https://interpreter.substack.com/p/america-is-burned-out-on-the-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;interpreter.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s okay. You can take a break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California reports first yearly population decline in history...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/society/california-reports-first-yearly-population-decline-in-states-history/10594297/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State officials announced Friday that California's population dipped 0.46% to just under 39.5 million people from January 2020 to January 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Headache' left behind on White House lawn...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/07/politics/white-house-construction-trump-biden/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The project that's currently tearing up the White House's South Lawn initially landed on Donald Trump's desk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why demand for armed drones is surging around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/07/turkey-and-china-disrupt-the-multibillion-dollar-armed-drone-market-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies in China, Turkey and Russia are increasingly producing armed drones, remotely piloted aircraft that can use guided weapons on and off the battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC still storing victims in refrigerated trucks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-68c9762a4420094d300f9cbada0186f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York City is still using refrigerated trucks to store bodies of coronavirus victims, more than a year after they were first set up as temporary morgues as deaths surged at at the height of the pandemic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA loses more than 182,000 residents; First yearly drop...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/californias-population-fell-182000-2020-yearly-drop-nations-77558321</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's population fell by more than 182,000 in 2020, the first yearly drop for the nation's most populous state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIPADVISOR removes insensitive review of Auschwitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/tripadvisor-removes-insensitive-review-auschwitz-museum-n1266685</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The author of the review said they went to Auschwitz to “test the chamber” and called the site “fun for the family."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The music festival refusing to bow to Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210507-the-music-festival-refusing-to-bow-to-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music festival refusing to bow to Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORWEGIAN Cruises threaten to skip Florida ports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-eb9db87299caeb813bb7aa4c0194c780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norwegian Cruise Lines is threatening to steer clear of Florida after the governor signed an order banning businesses from requiring that customers show proof of vaccination against COVID-19. The company says the order by Gov...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiring bust as unemployment rate RISES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-5dc338627748f7c75ba7e9a040a894d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — America’s employers added just 266,000 jobs last month, sharply lower than in March and a sign that some businesses are struggling to find enough workers as the economic recovery rapidly strengthens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S:  STOCKS SET MORE RECORDS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-financial-markets-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-78ed5d6167e083061655f79a72b91297</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Stocks are rallying to records on Wall Street Friday despite a stunningly disappointing report on the nation's job market, as investors see it helping to keep interest rates low. The S&amp;amp;P 500 rose 0...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
