<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept Legal Opinion To Support Whitaker Appointment...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/democrats-seek-ethics-advice-sought-or-received-by-acting-attorney-general-matthew-whitaker-1542048901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is expected to publish a legal opinion backing Matthew Whitaker’s installation as acting attorney general following questions about whether he can legally serve in the role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district investigates group Nazi salute photo...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbc15.com/content/news/District-responds-to-viral-photo-of-Baraboo-students-possibly-making-anti-semitic-gesture-500281042.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Baraboo School District is responding to a photo being shared thousands of times on social media of young men with their arms extended in the air appearing to give the Nazi salute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Personality Chased Out Of Brooklyn Bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/kat-timpf-chased-out-of-brooklyn-bar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fox News and National Review contributor was publicly harassed over the weekend in the third such politically motivated incident she’s faced in the last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm to decide if D unseats R in Maine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6380899/New-way-voting-faces-test-Maine-congressional-district.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP incumbent Bruce Polquin's Maine seat is being decided by a new system which asks voters to rank candidates by preference then counts 2nd and 3rd preferences until one has 50 per cent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi Predicts Mueller Indictment Likely In Days...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-counsel-witness-expects-charged-mueller-probe/story?id=59148352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Infowars Washington bureau chief tells ABC News that the special counsel has now indicated he will be charged in within a matter of days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Trebek: #MeToo 'Scary Time' For Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/article/entertainment/2018/11/12/alex-trebek-met-with-jeopardy-staff-at-the-start-of-metoo-i-said-this-has-got-to-be-a-scary-time-for-men/23587544/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“When the #MeToo movement started, I had discussions with the staff during production meetings. I said, ‘My gosh, this has got to be a scary time for men."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEC Defends Itself After Saudi Questions Its Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/opec-defends-itself-after-saudi-study-questions-its-future-1542043827</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two leading voices for OPEC defended the oil cartel’s record Monday, saying it was not at risk of disbanding. The statements came in response to Saudi-funded research exploring how an OPEC breakup might impact oil markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM WINS AZ SENATE RACE</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/arizona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Arizona election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mourning dog waits for 80 days in road where owner died...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/blogs-trending-46180260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video which shows the dog waiting in the middle of the busy road has 1.4 million views.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish launch UFO investigation after pilots see bright lights 'moving fast'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6380573/UFO-probe-pilots-report-seeing-mysterious-bright-lights-moving-fast-crossed-Ireland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Irish Aviation Authority launched the probe after a number of sightings over the country on November 9 at around 7.40am.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 voted by email. That's not allowed...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/election/article221536055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Hurricane Michael devastated the Panhandle in October, Bay County Supervisor of Elections Mark Andersen allowed about 150 displaced voters to cast ballots by email, even though there is no provision that allows for it in state law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Average Consumer To Spend $520 On Black Friday...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/thankful-black-friday-average-consumer-spend-520/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Love it or hate it, about half of all Americans are gearing up for Black Friday deals, and they're planning on spending some serious cash, according to an October 2018 survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Music In Middle Of Night Plagues NJ Communities, Perplexes Police...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/11/09/mysterious-music-plaguing-several-south-jersey-communities-in-middle-of-night-leaves-authorities-perplexed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a noise that's plagued Salem County residents along the Delaware River for months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL's $100 Million Bust...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/12/i-gotta-get-the-f-k-outta-here-jon-grudens-raiders-are-lost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2018 Raiders are what nightmares are made of. Following Oakland’s fifth straight loss Sunday, which dropped it to 1-8 on an already disastrous season, the $100 million coach said the curr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow To Host CBS Series 'MILLION DOLLAR MILE' From LeBron...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/lebron-james-tim-tebow-million-dollar-mile-cbs-1202499894/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NFL quarterback Tim Tebow has landed a new gig as host of the forthcoming CBS physical competition series Million Dollar Mile from executive producers Allison Grodner and Rich Meehan with Fl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blaze Breaks Out Off 118 Freeway In SoCal...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/12/rocky-fire-new-blaze-breaks-out-off-118-freeway-in-simi-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An immediate evacuation has been ordered in the areas of Box Canyon and Lake Manor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>170 neglected dogs seized from puppy mill...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nearly-170-neglected-dogs-seized-iowa-puppy-mill-173924207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHWOOD, Iowa (AP) — Officials say nearly 170 dogs showing signs of neglect in filthy kennels have been seized from an overcrowded puppy mill in northern Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW plunges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/12/stock-market-dow-futures-lower-on-thin-trading-on-veterans-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks fell on Monday as a decline in Apple shares, a strong dollar and lingering worries about global trade offset positive news on the dealmaking front.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke Plumes May Extend To East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/11/12/california-wildfires-smoke-plumes-new-england/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite imagery shows just how massive the fires are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home intruder bleeds to death after cutting self on broken window...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/12/home-intruder-bleeds-to-death-after-cutting-himself-on-broken-window/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An intruder who attempted to burglarize a home in El Paso, Texas, last week bled to death after cutting himself on a broken window, police said. The homeowner, who is not being publicly identified,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAN LEE DEAD AT 95...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/11/12/stan-lee-dead-dies-marvel-comics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stan Lee, the man who co-created Marvel Comics, has died ... TMZ has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Sam wants you -- to play video games for US Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/uncle-sam-wants-you-to-play-video-games-for-the-us-army-1.555885</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 15 years after launching “America’s Army,” a first-person shooter game aimed at enlisting real world soldiers, the Army is calling for active duty troops and reservists to compete in video gaming tournaments, or esports, in one of its latest recruiting efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen mysteriously arrives in DC...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/michael-cohen-president-trumps-personal-attorney-mysteriously-arrives/story?id=59141826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, President Trump's former personal attorney, was in D.C. Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom, Please Stop Talking to My Boss! Parents Invade the Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mom-please-stop-talking-to-my-boss-parents-invade-the-office-1542042333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eager to see what their adult offspring do all day, moms and dads embrace Bring Your Parents to Work Day; ‘It’s almost like we’re in a zoo, and we’re the animals’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Abrams files new suit in GA governor's race...</title>
      <link>http://www.onlineathens.com/nationworld/20181111/democrat-abrams-files-new-suit-in-georgia-governors-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA | Stacey Abrams' Democratic campaign filed a federal lawsuit Sunday asking a judge to delay vote certifications in Georgia unsettled governor's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA locates secret NKorea missile sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-analysts-id-13-secret-north-korean-missile-151833745.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. analysts said Monday they have located more than half of an estimated 20 secret North Korean missile development sites, highlighting the challenge the Trump administration faces in ensuring that North Korea complies with any eventual agreement to end its nuclear and missile programs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: May stares into abyss...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu/may-stares-into-brexit-abyss-as-domestic-opposition-mounts-idUSKCN1NH140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Theresa May's Brexit strategy came under attack from all sid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health department raids parks, pours bleach on food being given to homeless...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/kansas-city-health-department-pours-bleach-on-food-meant-for-homeless-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, MISSOURI (Fox 32 News) - The Kansas City Health Department threw away and poured bleach on food meant for homeless people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUNDLED AND BAGGED</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/must-see-video-broward-county-elections-officials-block-view-as-ballots-are-bundled-and-bagged-in-davie-florida-voting-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congo Ebola outbreak worst in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1044207/ebola-outbreak-congo-2018-ebola-symptoms-vaccine-who-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE current Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is the most severe in the country's history with 319 confirmed and probable cases and at least 198 dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST DEM IN:   OJEDA ANNOUNCES RUN FOR PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/11/11/richard-ojeda-2020-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I'm not trying to throw stones at people that are rich, but once again, we will have a field that will be full of millionaires," Ojeda said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke reaches Michigan...</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/smoke-from-california-wildfires-reaches-metro-detroit-michigan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are three wildfires raging in California, and the smoke from those wildfires is stretching across the entire United States and is even arriving in metro Detroit and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France calls for Europe to become a powerful new 'empire' to rival USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7721886/europe-should-become-empire-to-compete-with-china-and-us-says-french-minister-after-trump-rubbishes-calls-for-eu-army/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE’S finance minister has called for the EU to become a powerful new “empire” to rival the US and China in an interview which will infuriate Donald Trump. Bruno Le Maire’s comments come a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman blows up wedding dress at divorce party. Blast felt miles away...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article221527670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Santleben-Stiteler blew her wedding dress up at her divorce party Saturday in Lacoste, Texas. It was rigged with 20 pounds of explosives and she shot it from 200 yards away, video shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area residents urged to stay indoors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-wildfires/article/Smoke-from-deadly-Camp-Fire-still-blankets-Bay-13384133.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smoke from the deadly Camp Fire in Paradise is still drifting into the Bay Area, prompting public health officials to send out renewed alerts about air quality and urge residents to stay indoors. On Monday morning, an orange "unhealthy air" alert went out across the entire region, as air quality indexes range from 101 to 124, according to Bay Area Air Quality Management District. The polluted air is especially unhealthy for those with sensitive heart and lung conditions. Fine particles drifting in from the wildfire burning in Butte County can accumulate in the body to cause persistent coughing, difficulty breathing and reductions in lung function, according to the California Department of Public Health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECOUNT 2018!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/step-right-recount-circus-has-come-back-florida-n935011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pro-Trump protesters to swarming lawyers to paper jams, the latest ballot counting isn't making the state look any better than the last one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE THAN 70 ROCKETS FIRED FROM GAZA TO ISRAEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/More-than-50-rockets-fired-from-Gaza-to-Israel-571687 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After yesterday's firefight in Gaza, escalation between the IDF and Gaza appears inevitable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Top Threats to World 'Climate Change', Nuclear War...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2018/11/12/pope-francis-chief-threats-world-climate-change-nuclear-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis highlighted what he considers two main threats to humanity: the “immense crisis” of global warming and nuclear war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM WARNS</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/11/12/count-vote-candidates-election-recount-rick-scott-bill-nelson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As election departments across the state begin the process of recounting the votes from the 2018 midterm elections, the candidates whose races will be decided by the count are speaking out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein's Secret Weapon:  'Bloodhound' NYPD Detective Turned Private Eye...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/weinsteins-secret-weapon-is-a-bloodhound-nypd-detective-turned-private-eye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herman Weisberg worked in the same D.A.’s office prosecuting the movie mogul. Now he’s working against it. ‘He’s the knock at the door you don’t want.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters tells Trump to 'keep his mouth shut'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/mad-maxine-tells-trump-to-keep-his-mouth-shut-over-california-fires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Maxine Waters, who has criticized President Donald Trump and Republicans for their “rhetoric,” has been cranking up her tone since Democrats won the U.S. House of Representatives last week. During an interview on Sunday on MSNBC’s “AM Joy,” the California Democrat claimed that the Republican Party fears “strong, black” women like her. She also said she …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dems consider impeaching Trump, GOP leaders regret pursuing Clinton...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-as-dems-consider-impeaching-trump-gop-leaders-regret-pursuing-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Democrats are trying to reassure anyone that they won't impeach President Trump, they're aren't doing a very good job of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rick Scott wants state police to impound voting machines....</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/election/article221502395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys representing the U.S. Senate campaign of Florida Gov. Rick Scott filed emergency motions in Broward and Palm Beach courts Sunday seeking to have state police and local sheriff’s deputies impound voting machines while not in use during a statewide recount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ballot Boxes Left Inside AVIS Rental Car At Fort Lauderdale Airport? </title>
      <link>https://www.lauraloomer.us/blog/exclusive-provisional-ballot-boxes-left-inside-avis-rental-car-at-fort-lauderdale-airport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news, original research, stories you won't find anywhere else by investigative journalist Laura Loomer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI HIT LIST: 85 TRUMP TARGETS... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/house-democrats-subpoenas-trump-administration-cf3ed351-ff11-4498-89f4-cee588145198.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight will test the power of the presidency, Congress and the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  STARS LOSE HOMES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/woolsey-fire-miley-cyrus-gerard-butler-lose-home-1203025964/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive wildfires that continue to rage in California have forced hundreds of thousands in Southern California to evacuate from their homes. Miley Cyrus, Gerard Butler, and Neil Young are among…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O: Like, Like, You Know, Like, Dude, You Know?</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-michelle-o-you-know-dude-you-know</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I was like, dude, you're cute'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now 90% chance tropical wave in Atlantic becomes storm or depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.tcpalm.com/story/weather/hurricanes/2018/11/12/tropical-storm-possible-later-week-what-impact-florida/1974477002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tcpalm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chances for development of the system have increased to 90 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 million Americans live in RVs. Meet 'modern nomads'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/1-million-Americans-live-in-RVs-Meet-the-modern-13383991.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Robert and Jessica Meinhofer told friends they were moving into an RV in 2015, most thought they were crazy. The questions poured in: How could they go from living in a 2,000-square-foot home to living in a 250-square-foot trailer? What would they do with their stuff? What would their children, ages 6 and 9, do for school? Was this a midlife crisis? The hardest people to convince were Jessica's parents, who grew up in an impoverished Latino neighborhood in the Bronx and worked hard so their daughter could have a better life. They couldn't understand why the couple wanted to live like migrant laborers. The Meinhofers are doing this by choice, not financial desperation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right parents who named son after Hitler jailed in Britain...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/far-parents-named-son-hitler-jailed-britain-150107372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A couple who named their child after Adolf Hitler were convicted in Britain on Monday for being members of banned far-right group National Action. Adam Thomas, 22, and Claudia Patatas, 38, were convicted along with Daniel Bogunovic, 27, of being members of the organization, after they shared messages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos, deal or new vote: What is grand Brexit finale?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chaos-deal-vote-grand-brexit-finale-150958780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Theresa May is trying to clinch a Brexit divorce deal with the European Union but the bigger challenge may be to get any agreement approved by the British parliament. Any deal must be approved by British lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Vatican's request, bishops delay votes addressing sex abuse scandals...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/religion/2018/11/12/vatican-asks-us-bishops-not-vote-sexual-abuse-proposals-they-planned/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. bishops wanted to vote on major proposals for addressing sexual abuse. The Vatican called a last-minute halt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortar hits bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-november-12-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sides exchange fire following incident, with Palestinian rockets setting off Red Alert sirens as far away from coastal enclave as Kiryat Gat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza launches massive rocket barrage at Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Hamas-fires-rockets-from-Gaza-on-southern-communities-in-the-Negev-571683 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>93-year-old pulled to safety by garbageman...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcra.com/article/garbageman-pulls-93-year-old-into-truck-as-camp-fire-spreads/24951841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Camp Fire encroached on Magalia, a 93-year-old woman stepped out on her front porch hoping someone might see her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE shares sliding...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/12/apple-stock-slides-after-supplier-lumentum-cuts-outlook.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Apple's facial recognition suppliers cut its outlook based on a reduced shipment request from one its largest customers. Shares of Apple slid as much as 3.7 percent on the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less than 1 in 3 meet new fitness guidelines...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2018/11/12/physical-fitness-aerobic-activity-sports-social-media-health-human-services-department/1943318002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Baugh, who founded the fitness advocacy non-profit group PHITAmerica, says even the dire picture painted in the federal reports may be too optimistic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown Blames Climate Deniers...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/news-and-politics/jerry-brown-climate-change-deniers-definitely-contributing-to-the-new-abnormal-of-wildfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're getting caught up here in a changed world that not so many people were aware of or thinking about... the chickens are coming home to roost," says California governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST: Sorry State of John Travolta...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-sorry-state-of-john-travolta-scientology-movie-bombs-and-dark-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The star of ‘Grease’ and ‘Pulp Fiction,’ who’s thus far eluded the wrath of #MeToo, is in yet another laughably bad film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ could probe COMCAST as pressure mounts over alleged antitrust violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/pressure-builds-on-doj-to-probe-alleged-anti-trust-violations-committed-by-comcast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ACA says Comcast is an even greater anti-competitive threat than AT&amp;T-Time Warner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China launches 'pop star ban': TV stations told to cut air time of celebs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6379655/Chinas-pop-star-ban-TV-stations-told-cut-air-time-celebrities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The edict comes after A-list movie star Fan Bingbing was ordered to pay about 884 million yuan (£98 million) in taxes and fines, spurring discussion on the moral health of China’s film industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice of HAL dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/movies/douglas-rain-creepy-voice-hal-2001-dies-90-n935036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rain's sinuous, detached reading of HAL's lines made the computer's murders of four astronauts all the more shocking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit list: At least 85 Trump investigation targets!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2018-midterm-elections-house-democrats-investigations-6bcfabb1-f1b2-49ce-8014-3e9b0c30db6c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Mueller to North Korea, there's a lot on the table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm suffocating': Khashoggi final words revealed in audio recording...</title>
      <link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/suffocating-khashoggi-words-turkish-reporter-181111085534099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Turkish journalist tells Al Jazeera what Khashoggi's last words were, according to unpublished audio recording.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The animals caught in destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46178230 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deadly blazes are unleashing destruction across California, forcing thousands to evacuate their homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training kids to kill at Ukrainian nationalist camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/94fe1c68205a43ca96fcc89c88a7cc9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIEV, Ukraine (AP) — The campers, some clad in combat fatigues, carefully aim their assault rifles. Their instructor offers advice: Don't think of your target as a human being. So when these boys and girls shoot, they will shoot to kill. Most are in their teens, but some are as young as 8 years old. They are at a summer camp created by one of Ukraine's radical nationalist groups, hidden in a forest in the west of the country, that was visited by The Associated Press. The camp has two purposes: to train children to defend their country from Russians and their sympathizers — and to spread nationalist ideology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flintstones' couple live like cave dwellers at own 'Stone Age' village ...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/flintstones-couple-build-stone-age-13577912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naomi Walmsley and husband Dan Westall wear Paleolithic designs made from rabbit fur and hunt with a bow and arrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mishaps, protests and litigation overshadow...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/105ce13715ae4c9da23ba2adf5cafae0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Mishaps, protests and litigation are overshadowing the vote recount in Florida's pivotal races for governor and Senate, reviving memories of the 2000 presidential fiasco in the premier political battleground state. All 67 counties are facing a state-ordered deadline of Thursday to complete their recounts, and half had already begun. Many other counties were expected to begin the work Monday after a weekend of recount drama in Broward and Palm Beach counties, home to large concentrations of Democratic voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhol in New York: Fresh experience for audiences old and new...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/warhol-york-fresh-experience-audiences-old-011405621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His Marilyn Monroe paintings and oversize soup cans are cultural icons, but in an exhibition opening Monday, New York's Whitney Museum hopes to paint a new, more complex picture of Andy Warhol. Now the Whitney, located on the banks of the Hudson River in the city's Meatpacking District, hopes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned to death because of rumor on WHATSAPP...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/whatsapp-rumours-incite-angry-mob-13576897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING CONTENT: The men were dragged out of a jail cell and killed as hundreds cheered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO maps dangerous misuse of antibiotics...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181112-who-maps-dangerous-misuse-antibiotics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 200 still missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/more-200-still-missing-californias-deadliest-wildfire-record-092228965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 people were missing early on Monday in California's deadliest and most destructive blaze on record, one of two fires raging in the state which have killed at least 31 people and forced more than a quarter of a million evacuations. The so-called Camp Fire 40 miles northwest of Sacramento</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Flight: AI in Cockpit...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-future-of-flight-ai-in-the-cockpit-1542018600 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI-empowered systems may soon allow autonomous flying machines to reduce the number of pilots and soldiers working in high-risk environments. Could these flying robots also be firing weapons? WSJ’s Jason Bellini reports, in the latest episode of Moving Upstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Much Caffeine May Stress Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/12/well/live/too-much-caffeine-may-stress-the-heart.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In moderate doses caffeine has mainly positive effects for most people. But it increases production of cortisol, which can lead to health problems including anxiety, weight gain and heart disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress braces for high-drama lame duck...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/416037-congress-braces-for-high-drama-lame-duck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress is returning to Washington this week for an end-of-the-year session that’s expected to be filled with high-stakes legislative flights and plenty of drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O: 'I stopped even trying to smile' during Trump's inauguration...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/416171-michelle-obama-i-stopped-even-trying-to-smile-during-trumps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Michelle Obama says in her new book that she stopped “even trying to smile” during President Trump’s 2017 inauguration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if Weinstein walks free?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/12/what-if-harvey-weinstein-walks-free/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What seemed unthinkable one year ago is on the verge of happening: Harvey Weinstein will probably walk. Last Monday, Weinstein’s attorneys filed a motion to dismiss the entire criminal case against…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man marries hologram...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/crazy-love-japanese-man-married-hologram-doc-1ar15l1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll parties part of 'burgeoning zeitgeist'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/741169/sex-doll-party-texas-brick-dollbanger-realdoll-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMP FIRE MATCHES DEADLIEST IN STATE HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/11/11/crews-continue-to-battle-strong-winds-in-deadly-camp-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters worked to contain the deadly Camp Fire, which had burned some 109,000 acres Sunday and was 25 percent contained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 Chinese Space Startups Race to Get Into Orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinese-startups-push-into-space-business-1541851211</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space is corporate China’s newest frontier, as Chinese startups prepare to boldly go head-to-head with the likes of Elon Musk’s SpaceX for a slice of the space market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighter saves American flag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/11/firefighter-saves-american-flag-from-california-inferno/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A firefighter battling the devastating blazes ripping through California was caught on video saving an American flag and draping it over the mailbox of a gutted home. The touching footage shared by…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious bubbling pool of mud is moving, and so far it can't be stopped...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/11/bubbling-pool-mud-moving-california-dont-know-why-geology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traveling at about 20 feet a year, the muddy mystery has no obvious driver—and so far, it can't be stopped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailbreaks, Submarines, Gold-Plated AK-47: El Chapo Trial Epic Tale... </title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/el-chapo-s-trial-will-tell-an-epic-tale/17987502/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — Even as the Mexican police jet started its descent into Long Island, Joaquín Guzmán Loera had no idea where he was going. All he knew was that hours earlier, he had been whisked from a prison in Ciudad Juárez and put aboard the plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy Attack Sub Unit Trains to Fight Russia, China...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2018/11/08/submarine-forces-china-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy submarine force is creating an aggressor squadron as one initiative to ensure all subs and their crews are combat-ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest air tanker joins fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/11/11/california-fires-global-supertanker-joins-fight-against-camp-fire/1970166002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Global SuperTanker, a converted 747,Â on Sunday morning joined the aerial firefight against what is now Californiaâ€™s most devastating wildfire.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
