<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump Administration Weakens Protections for Endangered Species...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/aug/12/endangered-species-act-trump-administration-protection-changes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Changes to how Endangered Species Act is implemented come as world scientists warn biodiversity crisis will put humanity at risk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Alarming Rise In Teens Who Need Glasses; Excessive Screen Time Blamed...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-blames-disturbing-rise-in-teens-who-need-glasses-on-excessive-screen-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study is warning parents that all that screen time may be behind a stunning rise in children who need prescription glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARIANNE WILLIAMSON: You Can't Just Assume Democracy Is Okay...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/08/12/marianne_williamson_you_cant_just_assume_democracy_is_okay_because_it_was_okay_decades_ago.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FNC's Steve Hilton interviews Democratic presidential hopeful Marianne Williamson during her time at the Iowa State Fair. Williamson said democracy must be tended to like you would your body or your marriage. "You can't just assume that your democracy is okay because it was okay several decades ago. We are learning, and we are learning it the hard way, that our democracy must be tended to," Williamson said in an interview.  WILLIAMSON: The American revolution is an ongoing process. You can't say I was healthy in 1995 so I don't have to take care of my health anymore. You can't say my body was in shape in 2013 so I don't have to work out anymore. And it turns out, and we're experiencing it now. You can't just assume that your democracy is okay because it was okay several decades ago. We are learning, and we are learning it the hard way, that our democracy must be tended to. If you don't take care of your marriage, don't be surprised that you lose your marriage. If you don't take care of your business, don't be surprised if you lose your business. If you don't take care of your health, don't be surprised if you lose your health. And if you don't care and tend to your democracy, don't go being surprised when all these forces that would assault it are at the door. So it's the 11th hour, but it is not midnight yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Serious irregularities'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/jail-where-jeffrey-epstein-died-had-serious-irregularities-ag-barr-n1041421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barr's remarks came two days after Epstein was found unresponsive in his cell at the federal detention center in lower Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Man Causes Panic At Houston Mall...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/08/12/masked-man-causes-panic-houston-mall-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people rushed out of a Houston mall on Sunday after a masked man jumped on a food court table and said he would kill himself before throwing down an unknown object covered in toilet paper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HONG KONG DEFIANT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1131c0f97db34e1293862ca7fa8d4f06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — One of the world's busiest airports canceled all flights after thousands of pro-democracy demonstrators crowded into Hong Kong's main terminal Monday, while the central government...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Municipalities nationwide grapple with bans on pet pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Municipalities-nationwide-grapple-with-bans-on-14297855.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The knock on Dani Guill's door came in early May. It was a zoning compliance officer, there to investigate a complaint from a neighbor. Word was that a pig lived in her Virginia Beach, Virginia house, he told her.  He wasn't wrong. In fact, 3-year-old, 120-pound Pumpkin has her own bedroom and wardrobe. She loves Honey Nut Cheerios and acts grumpy when she doesn't get as much as she wants.  But unlike Guill's dog, Pumpkin is not allowed to reside in Virginia Beach. City law views her as livestock, though she is a potbellied pig bred to be a pet. Guill said the officer gave her 30 days to relocate the pig.  The eviction is now on hold as two city council members, at Guill's urging, draft a proposal to legalize Pumpkin and other pet pigs in the city. Guill said seven other owners have surfaced since she took up the cause. "Out of the woodwork, here come all the other pig parents," she said.  It's hardly an unusual municipal matter. Across the nation, pet pig owners are forcing cities and towns to grapple with the definition of swine and reassess zoning laws written in eras when the divide between pets and farm animals was far starker.  In the past year, pet pig legalization has been on the agenda in Holland, Michigan; Brookhaven, Georgia; and Chatfield, Minnesota - all of which decided to allow pigs. In Amherst, New York and Eureka Springs, Arkansas, officials did the opposite, upholding bans and calling for the ouster of outlaw pigs. Officials in other places are still mulling what to do.  "This is a growing concern. . . . It's hitting councils all over the country," said Mickey Schneider, a Eureka Springs alderwoman who pushed to change local law so that two potbellies in the Ozarks tourist town could stay. The animals have not been expelled, and Schneider said she's still trying. "These pigs are not stinky. And they are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather app alerts when about to rain, down to minute, all around world!</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/business/article/ClimaCell-weather-app-alerts-when-it-s-about-to-14297708.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if, wherever you're living, working or traveling, you could receive an alert before it's about to rain or snow and when the precipitation is about to end? And it's pretty accurate, too?  ClimaCell, a fledgling weather technology company based in Boston, released a mobile app Monday that provides notifications for exact locations in more than 50 countries. It promises "street-by-street, minute-by-minute short-term forecasts."  The app leverages the company's technology innovations, which are making waves in weather business industries.  ClimaCell, founded in 2015, has developed a global network of weather data that marries traditional observations of pressure, temperature, precipitation and wind with information drawn from wireless signals, satellites, connected cars, airplanes, street cameras, drones and other electronic sources. Millions of pieces of weather data can be derived from these technologies. It's what the company describes as the "weather of things."  This mix of data is fed into ClimaCell's forecast models, operated in Boulder, Colorado. The company created the NowCast model that gives highly specific, minute-by-minute forecasts out to six hours and a longer-term model, known as CBAM, that produces forecasts out to six days.  These models are designed to provide forecasts to help businesses solve problems in which "extra accuracy" is needed, according to Shimon Elkabetz, ClimaCell's chief executive.  Many of the weather companies operating today, spun up in the 1960s and 1970s, just take model forecasts from different governments, blend them and use statistical techniques to try to make them better. But ClimaCell is creating its forecasts from scratch.  Elkabetz said early results on its accuracy are promising. Compared with government forecasts, "we've...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In town called 'Thank God,' Central Americans' pursuit of promised land fades...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-08-11/guatemala-smuggling-hub-quiet-mexico-slows-migration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once bustling with migrants on their way to the United States, Gracias a Dios — whose name translates to 'Thank God' — now feels like a ghost town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE First Look at Witherspoon-Aniston Drama...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/apples-morning-show-teaser-first-look-at-reese-witherspoon-jennifer-aniston-drama-1230792 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The teaser brings viewers inside the drama of the fictional TV news show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogfishing: Online daters pose with adorable pets that aren't theirs...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/article/Dogfishing-When-online-daters-pose-with-adorable-14297742.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tinder, Avery Chuang developed a bad habit: She almost always swiped right on guys with a ridiculously adorable dog photo. It's not a high standard to go by, the 25-year-old in Elk Grove, California, admitted, but it helped her find men who are dog owners like herself - presuming that, of course, the featured pup is theirs.  She encountered her fair share of dog-baiters on dating apps (which she no longer uses since they are "addictive and demoralizing"). Most men were upfront in conversation with Chuang, but a few did slip through the cracks until she pieced it together.  There was a guy Chuang found attractive and charming and normal - until he turned around and questioned her for probing about his dog. And there was another who profusely apologized for displaying a friendly corgi that wasn't his (after she called him out) and then ghosted her.  Dogs, notably adorable photos of dogs, are a ubiquitous aspect of dating. They're convenient icebreakers on apps and on first dates. They add a nugget of personality to a profile. On Apple's App Store, Bumble features a photo of a bespectacled man cuddling a goldendoodle to insinuate how likable that is. There's also Dig, a new dating app specifically for dog owners.  This cultural obsession with dogs on the apps has spiraled into another problem: Daters are posting photos of pups they don't own, to attract matches. "Dogfishing" is not exactly a lie - the person did take a photo with that dog - but to some daters, it feels like a veiled form of deception. And things can get awkward fast when a date realizes that the pet in the profile solely exists as bait.  "That's the main thing: Stop borrowing dogs," said Erika Ettin, an online dating coach in Washington. She advises her clients to curate profiles representative of their actual life. "It's just odd when you're using...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Unanswered Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-08-12/7-unanswered-questions-about-epsteins-death-mainstream-media-not-talking-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocking suspect's hairstyle could get you prosecuted, police warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/08/12/mocking-suspects-hairstyle-could-get-prosecuted-police-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have warned social media users they could face arrest if they &amp;quot;troll&amp;quot; a wanted drug dealer by mocking his distinctive hairstyle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE BOMBS AT BOX OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-kitchen-bombs-furthers-hollywoods-identity-crisis-1230760 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only new movie to impress over the Aug. 9-11 weekend was 'Scary Stories We Tell in the Dark,' a parting gift from the disappearing CBS Films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA raises chance of recession to 1-in-3...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/12/bank-of-america-raises-chance-of-a-recession-to-1-in-3-in-the-next-12-months.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bank of America said recent data leads it to believe there is a 1-in-3 chance of a recession in the next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentine election surprise triggers crash in peso...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/12/argentina-election-macri-suffers-setback-as-analysts-warn-of-peso-depreciation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presidential primaries were viewed by many as a referendum on Macri's painful economic reforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Satellite Catches Footage of Flying Orb...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/viral/201908111076522269-spacex-satellite-catches-mysterious-object-flying-camera/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage posted by YouTube conspiracy theory channel thirdphaseofmoon was apparently taken onboard SpaceX’s Amos 17 satellite, which launched earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 tires slashed in Orthodox Jewish community...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/100-tires-slashed-orthodox-jewish-community-police/story?id=64919973</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 tires have been slashed in a predominately Orthodox Jewish community in New Jersey in recent days, according to authorities there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guatemala election winner sets sights on changing Trump migrant deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-guatemala-election-migrants/guatemala-election-winner-sets-sights-on-changing-trump-migrant-deal-idUSKCN1V20OE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guatemalan conservative Alejandro Giammattei secured a crushing victory in a pre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals chafe at president's blasphemy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/12/trump-evangelicals-blasphemy-profanity-1456178</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Trump-supporting West Virginia state senator who represents many evangelicals got three phone calls from constituents complaining about Trump's profanity after a recent rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellmate transferred hours before...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/jeffrey-epstein-checked-for-hours-apparent-suicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correctional officers at the New York City prison housing Jeffrey Epstein didn't check in on him for hours leading up to his apparent suicide on Saturday after his cellmate was transferred for reasons that were not immediately clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO DONE IT?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-death-investigation-alleged-victims-vow-to-keep-seeking-justice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As probes are launched over how it happened in a federal lockup known for its tight security, his alleged victims vow to keep seeking justice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death shifts focus to alleged co-conspirator Ghislaine Maxwell...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/epstein-death-britain-alleged-co-conspirator-ghislaine-maxwell-prince-andrew-2019-08-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Socialite Ghislaine Maxwell has been accused of finding teenage girls for Epstein and his friends, including a British royal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE CRAZY: UNIVERSITY BANS BURGERS TO SAVE PLANET...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/university-bans-burgers-help-save-114859056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beef products are to be removed from sale at Goldsmiths University as part of a plan to become carbon neutral by 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Mystery: Man's Penis Turning To Bone...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/09/doctors-penis-turning-to-bone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bronx doctors say the unidentified man was likely suffering from an “exceedingly rare” case of ossification, or the abnormal formation of bone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay-TV Subscriber Losses More Than Triple in Quarter...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/u-s-pay-tv-subscriber-losses-more-than-triple-to-1-5m-in-q2-report-1202666232/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The largest pay-TV providers in the U.S. saw video subscriber losses more than triple to 1.53 million in the second quarter, according to the latest report from Leichtman Research Group. The tally …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Republicans brace for drubbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/12/texas-republicans-2020-elections-1456161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Republicans need to be very concerned,&amp;quot; says a GOP member of the state's congressional delegation of next year's elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury yields extend plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/treasury-yields-extend-plunge-as-geopolitical-tensions-heat-up-2019-08-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury prices rise Monday, pushing yields lower, as protests in Hong Kong underline the worsening geopolitical backdrop across the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake-like UFO returns as mystery object seen 'moving like it's alive' over New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/797792/Snake-UFO-return-mystery-object-filmed-New-York-state-Clayville-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leeches latest health trend...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/851730/how-leeches-became-latest-health-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancient cultures believed leeches had healing powers. Now, the practice is making a modern-day resurgence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers sent famous pathologist to watch over...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-camp-sends-pathologist-michael-baden-to-watch-over-his-autopsy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York City medical examiner is waiting on “further information” before ruling on an official cause of death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autopsy done...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/investigations/after-autopsy-cause-jeffrey-epstein-s-death-awaits-further-information-n1041216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The financier was found unresponsive Saturday in his jail cell in Manhattan, where he was being held on federal sex trafficking charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein kept detailed diaries which could haunt powerful friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9702330/jeffrey-epstein-diaries-prince-andrew-donald-trump-clinton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFREY Epstein kept “meticulously detailed” diaries of his friendships which could come back to haunt his powerful pals, reports claim. The billionaire paedo, who died from an apparent suicide on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choose your own reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/11/opinion/jeffrey-epstein-suicide-conspiracies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With each news cycle, the false-information system grows more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens to Epstein's money and homes now? Can feds seize everything?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/what-happens-to-jeffrey-epstein-s-money-and-homes-now/article_d7931aa7-ff5c-54ec-9d39-a8e0a882d40f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Jeffrey Epstein’s apparent suicide is a significant obstacle for federal prosecutors, who spent months painstakingly building a case against the multimillionaire who was charged in July with in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Republicans in Congress bolting for exits?</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/elections-2020/2019/08/09/many-texas-republicans-congress-bolting-exits-mean-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Four rapid-fire retirement announcements by Texas Republicans in Congress have prompted fresh soul-searching for a political party...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO DONE IT?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-death-apparent-suicide-inspires-conspiracy-theories-2019-08-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online theorists Saturday quickly offered unsubstantiated speculation — including some retweeted by President Trump — that Epstein's death wasn't a suicide, or it was faked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO VIDEO </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/11/theres-no-video-of-jeffrey-epsteins-apparent-suicide-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no surveillance video of the incident during which Jeffrey Epstein apparently hanged himself in a federal lockup in Lower Manhattan, law-enforcement officials told The Post on Sunday.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican challenger Weld warns party of Trump's 'racist tirades'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/republican-challenger-weld-warns-party-trumps-racist-tirades-193550990.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He wants to help the working poor, enact climate protections and unify Americans, but 2020 Republican presidential candidate Bill Weld saved his sharpest talk Sunday for Donald Trump, branding his rival a racist who could destroy their party. Weld, a former two-term governor of Massachusetts, is perhaps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren wows in Iowa... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d34646b9511f4d119f7e1af4057d766e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — The chant — "2 cents, 2 cents, 2 cents" — started in the back of a massive crowd that packed sidewalks at the Iowa State Fair. Elizabeth Warren, basking in the spontaneous...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  5 children killed in day care center fire in PA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9c940d4b2544facaf60ea18dc03e0da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ERIE, Pa. (AP) — An early morning fire in Pennsylvania at a residential building housing a day care center killed five children and sent the owner to the hospital, authorities said. The fire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HEADS MUST ROLL'...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/investigation-underway-after-death-of-jeffrey-epstein-in-nyc-jail/5457853/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Attorney General William Barr said the suicide death of accused sex trafficker Jeffrey Epstein raises "serious questions that must be answered." The FBI is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci fires back at President: He will turn 'on everyone' and then 'entire country'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/08/11/donald-trump-and-former-aide-anthony-scaramucci-engage-twitter-war/1980716001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scaramucci calls Trump's trips to mass shooting sites a 'catastrophe;' Trump says Scaramucci doesn't know anything about him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed remains target as economy falls short of Trump's goals...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-fed-trump/fed-remains-a-target-as-economy-falls-short-of-trumps-ambitious-goals-idUSKCN1V10BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has become a jarring and frequent contradiction. President Donald Trump blame...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royals rally round Prince Andrew...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7346077/Prince-Andrew-joined-fellow-royals-church-Balmoral-day-Jeffrey-Epsteins-suicide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew joined the Queen and his daughter Beatrice today at church in Balmoral, after his former friend Jeffrey Epstein was found hanged in his jail cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BLUNDERS PILE UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-gaffes-parkland-trump-467d4127-0107-4ca7-adf9-40e1937ca8c6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden called himself a "gaffe machine" eight months ago, and his slips have long been part of his persona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US gold medallists at Pan American Games face sanctions over anti-Trump podium protests...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/us-gold-medallists-pan-american-games-face-sanctions-173542304--sow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two US gold medal winners could face sanctions after staging dramatic podium protests against US President Donald Trump at the Pan American Games in Lima. Gwen Berry stunned the crowd when she raised a clenched right fist on the podium and bowed her head as the US national anthem closed her gold medal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fencer Kneels...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-olympic-fencer-kneels-national-145909463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He may face disciplinary action from the U.S. Olympic Committee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's Salvini Tells Richard Gere to Take Stranded Migrants to Hollywood on his Jet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-star-gere-speaks-support-113740190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood star Richard Gere on Saturday urged the Italian government to stop "demonising people" and instead help migrants who have been stranded on a Spanish charity boat in the Mediterranean for more than a week. Gere, who visited the Open Arms ship in a show of support on Friday, joined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes at Temple Mount between Muslim protesters, Israel Police...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed7127e96f18434599bb0b58b04dc84f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Muslim worshippers and Israeli police clashed Sunday at a major Jerusalem holy site during prayers marking the Islamic holiday of Eid al-Adha. Palestinian medics said at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HEADS MUST ROLL'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b609668da05c4ac5bbc9aa50c9e6b6d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Investigators have long been digging into allegations of sexual abuse and conspiracy against Jeffrey Epstein . The financier's apparent suicide brings another mystery to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia tells GOOGLE not to advertise "illegal" events after election protests...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190811132824-4jt3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/PROTESTS-GOOGLE (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Russia tells Google not to advertise</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
