<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER Publisher Subpoena In Cohen Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/publisher-of-national-enquirer-subpoenaed-in-michael-cohen-probe-1529529151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities have subpoenaed the publisher of the National Enquirer for records related to its $150,000 payment to a former Playboy model for her story alleging an affair with Donald Trump, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Northern California, Rent Disputes Turn Deadly...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/california/articles/2018-06-20/northern-california-landlord-charged-with-shooting-tenant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Naked lady dies of hypothermia... After trapped in closet 'mistook' for bathroom for days... Broke pipe, clawed walls...</title>
      <link>https://www.walesonline.co.uk/news/wales-news/sporty-fit-healthy-mum-who-14808581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.walesonline.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Mary Isherwood's family said they were 'absolutely devastated' by her tragic death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stonehenge builders used Pythagoras' theorem -- 2,000 years before he was born...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/06/20/stonehenge-builders-used-pythagoras-theorem-2000-years-greek/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The builders of Britain&amp;rsquo;s ancient stone circles like Stonehenge were using Pythagoras' theorem 2,000 years before the Greek philosopher was born, experts have claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algeria turns off internet to stop exam cheating...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/algeria-has-done-away-with-internet-to-stop-students-from-cheating-1870727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Algeria went offline on Wednesday for the start of high school diploma exams, the first in a series of internet blackouts to stop students cheating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau picks Oct. date for marijuana legalization...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4285946/marijuana-legal-date-october-17-canada-trudeau-confirms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational marijuana will officially become legal in Canada on Oct. 17, 2018, the prime minister announced on Wednesday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA steps up protection from asteroids, comets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-stepping-earths-protection-asteroids-comets-193810541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The U.S. government is stepping up efforts to protect the planet from incoming asteroids that could wipe out entire regions or even continents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Archbishop of DC Removed After Sex Abuse Allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/20/politics/theodore-mccarrick-washington-abuse-allegation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cardinal Theodore McCarrick, who led the Archdiocese of Washington and was a political force in the nation's capital, said on Wednesday that he has been removed from public ministry by the Vatican because of a decades-old allegation of sexual abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX AGREES TO HIGHER DISNEY BID...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fox-disney-announce-new-deal-1529496937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney raised its offer to purchase most of 21st Century Fox to more than $70 billion in cash and stock, topping an unsolicited offer from rival Comcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Hugh Hefner's 26-year-old son save PLAYBOY?</title>
      <link>http://nationalpost.com/news/world/we-should-not-apologize-for-sex-can-hugh-hefners-26-year-old-son-save-an-ailing-playboy-empire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Hugh’s death at 91, Cooper Hefner has stepped up as the creative mind of the sprawling 65-year-old brand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beer may lack fizz in Europe amid carbon dioxide shortage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3e238478e4d24430bf05b8e8ccb08730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — No beer at this time of year?        A British trade group says there's a shortage of carbon dioxide in Northern Europe, sparking fears that drinks may lack f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man crushed to death by coffin at mother's funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/06/20/indonesian-man-crushed-coffin-mother-funeral/717591002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indonesian man was crushed to death by his mother's casket at her funeral on Friday on the island of Sulawesi, according to police.  Pallbearers at the funeral were carrying the casket up a bamboo ladder onto a lakkian  when the ladder slipped and the coffin landed on Samen Kondorura, 40.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURGER KING rescinds offer for women impregnated by World Cup players...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2018/06/20/burger-king-russian-world-cup-pregnancy-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burger King says it’s sorry for offering a lifetime supply of Whoppers to Russian women who get pregnant from World Cup players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman may have served ex-lover's remains at BBQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2018/06/20/serial-killer-kelly-cochran-bbq-michigan/716988002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alleged serial killer fed the remains of her lover at a neighborhood barbecue before turning around and killing her husband two years later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE CRITICIZES...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-pope-criticises-trump-administration-policy-migrant-family-092151372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has criticised the Trump administration's policy of separating migrant families at the Mexican border, saying populism is not the answer to the world's immigration problems. Speaking to Reuters, the Pope said he supported recent statements by U.S. Catholic bishops who called the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SO SORRY...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/politics/abc-news-apologizes-banner-falsely-claims-paul-manafort-killed-five-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News issued an apology Wednesday after a banner during a live report claimed that former Trump aide Paul Manafort had copped to killing five people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Falsely Reports Manafort Guilty of Manslaughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chyron-malfunction-abc-apologizes-for-graphic-declaring-manafort-pleaded-guilty-to-manslaughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England fans do Nazi salutes, sing anti-Semitic songs...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/breaking-england-fans-nazi-salute-12754254</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The supporters sang a song, knowing they were being filmed, in Volgograd where England played on Monday night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resigns from RNC, cites investigation and immigration policy...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/michael-cohen-resigns-rnc-committee-post/story?id=56033406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, President Trump’s longtime confidant and former personal attorney, has resigned from his post as deputy finance chair of the Republican National Committee's Finance Committee, sources close to the RNC told ABC News. In his resignation letter to Ronna McDaniel, the RNC chair, Cohen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO: Woman Drinks Dog's Urine To Cure Acne...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/06/20/woman-drinks-dogs-urine-acne/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman claims that drinking dog urine cleared her skin of acne and helped her overcome depression in new viral video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg to Spend $80 Million on Midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/20/us/politics/mike-bloomberg-democrats-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Bloomberg plans to pour money into advertising on television, online and in the mail, with most of it going to support Democratic congressional candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos at MANDALAY BAY after water crashes through ceiling...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5865635/Mandalay-Bay-hotel-water-main-bursts-sending-thousands-gallons-water-ceiling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A water main broke Tuesday creating massive flooding in the convention center at the Mandalay Bay hotel in Las Vegas leaving the venue's floor covered in water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condoms, kites, balloons: 'Silly' Gaza weapons could lead to real war...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/condoms-kites-birthday-balloons-silly-gaza-weapons-could-lead-to-serious-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians in the Gaza Strip are relentlessly flying a variety of airborne arson and explosive devices into Israel, causing hundreds of fires, millions of shekels in damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops stop traffic so rattlesnake can cross busy intersection...</title>
      <link>http://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article213509939.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video shows Roanoke, Virginia, police diverting traffic to allow an endangered timber rattlesnake to cross the road. Some on social media questioned the wisdom of impeding traffic for a snake, while others praised the officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Immigrant Detainee Family Sues Obama, Gov't For Wrongful Death...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2014/08/29/family-of-immigrant-detainee-sues-president-obama-government-for-wrongful-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy Luna fought back tears Friday as she discussed her husband's ordeal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  TRUMP 48% APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_jun20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  Massive surge of jellyfish sparks concerns at Florida beaches... </title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/unusual-surge-of-jellyfish-on-volusia-beaches-sparks-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beaches in Volusia County continue to deal with jellyfish problems as thousands of people are still being treated for stings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboard tells liberals: Keep driving 'until you have left our great state of Texas'...</title>
      <link>http://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article213508754.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A billboard along Interstate 40 near the town of Vega, Texas, tells liberals to keep driving "until you have left our great state of Texas." The reaction on social media has been swift and has fallen along political party lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charleston, SC apologizes for slavery after heated debate...</title>
      <link>http://www.thestate.com/news/local/article213501394.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charleston City Council approved a resolution to denounce and apologize for the city's role in slavery. Almost half of all enslaved Africans came through the port of Charleston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95% of manufacturers bullish on future, 'record optimism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/boom-over-95-of-manufacturers-bullish-on-future-record-optimism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a stunning turnaround sparked by the improving economy and last December’s tax cuts, over 95 percent of manufacturers have turned bullish about their future, an all-time record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Plagued By Internal Rift Over Politics; Some Shows 'Too Black'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/espns-internal-political-divide-bristol-tradition-woke-reformers-1121634 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the network eyes a new 'Monday Night Football' deal amid NFL protests and Trump culture wars, new chief Jimmy Pitaro faces warring factions inside a company that staffers say is unfairly branded as a "bastion of liberalism" as one exec calls a show "too black."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC trying to fix massive plumbing leak 55 stories underground!</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/plumbing-leak-55-stories-underground</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City is in the midst of a plumbing repair job of monumental proportions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECUTIVE ORDER TO STOP SEPARATIONS?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/20/white-house-considering-executive-action-to-prevent-family-separations-at-border.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is considering executive action to allow children to stay with parents caught crossing the border illegally, Fox News has learned -- a step that could avoid the family separations that have triggered a national outcry and political crisis for Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP VOWS TO STOP ILLEGALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-44538110</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US president claimed that separating families was "the only solution" to end illegal immigration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian trolls exploiting family-separation stories 'to sow discord among Americans'...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/20/russian-internet-trolls-stoking-family-separation-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian bots and internet trolls are stoking the U.S. debate over family separation, a Republican senator said Wednesday, dropping a bombshell into the middle of the immigration debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Chase Homeland Security Secretary From Restaurant...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/393151-chanting-activists-confront-dhs-secretary-during-dinner-at-mexican</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists disrupted Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen's dinner at a Mexican restaurant in Washington, D.C., on Tuesday night amid growing outcry over the Trump administration's "zero tolerance" immigration policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE arrests 100 at meatpacking plant...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/another-large-scale-immigration-raid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 workers were arrested Tuesday at an Ohio meatpacking plant by federal agents following a yearlong immigration investigation, the second large-scale raid within the state in the past two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: AMAZON Alexa declares 'Every time close eyes all see is people dying'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/20/amazon-alexa-horrifies-owner-declaring-every-time-close-eyes-i-see-people-dying-7644624/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shawn Kinnear said the Amazon Echo made the outburst unprompted and out of the blue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood, sweat and accessories: Bodily fluids recycled for fashion...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/blood-sweat-accessories-artist-recycles-bodily-fluids-fashion-132802826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Stuart McDill LONDON (Reuters) - Struggling to make your fashion more personal? A London fashion student can help you decorate your attire with crystal accessories formed from your bodily excretions. Royal College of Art graduate Alice Potts showcased her quirky design methods with a pair of ballet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary passes 'STOP Soros' laws, defying EU and rights groups...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180620140553-uotyk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNGARY-SOROS/ (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Hungary approves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials moving out of Mom and Dad's place!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/20/millennials-moving-out-of-mom-and-dads-place-study-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Due to the strength of the job market, fewer young adults lived with their parents in 2017 than in 2016, according to new data from CoStar Group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts and Iger Go Head-to-Head...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/brian-roberts-bob-iger-fox-comcast-disney-1202851007/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One is the consummate manager and operator. One is the scion of a media pioneer who has taken the family business to impressive heights through his drive and ambition. Bob Iger and Brian Roberts ar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns against Trump's 'alarming' plans for space domination...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180620-russia-warns-against-trumps-alarming-plans-us-space-domination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Fonda Encourages Targeting Children of Border Agents...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/actor-peter-fonda-encourages-targeting-children-of-border-patrol-ice-agents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FEAR ON BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/karlazabludovsky/trumps-family-separations-are-leaving-people-waiting-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If they take my son from me, I would die,” one woman, who was seeking asylum when she was turned away from the border, told BuzzFeed News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa Blasts List Of ICE Personnel's Photos And Identities...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/antifa-spreads-ice-agents-identities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antifa has been known to get violent ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates vow to dump Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/20/pelosi-democrats-candidates-midterms-655484</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of hopefuls say they won’t back her for speaker if Democrats win the House. Pelosi has little margin for error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Global warming,' now brought to you by local TV weathercaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/global-warming-now-brought-you-your-local-tv-weathercaster-n884831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local weathercasters have become one of the primary conduits for news on global warming. One nonprofit helped push the change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Subway Conductor Sucker-Punched Aboard Train...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/19/mta-conductor-attacked-q-train/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim says getting assaulted in broad daylight was something he never thought he'd have to worry about. That is, before this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY: Left-wing violence and extremism on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/germany-left-wing-violence-extremism-rise-113644138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German security officials say left-wing extremists have become more willing to use violence over the past five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE: Populism not the answer...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-interview/exclusive-pope-criticizes-trump-administration-policy-on-migrant-family-separation-idUSKBN1JG0YC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has criticized the Trump administration's policy of separating migrant families at the Mexican border, saying populism is not the answer to the world's immigration problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE FOR FOX: DISNEY UPS BID...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/20/disney-raises-bid-for-fox-assets-to-38-a-share.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big banks embrace 'pay by voice'...</title>
      <link>http://www.kansas.com/news/business/article213503889.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banks start to offer banking through virtual assistants like Amazon's Alexa, but security experts express worry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mosquitoes Remember Your Smell -- And Swat...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mosquitoes-remember-human-smells-swats-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might think that bug spray or citronella candles are the best repellants, but a recent study found that swatting at mosquitoes may actually help them learn to stay away from you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops fire rubber bullets, tear gas to disperse crowd at rapper's memorial...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/06/20/cops-fire-rubber-bullets-tear-gas-to-disperse-crowd-at-xxxtentacion-memorial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 20-year-old artist – born Jahseh Dwayne Onfroy – was gunned down in a drive-by shooting Monday night in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bots poised to wreak havoc in midterm elections?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/expert-bots-poised-wreak-havoc-2018-midterm-elections-090048965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Automated bot accounts that spread disinformation and sowed disgust and confusion among voters during the 2016 presidential election are poised to wreak havoc again in this year’s midterm elections, according to Samuel Woolley, a leading expert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu warns of cyber risks that can down fighter jets...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180620105719-jfpys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-CYBER/NETANYAHU (TV, PIX):Israel's Netanyahu warns of cyber risks that can down fighter jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flames sweep through barn killing 5,000 pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.10tv.com/article/5000-pigs-killed-fayette-county-barn-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire started around 1 p.m. at the Straathoff Swine Farm on Old Route 35 in the southeastern part of the county.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant operation against wildlife crime in 92 countries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/abb53f5d1921485dae23dde73d40950d/Giant-operation-against-wildlife-crime-in-92-countries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A monthlong global operation against illegal trade in wildlife and timber has resulted in the seizure of thousands of live animals and tons of meat and ivory, interna</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another test of loyalty looms over Trump's Minnesota visit...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/another-test-of-loyalty-looms-over-trump-s-minnesota-visit/485995871/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's campaign trip Wednesday to Minnesota could signal whether he'll wade into the GOP's primary for governor between a former two-term governor who once called him "unhinged" and an underdog who is an avowed supporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
SCHWARZENEGGER: Politicians Should Be Held In 'Cages'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5863995/Arnold-Schwarzenegger-speaks-against-Trumps-immigration-policy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arnold Schwarzenegger has spoken out against Trump's immigration policies saying that innocent children shouldn't be used as pawns after it emerged they were being held in detention cages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel says could get tougher on Gaza after warplanes hit Hamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israel-says-could-tougher-gaza-warplanes-hit-hamas-093936719.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli warplanes pounded Hamas targets in the Gaza Strip early Wednesday in a new flare-up of hostilities that saw dozens of rockets and mortar shells fired from the Palestinian enclave, the army said. A military spokesman said all targets belonged to Hamas's military wing, the Ezzedine al-Qassam</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death threats 'become routine' in toxic Brexit debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/death-threats-become-routine-toxic-brexit-debate-030925681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro-EU lawmakers challenging the government's Brexit strategy have received repeated death threats, and at least one MP recently decided not to rebel on a bill for fear of reprisals. One member of Prime Minister Theresa May's Conservative Party is under such threat that they had to be accompanied</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest U.S. Oil Patch Near Its Limit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-20/shale-giant-says-permian-oil-faces-shut-ins-on-pipeline-shortage </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Permian oil region will have to shut wells within four months because there aren’t enough pipelines to get the oil to customers, the head of one of the industry’s largest producers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Whites Dying Than Being Born in Majority of States...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/20/us/white-minority-population.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pattern first started more than a decade ago. But lagging fertility rates and rising white mortality rates have sped demographic change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA TESTS FOR BORDER KIDS, PARENTS?</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/tony-perkins-sessions-dna-tests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Sessions is talking to congressional members and is hoping for a legislative fix'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORRIFYING PHOTOS OF OBAMA'S ILLEGAL ALIEN FACILITIES MEDIA REFUSES TO SHOW...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/photos-obama-immigration-detention-facilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negligent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urgent need to prepare for manmade virus attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jun/19/urgent-need-to-prepare-for-manmade-virus-attacks-says-us-government-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swift progress in our ability to manufacture viruses is making us vulnerable to biological attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showdown over extradition...</title>
      <link>https://www.hrw.org/news/2018/06/19/uk-should-reject-extraditing-julian-assange-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hrw.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been six years since Julian Assange, founder of Wikileaks, fled to the Ecuadorean Embassy in London to seek asylum from possible extradition to the United States to face indictment under the US Espionage Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN:  Disability Applications Plunge as Economy Strengthens...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/disability-applications-plunge-as-the-economy-strengthens/17639836/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans seeking Social Security disability benefits is plunging, a startling reversal of a decades-old trend that threatened the program’s solvency. It is the latest evidence of a stronger economy pulling people back into the job market or preventing workers from being sidelined in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaraguan city chooses to govern self as crisis intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Nicaraguan-city-chooses-to-govern-itself-as-13005485.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANAGUA, NICARAGUA - Amid the deepening political crisis in Nicaragua, opposition leaders from a key city that had once cradled President Daniel Ortega's socialist revolution on Monday announced that they do not recognize Ortega's leadership and that they would create a commission to self-govern the city. The town of Masaya, about 15 miles south of the capital city of Managua, was a bastion of support for Ortega and his Sandinista rebels who overthrew the dictatorship of Anastasio Somoza in 1979. For the past few weeks, Masaya has been controlled by protesters, a warren of citizen-manned roadblocks and barricades, with city hall abandoned and police hunkered down in their barracks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas hotel EVACUATED after 'SHARK Reef Aquarium leaks and roof COLLAPSES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/976747/flood-las-vegas-mandaly-bay-hotel-shark-reef-aquarium-leak-roof-collapse </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMERGENCY services are responding to reports of a huge water leak at the Mandalay Bay Hotel in Las Vegas, Nevada with images showing the venue floor covered in gallons of water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film director on hunger strike in Russian prison casts dark cloud over World Cup...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-russia-sentsov-20180619-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revered Ukrainian film writer Oleg Sentsov has been on a hunger strike for 36 days in a Russian prison colony in northern Siberia. Concerns are growing about his fate after he has refused to eat until the Kremlin releases all 64 Ukrainian political prisoners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton 'son' slams former president for showing compassion for immigrant children but 'abandoning his own'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5862413/Bill-Clintons-son-slams-former-president-defending-migrant-children-abandoning-him.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danney Williams, 32, has slammed former president Bill Clinton on Twitter for showing compassion for the immigrant children separated from their families at the border, but abandoning him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS faces backlash from Hollywood creators...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fox-news-channel-faces-backlash-hollywood-creators-213127128--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fox News Channel faces a growing backlash among Hollywood creators that intensified Tuesday following Laura Ingraham's description of "zero tolerance" detention facilities for children separated from their parents as "essentially summer camps."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen Wants Trump to Pay His Attorney Fees...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-wants-trump-to-pay-his-legal-fees-1529447136 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen has hired New York lawyer Guy Petrillo to represent him in a federal investigation into his business dealings, and has told associates he wants President Donald Trump, his former boss, to pay his legal fees, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe obesity rates surging in rural America...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-obesity-rural/severe-obesity-rates-surging-in-rural-america-idUSKBN1JF2ID </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters Health) - Severe obesity rates have been on the rise nationwide since the turn of the century, disproportionately affecting children and adults in rural communities, two U.S. studies suggest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Freedom city'? Going beyond 'sanctuary,' Austin, Texas, vows to curtail arrests...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-austin-freedom-city-2018-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid concerns over arrests of minorities and immigrants, Austin, Texas has declared itself a 'freedom city.' The term goes a step beyond 'sanctuary city,' requiring officers to avoid discretionary arrests and to inform immigrants of the right to not cooperate with police. Will other cities follow?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS CLOSING 150 STORES...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-19/starbucks-pumps-the-brakes-in-its-home-market</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Schultz exiting, it’s now up to CEO Kevin Johnson to decide where to slow versus grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Organizations Consider Suing SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER over 'extremist' labeling...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/about-60-organizations-are-considering-a-lawsuit-against-the-splc-following-3m-nawaz-settlement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are reviewing all our legal options."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR ON BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/karlazabludovsky/trumps-family-separations-are-leaving-people-waiting-to?utm_term=.rhpGn6RY9A#.loy2VoKdYk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If they take my son from me, I would die,” one woman, who was seeking asylum when she was turned away from the border, told BuzzFeed News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Will Harass You Mercilessly if You Try to Quit...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/facebook-will-harass-you-mercilessly-if-you-try-to-break-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They're like that bad boyfriend who just can't quit you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strzok escorted out of FBI, but still employed...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5862743/FBI-lover-Peter-Strzok-escorted-FBI.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agent Peter Strzok, who was revealed to have sent a text to his FBI lover saying he would 'stop' Trump, was marched out of the building Friday, following an IG report that criticized his conduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Chase Homeland Security Secretary from Restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/protesters-harass-chase-dhs-secretary-from-dinner-at-mexican-restaurant-watch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists with the D.C. chapter of the Democratic Socialists of America crashed Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen's dinner Tuesday evening and appeared to chase her from the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL INTERN SCREAMS 'F*CK YOU!' AT PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/audio-congressional-intern-screams-f-you-at-president-trump-at-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW CRIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/rachel-maddow-breaks-down-on-air-delivering-news-of-migrant-babies-being-detained/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undocumented kills women in Miami, dumps bodies on street...</title>
      <link>http://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article213426999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Honduran national in the U.S. illegally has been charged with the murders of two women, both prostitutes, police said. Juan Carlos Hernandez-Caseres, 37, is suspected of killing the women in Miami and leaving their bodies on the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth of world's millionaires tops $70T!</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/World-News/2018/06/19/Wealth-of-worlds-millionaires-tops-70-trillion-for-first-time/8231529424130/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The combined wealth of all the world's millionaires rose in 2017 for the sixth straight year, and topped the $70 trillion-mark for the first time on record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENERAL ELECTRIC Booted From DOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/walgreens-to-replace-ge-in-dow-industrials-1529443336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Electric will drop out of the Dow Jones Industrial Average next week, a milestone in the decline of a firm that once ranked among the mightiest of U.S. blue-chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUDDLE ON CAPITOL HILL...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/393127-trump-vows-to-stand-with-house-gop-1000-percent-on-immigration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump urged House Republicans to get an immigration bill to his desk during a closed-door meeting Tuesday evening, vowing to stand with them “1,000 percent” as they attempt to pass legislation meeting his demands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Saudi Moves Ahead With Canal Plan To Make Qatar An Island...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/news/gulf/saudi-arabia/saudi-arabia-moves-ahead-with-salwa-canal-plan-1.2238965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waterway alongside Saudi-Qatari border to be completed within 15 months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE 'Home' leaks location to hackers?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/talkingtech/2018/06/19/your-google-home-and-chromecast-may-leaking-your-precise-location/716018002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is working on a fix that could plug a Chromecast, Google Home link that could reveal your precise whereabouts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
