<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Activists want to change town's 'racist name'. Officials pushing back...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/nov/25/squaw-valley-california-indigenous-racist-misogynistic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roman Rain Tree has tried to convince local officials to do away with a name that ‘memorializes sexualized and genocidal acts’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday shopping 'hell': Workers brace for unruly customers and labor strikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/nov/24/holiday-shopping-hell-workers-brace-for-unruly-customers-and-labor-strikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holiday retail sales are expected to increase up to a record 10.5%, despite supply chain issues and employee shortages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Variant Puts SAfrica at Risk of Global Shut Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/new-variant-puts-south-africa-at-risk-of-global-shut-out-2625767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa's recovery from its deepest economic contraction in almost three decades risks being derailed by the identification of a new coronavirus variant that prompted several European nations to ban travel to and from the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How shaky cellphone video changed course of Arbery case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-a-shaky-cellphone-video-changed-the-course-of-the-ahmaud-arbery-murder-case/ar-AAR6HED</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party like it's 1919? Rio hopes for Carnival comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211126-party-like-it-s-1919-rio-hopes-for-carnival-comeback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sequins are swirling, the bass drums are booming: after being canceled by Covid-19, carnival is back -- at least at Rio de Janeiro's samba schools, which hope to put on the party of the century i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riots rock Solomons Islands for third day...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20211126-riots-rock-solomons-islands-capital-again-despite-australian-troop-deployment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police fired warning shots and tear gas to disperse rioters attacking the home of the Solomon Islands prime minister on Friday, in a third day of political violence that prompted the snap deployment…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning 9-month expiration on 'passports'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/25/covid-travel-eu-proposes-a-9-month-expiration-date-on-vaccine-pass.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea now is that the document has a life span of nine months after the first set of vaccines are administered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe surge highlights warnings for USA...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/583085-europes-covid-19-surge-highlights-warnings-for-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say a COVID-19 surge in Europe serves as a warning to the United States about the continued threat of the virus, even as many are ready to move past the pandemic era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian military buildup puts Washington on edge...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/583093-russian-military-buildup-puts-washington-on-edge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is on edge as Russia's military buildup threatens a confrontation, with fears escalating following reports that U.S. intelligence shows Russian forces preparing to push into Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, NORDSTROM stores hit in latest smash-and-grab robberies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/583142-apple-nordstrom-stores-hit-in-latest-smash-and-grab-robberies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Apple and Nordstrom were robbed on Wednesday in California, the latest in a string of smash-and-grab robberies that have spurred an increasingly hard-line response from officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood of cases 'unmanageable strain' in Michigan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/flood-covid-patients-causes-almost-150813393.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAND RAPIDS, Mich. - At Spectrum Health, a major health-care system here, officials spent part of last week debating whether to move to "red status" in a show of how strained hospitals had become. A flood of mostly unvaccinated covid-19 patients was arriving at emergency departments already packed with people suffering other medical issues, sending capacity to unprecedented levels. The only hesitation for Spectrum's decision-makers? Data suggested the covid surge was not over.Subscribe to The P</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearing empty shelves, Black Friday 'early birds' head to stores...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211126095924-ozsyv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RETAIL-HOLIDAYSHOPPING/BLACK FRIDAY (PIX, GRAPHIC):Fearing empty shelves, Black Friday 'early birds' head to U.S. stores</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German air force transfers patients as hospitals overwhelmed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211126095122-zg64l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-German air force to transfer COVID patients as some hospitals overwhelmed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ed the Trucker': Trump Republican Riding High in NJ...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/26/ed-the-trucker-the-trump-republican-whos-riding-high-in-new-jersey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edward Durr Jr., a Republican who this month toppled New Jersey’s second most powerful lawmaker, had three children under 13</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel warns of 'emergency' after detecting strain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-south-africa-middle-east-14b1419135057aaf96bfb495742e4ab1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Prime Minister Naftali Bennett said Israel is "on the threshold of an emergency situation” on Friday after authorities detected the country’s first case of a new coronavirus variant in a traveler who returned from Malawi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Leaked U.S. Missile Secrets. Turned Into 'Dark Comedy of Errors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/leaked-u-missile-secrets-turned-225131446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/Photos GettyA former Raytheon missile defense engineer who recently pleaded guilty to leaking U.S. military secrets claims he did so only because his desperate attempts to correct a potentially deadly software error he accidentally made went completely unheeded by authorities.“My approach and code were not adequately reviewed,” James Robert Schweitzer told The Daily Beast in his first public comments since his arrest. “I was told to ignore the anomaly that I</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver killed as his car plunges into Dead Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/driver-killed-as-his-car-plunges-into-dead-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;30-year-old man reportedly lost control of the vehicle during medical emergency; 2nd passenger escapes unharmed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Greene Says McCarthy 'Doesn't Have Votes' to Become Speaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/marjorie-taylor-greene-says-kevin-mccarthy-doesnt-have-the-votes-to-become-speaker-if-gop-wins-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) joined Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-FL) on his podcast Firebrand and weighed in on the growing battle within the Republican Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Lock 81 People in Hostel After 1 Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10241195/Covid-Australia-Byron-Bay-hell-Schoolies-trapped-hostel-infected-woman-sparks-lockdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have sealed off the building with no-one allowed out after all guests and staff were deemed close contacts by NSW Health which has escalated the crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea to launch task force on banning dog meat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-south-korea-restaurants-dogs-8d3bcb1d810f6c464b5d39ca0a6772c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — South Korea on Thursday said it will launch a task force to consider outlawing dog meat consumption after the country’s president offered to look into ending the centuries-old practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Star Buried Without His Heart So Fans Wouldn't Steal It...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k7w8mn/diego-maradona-heart-removed-after-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The odd story is only the latest post-death scandal for the Argentine soccer legend, who was also recently accused of sex trafficking and abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Special radiation can kill COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/special-radiation-can-kill-covid-19-and-polio-virus-israeli-study-shows-686981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA firefighter accused of wiping feces on non-compliance letter...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/l-a-firefighter-accused-of-wiping-butt-leaving-fecal-matter-on-non-compliance-letter-in-protest-of-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Fire Department is investigating an incident in which a firefighter “responded inappropriately” after being handed a letter to comply with the city’s vaccine mandate, a departm…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimism over Israel's child shots marred by spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/bad-omens-optimism-over-israels-child-vaccine-marred-by-covid-spike-expert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top immunologist Cyrille Cohen reflects on the dosage, efficacy and timing of the shots being rolled out for kids</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe reins in Big Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/europe-digital-markets-act-dma-digital-services-act-dsa-regulation-platforms-google-amazon-facebook-apple-microsoft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ministers sign off on new EU tech rulebook to curb abuse and harm online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash brewing against bail reform...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/25/1059019616/theres-a-backlash-brewing-against-bail-reform-after-the-parade-tragedy-in-waukes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics of the movement to reduce cash bail cite the $1000 cash bail paid by Darrell E. Brooks, Jr., weeks before he allegedly plowed his SUV through the Waukesha Christmas parade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near strike by Hollywood crews could be sign of things to come...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/near-strike-by-hollywood-crews-could-be-a-sign-of-things-to-come/ar-AAR7VUg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record number of Americans not buying gifts this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/25/holiday-shopping-2021-more-americans-wont-be-buying-holiday-gifts-this-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are predictions for record retail sales this holiday season but a record number of people say they won't be buying any gifts this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA chief delivers 'Havana Syndrome' warning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cia-chief-warns-russians-consequences-221755624.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIA chief William Burns warned Russian intel services of “consequences” if they're found to be behind the health incidents called “Havana Syndrome.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher prices, barer tables for many at Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/everything-sky-high-higher-prices-130050419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From canned staples to full Thanksgiving dinners, L.A. food banks and community centers help households feeling the pinch of higher prices this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines Bracing for Anti-Vax Fallout After Sunday Deadline...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-11-24/marines-face-defining-moment-ahead-of-vaccine-mandate-deadline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The youngest and most conservative service with some of the most consequential missions also has the lowest levels of compliance to the mandatory vaccine orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunfire, rockets, big black SUVs. VIP protection 'live action' training...</title>
      <link>https://www.unionleader.com/news/back_page/gunfire-rockets-big-black-suvs-it-s-vip-protection-live-action-training-in-miami/article_e087f924-9158-5d1d-a053-5b773b71c9d2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high value target had just arrived at the summit. Well-armed agents hurried her from the backseat of the black SUV to inside the building’s front doors. Then, three large</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General accused of torture elected Interpol president...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-59417409</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahmed al-Raisi was chosen despite facing claims of complicity in torture by UAE security forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVADES IMMUNITY?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/b-1-1-529-new-covid-variant-evade-immunity-countries-cases-south-africa-1653257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new variant has a large number of mutations on the spike the virus uses to invade the body, prompting concern from scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: JPMORGAN Dimon issues two groveling apologies for Communist Party joke...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10242371/JPMorgan-CEO-Jamie-Dimon-issues-two-grovelling-apologies-joking-Chinas-Community-Party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking at Boston College, Dimon quipped: 'I was just in Hong Kong and I made a joke that the Communist Party is celebrating its hundredth year. So is JP Morgan. I'd make a bet we last longer.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Power Outages Rise as High Winds Raise Fire Risk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-utility-starts-cutting-power-204632483.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The largest utility in Southern California cut power for more customers in the mountains near Los Angeles as strong winds raised the risk of wildfire, marking the second year in a row that parts of the region will spend Thanksgiving in the dark.Most Read from BloombergBillionaire Family Feud Puts a Century-Old Business Empire in JeopardyAsia’s Richest Man Looks to Walton Family Playbook on SuccessionThe 24-Year-Old Aiming to Dethrone Victoria’s SecretThe Winners and Losers From a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France calls for European aid after 27 migrant deaths at sea...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-europe-france-migration-english-channel-6710d4f3a705c0809abf663f66e6975e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALAIS, France (AP) — President Emmanuel Macron appealed Thursday to neighboring European countries to do more to stop illegal migration into France after at least 27 people died trying to cross the English Channel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers shows off bare foot to prove doesn't have 'covid toe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/aaron-rodgers-shows-off-bare-foot-to-prove-he-doesn-e2-80-99t-have-e2-80-98covid-toe-e2-80-99-says-it-e2-80-99s-a-fracture/ar-AAR6Da5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOFUNDME pulls fundraiser for Waukesha suspect...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/gofundme-pulls-down-fundraiser-for-waukesha-suspect</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GoFundMe has removed a fundraiser for Darrell Brooks Jr., who has been charged with five counts of first-degree intentional homicide Tuesday after the Waukesha Christmas parade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor recommends 'routine surveillance' after Biden colonoscopy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/583132-doctor-recommends-routine-surveillance-after-polyp-removed-from</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said late Wednesday that a polyp removed from President Biden's colon last Friday was "benign" and "thought to be precancerous," and requires no further action,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota Calls in Troops...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/minnesota-calls-up-national-guard-as-covid-19-overwhelm-1848108187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota has seen a huge jump in covid-19 hospitalizations over the past two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertilizer shortage sparks fears of higher food prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/nov/25/fertilizer-shortage-north-america-farmers-food-prices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warning to ‘get your fertilizer now’ as farmers postpone nitrogen purchases, raising threat of rush on supplies before planting season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires break out as unrest spreads through Caribbean...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20211125-fires-break-out-as-covid-19-unrest-spreads-through-french-caribbean</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters looted shops and set up burning barricades overnight on France's Caribbean island of Martinique, France Info reported on Thursday, as demonstrations against Covid-19 protocols intensified…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt to reopen ancient 'Avenue of Sphinxes' centuries after hosted parades for gods...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/egypt-ancient-avenue-sphinxes-luxor-karnak-ceremony-opet-parade-route/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 1.7-mile-long "Path of God," lined with more than 1,000 sphinx and ram statues, spent centuries buried by the sands of time. But it's about to come back - with all due pomp and ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop Fatally Struck Nurse, Brought Body Home To Mom...</title>
      <link>https://patch.com/new-jersey/newarknj/nj-cop-fatally-struck-nurse-brought-body-home-mom-prosecutor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;patch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis Santiago, 25, is accused of killing a nurse with his car and bringing the body home to his mom to discuss "what to do with the body."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France opts for 3rd shots, not lockdown, to fight new wave...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-france-467c6de9c305f7e4df1b53749b2efd23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France has launched a plan Thursday to give COVID-19 booster shots to all adults, as it opted against a further lockdown or curfew to help combat a worrying uptick in infections in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Webcam Model Shoots Self In Private Parts...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/georgia-discharge-749218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOVEMBER 24--A webcam model accidentally shot herself in the vagina with a 9mm handgun while recording a video earlier this month in her Georgia home, according to a police report. Responding to an “</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five years after death, is Castro revolution floundering?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/five-years-after-his-death-is-castro-s-revolution-floundering/ar-AAR6gsQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five years after Fidel Castro's death, the revolution he started in 1959 appears to be at an impasse, with Cuba's economy battered and an ever-larger part of its population clamoring for change. The communist island has seen unprecedented protests in the last year as more and more citizens blame the one-party state for a variety of social and economic ills. A younger generation of Cubans, the so-called "grandchildren" of the revolution, are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany death toll passes 100,000 as virus surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211125-germany-s-death-toll-from-covid-19-passes-100-000-as-virus-surges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100,000 people have died of Covid-19 in Germany since the start of the pandemic, a public health agency announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia moving forces to Crimea in Ukraine buildup, analysts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2021/11/24/russia-s-military-build-up-near-ukraine-is-different-this-time-say-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“What we see is a significant, large Russian military build-up. We see an unusual concentration of troops."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS LOWEST SINCE 1969...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/24/us-jobless-claims-fall-to-just-199000-the-lowest-level-since-1969.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial jobless claims totaled 199,000 last week, the lowest since 1969, easily beating Dow Jones estimates for 260,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungarian Tycoon Who Made Fortune in Porn Weighs Election Challenge to Orban...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/hungarian-tycoon-who-made-fortune-in-porn-mulls-taking-on-orban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungarian Tycoon Who Made Fortune in Porn Weighs Election Challenge to Orban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran nuke work mystery to global monitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/iranian-nuclear-work-is-becoming-a-black-box-to-global-monitors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian Nuclear Work Is Becoming a Mystery to Global Monitors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA law allows trans inmates in women's prisons. Now, female inmates suing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/california-law-allows-transgender-inmates-in-womens-prisons-now-female-inmates-are-suing/article_5380a9d5-fd54-5fc4-abeb-daed3e5e1eef.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — A woman's rights group is suing the state to overturn a new law that requires prisons to place transgender and gender nonbinary inmates in facilities that correspond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers clears up COVID toe claims by showing off bare, fractured toe...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/nfl-packers-aaron-rodgers-covid-toe-actually-fractured-toe-injury-212044250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers was quick to show his legion-less toes and explain he has a fractured one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron gets fans ejected in return from suspension...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/24/returning-lebron-james-gets-pacers-fans-ejected-in-lakers-win/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James just can’t stop getting people ejected from games — this time two fans. The Lakers star — in his first game back from his one-game suspension for bloodying Pistons forward Isaiah Stewa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU to recommend passes last for nine months after full vaccination...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211125105135-iu7n4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/EU-TRAVEL (URGENT):EU to recommend COVID passes last for nine months after full vaccination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. lawmakers coming to Taiwan on military-focused trip...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211125101633-sc8h9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-USA/VISIT:U.S. lawmakers coming to Taiwan on military-focused trip -report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Psychedelic Retreats...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/25/the-rise-of-psychedelic-retreats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One night in 2019, while strangers vomited around her, Lynn Cohen had a vision. After being tipped off by a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Pagans and Smartphone Witches: Where Tech Meets Mysticism...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/24/space-pagans-and-smartphone-witches-where-tech-meets-mysticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DORTMUND, Germany — “Let’s use smartphones and tarot cards to connect to spirits,” reads the writing on the wall, illuminated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's Christmas markets warily open as COVID cases rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-travel-business-b5dd27e7e01b1c94f458662ef7768f62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — The holiday tree is towering over the main square in this central German city, the chestnuts and sugared almonds are roasted, and kids are clambering aboard the merry-go-round just like they did before the pandemic .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia sending troops to Solomon Islands as unrest grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/australia-solomon-islands-honiara-a87d6b12d46642bf58c35aabd616ae0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Australia announced Thursday it is sending police, troops and diplomats to the Solomon Islands to help after anti-government demonstrators defied lockdown orders and took to the streets for a second day in violent protests.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
