<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bibi Banks on Right-Wing Base as Troubles Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/netanyahu-banks-on-his-right-wing-base-as-legal-troubles-mount-11551452516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is betting his political survival on a dedicated base of conservative voters ignoring potential bribery charges that could undo his bid for a fifth term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French prosecutors want Le Pen tried over tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190301-french-prosecutors-want-le-pen-tried-over-tweet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French prosecutors want Le Pen tried over tweet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles alert at Chicago airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-measles-midway-infectious-20190228-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Illinois Department of Public Health confirms that travelers passing through the Chicago airport on Feb. 22 may have been exposed to measles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia revokes citizenship of bin Laden son...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2c52afad8fbe433f84f6eafb317c1ade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Saudi Arabia announced Friday it had revoked the citizenship of Hamza bin Laden, the son of the late al-Qaida leader who has become an increasingly prominent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fake Sex Doctor Who Conned Media Into Publicizing Bizarre Research...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-fake-sex-doctor-who-conned-the-media-into-publicizi-1832711205 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on the information available online, Sendler could be one of the most accomplished 28-year-olds in medicine. But he’s not. Those are all lies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In America, talk turns to something unspoken for 150 years: Civil war...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/In-America-talk-turns-to-something-unspoken-for-13654893.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a moment when the country has never seemed angrier, two political commentators from opposite sides of the divide concurred last week on one point, nearly unthinkable until recently: The country is on the verge of "civil war." First came former U.S. attorney Joseph diGenova, a Fox News regular and ally of President Trump. "We are in a civil war," he said. "The suggestion that there's ever going to be civil discourse in this country for the foreseeable future is over. . . . It's going to be total war." The next day, Nicolle Wallace, a former Republican operative turned MSNBC commentator and Trump critic, played a clip of diGenova's commentary on her show and agreed with him - although she placed the blame squarely on the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER SUV: Ten-wheeled vehicle built for sheikh...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6760511/Abu-Dhabi-Sheikh-builds-incredible-ten-wheeled-vehicle-military-truck-Jeep.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheikh Hamad bin Hamdan Al Nahyan, who is based in Abu Dhabi, shared snaps of the monster SUV on his Instagram page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>63% of millennial homeowners regret buying: survey...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/28/63-percent-of-millennial-homebuyers-have-regrets-heres-why.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of them made the same mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Walk Of Fame Named 'World's Worst Attraction'...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/02/28/hollywood-walk-of-fame-named-worlds-worst-attraction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have the stars lost their shine? The new survey -- in TripAdvisor -- seems to suggest the answer is yes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders hires illegal to be press secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/bernie-sanders-hires-illegal-immigrant-to-be-press-secretary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders' new deputy national press secretary likely won't be eligible to vote in the 2020 election due to what she says is her status as an undocumented immigrant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada Tracking People's 'Negative' Behavior In 'Risk' Database...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_ca/article/kzdp5v/police-in-canada-are-tracking-peoples-negative-behavior-in-a-risk-database</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The database includes detailed, but "de-identified," information about people's lives culled from conversations between police, social services, health workers, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translation site lashed for 'shocking' racist explanations...</title>
      <link>https://www.malaymail.com/news/world/2019/03/01/translation-site-lashed-for-shocking-racist-explanations/1728261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.malaymail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS, March 1 — A major translation website was lashed today for offering up anti-Semitic and racist explanations of words. Users who typed “nicer” into Reverso looking for a French equivalent were offered the example: “Hitler was a lot nicer to the Jews than they deserved.” A search of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staunchly liberal Hawaii in no rush to legalize marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/staunchly-liberal-hawaii-in-no-rush-to-legalize-marijuana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the political spectrum, Hawaii is among the bluest of states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest under siege in battle over Venezuela's political soul...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/aa4e8b3ae7024a778dcf87a2a694c230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Salsa music and long tirades blasted through loudspeakers for days at a colonial church in one of Venezuela's toughest slums aimed at drowning out Monsignor Hector Lunar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In This Oil Boom Town, Even Barber Can Make $180,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-this-oil-boom-town-even-a-barber-can-make-180-000-11551436210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of America’s hottest labor markets is in West Texas, where the brisket is scarce, the ‘man-camps’ are full, and oil workers with no time to spare pay $75 to skip the line at the barber shop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March roars in with coast-to-coast snow, record cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/03/01/winter-storm-coast-coast-snow-then-record-cold-march-roars/3020109002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;March is definitely coming in like a lion over the next few days. A winter storm will spread snow along a 2,500-mile path from California to Maine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Gov Inslee enters with focus on 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/01/washington-gov-jay-inslee-enters-2020-presidential-race-with-focus-on-climate-change.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Gov. Jay Inslee says he will emphasize climate change during his bid for the Democratic presidential nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There will be 1,075 tornadoes': Weather vendor's prediction draws scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/There-will-be-1-075-tornadoes-Weather-vendor-s-13652811.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Popular weather vendor AccuWeather took the meteorological community by storm Tuesday, releasing its highly specific outlook for the 2019 tornado season. "AccuWeather predicts there will be 1,075 tornadoes in 2019," their piece begins, adding that Oklahoma, Kansas, Texas and southern Nebraska have the highest risk of twisters this spring. "The 525 tornadoes expected from March through May is almost exactly the normal average of 526 from March through May," AccuWeather wrote. In other words, they are expecting one less tornado than average in the spring. Many broadcast and private-sector meteorologists took issue with bold forecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOONAN:  Michael Cohen Makes History...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-makes-history-11551397848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no precedent for such an attack on the essential nature of an American president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITY CRACKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/gop-motions-in-house-put-pressure-on-democrats-unity-11551390357</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is split with her leadership team over how to handle moderate Democrats who are siding with Republicans on procedural votes to carve out independence from their party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOO OLD?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden/as-biden-weighs-2020-bid-democrats-ask-does-he-meet-the-moment-idUSKCN1QH1EX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former U.S. Vice President Joe Biden said this week he was "very close"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheldon Adelson reveals cancer... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f860f202dd1e4f21bdf29498c82784a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Casino magnate and GOP donor Sheldon Adelson has cancer and has not been at his company's offices in Las Vegas since around Christmas Day. Adelson's poor health was revealed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime HBO boss Richard Plepler steps down amid AT&amp;T restructuring... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/hbo-ceo-richard-plepler-expected-to-resign-amid-at-t-restructuring-11551393267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO Chairman and Chief Executive Richard Plepler said he is stepping down, a move that comes as new owner AT&amp;T Inc. is looking to put its own stamp on the premium cable channel that was part of its $80 billion acquisition of Time Warner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans could get super vision implants to see in dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8535024/humans-could-get-x-men-style-super-vision-to-see-in-the-dark-after-nanotechnology-gives-mice-power-to-see-infrared/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUMANS could get the power to see in the dark after mice were injected with nanoparticles which gave them the ability to see infrared light. The rodents were given infrared night vision for 10 week…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau's Political Woes Mount With Demands for More Inquiries... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/28/justin-trudeau-election-1229686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian leader faces unprecedented political peril as a fast-escalating scandal implicates him specifically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment on hold...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/democrats-look-steer-clear-impeachment-talk-after-cohen-testimony-n977736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after the former Trump lawyer's public session on the Hill, more Republicans than Democrats were framing it as a significant step in a push to remove the president from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO-CORTEZ THREATENS 'LIST'... </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/House-Democrats-explode-in-recriminations-as-13653983.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats exploded in recriminations Thursday over moderates bucking the party, with liberal Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez threatening to put those voting with Republicans "on a list" for a primary challenge. In a closed-door session, a frustrated Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., lashed out at about two dozen moderates and pressured them to get on board. "We are either a team or we're not, and we have to make that decision," Pelosi said, according to two people present but not authorized to discuss the remarks publicly. But Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff says 'Scared Straight' program helps troubled kids. Experts say it's child abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article226325665.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN READY TO RUMBLE</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/432131-exclusive-inside-joe-bidens-campaign-in-waiting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has a campaign-in-waiting as soon as he decides to launch a White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN warns of 'complacency' as measles cases soar worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/un-warns-complacency-measles-cases-soar-worldwide-011338595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 10 countries were responsible for three-quarters of a global surge in measles cases last year, the UN children's agency said Friday, including one of the world's richest nations, France. Ninety-eight countries reported more cases of measles in 2018 compared with 2017, and the world body</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Number Of Sick, Dead Dolphins Washing Ashore Along Southern CA Beaches...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/02/25/dead-and-sick-dolphins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Laguna to Huntington Beach, an unprecedented number of dolphins are washing ashore dead or so sick that they have to be humanely euthanized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Rare Fish Never Seen in N Hemisphere Washes Up in CA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/rare-fish-alien-santa-barbara-hoodwinker-fish-506450281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare fish that looks more alien than aquatic washed up in Santa Barbara County, scientists said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,800-year-old phallic graffiti found near Hadrian's Wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2019/02/28/1800-year-old-roman-penis-carvings-discovered-near-hadrians-wall-some-things-never-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Militarized affinity for phallic scribbling dates back long before the first illustrations were ever fashioned by bored American service members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend snooze-in can ruin your waistline, health...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/28/health/weekend-sleep-weight-gain-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Think twice about using weekends to recover lost sleep. A new study finds that not only are you still sleep-deprived, you are also more likely to gain weight and harm your health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS WARNED: STOP VOTING WITH REPUBLICANS!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/28/nancy-pelosi-house-democrats-1195854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are divided over how to respond to Republican procedural attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Highest Rated [Non-Election] Day Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2019/02/28/maddow-wins-wednesday-night-ratings-as-msnbc-has-its-highest-rated-day-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a big news day, MSNBC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon ramps up Bin Laden son hunt: 'Jihad crown prince'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6758267/US-offers-1-million-reward-hunt-bin-Ladens-son.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The location of Hamza bin Laden (left) has been the subject of speculation for years with reports of him living in Pakistan, Afghanistan, Syria or Iran following the death of his father (right).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 'Clarifies' Calling Pence 'Decent Guy' After Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/432137-biden-responds-to-criticism-over-calling-pence-decent-guy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden on Thursday clarified that "there is nothing decent about being anti-LGBTQ" after he took fire from usually friendly sources over calling Vice President Mike Pence a "decent guy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA closing stores, only selling cars online...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/2/28/18245296/tesla-stores-closing-online-only-car-sales</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Described as a way to keep Tesla financially stable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Evidence of Mars Planet-Wide Groundwater System...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-first-geological-evidence-of-mars-planet-wide-groundwater-system</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mars may look like a dry, dusty planet today. But scientific models indicate that it was likely once home to massive amounts of water, both above and below its surface - and now, researchers have evidence to back those models up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge: Making Motorcycle Gang Surrender Logo After Conviction Unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/02/28/judge-wont-make-mongols-motorcycle-gang-surrender-trademark-logo-after-racketeering-conviction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge delivered a blow Thursday to a decade-long effort by prosecutors to strip the Mongols motorcycle gang of its trademarked logo, ruling it would be unconstitutional. U.S. District Court Judge David O. Carter in Santa Ana, California, essentially reversed a first-of-its-kind jury verdict that would have given the government control of the logo of a Mongol warrior astride a chopper-style motorcycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat grown in labs on menus, counters this year?</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/US/2019/02/28/Meat-grown-in-labs-could-hit-the-market-this-year/3501551219166/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meat that has been grown in a laboratory -- not raised in a farmyard -- might begin to appear in restaurants and at meat counters around the world this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP MISSES 3%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/28/trumps-economic-policies-failed-to-deliver-promised-3percent-growth-in-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New government data show that President Trump has failed to reach the 3 percent promised land for economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7,000 Migrants Apprehended in Week in TX Border Sector...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/02/28/7k-migrants-apprehended-in-one-week-in-texas-border-sector/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents reported apprehending nearly 7,000 migrants in a single week who illegally crossed the border from Mexico into Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Industry Revenue Hits Highest Level in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/u-s-music-industry-posts-third-straight-year-of-double-digit-growth-as-streaming-soars-30-1203152036/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. music industry posted its third consecutive year of double-digit growth, according to the RIAA’s year-end revenue report issued today. The report notes that in 2018 U.S. recorded-music rev…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57-PAGE DOC OUTLINES NETANYAHU ALLEGED CRIMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/you-knew-you-were-taking-a-bribe-the-specifics-of-netanyahus-alleged-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 57-page 'announcement of suspicions,' attorney general details instances in which PM was party to illicit deals and conflicts of interest, harmed public trust, abused his office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: 'Certainly Hoped' Offered White House Job...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/2016-michael-cohen-interview-shows-he-certainly-hoped-hed-be-offered-a-white-house-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyal Soldiers to Whistle Blowers: Confidants Turned...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-these-are-the-netanyahu-confidants-who-turned-state-s-evidence-1.6979383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of World's Greatest Art Thief...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/secrets-of-the-worlds-greatest-art-thief</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stéphane Breitwieser robbed nearly 200 museums, amassed a collection of treasures worth more than $1.4 billion, and became perhaps the most prolific art thief in history. And as he reveals to GQ’s Michael Finkel, how Breitwieser managed to do all this is every bit as surprising as why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town seizes family pug over unpaid debts, then sells on EBAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47401439</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in a German town decided the most valuable item in a home was Edda, the family dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's Guaido vows to return to Caracas despite threat of prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/venezuelas-guaido-vows-to-return-to-caracas-despite-threat-of-prison-idUSKCN1QH1XK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido, visiting Brazil to drum up support for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret to long, blissful marriage: Genetics...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-the-science-behind-the-secret-of-a-good-marriage-2019-02-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study looks at Cupid’s chemistry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New sex lawsuits could push NY dioceses to bankruptcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.democratandchronicle.com/story/news/2019/02/28/catholic-priest-abuse-rochester-ny-child-victims-act/2949197002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.democratandchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expect a wave of fresh allegations in the coming months that Catholic clergy in New York engaged in sexual abuse of children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Home Sales Plunge 17%...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/02/28/southern-california-home-sales-plunge-17-prices-increase-modestly-in-january/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sluggish Southern California housing market took another hit in January, with sales plunging 17% from a year earlier, according to a report released Wednesday. The six-county region’s median price rose only modestly, climbing 2% from January 2018 to $505,000, according to real estate data firm CoreLogic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LEAVING NEVERLAND' Review: Dark Side of Moonwalks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/leaving-neverland-review-the-dark-side-of-the-moonwalks-11551383110</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An HBO documentary on Michael Jackson is an appalling story of predatory child sexual abuse, told in such painful detail that it’s impossible to dismiss</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andre Previn Dead At 89...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2019/02/28/517960940/andre-previn-musical-polymath-has-died-at-age-89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;André Previn died Thursday morning in Manhattan. He was a composer of Oscar-winning film music, conductor, pianist and music director of major orchestras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents' sleep takes YEARS to recover after having baby...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-parents-sleep-deprivation-parents-sleep-doesnt-recover-until-6-years-after-having-a-baby-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study finds new moms lose an average of 62 minutes of sleep a night, while dads only lose about 13 minutes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheldon Adelson health in question ahead of court hearing...</title>
      <link>https://thenevadaindependent.com/article/sheldon-adelsons-health-in-question-ahead-of-court-hearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenevadaindependent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Questions have been raised over the health of Las Vegas Sands Chairman and CEO Sheldon Adelson as the start date looms for a trial in Clark County District Court that could cost the company millions of dollars in damages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: PHILLIES Sign Superstar To $330M Deal...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/02/28/bryce-harper-signs-philadelphia-phillies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 26-year-old former MVP finished last season with 34 home runs, 100 RBI, a .249 batting average and an .889 OPS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress leading workplace health problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-hidden-costs-of-stressed-out-workers-11551367913</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies often don’t realize how much they pay for lost time and productivity from unhealthy workplace dynamics. But there are ways to lower the stress level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Requests Docs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-york-requests-documents-from-facebook-apps-on-data-sharing-11551373115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York regulator is ramping up a promised investigation of how Facebook gathered sensitive personal information from popular smartphone applications, after a report by The Wall Street Journal revealed that many such apps were sending the social-media giant data including users’ body weight and menstrual cycles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI: LEFT KNOWS THEY CAN'T DEFEAT ME...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Benjamin-Netanyahu/Netanyahu-The-Left-knows-they-cant-defeat-me-calls-cases-fake-582085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu on corruption charges: "This house of cards will collapse."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors perform emergency c-section on crash victim -- who wasn't pregnant...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/02/28/doctors-carried-emergency-c-section-crash-victim-48-wasnt-pregnant-8773864/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paramedics told doctors at A&amp;E that they suspected Adele Barbour was eight-months pregnant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Dr. Seuss book coming 28 years after death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fc20b57000c44f3c98986acb84de280f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — There is no muse like Dr. Seuss. An unfinished manuscript by the late children's author is the basis for "Dr. Seuss's Horse Museum," coming Sept. 3. Random House Children's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk Russian Sailor Rips Gaping Hole in Bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2019/02/28/drunk-russian-sailor-rips-gaping-hole-south-korean-bridge-a64664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKoreans Try To Embarrass...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6757367/North-Koreans-insist-Trump-demanded-nuke-deal-proposal-never-change.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korean officials made a rare press appearance on Thursday after President Trump departed Vietnam to publicly dispute aspects of his claims about the breakdown in talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martha Stewart partners with cannabis firm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c082c444b9a543ed88fdc274d5cd1c29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No, you're not smoking something. Martha Stewart is really joining the cannabis craze. The domestic diva said Thursday she is partnering with Canopy Growth Corp. to assist in developing new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUKE PERRY SUFFERS STROKE...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/28/luke-perry-stroke-riverdale-beverly-hills-90210-hospitalized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luke Perry suffered a stroke Wednesday in L.A. and is currently hospitalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Insider Leaks Documents; Explains 'Deboosting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.projectveritas.com/2019/02/27/facebook-insider-leaks-docs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.projectveritas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Witch hunt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/israel-prime-minister-benjamin-netanyahu-indicted-bribe-fraud-charges-n977571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An indictment would mark the first time in Israeli history that a sitting prime minister has been charged with a crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resign?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Does-Benjamin-Netanyahu-need-to-resign-Analysis-582033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The answer is not yet, but that could change in three to 12 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury: Tax Refunds Match Previous Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/treasury-tax-refunds-match-previous-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tax refunds increased by 17 percent last week and are now at the same level as last year, according to Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;The left and the media have spent the past few weeks arguing that the reduction in tax refunds in the first few weeks of tax filing season meant that families are seeing a tax increase.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;This is misleading and wrong. Even if an individual has a lower refund, this is not cause for a concern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP OR DOWN?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/86e447c98bdd4ecaae29c06c19edff4b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. economy slowed in the final three months of last year to an annual growth rate of 2.6 percent, the slowest pace since the beginning of 2018, as the government shutdown...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 3...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/former-trump-lawyer-back-congress-third-day-testimony-150706917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump's former attorney Michael Cohen was testifying in Congress again on Thursday, one day after a dramatic appearance during which he accused his longtime boss of being a racist, conman and cheat. Unlike Wednesday's riveting nationally televised public testimony, Cohen&amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robert Kraft could get off in prostitution case...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/28/how-patriots-owner-robert-kraft-could-get-off-in-prostitution-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prostitution case against Patriots owner Robert Kraft linked to a Florida sex-trafficking ring could be a long shot for prosecutors — partly because the women he was caught on video with are th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Warns: MS-13 Planning To Target Off-Duty Cops At Their Homes...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/02/27/nypd-ms-13-planning-to-target-off-duty-cops-at-their-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bulletin says that the gang members would carry out the attacks on off-duty officers "in order to gain street credibility."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sentenced to jail for helping crying bear cub escape trap...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/sussex-county/2019/02/she-freed-a-crying-bear-caught-in-a-trap-meant-for-momma-bear-now-shes-been-sentenced-to-jail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An animal rights activist who admitted to helping free a bear from a trap in Vernon has been sentenced to 15 days in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel election chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Mandelblit-announces-intent-to-indict-Benjamin-Netanyahu-for-bribery-582026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision could decisively impact election; Case 2000 indictment for breach of trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu to Be Charged With Bribery... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/netanyahu-to-be-charged-with-bribery-pending-hearing-1.6961872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicare for All!</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/28/democrats-introduce-medicare-for-all-bill-eliminates-employer-based-health-insurance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Medicare for All" would eliminate private health insurance -- including individual and employer-provided insurance -- within two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RABID COHEN BACK ON HILL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d29f404c6d846f29c734f8b8ccd54e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's former lawyer returned to Capitol Hill on Thursday for hours of closed-door questioning after publicly branding his former boss a racist and a con man...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
