<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Covid map hidden by Trump reveals worst hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2231507/covid-map-hidden-by-trump-published-virus-hotspots-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID data which Democrats claim was “hidden” by the Trump administration has been published for the first time, revealing the worst virus hotspots. Donald Trump had allegedly told stat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Says Bug Will Last Forever, Isolation Leads Nowhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bolsonaro-says-covid-will-last-forever-isolation-leads-nowhere/ar-BB1dbKac?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT FENZY PUMPS UP DOGECOIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/dogecoin-cryptocurrency-rises-over-400percent-after-reddit-group-talks-it-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogecoin added about $7.17 billion to its market capitalization in 24 hours, thanks to the SatoshiStreetBets Reddit group talking it up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus consequence: World without cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/consumers-abandon-cash-altogether-because-of-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because of the coronavirus pandemic, Americans are finally embracing touch-free payments. And they may never go back to paper currency again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Le Pen, at record high in polls, proposes hijab ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210129-france-s-le-pen-at-record-high-in-polls-proposes-hijab-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's Le Pen, at record high in polls, proposes hijab ban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/sec-reviewing-recent-trading-volatility-amid-gamestop-frenzy-vows-to-protect-retail-investors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC said it will work to protect investors by reviewing the recent volatility that has fueled a meteoric rise in stocks like GameStop and AMC Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Antipope of Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/01/29/trump-antipope-president-mar-a-lago-463238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a medieval religious schism can teach us about Donald Trump’s unprecedented and radically antagonistic approach to the ex-presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury house listings grow as wealthy flee tax-heavy states...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/luxury-house-listings-grow-as-wealthy-flee-high-tax-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the world’s most expensive homes, Villa Firenze, comes on the market as a growing number of high-priced homes are up for sale, especially as celebrities and wealthy individuals are fleeing high-tax states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-zero rally...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129130354-m7zs0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY-YAKUTSK (PIX):Some Russians gear up for sub-zero rally for Kremlin critic Navalny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China derecognizes British National Overseas passport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-beijing-hong-kong-immigration-china-9eff79173444f227c67c838fd86a45aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China said Friday it will no longer recognize the British National Overseas passport as a valid travel document or form of identification amid a bitter feud with London over a plan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELESTE: Modern soul hero comes good on the hype...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/en_asia/reviews/album/celeste-not-your-muse-review-2867890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She topped every tipster's poll as once to watch for 2020 and the London star has proved herself a generational talent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Moscow cultivating Trump as asset for 40 years, says former KGB spy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-cultivating-trump-asset-40-122505054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yuri Shvets told the Guardian that the KGB had identified Trump as a potential asset as far back as the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamlet absorbs charges of  unknowing role in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-columbus-media-social-media-ohio-b033c3b44e9a260a26dc10172dc7e7cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOODSTOCK, Ohio (AP) — In this don't blink-or-you'll-miss-it, one-stoplight town, dozens of residents still fly “Trump 2020” and “Make America Great Again” flags. But it's a now-shuttered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Black man denied spot in 'Whites-only' cemetery in Louisiana, graveyard apologized...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/after-a-black-man-was-denied-a-spot-in-a-e2-80-98whites-only-e2-80-99-cemetery-in-louisiana-the-graveyard-has-apologized/ar-BB1dcXLe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oaklin Springs Cemetery in Oberlin, La., has since amended a provision that says only White people could be buried there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Liaison: New Zealand quarantine flaw exposed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-coronavirus-pandemic-new-zealand-4e0c3e83080ba770f6e3a9241827618f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — The woman who took a flight back to New Zealand was supposed to avoid all physical contact with others for 14 days as she went into mandatory quarantine. The man...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain bans flights from Dubai -- as influencers, TV stars rush to get home...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/britain-bans-flights-from-dubai-as-influencers-and-tv-stars-who-flocked-to-the-city-rush-to-get-home/ar-BB1db5Xa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Influencers and reality TV stars have been branded insensitive for jetting off to sunny destinations amid the global health crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart shopping carts on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/smart-shopping-carts-on-the-rise-as-stores-adapt-to-pandemic-era/ar-BB1dcPed?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kroger is introducing smart shopping carts as a way to encourage social distancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire blasts 'Robinhood market' as Jon Stewart, others herald rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Billionaire-blasts-Robinhood-market-as-Jon-15907694.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unlikely rise of GameStop stock was already seen by someas a populist war against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak rattles crew of Navy warship...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2021/01/29/people-are-scared-covid-19-outbreak-rattles-crew-of-the-warship-chafee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. 3rd Fleet officials confirmed that some personnel had tested positive for the coronavirus on the guided-missile destroyer, but declined to say how many cases had emerged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Most Inoculated Nation Struggles With Strains...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/worlds-most-vaccinated-nation-struggles-with-virus-variants/ar-BB1dcbHR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 30% of its population vaccinated, Israel leads the fight against Covid-19. Yet the emergence of more infectious variants is overwhelming its hospitals, showing the long road ahead for the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Investors May Lose Everything, Central Banker Warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-investors-may-lose-everything-central-banker-warns/ar-BB1dcO4H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin investors need to be prepared to “lose all their money,” European Central Bank governing council member Gabriel Makhlouf said, the latest warning from a central banker on the cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baquet home purchase reignites retirement, LA TIMES chatter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/28/dean-baquets-la-home-purchase-reignites-retirement-la-times-chatter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News that New York Times executive editor Dean Baquet just purchased a $2.1 million home in a tony neighborhood near Los Angeles has renewed speculation about whether he might take over the top job…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic-weary Ecuadoreans lean toward return to socialism...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129050242-mroaq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ECUADOR-POLITICS/ (PIX):As election nears, pandemic-weary Ecuadoreans lean toward return to socialism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA lawmaker's white privilege teaching inquiry sparks anger, support...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/education/ga-lawmakers-white-privilege-teaching-inquiry-sparks-anger-support/HCUEVLVXZFGEFOXLYMALH3GG5M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white Georgia state representative is drawing outrage from several educators and support from some students after requesting information to determine whether professors are teaching materials that say white people are privileged and oppressive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Ties to Extremist Groups Under Scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/29/republican-ties-to-extremist-groups-are-under-scrutiny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The video’s title was posed as a question, but it left little doubt about where the men who</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Us in Miami! Love, Masters of Universe...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/29/join-us-in-miami-love-masters-of-the-universe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — America’s business leaders, freed from the office, looked around the country, taking note of its coronavirus lockdowns, taxes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Has Erased Entire Categories of Friendship...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/the-pandemic-has-erased-entire-categories-of-friendship/ar-BB1d8ZIr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a reason you miss the people you didn’t even know that well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon evaluating request for help...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210128164554-70rxe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-PENTAGON (URGENT):Pentagon evaluating request for help in administering COVID-19 vaccines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Oxford Street Faces 'Boarded Up' Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/londons-oxford-street-faces-boarded-up-future-retailers-warn/ar-BB1dbNie?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinic in Ecuador that gave fake jabs to 70,000 patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9199033/Authorities-shut-clandestine-clinic-Ecuador-offered-FAKE-COVID-19-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quito security chief César Díaz told reporters that the bogus facility had treated at least 70,000 patients who were charged $15 for each of the three doses they were required to take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will vaccines keep up?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/01/27/covid-vaccines-new-strains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race is on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazonian city that hatched Brazil variant has been crushed by it...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/the-amazonian-city-that-hatched-the-brazil-variant-has-been-crushed-by-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another surge was coming. This time, Uildéia Galvão thought they were prepared. Galvão, the lead physician in the coronavirus ward at a public hospital in the Brazilian city of Manaus, had been haunted by the wave that crashed last spring....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How minnows sank the sharks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9199783/How-minnows-sank-Wall-Street-sharks-astonishing-financial-story-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOM LEONARD: Most City share-tippers would be unlikely to recommend putting money on a chain of video game shops. Yet if you'd taken a punt on GameStop you would have made serious money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter Threatened With Arrest After Asking Her Question...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/01/28/georgia-news-crew-marjorie-taylor-greene-town-hall-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local Georgia news crew was removed from a town hall hosted by Representative Marjorie Taylor Greene on Jan. 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep me in handcuffs': Navalny denounces criminal proceedings...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jan/28/alexei-navalny-release-bid-fails-and-senior-aides-charged-over-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin critic will remain in jail until parole hearing next week where he could be sent to penal colony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CICELY TYSON DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/01/28/rip-the-amazing-cicely-tyson-age-96-award-winning-actress-activist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I have managed Miss Tyson’s career for over 40 years, and each year was a privilege and blessing,” her manager, Larry Thompson, said in a statement. “Cicely thought of her new memoir as a Christma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene faces mounting calls for repercussions over her words, actions...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/01/28/greene-faces-mounting-calls-for-repercussions-over-her-words-actions-and-social-media-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia Republican Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene has called a Parkland shooting survivor a “coward” and sympathized with QAnon conspiracy theories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS ON STREET:  Stocks targeted by REDDIT users plummet...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/GameStop-shares-whipsaw-as-other-stocks-targeted-15905279.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of GameStop and other companies plummeted in regular trading Thursday even as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGET:  APP STORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/facebook-out-to-loosen-apple-s-grip-on-app-store-report-01611864310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is readying a lawsuit aimed at loosening Apple's grip on the App Store that serves as an exclusive gateway onto iPhones, a tech news outlet reported on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren calls CNBC reporter's 'bluff' on rich leaving USA over wealth tax...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/536404-warren-calls-cnbc-reporters-bluff-on-rich-leaving-us-over-wealth-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) called a CNBC reporter’s “bluff” after the reporter suggested that wealthy Americans would leave the U.S. over a new tax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House press briefing is nearly ALL women...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/536363-white-house-press-briefing-is-nearly-all-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thursday's White House press briefing was a woman-dominated event, Twitter users were quick to note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Trump bromance, Biden quickly shifts cold on Putin...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-bromance-biden-quickly-shifts-204701609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Donald Trump's four-year flirtation with Russian President Vladimir Putin, Joe Biden is setting a new, colder tone -- unhesitant criticism, despite openness on arms control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic caused worst year for US economy since 1946...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-caused-worst-us-economy-151711603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States saw its sharpest contraction in growth since 1946 as the coronavirus pandemic hammered the economy last year, but while the country may be set for a recovery, it hasn't arrived yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg 'supreme court' overturns four content-removal rulings...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-review-board-first-action-155534110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's newly-launched 'supreme court' issued its first rulings on Thursday, overturning four of five decisions to remove controversial posts from the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIONEERING HOLLYWOOD ICON</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cicely-tyson-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cicely Tyson, the iconic and incomparable screen and stage actress and Black American trailblazer, died on Thursday. She was 96.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel leads world time spent with lockdowns...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israel-leads-the-world-in-time-spent-in-coronavirus-lockdowns-657028</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the beginning of the pandemic, Israel has been in lockdown for 139 days, longer than any other country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's holding up next test of SPACEX Starship? Musk blames FAA...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/news/spacex-starship-sn9-high-altitude-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM plans electric-only vehicles by 2035!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gm-sets-goal-of-all-electric-by-2035-going-carbon-neutral-by-2040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Motors announced Thursday it wants to eliminate non-electric light-duty vehicles by 2035 in a goal to go carbon neutral by 2040.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College uses dead teacher for online class...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/concordia-university-says-lectures-from-dead-professor-were-teaching-tool</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concordia University says there should have been no confusion about who was teaching an online class after a student said he was surprised to discover the professor delivering the video lectures had died in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CICELY TYSON DEAD</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/cicely-tyson-dead-dies-1234895188/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emmy- and Tony-winning actress Cicely Tyson, who distinguished herself in theater, film and television, died on Thursday afternoon. She was 96. “I have managed Miss Tyson’s career for o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowy Owl Spotted In Central Park For First Time In More Than Century...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/01/27/snowy-owl-central-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say the last recorded sighting of a snowy owl in Central Park was back in 1890.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Starved Hollywood Starts To Lose Its 'Marbles' With New Reality Show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/01/john-de-mol-marble-mania-us-format-talpa-1234681128/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after launching his latest company, John de Mol is taking out what he hopes to be a successful global format with Marble Mania on the heels of a promising launch for the celebrity marble rac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept investigating Musk's SPACEX following complaint of hiring discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/doj-investigating-spacex-after-hiring-discrimination-complaint-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DOJ is investigating Elon Musk's SpaceX over whether the company "engages in any pattern or practice of discrimination" in its hiring, court filings say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus variant from South Africa detected in USA for 1st time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-variant-south-africa-us-2bc397370cdd44afe916ddd6edbaf870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — A new variant of the coronavirus emerged Thursday in the United States, posing yet another public health challenge in a country already losing more than 3,000 people to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star NYTIMES Reporter Accused of Using 'N-Word'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/star-new-york-times-reporter-donald-mcneil-accused-of-using-n-word-making-other-racist-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The paper’s top COVID reporter joined a group of students on a trip to Peru in 2019. Participants alleged he repeatedly made racist comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BULLSH*T!' Hedge Fund Billionaire Rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/bullsht-hedge-fund-billionaire-leon-cooperman-rages-over-gamestop-surge-rips-small-investors-for-having-no-idea-what-theyre-doing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hedge fund titan is lashing out at the small-time investors who have banded together to disrupt Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Found Biblical 'royal purple' offers look at King David wardrobe...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/biblical-royal-purple-found-at-timna-offers-look-at-king-david-wardrobe-657082</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The color, a bright shade of purple, was extracted from mollusks fished in the Mediterranean Sea through a very expensive process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD will NOW allow limited buying of restricted securities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/robinhood-will-allow-limited-buying-of-restricted-securities-friday-gamestop-jumps-after-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Medical Center Gave Shots To Donors, Relatives Of Top Execs...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/01/28/hunterdon-medical-center-gave-covid-19-vaccine-to-donors-relatives-of-top-hospital-executives-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shots were administered by Hunterdon Medical Center in December and early January, at a time when only front-line health care workers and residents of long-term care facilities were eligible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: SUBWAY's tuna sandwich doesn't have tuna in it...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/28/subways-tuna-doesnt-actually-have-tuna-in-it-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two California women claim Subway’s tuna sandwich actually contains not a “scintilla” of the fish — and that they were duped by the fast-food joint’s claims, a new $5 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Falls Into Coma After Getting Vaccine, Dies 4 Days Later...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/01/27/pfizer-vaccine-orange-county-moderna/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 60-year-old Orange County man died after receiving a second dose of the coronavirus vaccine. Now investigators are trying to determine if the vaccination played any role in his death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checked by reality, some QAnon supporters seek way out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-us-news-media-social-media-4ea47c2966a41b30ae678e5f471f6070</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — Ceally Smith spent a year down the rabbit hole of QAnon, spending more and more time researching and discussing the conspiracy theory online. Eventually it consumed her,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Guard isn't going home...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/01/28/the-guard-isnt-going-home-leaders-fear-retention-may-suffer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high operational tempo for the National Guard has continued into 2021, and that has some senior leaders concerned about retention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star NYTIMES Reporter Accused of Using 'N-Word'...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/star-ny-times-reporter-accused-202753548.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gary HershornLess than six months before he became the New York Times’ go-to reporter on the coronavirus pandemic, Donald McNeil Jr. was under intense scrutiny from the paper’s top brass over accusations that he made wildly offensive and racist comments while leading a Times student trip.Every summer over the past several years, the Times has selected some of its top reporters to serve as subject guides for high-school students on trips to various locations around the world, operated in some instances by Vermont-based company Putney Student Travel. The goal, according to the paper, is to give travelers a foreign vacation with educational value.In 2019, one of those experts was McNeil, a high-profile health and science reporter who joined the paper in 1976. He accompanied a student group on a Times “Student Journey” to Peru that focused on community-based health care in the region.After the excursion ended, multiple students and parents of those on the trip relayed a series of troubling complaints, according to multiple parents of students on the trip who spoke with The Daily Beast, along with documents shared with the Times and reviewed by the Beast: McNeil repeatedly made racist and sexist remarks throughout the trip including, according to two complaints, using the “n-word.”A photo from the trip showed that at least 26 students participated. Of that group, at least six students or their parents told the tour company that partnered with the Times that McNeil used racially insensitive or outright racist language while accompanying the participants on the trip, which according to the Times website typically costs nearly $5,500. Two students specifically alleged that the science reporter used the “n-word” and suggested he did not believe in the concept of white privilege; three other participants alleged that McNeil made racist comments and used stereotypes about Black teenagers.Inside the NY Times Probes Threatening a Star Reporter’s Career“I expect immediate action on the actions taken by Donald, I am deeply disappointed about the New York Times because of the comments he made during our trip. I think firing him would even be appropriate,” one participant wrote.“Not only did Donald say various racist comments on numerous occasions, but he was also disrespectful to many students during mealtimes and in other settings,” another wrote in their review.“I would change the journalist. He was a racist,” a third person wrote. “He used the ‘N’ word, said horrible things about black teenagers, and said white supremacy doesn’t exist.”“He wasn’t respectful during some of the traditional ceremonies we attended with indigenous healers/shamans,” yet another wrote. “He made students in the program feel uncomfortable with his remarks. I was really disappointed after hearing great things about his work.”A Times spokesperson told The Daily Beast on Thursday: “In 2019, Donald McNeil, Jr. participated in a Student Journeys as an expert. We subsequently became aware of complaints by some of the students on the trip concerning certain statements Donald had made during the trip. We conducted a thorough investigation and disciplined Donald for statements and language that had been inappropriate and inconsistent with our values. We found he had used bad judgement by repeating a racist slur in the context of a conversation about racist language. In addition, we apologized to the students who had participated in the trip.”Following the reviews from participants, Times managers were immediately concerned, alerting the paper’s public-relations shop and its publisher, A.G. Sulzberger, to the alarming accusations.“It’s highly likely his comments will become public at some point,” Danielle Rhoades Ha, a vice president of communications for the Times, warned colleagues in an email exchange reviewed by The Daily Beast.“This is outrageous, in my view,” former corporate comms director Linda Zebian said. “I do think his manager needs to be made aware as a first step. Depending on their response, we can prepare a statement on any action that is being put into place.”Multiple people familiar with the situation told The Daily Beast that an internal investigation was conducted into the claims, and that the top science reporter was reprimanded. The paper also reached out to some parties who complained to apologize for McNeil’s behavior and to assure the students and parents that action had been taken internally against him.Jeff Shumlin, director at Putney Student Travel, did not deny to The Daily Beast that his company had received complaints from parents about McNeil. “The New York Times shares some of its writers and experts with our programs for a short period of time but that is their area of responsibility so I would refer you to them for further comment,” he said.McNeil’s racist remarks have come to light during a period of controversy for the paper. Its award-winning podcast, Caliphate, has now been debunked; questions about its Pulitzer finalist host, star reporter Rukmini Callimachi, and her body of work for the paper remain unanswered. Last week, the Times came under intense criticism for firing a contract-based editor for tweeting that she had “chills” on Joe Biden’s inauguration day.A longtime reporter at the Times, McNeil has won numerous awards for his hard-hitting and incisive reporting on infectious diseases, including his coverage of the Zika and Ebola outbreaks, along with the AIDS crisis and has served as a foreign correspondent reporting from Africa and Europe.New York Times Admits Its Caliphate Podcast Fell for ISIS Hoaxer’s BullshitSince the beginning of the coronavirus pandemic, McNeil has emerged as one of the paper’s breakout stars and one of the country’s most prominent journalistic voices on the pandemic. While many Americans were still seemingly unconcerned about the virus in early 2020, McNeil’s reporting and a key appearance on the popular Times podcast The Daily emphasized its severity and potential to become a deadly global pandemic. Earlier this week, the Times published a candid sit down with Dr. Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, who opened up to McNeil about his difficult relationship with former President Donald Trump.Still, over the course of his tenure at the esteemed newspaper, he’s occasionally run afoul of the management. In 2012, he sent a blistering email to friends mocking and criticizing the Times’ then-publisher Arthur Sulzberger for his seeming absence amid tense guild contract negotiations.Nevertheless, the paper has been eager to highlight McNeil’s work. According to a person familiar with the matter, his COVID-19 coverage is among the New York Times’ submissions for this year's Pulitzer Prize for public-service journalism.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top cop calls for 'permanent fencing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/capitol-riot-prompts-acting-chief-to-call-for-permanent-fencing-backup-forces</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Capitol riot prompted unprecedented efforts by law enforcement and the military to protect D.C. ahead of President Joe Biden’s inauguration, and now the acting Capitol police chief wants some of those measures to become permanent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 MINS SUNDAY: CHINA COLLECTING AMERICAN DNA, INTEL OFFICIALS WARN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/china-us-biodata-60-minutes-2021-01-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;60 Minutes has learned Chinese company BGI Group, the largest biotech firm in the world, offered to build COVID labs in at least six states, and U.S. intelligence officials issued warnings not to share health data with BGI. See the story, Sunday on CBS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: ABCNEWS president out....</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/james-goldston-abc-news-president-exit-step-down-1234894918/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Goldston, the president of ABC News, will leave the Walt Disney-backed unit at the end of March, the latest in a recent series of changes among top national news executives. “It’s a rea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to let mankind hear sounds of Mars for very first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/nasas-perseverance-rover-mankind-hear-23398458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Humanity will hear the sounds on the surface on Mars for the first time as NASA chiefs reveal plans to carry a tribute to medics who battled coronavirus to the Red Planet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers demand more cash for security...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9197533/Terrified-members-Congress-demand-funds-hire-24-hour-armed-guards-homes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi blasted armed Republican members of Congress as 'the enemy within' as lawmakers asked for additional funds for security amid increasing threats to their safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley venture capital behemoth's plan to eat the media...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/analysis/andreessen-horowitz-silicon-valley-venture-capital-media.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a relatively innocuous job ad on LinkedIn, seeking an executive editor. It said things like “our editorial mission is to be the go-to place for understanding technology, innovation, and change, as it impacts all of our lives” and “we are unapologetically pro-tech, pro-future, pro-change.” Pretty anodyne stuff, typical of half a dozen tech […]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO:  'Incompetent Government Kills'...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/01/28/andrew-cuomo-covid-19-nursing-home-deaths-incompetent-government-kills-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York governor should look to his own state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State bars counties from vaccinating anyone 65 and older...</title>
      <link>https://buffalonews.com/news/local/state-bars-county-governments-from-vaccinating-anyone-65-and-older/article_11e658fa-617a-11eb-a006-777741aa5483.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;buffalonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The county will still vaccinate those 65 and older who had previously made an appointment with the county Health Department and either had their appointment canceled or are already scheduled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State lawmakers pushing to curb governors' virus powers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/state-lawmakers-governor-coronavirus-7d5710f2d8aa4e659c0ec68400ad3d3c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irritated by the sweeping use of executive orders during the COVID-19 crisis, state lawmakers around the U.S. are moving to curb the authority of governors and top health officials to impose...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron weighs 3rd lockdown despite signs French 'can't take it anymore'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210128-macron-weighs-up-a-third-lockdown-despite-signs-the-french-can-t-take-it-anymore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid risks of a push back from a population wearied by successive restrictions, the French government is mulling tougher anti-Covid curbs – including a third lockdown – after conceding a nightly curf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: 'The enemy is within' the House of Representatives...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nancy-pelosi-the-enemy-is-within-the-house-of-representatives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House speaker called out lawmakers attempting to bring guns on the floor of the House and threatening their colleagues with violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Delivery Drones Take Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pizza-drone-delivery-faa-aproval-8d29d6e8-d703-4bd0-8fc3-0def94c6ed13.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Momentum is building in the U.S. for drones to deliver food and merchandise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid nitrogen leak at Georgia poultry plant kills 6...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/georgia-gainesville-34698174274717f4ec84b6964782e9fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAINESVILLE, Ga, (AP) — A liquid nitrogen leak at a northeast Georgia poultry plant killed six people Thursday, with multiple others taken to the hospital. Beth Downs, a spokesperson for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Race against time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/u-s-race-against-time-new-coronavirus-variants-scientists-warn-n1255963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Without a stable pipeline between manufacturing and distribution, the country remains vulnerable to emerging new strains, said one health professor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators consider censure due to likely impeachment acquittal...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/senators-consider-censure-alternative-impeachment-trial-view-likely-trump-acquittal-n1256016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A censure resolution requires only a simple majority vote. One senator said it could prevent Trump from holding future office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGE OVER BLOCKED STOCKS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/gamestop-cruz-ocasio-cortez-blast-robinhood-over-trade-freeze.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AOC, Ted Cruz, Elizabeth Warren and other lawmakers criticized Robinhood after it restricted trading in GameStop and other companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCarolina detects first US case of SAfrica-strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/28/health/south-carolina-variant-south-africa/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Carolina officials have announced the United States' first two confirmed cases of a more contagious coronavirus strain first spotted in South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE CEO links FACEBOOK to real-world violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/apple-ceo-tim-cook-says-f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If a business is built on misleading users, on data exploitation, on choices that are no choices at all, it does not deserve our praise. It deserves scorn"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops to boost pace of shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.wyso.org/2021-01-27/feds-to-reimburse-states-for-vaccine-duty-by-national-guard-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wyso.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden ordered full reimbursement to states using the National Guard in the battle against the coronavirus pandemic. Many troops will be used to boost the pace of vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 0.04% of Israelis infected after 2 shots of PFIZER...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-shows-promising-results-from-pfizer-vaccination-campaign-657051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maccabi health fund releases preliminary results of a study comparing vaccinated and not vaccinated members’ likability to contract the disease and said vaccine 92% effective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto mulling run for Texas gov...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/536287-orourke-mulling-run-for-texas-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O'Rourke (D-Texas) said this week he is considering a 2022 gubernatorial run, setting up a potential challenge against incumbent Texas Gov. Greg Abbott (R).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVER 4,000 TODAY...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Esx5hTZUYAEE8UJ?format=jpg&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's response ranks among WORST in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9197989/The-United-States-worlds-fifth-worse-response-coronavirus-pandemic-scientists-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US came 94th out of 98 countries in the study by the Lowry Institute, followed only by Iran, Colombia, Mexico and Brazil in last place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No bathrooms. No seating. Endless lines. Seniors face vax misery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-bathrooms-no-seating-endless-130050618.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology and social media skills, reliable transportation and even physical stamina have become near prerequisites for obtaining the coveted shots.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
