<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>OFFSPRING drummer dropped from band for refusing vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/offspring-drummer-pete-parada-says-band-cut-him-loose-over-covid-19-vaccine-decision/ar-AAMWsN8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Offspring drummer Pete Parada explains why he decided against a vaccine. 'The hesitant population is not a monolithic group,' he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State spending billions to house homeless in hotels...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-california-coronavirus-pandemic-835c2091c63c199d397346a497e7ae49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — When homeless outreach workers first visited her encampment under a Los Angeles highway overpass last fall, Veronica Perez was skeptical of their offer of not just a bed, but a furnished apartment complete with meals, counseling and the promise of some stability in her life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterinarian Pleads Guilty to Making Animal Torture Porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/k78kdv/florida-veterinarian-guilty-plea-sexual-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsealed court documents about a Florida vet accused of possession of child porn reveal disturbing details of torture and abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases among children, teens jump 84%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/us/covid-19-children-teens/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 72,000 children and teens caught Covid-19 last week -- a "substantial" increase from a week earlier, the American Academy of Pediatrics reported Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abandoned chickens reveal trend is fizzling...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/abandoned-chickens-roosters-city-zoning-pandemic-16361232.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some, raising backyard chickens seemed like a good idea — at the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana Nurse Breaks Down: 'Worse Now Than Ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/louisiana-icu-nurse-breaks-down-over-skyrocketing-covid-19-cases-68845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Felicia Croft said that two of the patients in her hospital's ICU are the parents of her daughter's friend. "As a nurse, to know that if you can't get these two people home, that their kids will be orphaned," Croft said in a now-viral video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Auto Show Cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/04/new-york-auto-show-cancelled-due-to-covid-19-delta-variant-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers cited "growing incidences of the COVID-19 Delta variant and the increased measures announced recently by state and local officials to stop its spread."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dre's daughter reveals she's homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9857957/Dr-Dres-eldest-daughter-reveals-shes-homeless-living-car.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LaTanya Young, 38, works as a delivery driver for DoorDash and Uber Eats and as an assembler at a warehouse but claims that she can't afford to secure an apartment in California, DailyMail.com can reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Hospitals' Request For Emergency Staff Denied As Hospitalizations Quadruple...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/texas-hospitals-request-emergency-staff-denied-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals in North Texas say they need hundreds of additional staff to deal with a surge of COVID-19 cases, but the state has denied their requests for emergency personnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Bill to Require Alcohol Monitors for All New Cars...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/infrastructure-bill-would-require-alcohol-monitors-for-all-new-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bipartisan infrastructure bill includes a provision that would require auto manufacturers to equip "advanced alcohol monitoring systems" in all new cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China seals city as its worst virus outbreak in year grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-china-coronavirus-pandemic-46fd21e9be94b2b3f4ebeb59ec4fa77c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China's worst coronavirus outbreak since the start of the pandemic a year and a half ago escalated Wednesday with dozens more cases around the country, the sealing-off of one city and the punishment of its local leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROSECUTORS PROBE CUOMO</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/manhattan-and-westchester-prosecutors-seek-materials-about-cuomo-s-conduct-for-possible-criminal-probes/ar-AAMWfel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The request from the district attorneys came a day after the top prosecutor in Albany confirmed his office is conducting a criminal investigation of alleged sexual harassment by the New York governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While they were asleep, their TESLAa burned in garage. It's risk many automakers taking seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/while-they-were-asleep-their-teslas-burned-in-the-garage-it-e2-80-99s-a-risk-many-automakers-are-taking-seriously/ar-AAMVBlV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire inspector cited the thermal management system in one of the Tesla Model S sedans as one of two possible causes in the blaze, which showed what can happen when one electric car ignited another in the garage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In drought-plagued northern Mexico, tens of thousands of cows starving to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/latino-life/story/2021-08-02/in-drought-plagued-northern-mexico-cows-are-starving-to-by-the-tens-of-thousands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sonora is the cattle capital of Mexico. But prolonged drought is killing off the herds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Torrez entered to Beethoven, bloodied foe's face and can win gold for USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/olympics/richard-torrez-entered-to-beethoven-bloodied-a-foe-e2-80-99s-face-and-can-win-gold-for-the-us/ar-AAMVwNf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No U.S. man has won boxing gold since 2004. The Super-heavyweight has a chance Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORBES: Rihanna Billionaire...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/maddieberg/2021/08/04/fentys-fortune-rihanna-is-now-officially-a-billionaire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the singer became the richest female musician on the planet. Hint: it wasn't performing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cuomo brothers: New spotlight on unique relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/media/andrew-cuomo-chris-cuomo-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albany, Westchester criminal probes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/04/cuomo-allegations-westchester-county-da-seeks-evidence-for-potential-criminal-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DA Mimi Rocah asked NY AG Letitia James to send her materials related to one of the 11 women who in a bombshell report accused Cuomo of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic of hypocrisy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/566257-americas-pandemic-of-covid-hypocrisy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If COVID-19 continues in some variation, the same politicians who fanned its spread will be the first to condemn the Biden administration for not ending it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY vs. Scarlett Johansson: Ton of Lawsuits May Be Next...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/disney-vs-scarlett-johansson-lawsuits-next-1234992368/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Bob Chapek-led regime goes to war with a Marvel star, Hollywood stars and creatives fear the end of massive backend deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Americans believe worst still ahead...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/566256-majority-in-new-polling-believes-worst-in-pandemic-is-still</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Americans say in new polling that the worst of the coronavirus pandemic is still ahead of us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitmen Dressed Up in PPE to Murder Politician...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbv4m/hitmen-dressed-up-in-covid-ppe-to-murder-this-politician</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Killers in Honduras often disguise themselves as police or military officers. But this team had a pandemic ruse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: American Obsession With Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/08/the-american-obsession-with-decline/619656/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether economic times are good or bad, the lament for the old days of factories and mills never changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising Benefits of Talking to Strangers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/08/why-we-should-talk-strangers-more/619642/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So often we’re raised to see strangers as dangerous and scary. What would happen if we instead saw them as potential sources of comfort and belonging?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta Seen to Push Herd Immunity Threshold Above 80%...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/delta-seen-to-push-herd-immunity-threshold-above-80/ar-AAMT9bD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spread of the delta coronavirus variant has pushed the threshold for herd immunity to well over 80% and potentially approaching 90%, according to an Infectious Diseases Society of America briefing on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas Gov Admits Mistake on Mask Mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/arkansas-republican-governor-admits-mistake-on-mask-mandates-as-cases-soar-i-wish-that-had-not-become-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Covid-19 cases surging in his state, Gov. Asa Hutchinson (R-AR) wishes he could take back the ban on local mask mandates that he signed into law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Facing Dead Heat In Recall Election..</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/update-new-poll-shows-newsom-facing-near-dead-heat-in-recall-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Governor Gavin Newsom could be facing a dead heat in the recall election next month, according to a newly released poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighter said he had covid to get paid time off. He lied and vacationed at resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-firefighter-said-he-had-covid-19-to-get-paid-time-off-he-lied-and-vacationed-at-a-resort-prosecutors-say/ar-AAMVoYH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas firefighter William Jordan Carter received nearly $12,600 in paid time off after claiming he and his family members tested positive for covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Men who ejaculate 21 times a month slash risk of prostate cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9857953/Men-ejaculate-21-times-month-slash-risk-prostate-cancer-THIRD.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men who ejaculate at least 21 times a month may be at a decreased risk at contracting prostate cancer, a Harvard study finds. The scientific consensus is not certain on the issue, though.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to school turns ugly as variant rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/04/school-delta-variant-502331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 18 months into the pandemic, there’s no consensus on how to keep students and staff safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICUs overwhelmed with younger, sicker...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/it-just-went-boom-icus-are-being-overwhelmed-with-younger-and-sicker-patients/ar-AAMQly4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Inside a COVID-only intensive care unit at Jackson Memorial Hospital in Miami, all eight beds are filled with patients. Six of the eight patients are younger than 50 years old. None of them has been vaccinated against COVID-19. The youngest patient, a 27-year-old woman on a ventilator, had to be resuscitated with a bag valve mask after her blood oxygen saturation levels crashed. The ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albany DA criminally investigating...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/albany-da-criminally-investigating-cuomo-will-request-evidence-from-ag-sexual-harassment-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo has denied sexually harassing 11 women whose claims are detailed in a report by the office of Attorney General Letitia James.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta peak this month?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/566212-deltas-peak-is-difficult-to-project-but-could-come-this-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The delta variant surging through the United States could peak later this month, but experts say projections are difficult and much will depend on an unpredictable factor: human behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan warns of unprecedented COVID spread as Tokyo cases hit new record...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210804085329-74b2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-Japan warns of unprecedented COVID spread as Tokyo cases hit new record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carl Heastie: Man Who Would Oversee Cuomo Impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/04/carl-heastie-the-man-who-would-oversee-cuomos-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s call for Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo of New York to resign after a state investigation found he had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After decades in woods, New Hampshire man forced from cabin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-new-hampshire-e0ef2fb3349a23ceebaa9e244b97eb5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANTERBURY, N.H. (AP) — For almost three decades, 81-year-old David Lidstone has lived in the woods of New Hampshire along the Merrimack River in a small cabin adorned with solar panels. He has grown his own food, cut his own firewood, and tended to his cat and chickens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC PROOF OF VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/nycs-de-blasio-mandates-vaccines-for-all-indoor-activities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio issued a mandate requiring employees and customers of indoor eateries, gyms and entertainment centers to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: DeSantis falls behind Crist as virus cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/566218-florida-poll-desantis-falls-behind-crist-as-covid-19-cases-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Ship Hijack Near Iran Ends as Mideast Tensions Mount...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/possible-ship-hijack-near-iran-082450206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A suspected hijacking of a vessel near Iran has ended, the British Navy said Wednesday, days after a deadly drone attack on a tanker in the same area that the U.S and its allies blamed on the Islamic Republic.The events have stoked tensions in and around the waterways of the Persian Gulf, through which many of the world’s oil exports are carried.The U.S. has vowed a “collective response” to last week’s strike on an Israeli-operated vessel, which killed a Romanian and a Briton, as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Significantly Scales Back 60th Birthday Party as Virus Cases Rebound...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/04/obama-significantly-scales-back-60th-birthday-party-as-virus-cases-rebound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The party plans had been months in the making and many invitees had already arrived on Martha’s Vineyard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Lebanon's Worst Economic Meltdown in More Than Century...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/04/collapse-inside-lebanons-worst-economic-meltdown-in-more-than-a-century/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRIPOLI, Lebanon — Rania Mustafa’s living room recalls a not-so-distant past, when the modest salary of a security guard in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record wildfire burns amid drought in Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-environment-and-nature-droughts-hawaii-wildfires-ca2f8cbf76abf6affbbee9fce3be69a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Firefighters gained more control over a wildfire in Hawaii that forced thousands of people to evacuate over the weekend and destroyed at least two homes on the Big Island, but officials warned that strong winds will return on Tuesday, raising the danger again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titanic museum iceberg wall collapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/us/titanic-museum-iceberg-injured-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wall of ice collapsed Monday at the Titanic Museum Attraction, injuring three visitors to the popular tourist spot in Tennessee's Smoky Mountains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran to give J&amp;J recipients 'supplemental dose'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/jj-covid-vaccine-recipients-can-get-supplemental-pfizer-or-moderna-shots-in-san-francisco.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J&amp;J recipients can make special requests to get a "supplemental dose" of an mRNA vaccine, San Francisco health officials said in a statement to CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan &amp; Harry set to make Hollywood debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3407104/meghan-markle-prince-harry-present-emmy-award/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMY awards bosses want Prince Harry and wife Meghan to make their Hollywood debuts at the ceremony next month. TV execs are keen for the pair to attend the A-list event in downtown LA. They may ev…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Covid Wave Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-faces-its-worst-coronavirus-wave-yet/ar-AAMRrMm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the highly contagious Delta variant of the virus rips through the unvaccinated population in the United States, Florida is heading toward its worst outbreak since the start of the pandemic. The state is still about one month away from its peak, according to an epidemiologist who has been tracking the virus’s reach there. “Short term and long term, the cases are going to explode,” Edwin Michael, a professor of epidemiology at the University of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Mexico's most terrified city...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/featured/ct-aud-nyt-mexico-fresnillo-20210803-b447rgfxsjhhhg7nlqugcloovi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The violence was already terrifying, she said, when grenades exploded outside her church in broad daylight some five years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL hospitalizations break record for 3rd straight day...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/566156-florida-covid-19-hospitalizations-break-record-for-third-straight-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's COVID-19 hospitalization record was broken on Tuesday for the third day in a row as the state struggles with the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  RESIGN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/biden-calls-on-cuomo-to-resign-after-bombshell-sexual-harassment-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden called on Democratic New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo to resign Tuesday, following a report that Cuomo sexually harassed 11 women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth About the Quietest Town in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-truth-about-the-quietest-town-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Radio Quiet Zone limits wireless communications. But a journey to its center in Green Bank, West Virginia reveals a town at odds with itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabinet approves new restrictions, considers lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/covid-israel-registers-almost-4000-cases-as-cabinet-prepares-to-meet-675707</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting August 20, the full green pass system will be in place again, and starting Sunday, masks will be mandatory in all outdoor gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Philadelphia Reveals About Homicide Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/philadelphia-homicide-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many explanations for the rise in killings in U.S. cities, including the pandemic and the choices made in response to it. In Philadelphia, the causes, the human costs — and the suffering — are particularly stark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PODHORETZ:  The Mad King, Alone Upon His Throne...</title>
      <link>https://www.commentary.org/john-podhoretz/cuomo-the-mad-king/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.commentary.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How art the mighty fallen. I encourage you, if you did not see it, to watch Andrew Cuomo's statement in response to the release of a report by New York</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
