<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China condemns latest U.S. warship transit of Taiwan Strait...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-warship-transits-taiwan-strait-001356953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING/TAIPEI (Reuters) -China condemned the United States on Wednesday as the region's greatest security "risk creator" after a U.S. warship again sailed through the sensitive waterway that separates Taiwan from China. The U.S. Navy's 7th Fleet said the Arleigh Burke-class guided missile destroyer USS Curtis Wilbur conducted a "routine Taiwan Strait transit" on Tuesday in accordance with international law. "The ship's transit through the Taiwan Strait demonstrates the U.S. commitment to a free and open Indo-Pacific."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand reports new daily record of covid deaths...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/thailand-reports-daily-record-51-011926590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thailand reported on Wednesday a new daily record of 51 COVID-19 fatalities, bringing total deaths to 1,744 since the pandemic started last year. The country, grappling with its third and most deadly outbreak, also reported 3,174 new infections, bringing total confirmed cases to 228,539. More than 85% of new cases and deaths came after April this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand on edge after virus-infected Australian visits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-zealand-australia-lifestyle-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-aeacc7186bb1e25dc90538460a7330ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — After enjoying nearly four months without any community transmission of the coronavirus, New Zealanders were on edge Wednesday after health authorities said an infectious traveler from Australia had visited over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS BAILOUT AIRPORTS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-ea5072c5f9c7397a8b01a4876abaccbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Airports around the country will share $8 billion in federal grants to help them recover from the pandemic, which caused a steep drop in air travel and a loss of revenue that airports expect from airlines and passengers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi to create special panel to probe Jan. 6 attacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-capitol-siege-government-and-politics-b05ca57ac271dc25f1739505357028ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is signaling that she is poised to create a new committee to investigate the Jan. 6 insurrection at the Capitol, pushing closer to a partisan investigation of the attack after Senate Republicans blocked the creation of an independent probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As homicides soar nationwide, mayors see few options for regaining control...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-homicides-soar-nationwide-mayors-see-few-options-for-regaining-control/ar-AALjht4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local leaders say they don’t expect the spike in killings to end anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi to create special panel to probe Jan. 6 attacks...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/crime-pmn/u-s-house-speaker-pelosi-to-create-special-panel-to-probe-jan-6-attack-source</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal right to disconnect from Internet could become norm in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/right-to-disconnect-could-become-the-norm-in-europe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In January, a majority of EU politicians backed a legislative initiative to call for a bloc-wide directive on the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Dems, NAACP Silent on Whitehouse's White-Only Club Membership...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/black-democrats-activists-silent-on-whitehouses-white-only-club-membership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic lawmakers and racial justice advocates have kept quiet about Sen. Sheldon Whitehouse’s membership in a racially exclusionary organization, seemingly satisfied with the Rhode Island Democrat's explanation that it is nothing more than "a long tradition."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Fat But Fit' Impossible...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fat-but-fit-metabolically-healthy-myth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study results show that "fat but fit" adults are around a fifth more vulnerable to heart attacks, strokes and COPD (chronic obstructive pulmonary disease).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican official faces charge for voting twice in Nov. election...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/republican-official-ohio-faces-charge-voting-twice-november-election-n1271985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I was simply trying to execute a dying man’s wishes," Ed Snodgrass said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 4 record travel expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/business/fourth-of-july-expected-to-bring-near-record-travel-volumes/TMP5IOTJBNCK5GEGA5UOR4L324/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A near record number of travelers is expected over the Fourth of July holiday period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Fund That Shorted GAMESTOP Shuts Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xzd8/hedge-fund-that-shorted-gamestop-shuts-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While a long list of firms collectively lost tens of billions of dollars betting against Gamestop, White Square is the first to close its doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money-Printing Machine Breaks Down as Futures Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bitcoin-e2-80-99s-money-printing-machine-breaks-down-as-futures-fall/ar-AALjTPz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most reliable trades in cryptocurrencies has gone awry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman robbed at gunpoint while on ZOOM call with co-workers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/22/texas-woman-robbed-at-gunpoint-while-on-zoom-call-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adrian Guillen and a 15-year-old girl allegedly forced their way into the woman’s San Antonio home, where Guillen held a gun to her head and demanded her belongings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They relied on Chinese vaccines. Now they're battling outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/they-relied-on-chinese-vaccines-now-theyre-battling-outbreaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent infections in Mongolia, Bahrain, Chile and the Seychelles suggest that the Chinese vaccines they use may not be very effective at preventing the spread of the coronavirus, particularly the new variants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Rabbi: 'Exhume Christian missionary from Jewish' cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/chief-rabbi-exhume-christian-missionary-from-jewish-plot-671767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amanda Elk was a covert Christian missionary and is buried in a Jewish cemetery. Her husband refuses to rebury her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Brown 'slapped woman so hard her weave flew off'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3131732/chris-brown-under-investigation-battery-woman-alleged-slapped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAPPER Chris Brown is being investigated for battery after a woman alleged he “slapped her so hard that her weave flew off”. Police responded to the musician’s San Fernando Valley home …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE funded virus research carried out by Wuhan-linked scientist...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9712997/Google-funded-research-carried-Wuhan-linked-scientist-Peter-Daszaks-charity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech giant's charity arm, Google.org, has repeatedly provided financial backing for research and studies carried out by Peter Daszak and his New York-based EcoHealth Alliance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach town writes AMAZON TV series to lure tourists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/florida-beach-town-writes-amazon-tv-series-tourists-568ca45ec52c5c182c32f549ad91744d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Remember that longing you felt after an episode of “Sex and the City” to shop at the characters' favorite New York haunts and drink cosmopolitans at the same bars? Or that sense of wanderlust for the seaside cliffs of Ireland after watching “Game of Thrones?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Results not known until mid-July?!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm/2021/06/22/why-nycs-instant-runoff-could-take-weeks-to-decide-493332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the For the People Act heads for defeat in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US planes launch first airstrikes from foreign ship since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/06/22/u-k-u-s-f-35bs-launch-anti-isis-strikes-from-hms-queen-elizabeth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British and American F-35B Lighting II Joint Strike Fighters flew anti-ISIS strike missions from the U.K. Royal Navy aircraft carrier HMS Queen Elizabeth (R08) – a first for the U.K. in a decade, defense officials confirmed to USNI News on Tuesday. The F-35s from the embarked Royal Air Force 617 Squadron, “The Dambusters” flew combat …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Star's Suit: Pastor Slept With My Wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.wjbf.com/news/lawsuit-former-mlb-star-ben-zobrist-says-wife-had-affair-with-their-pastor-sues-him-for-millions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wjbf.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Major League Baseball star Ben Zobrist claims his wife was having an affair with their pastor, according to court documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as Seattle Pride charges white people $50 'reparations fee' to attend...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3132240/seattle-pride-event-charging-white-people-50-reparations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIDE event has been accused of “reverse racism” after charging white people up to $50 in a “reparations fee” to attend. Seattle Human Rights Commission officials dismisse…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NYC guidelines: 'Make it kinky' at summer 'sex parties'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/22/make-it-kinky-at-summer-sex-parties-nyc-health-dept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graphic memo touts glory holes, synchronized masturbation and more new health department guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why single people smell different...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210621-why-single-people-smell-different</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a wealth of psychological and biological information stored in our scent, but for some reason we choose to ignore it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>900 Secret Service employees were infected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-22208672ed5c0bb126c00e0f6e91a7d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roughly 900 U.S. Secret Service employees tested positive for the coronavirus, according to government records obtained by a government watchdog group. Secret Service records show that 881 people on the agency payroll were diagnosed with COVID-19 between March 1, 2020 and March 9, 2021, according to documents obtained by Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-the-clock officers acting as on-duty cops: Father's death in Austin shows need for restraint, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/off-the-clock-officers-acting-as-on-duty-cops-alex-gonzales-death-shows-need-for-restraint-experts-say/ar-AALgO6j?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As investigations into Alex Gonzales' Austin police shooting death continue, focus is on peril of officers taking official action while off-duty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area has become more segregated over decades, report says...</title>
      <link>https://thesantaclaramail.com/politics/bay-area-has-become-more-segregated-over-decades-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesantaclaramail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big Tech created data 'treasure trove' for police...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/how-big-tech-created-data-treasure-trove-for-police-e8a664c7814cc6dd560ba0e0c435bf90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — When U.S. law enforcement officials need to cast a wide net for information, they’re increasingly turning to the vast digital ponds of personal data created by Big Tech companies via the devices and online services that have hooked billions of people around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Britney Quietly Pushed for Years to End Her Conservatorship... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/06/22/arts/music/britney-spears-conservatorship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidential court records obtained by The Times reveal that the singer has urged changes to the arrangement that controls her life, and her father’s role in leading it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant Industry Crippled By Staffing Shortages...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/06/21/many-restaurant-job-applicants-arent-showing-up-for-interviews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While fully open, many Twin Cities bars and restaurants are having trouble filling their staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa doctor did surgery on wrong testicle, state says. He tried to fix...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article252274043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tampa urologist marked a patient’s right testicle for removal of enlarged veins and did the procedure on that testicle. But the September 2019 procedure was supposed to be done on the left testicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER vaccine linked to rare blood disease, claims Israeli study...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/pfizer-covid-19-vaccine-linked-to-rare-blood-disease-israeli-study-671694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson from the hospital stressed that this study, which was very small, should in no way deter people from vaccinating and encouraged anyone who has not yet been inoculated to get the jab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  44% Of Americans Hit 'Lowest Emotional Point' Of Lives During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pandemic-lowest-emotional-point-doctors-telehealth-mental-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While 72 percent agree mental health care is just as important as physical health care, only 18 percent are currently enrolled in therapy sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PONNURU TOP AT NATIONAL REVIEW; LOWRY STEPS DOWN  AFTER 23 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/national-review-editor-rich-lowry-e152aee4-5d06-4f58-af9a-93d826cd1833.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He'll focus on more strategic long-term initiatives as National Review's editor-in-chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL BE FIRST?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/branson-bezos-space-tourism-billionaire-battle-81f7e1e5-eb54-425f-910e-bd8e63deb398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race to make suborbital space tourism a viable business is heating up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 1 million nonbinary adults in USA, pioneering study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/more-than-1-million-nonbinary-adults-live-in-the-us-a-pioneering-study-finds/ar-AALjqdz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The final frontier: Doing laundry in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210622114952-o3bpi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROCTER GAMBLE-NASA/ (PIX):The final frontier: doing laundry in space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High stakes and high stress, forecasting tornadoes can take psychological toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/high-stakes-and-high-stress-forecasting-tornadoes-can-take-psychological-toll/ar-AALjnSW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tornadoes can have profound impacts on the meteorologists who warn for them, especially when lives are lost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Troop Deployment Along Disputed Border Worries India...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/china-s-troop-deployment-along-disputed-border-worries-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Troop Deployment Along Disputed Border Worries India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising violent crime poses new challenge for White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/559467-rising-violent-crime-poses-new-challenge-for-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will detail his administration’s crime prevention strategy on Wednesday in a high profile address that comes as a series of major cities see spikes in crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Strawberry Moon to dazzle in last full moon of year...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3125408/strawberry-supermoon-june-full-moon-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE LAST Supermoon of the year will brighten up the night sky this week. June’s full Moon is called the Strawberry Moon and it will be at its fullest on Thursday June 24. The “Super Str…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican 'unprecedented' challenge to homophobia law...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210622-vatican-in-unprecedented-challenge-to-italy-homophobia-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vatican in 'unprecedented' challenge to Italy homophobia law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doge down 70% since Musk on SNL...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/currencies/news/dogecoin-price-elon-musk-snl-cryptocurrency-crash-china-bubble-2021-6-1030542208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Buyout Just the Start as Wealthy Flee Tax Hike...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/record-buyout-just-start-wealthy-120000843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For 110 years, four generations of Mills family members earned their money by expanding their great-grandfather’s Chicago apron business into a medical supplier that ranked among the nation’s largest private companies.But soon after Democrats turned their attention toward raising taxes for the wealthy this year, the family signed a deal to cash out billions.It was no coincidence, according to people close to the more-than $30 billion transaction, which sold part of Medline Industr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China crypto crackdown wipes $300 billion off market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/china-crypto-crackdown-wipes-nearly-300-billion-off-market-btc-slides.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Friday, China has stepped up its efforts to rein in the country's cryptocurrency industry from mining bans to warnings to financial institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin below key $30,000 level...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/bitcoin-falls-again-breaking-below-key-30000-level-that-traders-say-could-lead-to-more-losses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecocide: Fast-growing movement to put environmental destruction on par with war crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/22/how-a-growing-movement-plans-to-put-ecocide-on-a-par-with-war-crimes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecocide is an umbrella term for all forms of the mass damage of ecosystems, from industrial pollution to the release of micro plastics into the oceans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No one gonna steal election from me': Echoes of 2020 in NYC mayor race...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/city-hall/story/2021/06/22/no-one-is-gonna-steal-the-election-from-me-echoes-of-2020-in-nyc-mayors-race-1386767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A racially-tinged battle has erupted over the process, with the leading candidate&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;leveling accusations of voter disenfranchisement&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;after two of his opponents formed a last-minute alliance to bolster their own campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mouse plague forces Oz prison evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mouse-plague-forces-australian-prison-evacuation/ar-AALi9Qu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mouse plague ravaging Australia's farmlands forced the evacuation of hundreds of inmates from a rural jail on Tuesday, as the rodents broke in and chewed through essential infrastructure. "The health, safety and wellbeing of staff and inmates is our number one priority, so it's important for us to act now to carry out the vital remediation work," said Peter Severin od Corrective Services NSW. Up to 420 inmates and 200 staff from the Wellington...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia struggles to quash persistent outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210622-australia-struggles-to-quash-persistent-coronavirus-outbreaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia struggles to quash persistent coronavirus outbreaks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we be friends? Dating apps say sex isn't everything...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210622034933-9gsj0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOCIALMEDIA-DATING/ (GRAPHIC, PIX):FOCUS-Can we be friends? Dating apps say sex isn't everything in a post-pandemic world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fleet off Hawaii practices sinking aircraft carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9711403/Russian-fleet-35-miles-Hawaii-practices-sinking-aircraft-carrier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Monday announced that they had carried out an exercise simulating the sinking of an aircraft carrier, off the coast of Hawaii. The war games are the largest since the Cold War.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
