<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How Yulia Navalnaya Became Russia's Real First Lady...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/07/how-yulia-navalnaya-became-russias-real-first-lady</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Kremlin tried to kill Russian opposition leader Alexey Navalny, his wife launched an epic battle to save his life—and became the face of the resistance to Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some in USA pushing for more restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/some-in-us-pushing-for-more-covid-restrictions-masking-as-delta-variant-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Delta variant of the COVID-19 virus spreads around the world and within the United States, some in the U.S. are pushing to bring back health measures from the peak of the pandemic, like mask-wearing, even for vaccinated people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gravestones At Baltimore Jewish Cemetery Defaced With Swastika Graffiti...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/07/08/repulsive-act-gravestones-at-baltimore-jewish-cemetery-defaced-with-swastika-graffiti/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen gravestones in a Jewish cemetery in Baltimore had swastikas spray-painted on them over the holiday weekend, Baltimore County Councilman Izzy Patoka said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's summer in peril as France warns on Spain, Portugal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/europe-e2-80-99s-summer-in-peril-as-france-warns-on-spain-portugal/ar-AALULws?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France is warning its citizens against vacationing in Spain and Portugal in the latest sign that the rapid spread of the delta variant of Covid-19 could wreck Europe’s summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'Free Speech' GETTR: Porn, Racism, Conspiracies -- Censorship Complaints...</title>
      <link>https://thebulwark.com/gettr-by-the-puy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Miller pitched a free-speech utopia. He got a moderation nightmare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaders making sure Games are safe --  from liability...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/olympic-leaders-are-making-sure-the-tokyo-games-are-safe-e2-80-94-from-liability/ar-AALUWAb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IOC says there is no reason for fear — but tells athletes they must sign this expanded waiver anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia left thousands of citizens stranded abroad. But  let French rugby team in...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/australia-left-thousands-of-citizens-stranded-abroad-in-the-pandemic-but-it-let-the-french-rugby-team-in/ar-AALTSQA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are ways around the country's border blockade, as those who are good at swinging a racket, wielding a bat or kicking a ball have found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS DROP, YIELDS SKID ON COMEBACK CONCERNS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/07/stock-market-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The major U.S. stock indexes fell on Thursday on concern about the global economic comeback from Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grizzly bear kills bicyclist after pulling her from tent in Montana...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wy-state-wire-mt-state-wire-id-state-wire-montana-environment-and-nature-b97b23f04ec5e7689d660a0e3a9483af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA Mont. (AP) — A grizzly bear pulled a woman from her tent in a small Montana town in the middle of the night and killed her before fellow campers could use bear spray to force the bruin out of the area, wildlife officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country music festival leads to outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article252646193.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s reportedly the largest music festival in Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's plans to raise taxes losing momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/07/biden-tax-plan-corporate-capital-gains-and-income-hike-uncertain.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six months into President Biden's tenure, Wall Street remains divided over the likelihood one of his campaign promises: higher taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNCERTAINTY GROWS IN HAITI</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-caribbean-haiti-health-coronavirus-pandemic-bd1bc9e9e87247f1267d2c97c6ce94f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — An already struggling and chaotic Haiti stumbled into an uncertain future Thursday after the assassination of President Jovenel Moïse, followed by a gunfight in which authorities said police killed four suspects, detained two others and freed three officers being held hostage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi husband won big on ALPHABET stock...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/562030-pelosi-husband-won-big-on-alphabet-stock</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s (D-Calif.) husband gained nearly $5 million on a trade of stocks in Google parent company Alphabet Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA cases rise first time in months as Delta spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/coronavirus-cases-in-california-rise-for-first-time-in-months-as-delta-variant-spreads/ar-AALUYCp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rise in coronavirus cases in California due to the Delta variant increases urgency of calls for people to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House grapples with ethics of Hunter Biden pricey paintings...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/white-house-grapples-with-ethics-of-hunter-bidens-pricey-paintings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House officials have helped craft a deal under which purchases of Hunter Biden's artwork — which could be listed at prices as high as $500,000 — will be kept confidential from even the artist himself, in an attempt to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PETTY BILLIONAIRE: Charged Secret Service $10,200 in May for agents' rooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/trump-charged-secret-service-nearly-10200-in-may-for-agents-rooms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Trump left office in January, U.S. taxpayers have paid Trump's businesses more than $50,000 for rooms used by Secret Service agents, records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine Scandal Takes Dramatic Turn With Brazil Arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/vaccine-scandal-takes-dramatic-turn-with-brazil-arrest/ar-AALTzeq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Brazil health ministry official at the center of a vaccine-buying scandal was briefly detained amid a congressional hearing, the latest chapter in the televised drama that is eroding support for President Jair Bolsonaro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO FANS AT OLYMPICS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/08/japan-olympics-committee-bans-spectators-following-state-of-emergency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's state of emergency due to rising Covid-19 cases will last from July 12 through Aug. 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORT-AU-PRINCE PARALYZED</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jovenel-moise-reportedly-assassinated-at-his-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The capital city of Port-au-Prince was paralyzed in the wake of President Jovenel Moïse’s assassination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan state of emergency 2 weeks before Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/japan-coronavirus-olympics-emergency-tokyo-f882f356-98da-4185-b9db-ea684b7bad20.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country is considering banning all spectators from the games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Bezos called for tax hikes, AMAZON lobbied to keep its bill low...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/08/bezos-tax-amazon-498722</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lobbying effort shows the complications that come with the push to raise corporate revenues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laughter can make more productive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/08/why-laughter-can-make-you-more-productive-at-work.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While making time to laugh might not have seemed like a priority this past year, experts point out that it can play an important role in boosting productivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein says he's going blind and shouldn't leave New York jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/snyde/ny-harvey-weinstein-blind-eyeglasses-trial-20210708-3ggyeubnkbed3l6wa7vrlto3qi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though Harvey Weinstein claims he’s about to go blind, Los Angeles County is promising he’ll receive “continuity of care” for his ailing eyes once transferred from New York to California to face sex crime charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware attack takes small town offline...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98shut-down-everything-e2-80-99-global-ransomware-attack-takes-a-small-maryland-town-offline/ar-AALUPkh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leonardtown, Maryland lost access to their computer systems Friday in a massive ransomware attack that has hit organizations around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: BRANSON FIRST TO SPACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/07/tech/richard-branson-space-flight-risk-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Branson will take a rocket-powered space plane on a 2,400 mile-per-hour ride to the edge of space this weekend. That's if everything goes according to plan. And there's plenty that could go wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Scammers Rip Off Billions as Pump-and-Dump Schemes Go Digital...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-07-08/crypto-scams-rug-pulls-bitcoin-hacks-billions-lost-when-shit-coins-go-to-zero</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Everybody I know has gotten rug-pulled."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan asks USA not to cause 'misunderstanding' after flag tweet removed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210708044801-bdxk2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TAIWAN-USA:Taiwan asks US not to cause 'misunderstanding' after flag tweet removed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Making Out. Everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/08/people-are-making-out-everywhere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a Thursday afternoon in June, just days before the summer solstice, the scene in Hudson River Park looked straight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Warns Of 'Increased Potential' For Nuclear Conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41421/pentagon-warns-of-an-increased-potential-for-nuclear-conflict-in-newly-disclosed-manual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The risk of regional conflicts between nuclear-armed nations is rising according to a document prepared by the Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Series of attacks target U.S. personnel in Iraq, Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/rocket-attack-iraqi-base-housing-us-forces-iraqi-military-sources-2021-07-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. diplomats and troops in Iraq and Syria were targeted in three rocket and drone attacks in the past 24 hours, U.S. and Iraq officials said on Wednesday, including at least 14 rockets hitting an Iraqi air base hosting U.S. forces, wounding two American service members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENGLAND EUPHORIA AT EURO...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/sport/football/1459832/England-Denmark-Italy-Euro-2020-final</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;England beat Denmark 2-1 in extra-time to reach their first major final since 1966.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOOKS SPIED OVER PUTIN PITCH?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9766531/Tucker-Carlson-doubles-NSA-spying-claims-says-emails-leaked-journalists.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson was in talks with people close to Vladimir Putin to arrange an interview, it has been reported, at the time the Fox News host says his emails were spied on by the NSA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNCERTAINTY GROWS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/haiti-president-jovenel-moise-assassinated-111738294.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "alleged assassins" of Haiti's President Jovenel Moise were in custody Wednesday, a government minister said, less than 24 hours after the leader of the impoverished Caribbean nation was killed in a gun attack at his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Shares Surge to Record High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-shares-surge-record-high-201056732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc. rallied to close at record high Wednesday amid optimism on its corporate growth outlook for the second half of the year.It gained 1.8% to close at $144.57, smashing its January peak as some on Wall Street forecast a stronger rally over the next six months with iPhone sales poised to climb. It rose for a seventh day, the longest winning streak since April, propelling its market value to $2.4 trillion. Its shares remain slightly below an intraday record of $145.09, also s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis won't commit to statewide review of aging Florida buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desantis-won-t-commit-to-statewide-review-of-aging-florida-buildings/ar-AALTmaG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. — Gov. Ron DeSantis said Wednesday that condominiums in Florida are “kind of a dime a dozen, particularly in southern Florida,” but he would not commit to any state action to address concerns about the aging buildings, suggesting that Champlain Towers South “had problems from the start.” Speaking after a briefing on Tropical Storm Elsa at the state Emergency Operations Center ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba tightens measures amid record spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/cuba-tightens-covid-19-measures-amid-record-spike-in-cases/ar-AALTaxD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba has tightened lockdown measures to fight the COVID-19 pandemic as infection rates and deaths have reached consecutive record highs in the past week, while a vaccination campaign with homegrown shots struggles to gain traction and the highly contagious delta variant starts to spread in the island. Public health officials have imposed new measures to limit gatherings and mobility in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patio furniture shortage tells economic tale...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-business-government-and-politics-2c2d811df7e2b07dd927778fb7944c3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COCKEYSVILLE, Maryland (AP) — People used to go to Valley View Farms to buy five tomato plants and end up with $5,000 in patio furniture. This year is different. After a record burst of sales in March, the showroom floor is almost empty of outdoor chairs, tables and chaises for people to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAITI PRESIDENT ASSASSINATED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/haiti-president-jovenel-moise-killed-b56a0f8fec0832028bdc51e8d59c6af2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — Haiti’s communications secretary says police have arrested the “presumed assassins” of President Jovenel Moïse. Frantz Exantus did not provide further details about Wednesday's slaying of Moïse and the wounding of his wife, or say how many suspects had been arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adams win in NYC latest in surge for moderate Dems...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-2020-government-and-politics-209b2feb740ea6db4d3a2277e8fb38d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The triumph of a moderate Democrat in the mayoral primary in deep blue New York City appears to accelerate a recent trend of some of the party’s most fervent voters breaking away from its most progressive candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman tore artery on roller coaster, bled to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article252633518.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ohio woman was found unresponsive after riding the roller coaster, and later died at a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut to no longer report  daily death count...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/CT-scales-back-COVID-19-death-reporting-as-16299420.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement was made through a footnote on the daily summary of cases published by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job openings stay at historic high...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/561877-job-openings-stayed-at-record-high-of-92-million-in-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Job openings held at a record high of 9.2 million in May while resignations dropped slightly from a historic peak, according to data released Wednesday by the Labor Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More media merger mania at Sun Valley?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/06/discoverys-david-zaslav-promises-more-media-merger-mania-at-sun-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen &amp; Co.’s “summer camp for billionaires” kicked off on Tuesday with David Zaslav of Discovery promising that the media merger frenzy created by the video streaming wars is far from over.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Life satisfaction record high...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/351932/americans-life-ratings-reach-record-high.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An estimated 59.2% of U.S. adults rate their lives well enough to be categorized as "thriving" exceeding the previous record-high estimate of 57.3% from 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope had severe narrowing of the colon, recovery continues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-ap-top-news-europe-health-religion-b7eca4a04faf8b30db3e889fe838de50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis’ recovery from intestinal surgery continues to be “regular and satisfactory,” the Vatican said Wednesday, as it revealed that final examinations showed he had suffered a “severe” narrowing of his colon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK SHOCK: Trump told chief of staff Hitler 'did lot of good things'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jul/06/donald-trump-hitler-michael-bender-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remark shocked John Kelly, author Michael Bender reports, detailing former president’s ‘stunning disregard for history’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up next for Elsa: The I-95 corridor...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/elsa-to-impact-northeastern-us-new-york-city-boston-washington-dc/975561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elsa made landfall in northern Florida as a tropical storm, and AccuWeather forecasters say it’s set to motor right up the Eastern Seaboard, weakening and then possibly returning to tropical storm force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/lovindubai/status/1412869916835860486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire erupts on ship, causing explosion that rocks Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dubai-explosion-0a75a2a73e728de8a9f2b975e2f3b279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — A fiery explosion erupted on a container ship anchored in Dubai at one of the world’s largest ports late Wednesday, authorities said, sending tremors across the commercial hub of the United Arab Emirates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  TESLA Asked Chinese Govt To Help Censor Critical Social Media...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/tesla-reportedly-asked-chinese-government-help-censor-social-media-posts-critical-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Film Studio Sparks Protests for Plan to Clear 200-Acre Forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/atlanta-blackhall-studio-protests-200-acre-forest-soundstages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia's Blackhall Studios, where films like "Venom" have been shot, is under fire from environmental groups over its expansion plans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO SEND TROOPS IN?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3237291/us-could-send-troops-haiti/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US could send troops into Haiti after the bloody assassination of President Jovenel Moïse who was gunned down in his home. It is feared the Caribbean nation could be plunged into chaos after th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Mexico pageant hit by mass outbreak; HALF contestants positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3236972/miss-mexico-pageant-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MISS Mexico beauty pageant has been plagued by a Covid-19 outbreak as half of the contestants test positive. Eduardo Fernandez Herrea, the health secretary for the northern Mexico border state of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN FIGHTER JETS BUZZ AMERICAN SPY PLANE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3236454/russia-deploys-fighters-jets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA deployed fighter jets after a US spy plane was spotted over the Black Sea. This comes just two weeks after a major international incident when a Russian warplane reportedly dropped bombs on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleet of UFOs spotted near ISS?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3234774/ufos-spotted-international-space-station-nasa-live-stream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN eagle-eyed space-watcher has spotted at least ten small black objects hovering right below the International Space Station.  The conspiracy theorist believes the NASA live feed captured the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Company secretly RECORDING you...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3237591/google-has-been-recording-you-how-to-delete/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF you have a Google Home or Google Nest device in your home, it’s likely the smart assistance has been recording you. Thankfully, there are three simple ways to delete your voice history …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign of LIFE found on Saturn's moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3234699/life-on-saturn-moon-enceladus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;METHANE has been detected on Saturn’s icy moon Enceladus and the levels detected are consistent with that of microbes. A new study suggests that this could be sign of life on Enceladus or jus…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 3 Nights Of Poor Sleep Causes 'Great Deterioration' In Wellbeing...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/three-nights-poor-sleep-mental-physical-wellbeing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say all it takes is three consecutive nights of sleep loss to experience a "great deterioration" in both mental and physical wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPENING NIGHT MOVIE FALLS FLAT AT CANNES...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/07/cannes-2021-the-morning-after-adam-driver-a-no-show-for-annette-press-conference-after-rocky-reception-to-opening-night-film</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Driver? He’s outta here. The star of Cannes opening night film, “Annette,” skipped town first thing this morning, French time. He didn’t stick around for the press conf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book alleges bad Guilfoyle behavior at fundraisers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/national-politics/article/Kimberly-Guilfoyle-Donald-Trump-Jr-GOP-fundraiser-16295829.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It seems Republican megadonors really did not enjoy their time with Kimberly Guilfoyle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to sue FACEBOOKGOOGLETWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/policy/trump-lawsuit-zuckerberg-dorsey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president, who is still suspended from Facebook, Youtube and Twitter, has long tried to punish social media companies that he claims silence conservatives. It hasn't gone well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>36 states, DC sue GOOGLE for alleged antitrust...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/07/36-states-dc-sue-google-for-alleged-antitrust-violations-in-its-android-app-store-498622</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit filed in California federal court is the third by state attorneys general to target the company for alleged antitrust violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Wuhan to Paris to Milan, the search for 'patient zero'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/from-wuhan-to-paris-to-milan-the-search-for-patient-zero/ar-AALRS2B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists hunt for clues to what happened in the weeks before the first known coronavirus patient, an accountant, fell ill in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Claims NSA Leaked His Emails to Reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tucker-carlson-claims-the-nsa-leaked-contents-of-his-email-to-journalists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson claimed that the NSA leaked contents of his private emails to journalists during a Wendesday morning appearance on Mornings With Maria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOOTAGE POSTED ON SOCIALS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-footage-captured-of-assailants-posing-as-dea-agents-in-assassination-of-haitian-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage circulating online Wednesday displayed the moments that led up to Haitian President Jovenel Moise's killing — and revealed the seemingly American voice of one perpetrator who led the charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shootings in LA hit troubling highs. Officials brace for violent summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-07-07/a-deadly-july-4th-weekend-in-la-reflects-surge-in-homicides-and-increase-in-shootings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The availability of guns is fueling a surge in homicides and shootings in Los Angeles, police say, and activists are bracing for tough months ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'Lambda' variant causes concern for WHO...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/vaccine-less-effective-against-new-lambda-covid-variant-concerns-who-673103</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lambda Coronavirus variant is circulating in South America at high rates, and one study showed some vaccines to be less effective against it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study suggests cell phones sharply increase tumor risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-uc-berkeley-study-draws-strong-link-between-cell-phone-use-and-cancer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New UC Berkeley research draws a strong link between cell phone radiation and tumors, particularly in the brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online 'Death Calculator' Predicts When You Will Die Within Five Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90653318/when-will-i-die-scientists-have-created-an-end-of-life-calculator-that-lets-you-plan-for-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can’t cheat death, but you might be able to predict it. This tool is based on data from the daily habits of 491,000 people over a six-year period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK developing own city...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9764995/Facebook-developing-city-near-Silicon-Valley-HQ.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg's social network, which has 2.9 billion users, is now planning to build a real life community called Willow Park on a 59-acre site in Menlo Park, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery grows over why thousands of jellyfish gathering along RI coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.centredaily.com/news/nation-world/national/article252617633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.centredaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gathering “is not fully understood.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Grizzly Bear Attacks, Kills Bicyclist Camping In Montana...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/grizzly-bear-kills-bicyclist-montana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack triggered an intensive search by wildlife officials and law enforcement officers who planned to kill the animal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheaper to buy some cars new rather used...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/used-cars-more-expensive-than-new-auto-industry-chip-shortage-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Used-car prices have soared so much in recent months that some in-demand models are thousands of dollars cheaper to buy new.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:   Kept Adolf speeches by his bed?</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/donald-trumps-ex-wife-once-said-he-kept-a-book-of-hitlers-speeches-by-his-bed-2015-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If, I had these speeches, and I am not saying that I do, I would never read them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sought Putin interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tucker-carlson-putin-interview-surveillance-c9952d7c-33d7-45e9-be68-2ba4c3817f98.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlson learned that the U.S. government was aware of his Putin outreach, sources tell Axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad Agency Discriminatory in Cutting 5 Straight, White, Male Workers, UK Ruling Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.adweek.com/agencies/agency-jwt-was-discriminatory-in-cutting-5-straight-white-male-workers-u-k-ruling-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case was filed in 2018 before JWT became part of Wunderman Thompson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Nuke Gauge In Sacramento Spurs Homeland Security Alert...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/07/07/work-truck-nuclear-gauge-stolen-thieves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Car thieves got more than they bargained for, and now federal agents are on alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIMED TO BE DEA AGENTS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/07/haitian-president-jovenel-moise-assassinated-in-his-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Jovenel Moïse of Haiti was reportedly assassinated at his home on July 7, 2021. Moïse’s wife was wounded during the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU warns Hungary to fix anti-LGBTQ law or face action...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/eu-warns-hungary-fix-anti-104951477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Commission chief Ursula von der Leyen on Wednesday warned Hungary to reverse course on its controversial LGBTQ law, as pressure mounted on Brussels to cut EU funding to Budapest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troll Army Launches 'Military Grade Attack' on Israelis...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/report-malaysian-troll-army-targeted-israelis-during-conflict-with-hamas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of cyberattacks aimed at shutting down pro-Israel social media accounts and spamming Israelis with abusive messages during the military conflict with Hamas was coordinated by a Malaysian "troll army," according to researchers who have been tracking the network's activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Flouts Airport Mask Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/photos-john-kerry-flouts-mask-mandate-at-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House climate envoy John Kerry was photographed without a face mask while walking through Boston Logan International Airport on Monday morning—the second time he has been snapped apparently flouting the mask mandate during air travel this year—according to photographs obtained by the Washington Free Beacon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courts Deal Repeated Blows to Race-Based Stimulus...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/courts-deal-repeated-blows-to-race-based-covid-stimulus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal judges in three states have put on hold a Biden administration program that forgives farm loans on the basis of race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Val Kilmer Self-Lensed Autobiographical Doc Has Been 60 Years In The Making...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/val-review-val-kilmers-extraordinary-self-lensed-autobiographical-docu-has-been-60-years-in-the-making-cannes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have seen more than my share of show business documentaries in every shape and size, every variation of truth and lies, and every name from A to Z, but I have to say I have never seen one quite l…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
