<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'ART OF THE POSSIBLE'</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/President-s-policy-approach-is-the-art-of-the-16054266.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden, answering the 29th question in his first presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of life amid concern in second year of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Signs-of-life-amid-signs-of-concern-in-the-second-16052735.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic isn't over, but its psychological grip on the United States has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Exercise? 'Smart' Gear Measures Breathing, Blood Oxygen Levels...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2021-03-smart-movements.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years there have been exciting breakthroughs in wearable technologies, like smartwatches that can monitor your breathing and blood oxygen levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL STYLE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-biden-contrast-styles-debut-221325943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sporting a red tie, Donald Trump -- combative, goading, sometimes angry and insulting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE'S NO DRAMA PRESS CONFERENCE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-2804de86cb2bd901c14c109efe024e5d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden at his first news conference Thursday left the door open to backing fundamental changes in Senate procedure to muscle key parts of his agenda like immigration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 being monitored for Ebola virus in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.kgw.com/article/news/local/oregon-monitoring-4-people-ebola/283-234f6395-b2f4-4133-9354-4a2f79a1ac26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kgw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four people recently returned from Guinea and Democratic Republic of the Congo. The Oregon Health Authority said there is low risk for people in Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen caught driving 148 mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/queens-18-year-old-issued-43-tickets-after-upstate-police-chase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspect hit speeds as high as 148 mph while fleeing from police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT BACK:  Asian American businesses defending themselves against rise in violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Asian-American-businesses-are-defending-16053182.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To San Antonio restaurateur Mike Nguyen, the threat was clear. Alongside the racist...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia bans giving water to voters in line under sweeping restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325223236-nzehq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-GEORGIA/VOTING (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Georgia bans giving water to voters in line under sweeping restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STILL NO PEAK!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325211932-tw1el</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Brazil hits record 100,000 coronavirus cases in a day, piling pressure on Bolsonaro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Octopus research yields insight into evolution of sleep...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325210100-ulrbq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-OCTOPUS/ (PIX):Octopus research yields insight into the evolution of sleep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39% have no money in stock market and over 50% say it's 'rigged'...</title>
      <link>https://grow.acorns.com/what-keeps-people-from-investing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;grow.acorns.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"People who aren't investing predominantly say it's because they don't have the money available to invest, or they don't understand stocks."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:   LA TIMES Reveals 'Catastrophic' $50 Million Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/la-times-reveals-catastrophic-50-201038446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Times and the San Diego Union-Tribune lost “north of $50 million” in revenue in 2020, company leadership told staffers at an all-hands meeting on Thursday. Chris Argentieri, the president of the two papers’ California Times parent company, described the losses as a “catastrophic drop in revenue for the company north of $50 million on top of a business that was already using cash and not producing cash,” according to a recording of the meeting obtained by TheWrap. The majority of the losses came from print advertising, though digital advertising and print circulation also sustained some losses. “What we saw in 2020, was [an] acceleration of trends that we were well aware of and have been aware of, really, for far more than a decade,” Argentieri said. “We won’t go back, particularly in print advertising, to where we were.” Also Read: Los Angeles Times Discloses $10 Million PPP Loan Screenshot from California Times meeting Like many legacy print news operations, the L.A. Times has been losing millions of dollars in recent years — a departure from many decades of profitable operation. But the losses in the COVID year of 2020 have been much more damaging and lend credence...Read original story LA Times Reveals ‘Catastrophic’ $50 Million Revenue Loss in 2020 (Exclusive) At TheWrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says China Won't Be Most Powerful on His Watch..</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biden-china-idUSKBN2BH2ZE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Joe Biden on Thursday said he would prevent China from passing the United States to become the most powerful country in the world, vowing to invest heavily to ensure America prevails in the race between the world's two largest economies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Covid Cases Rising Again, Reversing Months of Progress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-covid-cases-are-rising-again-reversing-months-of-progress/ar-BB1eXMcj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid cases in the U.S. are rising again, reversing course after months of decline and threatening another setback in the return to normality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 being monitored for Ebola virus in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/4-people-being-monitored-in-oregon-for-ebola-after-returning-to-us-from-west-africa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people are being monitored by Oregon public health officials after potentially being exposed to Ebola while on a recent visit to Guinea and the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC), according to an Oregon Health Authority news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk-Bond Sales Break Record for Busiest Quarter in History...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-junk-bond-sales-break-202540274.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. high-yield debt sales set a new quarterly record as companies take advantage of low funding costs before potential inflation causes rates to rise further.Carvana Co. launched $600 million of notes Thursday, which pushed issuance over the mark to $139.6 billion for the first quarter. That surpasses the previous high of about $139 billion set in the second quarter of 2020, when businesses rushed to raise liquidity at the start of the Covid-19 pandemic, data compiled by Bloomberg show. MGM China Holdings Ltd., Interior Logic Group -- issuing through Signal Parent Inc. -- and Dycom Industries Inc. set sizes for their deals earlier in the day to help drive volume past the record.Junk-rated companies have tapped the market relentlessly this year, extending 2020’s record pace as yields have stayed relatively low, at least for now. A $1.9 trillion debt-funded stimulus package and inflation expectations have been pushing Treasury yields higher, encouraging corporations to take advantage of borrowing conditions that are still attractive.Risky borrowers, including those such as retailer Neiman Marcus Holding Co. Inc. that only recently emerged from bankruptcy, have tapped the market, while there’s also been a pick-up in leveraged buyout funding after a swath of refinancings this year. Ingram Micro Inc. is in the market with a $2 billion offering to support its acquisition by Platinum Equity, following similar deals from Triton Water Holdings Inc. and Interior Logic Group.“It’s really hard to keep up with the issuance,” said Kevin Loome, portfolio manager of the U.S. high yield fund at T. Rowe Price. “Now the pendulum is shifting a little bit toward more aggressive behaviors.”Companies have been issuing debt at a rampant pace all year with supply setting new high marks in January, February and March. In 2020, annual sales zoomed past the previous record by over $100 billion, ending at nearly $432 billion.With the Federal Reserve and central banks globally keeping rates low, investors have sought out U.S. junk bonds for higher returns, which pushed average yields below 4% for the first time ever in February. Although they’re back up to 4.34% now, mostly thanks to the selloff in Treasuries, that’s still well below the 10-year average of 6.4%.Read more: Junk Bonds With Low Yields? Here’s Why They’re Hot: QuickTakeThat strong demand has allowed jumbo deals to easily clear syndication and pad issuance volume. American Airlines Group Inc. sold $10 billion this month as part of a joint bond-and-loan package in the biggest ever airline debt sale. T-Mobile US Inc. issued $3.8 billion to help finance the purchase of 5G airwaves, an expenditure that’s also propelled a rush of borrowing in the investment-grade market.There have also been at least two dozen inaugural junk-bond issuers to come forward this year, contributing about $13 billion of supply, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Pandemic stock darlings Crocs Inc., the colorful clog maker made cool again thanks to Justin Bieber and Bad Bunny, and cloud-based software company Twilio Inc. seized on their equity valuations to sell their first bonds.As so many companies have pulled forward financing needs, it’s hard to imagine the issuance party going on forever. A slowdown could be coming as the market itself will eventually push back, Loome said.“It’s almost like an indigestion problem, and we’re getting to that point,” he said.U.S.MGM China Holdings, Dycom Industries, Oasis Midstream and Interior Logic Group are also in the high-yield pipeline and slated to sell notes Thursday. Meanwhile four other borrowers are in the market with debt deals that may wrap up before the end of the month.London Stock Exchange Group Plc is tapping the U.S. high-grade bond market to help refinance debt it took on related to its acquisition of Refinitiv Holdings Ltd.Green bonds. Blue bonds. Brown bonds. Environmentally-conscious investors may soon be able to buy a different color of asset every day of the weekFor deal updates, click here for the New Issue MonitorFor more, click here for the Credit Daybook AmericasEuropeThere are at least 14 deals in European primary markets on Thursday, including Advanz Pharma and utilities supplier E.ON, which is issuing an euro-benchmark green bond.A “meaningful acceleration” in the EU’s vaccine program is needed to kick start corporate rating upgrades in Europe, according to Bank of America strategistsFormer British Prime Minister David Cameron is under investigation by the Office of the Register of Consultant Lobbyists for possible unregistered consultant lobbying on behalf of Greensill Capital, according to the Daily TelegraphAsiaFirms in India rush to issue bonds in rupees before the end of the fiscal year on March 31, with at least seven borrowers seeking bids for deals on Thursday.The Philippines is marketing a yen bond, in what would be the sovereign’s first Samurai issuance since August 2019China’s central bank asked lenders to keep loan growth stable and reasonable, with increased support to house leasing, innovative technology and the manufacturing sector(Updates to reflect the record was hit starting in the first paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channels Reagan?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/joe-biden-press-conference-review-donald-trump-reelection-covid-1234721790/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I got elected to solve problems,” Joe Biden said today in response to the first question at his first solo press conference as President. “All I know is I’ve been hired to solve problems, not crea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Time for Putin's most outspoken opponent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-alexei-navalny-health-worse-prison-d3d79f448100dab11271a50d29ebf73a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny has accused prison authorities of failing to provide proper treatment for his back pain and leg problems, saying in a letter posted Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Final vote results show major setback for Israel's Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-parliamentary-elections-benjamin-netanyahu-elections-4cb571e47b2f1d8f7068e4e595777645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and his right-wing allies fell short of winning a parliamentary majority in Israel’s latest election, according to a final vote count released...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers press Big Tech CEOs on speech responsibility...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-media-misinformation-social-media-censorship-159ef7e3040dd65234e4e49404bfe00c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The CEOs of tech giants Facebook, Twitter and Google faced a grilling in Congress Thursday as lawmakers tried to draw them into acknowledging their companies' roles in fueling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says migrant surge was WORSE under Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2578690/biden-first-press-conference-migrants-guns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden blamed Donald Trump and the weather for the humanitarian crisis on the Mexican border in his first press conference as President. Having avoided the press for 65 days, Biden was grilled a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Income Growth Highest Ever Last Year on Govt Bailouts!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-personal-income-growth-highest-ever-last-year-on-stimulus/ar-BB1eX9yN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans earned an additional $1.1 trillion last year -- the most ever in data dating back to 1930 -- thanks entirely to stimulus checks and other government aid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUTGERS to Require Proof of Vaccination to Enroll for Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/lifestyle-buzz/rutgers-to-require-covid-19-vaccination-for-students-this-fall/ar-BB1eXp2g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rutgers University has announced that all students planning to attend in-person classes in the fall semester must be fully vaccinated, with limited exceptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA police clash with homeless activists as encampment dismantled...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/los-angeles-police-clash-with-homeless-activists-as-encampment-is-dismantled/ar-BB1eYftZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles officials have moved to evict a large homeless encampment from a major city park, sending police in riot gear to face off with unhoused residents and protesters supporting them. Late Wednesday night, hundreds of demonstrators gathered at Echo Park Lake, a public park in central LA, to denounce the planned expulsion of hundreds of people who have been camping out there. The park has become a major battleground in the city’s worsening...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cloud of corruption': Dems want DOJ probe of Florida state Senate races...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article250181055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A week after former Republican state Sen. Frank Artiles was arrested on felony charges of offering no-party candidate Alexis “Alex” Rodriguez $50,000 to run as an independent in a South Florida state Senate race, Florida’s Democrats in Congress are asking Attorney General Merrick Garland for an expansive corruption investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Extensive damage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/live-news/live-particularly-dangerous-situation-tornado-watch-issued-in-south/921465</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports, at least three people were killed Thursday and numerous homes were reduced to rubble amid an explosive severe weather outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Can't picture' troops still being in Afghanistan -- next year...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-says-he-can-t-picture-us-troops-still-being-in-afghanistan-next-year/ar-BB1eY2vD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We will leave. The question is when we leave," said Biden, who signaled that the longest war in US history will end within the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornadoes tear through Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/0aa701-alabama-severe-weather-march-25-2021-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama severe weather live updates: Damage reported as tornadoes hit state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANDEMIC DISAPPEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/25/biden-press-conference-pandemic-478041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s first news conference on Thursday was notable for what wasn’t asked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Unloads Column in Auction for $560,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/new-york-times-sells-nft-column-in-an-auction-for-dollar560000/ar-BB1eY0VQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times sold an article tied to an NFT, or nonfungible token, for about $560,000, another sign of the red-hot market for digital collectibles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' weighing major changes to fight domestic violent extremism...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/dhs-weighing-huge-changes-fight-domestic-violent-extremism-say-officials-n1262047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden officials say DHS wants more ability to track info on domestic extremists, like the social media posts that pushed violence before the Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Snubs FOXNEWS at Press Conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-correspondent-peter-doocy-calls-out-biden-for-snubbing-him-at-presser-i-had-a-binder-full-of-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News reporterPeter Doocy called out President Joe Biden for not taking questions from him in his first White House news conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden would 'be flattered' if surge is because of him...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/25/biden-would-be-flattered-if-migrants-are-surging-because-of-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden on Thursday said he would “be flattered” if migrants were surging to the US-Mexico border because of him — but disputed that notion, insisting that migration waves gener…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SESAME STREET Adds New Muppets To Teach Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/sesame-street-black-characters-teach-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one video, Elmo wants to know why his friend Wes' skin is brown. Wes' dad, Elijah, explains melanin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach Fired After High School Football Team Uses Anti-Semitic Play Calls...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/03/25/dave-maimaron-duxbury-high-school-football-coach-fired-anti-semitic-play-calls-game-canceled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duxbury High School fired football coach Dave Maimaron Wednesday and canceled the team's next scheduled game as a result of players using anti-Semitic language on the field earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK extends emergency powers by 6 months...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-travel-boris-johnson-coronavirus-pandemic-london-f03b0a4fc53d46370d2a164ac8740866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British lawmakers agreed Thursday to prolong coronavirus emergency measures for six months, allowing the Conservative government to keep its unprecedented powers to restrict U.K....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida manatee deaths spur federal investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-manatee-deaths-spur-federal-investigation/ar-BB1eXGVf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Efforts to figure out what’s killing scores of manatees in Florida’s waters this year just got a big boost from the federal government. This week, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration declared Florida’s manatee crisis an “unusual mortality event,” triggering a federal investigation to determine the causes of a recent spike in deaths and directing more money and resources ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER begins trial on infants...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/25/covid-vaccine-pfizer-begins-trial-on-infants-and-young-kids.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is unlikely to achieve herd immunity until children can get vaccinated, public health officials and infectious disease experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan sees surge, but tighter restrictions unlikely...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-public-health-gretchen-whitmer-michigan-coronavirus-pandemic-c24a9b31bfa000c2dfa3e52236ad790d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Michigan, which not long ago had one of the country's lowest COVID-19 infection rates, is confronting an alarming spike that some experts worry could be a harbinger...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes expand meaning of 'seizure' under 4th Amendment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/supreme-court-expands-meaning-of-seizure-under-4th-amendment/ar-BB1eXtOi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court says a person who is shot by a police officer can sue under the Constitution for an 'unreasonable seizure,' even if they drove away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEPSIPEEPS announce marshmallow soda...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2021/03/25/pepsi-peeps-marshmallow-soda-giveaway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how to get some, if you dare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JC6ciW3cjN8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is holding his first press conference since his inauguration. Reporters will likely ask him about the situation at the U.S.-Mexico border, th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Iran Missile Strikes Israeli Ship...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/report-iranian-missile-strikes-israeli-ship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli-owned cargo ship was reportedly struck by an Iranian missile on Thursday in the Arabian Sea, the latest escalation in an increasingly violent tit for tat between the nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates says world should be 'back to normal by end-2022'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-billgates-idUSKBN2BH0SX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world should be back to normal by the end of 2022 thanks to COVID-19 vaccines, Bill Gates said in an interview for Polish newspaper Gazeta Wyborcza and television broadcaster TVN24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's watching Big Tech? The dangers of using algorithms to fight 'extremism'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/544411-whos-watching-big-tech-the-dangers-of-using-algorithms-to-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration and Congress should insist upon answers from social media platforms before endorsing any strategy for countering extremism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeks to Free!?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325150758-sxz7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EGYPT-SUEZCANAL/SHIP (UPDATE 8, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 8-'Beached whale' ship could block Suez Canal for weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF warns of 'diverging recoveries'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/imf-warns-diverging-recoveries-post-154011066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IMF on Thursday warned of "diverging recoveries" among global economies as they struggle with the ongoing Covid-19 pandemic, even as vaccines are approved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims fall to pre-pandemic levels...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-jobless-claims-unemployment-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-75c27fd877d7a07ba2be1bba59cd82ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The number of people seeking unemployment benefits fell sharply last week to 684,000, the fewest since the pandemic erupted a year ago and a sign that the economy is improving....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAMALA NEW BORDER ENFORCER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-immigration-coronavirus-pandemic-xavier-becerra-a54e22fc2741346c0a4d6663d9a16283</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden has tapped Vice President Kamala Harris to lead the White House effort to tackle the migration challenge at the U.S. southern border and work with Central...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Saddest March of our lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/25/brazil-coronavirus-bolsonaro-300000-deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As country reaches 300,000 fatalities, doctors condemn ‘politics of death’ but pledge to fight on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds open inquiry into Wall Street's blank check IPO frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-sec-spacs-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-regulator-opens-inquiry-into-wall-streets-blank-check-ipo-frenzy-sources-idUSKBN2BH09F?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. securities regulator has opened an inquiry into Wall Street's blank check acquisition frenzy and is seeking information on how underwriters are managing the risks involved, said four people with direct knowledge of the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym offers free memberships to people who DON'T get vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nj-gym-owner-who-defied-covid-closure-offering-free-membership-for-non-vaxxers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The co-owner of a gym in New Jersey who refused to close during the pandemic is offering free memberships to those who don't get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Europe became top regulator...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/25/big-tech-how-europe-became-the-worlds-top-regulator.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 27-member bloc has been at the forefront of tightening the rules on big technology players and it's showing no signs of changing that approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN'S GRAND VISION FOR FDR PRESIDENCY</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-historians-meeting-filibuster-0a7d726c-4041-405f-a3ac-c31550c590bc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the two-hour-plus meeting, Biden told an aide: "I could have gone another two hours."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headmaster Resigns After Telling Black Student To Get On Knees While Apologizing To White Teacher...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/03/25/headmaster-john-holian-resigns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trisha Paul said John Holian told her 11-year-old Black son to get on his knees while apologizing to his white teacher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach On High Alert As Another Long Spring Break Weekend To Start...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/24/miami-beach-high-alert-spring-break-weekend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wednesday night, South Beach was once again relatively calm. But another long spring break weekend begins Thursday, and the city is on alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Now Leading Cause Of Death In Dallas...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/24/covid-19-fatalities-leading-cause-death-dallas-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report said mortalities due to the coronavirus pandemic are now the leading cause of death among Dallas County residents, surpassing heart disease, cancer and strokes in the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo's family members were given special access to testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/andrew-cuomo-e2-80-99s-family-members-were-given-special-access-to-covid-testing-according-to-people-familiar-with-the-arrangement/ar-BB1eVyM8?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the program, a state lab prioritized the results of well-connected people who were tested, even as average New Yorkers were struggling to get tested in the early days of the pandemic because of a scarcity of resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny in great pain, fears for life...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/lawyers-putin-critic-alexey-navalny-concerned-health-prison/story?id=76673068</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Alexey Navalny concerned about Russian opposition leaders health in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Fighter Jet Accidentally Shoots Self With Gatling Gun...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/military-fighter-jet-shot-itself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident caused at least $2.5 million in damages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suit jackets oppression? Lawmakers fight own dress codes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/legislature-rhode-island-dress-codes-coronavirus-pandemic-us-news-be10024e8e9039d7d4c209c8954f5ec6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — A sneaker-clad Latino state senator in Rhode Island is objecting to his chamber’s jacket and dress shirt edict as a form of white oppression. Female lawmakers in Montana complain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Island Nation Had Zero Cases for Months. Now  Overwhelmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/this-island-nation-had-zero-covid-cases-for-months-now-it-s-overwhelmed/ar-BB1eWCMW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The emergency rooms are heaving, health care workers are falling sick, and misinformation about the coronavirus is running rife. It has all left Papua New Guinea, an island nation just north of Australia, in the grip of a deadly crisis, as a tripling of infections over the past month has swamped an already fragile health care system. The wave of cases, which the authorities have described as a “major epidemic,” most likely began in February....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weeks to Free!?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/25/giant-ship-blocking-suez-canal-could-take-days-even-weeks-to-free/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO — As tugboats strained against the weight of the mammoth ship and dredgers worked to clear sand and mud,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Demanded His Final Paycheck. Auto Shop Delivered 91,500 Greasy Pennies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/25/a-man-demanded-his-final-paycheck-the-auto-shop-delivered-91500-greasy-pennies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A OK Walker Luxury Autoworks in Peachtree City, Ga., has built Ford Mustangs for the Clint Eastwood film “Trouble With</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSCORP to Buy INVESTORS BUSINESS DAILY for $275 Million...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/news-corp-buys-investors-business-daily-ibd-1234937954/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Corp plans to acquire stock-analysis and investment research publication Investor’s Business Daily for $275 million. IBD, which launched as Investor’s Daily in 1984, is a “high margin, p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poaching, habitat loss...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-animals-elephants-forests-africa-d01e1b8a441743d0ff02d64a1e1a16f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIBREVILLE, Gabon (AP) — Increasing threats of poaching and loss of habitat have made Africa's elephant populations more endangered, according to a report released Thursday by the International...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot 'self-portrait' NFT sells for $700K...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/nft-art-sophia-robot-self-portrait-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "self-portrait" by humanoid robot Sophia, who "interpreted" a depiction of her own face, has sold at auction for over $688,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims tumble to lowest level in more than year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/25/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claims totaled 684,000 for the week ended March 20, the first time the number has been below 700,000 during the Covid-19 era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>African elephants face growing risk of extinction...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325115543-34qxu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-ENVIRONMENT/WILDLIFE (PIX):African elephants face growing risk of extinction - Red List</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day after mea culpa, Merkel gives Germans virus pep talk...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325094802-tq4s2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY-MERKEL (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-A day after mea culpa, Merkel gives Germans virus pep talk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders faced with surge of infections, vaccine issues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-europe-global-trade-united-kingdom-coronavirus-pandemic-f0f2e31638dc92b56ac5b83d26056054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — European Union leaders are meeting Thursday to look for ways of ramping up COVID-19 vaccinations across the 27-nation region amid a shortage of doses, spikes in new cases, a feud...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPEYE Was Right! Eating Spinach Does Build Bigger Muscles...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/spinach-make-muscles-stronger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team from Australia reveals nitrate in green leafy vegetables is the secret behind their amazing power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Biden setting Harris up to fail?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/973921/biden-setting-harris-fail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration is a notoriously difficult issue to tackle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break Joker Unmasked...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/unmasked-spring-break-joker-covid-020020708.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;via TikTokMIAMI—On Saturday night, shortly after Miami Beach Police used pepper balls to force out thousands of vacationers jubilantly violating a new curfew, a literal Joker remained close to the city’s signature Ocean Drive, soaking in the mayhem.As the partying hordes crossed onto Washington Avenue, the shirtless white man with slick, green-dyed hair leapt from the bed of a pick-up truck while two young women twerked triumphantly atop the hood. “Wooooo!” he bellowed. “We’re still out here! Fuck the curfew!”The man with face warpaint resembling Heath Ledger’s version of the Clown Prince of Crime had already gone viral earlier in the day with an Only In Miami moment. A video depicting him on top of a black car, ferociously waving an American flag in one hand and throwing up a wad of cash with the other, eventually made its way from social media to late-night talk show monologues this week.“COVID is over baby!” he crowed. “Fuck that shit!”‘We Will Continue to Rage’: SWAT Breaks Up Massive Crowds Defying Curfew in Miami Beach The dual spectacles perfectly captured the collision between pandemic trutherism and the unbridled hedonism of Spring Break in South Beach, where elected officials and law enforcement are struggling under a comically COVID-skeptical governor. Only a month ago, at a large, annual indoor gathering of conservatives, Gov. Ron DeSantis proclaimed Florida an "oasis of freedom in a nation that is suffering from the yoke of oppressive lockdowns.” He has notoriously refused to enact a mask mandate, and even barred localities from enforcing their own rules just so he can stick it to "the elites."Still, fear of a weeks-long superspreader event, coupled with waves of violence involving street brawls, shootings, and a deadly rape, led the Miami Beach City Commission to extend an emergency curfew enacted this past weekend until mid-April. It’s being enforced from Thursday to Sunday, the prime partying days of the week.Meanwhile, police have fulfilled Miami Beach Mayor Dan Gelber's promise to lock up visitors getting faded in public and acting a fool.Between Feb. 3 and March 21, there have been 1,050 arrests in Miami Beach’s Art Deco Historic District, where Ocean Drive is located. More than half of the busts were for minor crimes such as consuming alcohol and drugs in public, obstruction, and resisting arrest without violence, according to police.But it’s going to take a lot more than the city's annual Spring Break police state to combat the disinformation and conspiracy theories personified by the self-styled Joker. In phone interviews with The Daily Beast, he scoffed at COVID-19 restrictions, hailed DeSantis for keeping the Sunshine State open for most of the pandemic, and falsely claimed vaccinations are part of a global mind-control experiment. 1308356544 Joe Raedle/Getty “We were invited to come down here by the governor,” the wannabe influencer told The Daily Beast.“When it comes to COVID and the guidelines, it’s all a joke. It’s all propaganda,” he added, falsely, referring to a disease that has killed nearly 550,000 Americans.In a rapid-fire baritone voice, he jumped from one conspiracy theory to the next, falsely claiming the government is altering U.S. currency to create a volatile market and that Centers for Disease Control and Prevention doctors have admitted masks don’t really help stop the spread of the coronavirus—two claims that are easily debunked.“It will be a New World Order,” he said. “I want to be part of the revolution in a positive way. When I yelled ‘COVID is over,’ I was definitely serious about it.”Of course, reality begs to differ. Three Florida counties where tourists tend to congregate—including Miami-Dade, where Miami Beach is located—experienced an increase in daily positive coronavirus tests last week after several weeks of declining positivity rates, according to the Miami Herald. The jump in cases appears to be a result of rising infections among people aged 25-49, who are still not eligible to receive vaccines under the criteria approved by DeSantis. Florida is also the nation’s ground zero for most cases involving new coronavirus variants.Spreading disinformation to throngs of out-of-town visitors and online viewers will only prolong the pandemic and make it harder to convince groups already skeptical about getting vaccines, infectious-disease experts say. But they concede that aside from pushing social media platforms to crack down on users who spread false information and ramping up public-relations campaigns to combat conspiracy theories, there’s not much that can be done to stop a man dressed up as a comic book villain from wreaking epidemiological havoc.“We live in an age where everyone has opinions and those opinions can be easily shared,” Dr. Marissa Levine, an epidemiology professor at the University of South Florida, said. “It is very unfortunate, because I think we could have done better to prevent a lot of the [disinformation] if there had been more cohesive coordination between local, state, and federal governments.”DeSantis has fomented doubt by constantly undermining science-based facts, such as the reality that wearing masks reduces the risk of being infected, Levine added. “If you flout the science and the evidenced-based approaches that work, you undermine public trust,” she said. “It doesn’t do anyone well to be a political leader who talks in a divisive manner.”Spokespeople for DeSantis did not respond to email requests for comment for this story. View this post on Instagram A post shared by LACE (@straightdroplace) Dr. Georges Benjamin, executive director of the American Health Association, suggested this particular influencer’s trutherism reflected a broader mistrust of the health-care system by Americans, regardless of race, ethnicity, or socioeconomic status. “It is extraordinarily dangerous,” Benjamin told The Daily Beast. “There are a great deal of people out there who just don’t know or want to understand the safety and efficacy of the vaccines. The real tragedy is that the political leadership from the governor is encouraging people to come and party. This is foolish.”The man known as Miami Joker is the embodiment of that foolishness.His comic-book villain turn appears to have begun last year, early on during the pandemic when he split with the mother of his son, he said. At the time, he added, they were living with her grandparents in Bakersfield, California.“The stress of the pandemic gave her some reason to break ties with me,” the green-haired truther explained. “Our relationship ended and I decided to start traveling. I took on the persona of the Joker to protest COVID restrictions and lockdowns.”During an initial phone interview, he declined to reveal his true identity and said he goes by Lace, his nom de guerre on Instagram, Facebook, and TikTok. He said he currently works as a muralist, event promoter, and a video editor. He also has rapper aspirations, and his Instagram feed is populated with videos of him spitting bars and hanging out with other aspiring emcees.Spring Break Sends Late-Night Miami Club Scene Over the Edge“I am a content producer trying to be an influencer,” he said. “I am documenting Spring Break for the American people so they can see that it is open down here and there is a place for you to lose yourself.”A search of public records databases and social media accounts connected him to a 34-year-old Chicago man named Kyle Mrzena. A LinkedIn account associated with that name describes a “versatile, driven manager with a talent for hospitality management and a focus on exceptional customer service.”During a second phone conversation, the Joker confirmed he was Mrzena.Among other highlights on his career history: Mrzena said he “acted as an undercover boss to uncover stealing and schemes causing profit loss” at a Chicago-area seafood restaurant. Meanwhile, in his home city, public health officials are warning that cases involving younger adults are going up toward the danger zone that emerged during a second surge in October, the Chicago Tribune reported.“Yeah that’s me,” he said when confronted with his legal name. “I don’t give out my name to protect myself from identity theft from people I don’t know. But obviously, you can find who I am if you search the internet.”Over the past year, he’s flown seven times and observed airport and airline workers not following CDC guidelines that they enforce on passengers, like making people keep their masks on during a flight, Mrzena claimed. “It’s all wishy washy,” he said. “No one wants to put the rules in stone that they claim they are following.”His travels took him to Memphis, Tennessee, where he alleges that Black residents threatened him with violence because he was painting Black Lives Matter murals. “I was trying to create positive artwork for the community,” he said. “When I would speak to business owners and community ambassadors, they didn’t support it.”There is vanishingly little evidence of Black people in Memphis opposing the modern-day civil rights movement. In fact, locals held social justice protests in the city for a month after Minneapolis police officers killed George Floyd.Before arriving in Miami in early March, Mrzena stayed for a few days in Orlando, where he was doing promotional work for the Mexican restaurant Senor Frogs, he said. “They were not following COVID guidelines at all,” he told The Daily Beast. “It was refreshing seeing people coming in to enjoy parties, doing Conga lines, and doing shots. It gave me a sense of normalcy.” On his Instagram account, one of his posts shows him hanging out at Senor Frogs, and nine out of 10 photos in the post show him and other patrons not wearing masks.Martin Zuniga, general manager for the Orlando restaurant, said he saw the Joker come in a few times, but that the clown anti-vaxxer did not work there. “I said hi and bye to him, but I don’t know him personally,” Zuniga said. He declined to comment on the Joker’s claims about Senor Frogs not following guidelines.Other Mrzena claims, such as his having allegedly been both a firefighter and cop in Chicago from 2003 and 2008, were even more wildly implausible. A Chicago Police spokeswoman said no one under that name was in the department's personnel records as either a current or former officer. A fire department spokesperson didn't respond to a request for comment.Upon touching down in Miami Beach, Mrzena has been documenting himself turning up with Spring Breakers on Ocean Drive and surrounding streets. He had also posted a video of himself calling 911 and standing over a woman who had passed out on the street. He took the video down, but would not explain why he did so.“I think I have helped 17 individuals out here for Spring Break, including guys, not just girls,” Mrzena said, adding that he doesn’t drink alcohol or do drugs. “I have called ambulances and I helped carry some people to their rooms.”As the vaccine rollout augurs a return to something resembling sane, post-coronavirus normalcy, the coronavirus comic book villain—who said he had not previously caught COVID-19, nor been sick for more than a year—was digging in his heels.“They are guinea piggying us,” Mrzena said of vaccines known to be safe and effective, before offering what might have been the most clearly factual thing to come out of his mouth this month.“I am willing to risk my health for a good time.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Real-Life 'Killer Clown' That Terrorized America...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/the-real-life-e2-80-98killer-clown-e2-80-99-that-terrorized-america/ar-BB1eWUYA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Wayne Gacy was one of America’s most prolific—and horrific—serial killers, responsible for the deaths of 33 young men, 26 of whom he buried in the crawlspace beneath his Norwood Park Township home in Chicago. An egomaniacal sociopath who ran a remodeling business, had strong local political ties (and aspirations), and moonlit as a children’s hospital clown named Pogo, Gacy was the worst of the worst. He was also, unsurprisingly, a cunning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Uncharted waters.' Judges banning suspects from internet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uncharted-waters-judges-banning-capitol-090007991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media was key to the Capitol riot. Now courts are struggling with whether suspects should be banned from using the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA's biggest quake threat sits on overlooked part of San Andreas...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-03-la-biggest-quake-threat-overlooked.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have pinpointed a long-overlooked portion of the southern San Andreas Fault that they say could pose the most significant earthquake risk for the Greater Los Angeles area—and it's about 80 years overdue for release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 report, 4 theories: Scientists mull clues on virus origin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-geneva-coronavirus-pandemic-china-united-nations-478237854902672ac53ab6d9dbfe59ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — A team of international and Chinese scientists is poised to report on its joint search for the origins of the coronavirus that sparked a pandemic after it was first detected in China...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China squeezes Western brands as Xinjiang backlash builds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/china-squeezes-western-brands-as-xinjiang-backlash-builds/ar-BB1eWJ6m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Thursday launched a PR war on Western brands critical of rights abuses against Uyghurs and other minorities in Xinjiang, with celebrities severing ties with Nike, H&amp;M facing a boycott and Burberry dumped from a deal with a gaming giant. Gaming giant Tencent pulled a new 'skin' project linked with Burberry on avatars in the Glory of Kings game, while Swedish clothing giant H&amp;M's products vanished from shopping sites in apparent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Alarm bells'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210325085558-23h1t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL-NEIGHBORS (PIX, TV, VIDEO):'Alarm bells': Brazil's COVID-19 chaos sparks fear, countermeasures from neighbors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paparazzi Agency Files for Bankruptcy Amid Markle Legal Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/splash-news-bankruptcy-meghan-markle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Splash News &amp; Picture Agency cited the coronavirus pandemic and legal battles, including one Meghan Markle, in its filing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite Team Set to Tackle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/elite-team-set-to-tackle-massive-ship-blocking-suez-canal/ar-BB1eWK9Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elite team is tackling the monumental challenge of freeing the massive container vessel that’s blocking the Suez Canal, as a backlog of ships continued to build up for a third day in what is arguably the world’s most important waterway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaned on Hollywood endings, Americans now face messy one...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-e311cadbb86f7165e7d21498548c1768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There will come a day — maybe even a day in the next few months — when Americans wake up, emerge from their homes, cast away their masks and resume their lives. On that day, the Great Coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rejects Depp bid to appeal 'wife beater' ruling...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/johnny-depp-europe-amber-heard-courts-6802370f6e080c19cbdac50a244a5e2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — A British court on Thursday refused Johnny Depp permission to appeal a judge’s ruling that he assaulted ex-wife Amber Heard. Two Court of Appeal judges said the Hollywood star...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrissy Teigen deletes TWITTER account, citing negativity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-chrissy-teigen-john-legend-1e06fc3751d50c47a3789014169071f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Chrissy Teigen has deleted her popular Twitter account, saying the site no longer plays a positive role in her life. “For over 10 years you guys have been my world,”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuck ship in Suez Canal imperils shipping worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/egypt-coronavirus-pandemic-asia-suez-canal-africa-d8b6696716ab45794cba583ecf0e4001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISMAILIA, Egypt (AP) — A skyscraper-sized cargo ship wedged across Egypt's Suez Canal further imperiled global shipping Thursday as at least 150 other vessels needing to pass through the crucial...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
