<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>For Latinos, devastating new low in era marked by hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-05/mood-in-latino-community-in-wake-of-shootings-in-el-paso-and-gilroy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massacre of 20 people by a man who reportedly wanted to shoot "as many Mexicans as possible" marks what appears to be one of the deadliest hate crimes ever against Latinos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malibu wanted to crack down on huge mansions. But fire losses could bring even bigger homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-04/malibu-scraps-anti-mansionization-plan-woolsey-fire-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the estimated 650 homes that burned inside Malibu city limits, just 113 replacement plans have been approved, and only 12 have received permits to start construction, records show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BLAMES INTERNET, VIDEO GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/trump-video-games-toledo-shooting-8chan-el-paso-press-conference-today-a9040066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BATWOMAN' Star Hopes Groundbreaking Lesbian Superhero Appeals to Everyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ruby-rose-batwoman-1229120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CW drama features the first out lesbian superhero to have her own show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does Brady do it? Starts with science, ends with something less precise...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/How-does-Tom-Brady-do-it-It-starts-with-science-14280905.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At this point it's fair to say that Tom Brady's personal science project is going well. He just celebrated his 42nd birthday with a new two-year contract extension, and he apparently runs faster than he did at 22, his legs limber and alive, which is to say nothing of that ring-heavy throwing arm. In his 20thNFL training camp, he's so radiant with health that he looks like he's got spring water for blood and years left.  Clearly, scoffers who called Brady quackish owe him an apology. He was right, and they were wrong. He was way ahead of his time in perceiving the evils of an NFL culture based on heavy weightlifting and painkillers and ditching them for a range of unconventional training methods. His elastic, tenacious body is the empirical proof, more convincing than any lab result. Of all of Brady's time-defiant feats, maybe the most impressive one is his physical resilience over the past decade from the age of 32 onward: In nine of his past 10 seasons he has started all 16 games. The only thing that could keep him off a field was NFL Commissioner Roger Goodell's tyrannical suspension in 2016. So laugh at Brady's avocado-chia smoothies if you want, but his habits line up with everything scientists know about anti-aging and avoiding illnesses such as arthritis.  None of it, however, explains how Brady keeps his mind right. How does he fight mental burnout and keep summoning the readiness to go through another August training camp? Years of success do not breed freshness in a quarterback. They breed expertise, regulation, know how. The wild raw physical music of a Patrick Mahomes is gone and so is the humbleness that begs to learn. What's left is pure tedious process. Mental exhaustion is what really gets most veteran quarterbacks, not the physical inability to perform. They get sick of it and choose liberation. What...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet people working to kick Chicago out of Illinois...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/lifestyles/ct-life-illinois-state-secession-movement-0801-20190801-iesnu74ogvfjxfk35sn72lq7ya-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look at the movement to split Chicago from the rest of the state — why it's not as crazy as you think it is, and how the secession plan reflects Illinois' rural-urban divide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services sector slips to worst growth in 3 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bb56f8243df34f79898512711edbc8a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After El Paso, why Trump could lose Texas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/456173-texas-dem-leader-after-el-paso-why-trump-could-lose-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Director of the Texas Democrats Manny Garcia discusses the weekend's violence in El Paso and Democrats Push to turn Texas Blue in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's going on between Lindsay Lohan and crown prince of Saudi Arabia?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/05/whats-going-on-between-lindsay-lohan-and-the-crown-prince-of-saudi-arabia/?_ga=2.25761149.1513688566.1565009911-1964899810.1565009911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wild rumor hit town that Lohan and Mohammed bin Salman have gotten close, and that he’s been flying her around in his jets and showering her with presents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Patron Urinates Into Nightclub Ice Maker...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/ice-cold-relief-018452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 5--A nightclub patron relieved himself into a commercial ice maker early Saturday, according to Florida police who arrested the intoxicated urinator for disorderly conduct. Investigators say t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Californians forced to live in cars, RVs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/aug/05/california-housing-homeless-rv-cars-bay-area</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the state grapples with a housing crisis, thousands of people around the San Francisco Bay Area are sleeping in their vehicles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing number of people stop bathing; Trust bacteria to do job...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/aug/05/i-dont-smell-meet-the-people-who-have-stopped-washing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of people are eschewing soap and trusting bacteria to do the job instead – and an entire industry has sprung up to accommodate them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect storm brewing for market correction...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/02/perfect-storm-building-for-market-correction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With new risks from trade wars, stocks head into the final weeks of summer vulnerable to a pull back or even a correction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns of copycat attacks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/456168-fbi-warns-of-copycat-attacks-in-wake-of-mass-shootings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is warning of the potential for copycat attacks by domestic extremists after two mass shootings rocked the country over the weekend, including one that appeared to be motivated by animus toward Hispanics and immigrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying car gets off ground -- for minute...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/tech/japan's-nec-shows-'flying-car'-hovering-steadily-for-minute</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese electronics maker NEC Corp on Monday showed a &amp;quot;flying car,&amp;quot; a large drone-like machine with four propellers that hovered steadily for about a minute. The test flight reaching 3 meters high was held in a gigantic cage, as a safety precaution, at an NEC facility in Abiko, Chiba Prefecture.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's child modelling industry booms amid controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinas-child-modelling-industry-booms-amid-controversy-023832585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manicured children strut down the catwalk at a Beijing fashion show, one of thousands of events driving huge demand for child models in China that insiders warn leaves minors vulnerable to physical abuse, 12-hour-days and unrelenting pressure from pushy parents. &amp;quot;If children don&amp;#39;t listen to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD Shows Most Powerful Street-Legal MUSTANG; 760 Hp...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/michigan/articles/2019-08-05/ford-shows-most-powerful-street-legal-mustang-with-760-hp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 3 workers would take pay cut for unlimited time off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/one-third-of-workers-would-give-up-some-pay-for-unlimited-vacation.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in three workers would give up some of their pay in exchange for unlimited vacation, according to a survey from Allianz Global Assistance. But unlimited vacation might not be all it's cracked up to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pets now get human treatment: Hydrotherapy, acupuncture, ultrasound...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pets-america-now-human-treatment-012804102.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven-year-old Bess waits patiently to be immersed in water just a little cooler than her body temperature. To ease her joint pain, the Maine Coon, a touch overweight at 21 pounds (10 kilograms), is taken every week to the Friendship Hospital for Animals, a veterinary clinic on a pleasant Washington</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to the wild: 'Ungardening' takes root...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/back-wild-ungardening-took-root-america-012337033.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retired union organizer Anna Burger lives by a busy road just a minute's walk from a metro station in the US capital Washington, but every morning she wakes up to a birdsong symphony. Butterflies, squirrels and even the occasional deer also come to visit the tree-covered property that she has cultivated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Mass Shootings Than Number Of Days In 2019?</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/08/04/there-have-been-more-mass-shootings-than-number-of-days-in-2019-so-far-nonprofit-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nonprofit "Gun Violence Archive" has been compiling data on mass shootings, and the group found there have been more mass shootings than the number of days so far in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOURTH Texas Republican Congressman Plans to Retire in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/08/05/kenny-marchant-becomes-fourth-texas-congressman-retire-gop-exodus-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight-term Rep. Kenny Marchant, who narrowly won reelection last November, is now the fourth Texas Republican congressman to pick retirement over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW SET FOR WILD RIDE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/us-futures-amid-trade-turmoil-between-beijing-and-washington.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures fell sharply as a trade war between the world's largest economies intensified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hit list, 'rape list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/83e222c2be834d1fb3b472f9f77aabb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment? Town halls may decide next steps...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/434ead07f1d64a24aa467291602b7717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Scraps Kashmir's Long-Held Autonomy, Escalating Tensions...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pakistan-leader-warns-crisis-india-023503550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- India has revoked the special constitutional status of Kashmir in a move that’s drawn protests in parliament and risks worsening its already fraught security relationship with rival Pakistan in the disputed region.It took Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s government just a couple of hours</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes, travel chaos in Hong Kong as leader warns city on brink...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-leader-says-city-brink-protesters-unleash-043109190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong riot police clashed Monday with pro-democracy protesters for a third straight day, as the city's leader warned the global financial hub was nearing a "very dangerous situation" and a rare strike caused transport chaos. Clouds of tear gas billowed across multiple locations on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Not Even Dollars Can Save Venezuelans From Inflation Wrath...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/not-even-dollars-save-venezuelans-090000480.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Carmen Rojas used to be one of the fortunate Venezuelans who lived off a steady flow of money from relatives abroad, with $150 from her two sons providing enough cash to last a month. Today, she’s lucky if that amount gets her through the week.Luxuries like trips to restaurants and the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of 'Chernobyl on ice' as Moscow prepares floating nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/04/russia-floating-nuclear-power-station-chernobyl-on-ice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scepticism and safety concerns persist before vessel begins 4,000-mile Arctic journey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia ready to defy Putin?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/04/moscow-protests-police-crackdown-putin-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discontent and a push for political reforms have led to the largest protests in Moscow in almost a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE: UFO sightings over Cincinnati as mystery lights filmed vanishing from sight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/796262/Cincinnati-UFOs-flood-Twitter-video-lights-vanishing-across-US</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans immortal -- 20 years? </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/794107/immortality-human-futurism-transhumanist-fountain-of-youth-science</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China lets yuan break key 7 level for first time in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/05/chinese-yuan-moves-against-the-dollar-amid-us-china-trade-turmoil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese yuan crossed a closely watched 7 barrier against the dollar on Monday following a recent reescalation in the trade war between Beijing and Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protest, strike brings city to standstill...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/hong-kong-protest-and-strike-brings-city-to-a-standstill-11777774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong's leader Carrie Lam says the ongoing protests are pushing the city to the "verge of a very dangerous situation".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion: Biden offers sympathy for 'tragic events in Houston and Michigan'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/confusion-biden-offers-sympathy-for-the-tragic-events-in-houston-today-and-also-in-michigan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden misstated the locations of mass shootings in El Paso, Texas, and Dayton, Ohio, while speaking to donors at a high-dollar fundraiser in San Diego on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECOND MASS SHOOTING IN 12 HOURS...!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9650601/el-paso-walmart-shooting-dayton-ohio-mass-shootings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT least 29 people have died in two US mass shootings in just 12 hours. Twisted gunman Patrick Crusius used an AK47-type weapon to gun down parents and kids in a packed Walmart in El Paso, Texas, o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>County sheriff: 'This Anglo man came here to kill Hispanics'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article233512672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI faces skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/FBI-faces-skepticism-over-its-anti-domestic-14279800.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The FBI insists it is fully engaged in combating the threat of violence from white supremacists, but some former federal officials charge that the government is still coming up short in the face of a strain of American terrorism that now seems resurgent.  The weekend massacre at a Walmart in El Paso has focused public debate once again on the issue, after federal prosecutors called it an act of domestic terrorism.  In recent congressional testimony, senior FBI officials said they were conducting about 850 domestic terrorism investigations - a decrease from a year earlier, when there were roughly 1,000. The category covers more than just racist-motivated violence, but officials say such motivations are a large part of their domestic terrorism caseload.  Yet by other measures, the threat of white nationalist violence appears to be rising. Between October and June, there were about 100 arrests of domestic terrorism suspects - and if that trend continues, the total for 2019 would outpace the prior year, when there were about 120 such cases. The year before that, about 150 domestic terrorism suspects were arrested.  "Our focus is on the violence," FBI Director Christopher Wray insisted at a congressional hearing two weeks ago. "We, the FBI, don't investigate ideology, no matter how repugnant. . . . When it turns to violence, we're all over it."  That poses particular challenges in the world of white supremacists, who often do not belong to specific groups but find congregations of similar-minded people online, and feed each other's anger and hate.  That general lack of centralized groups or leaders among many white supremacists presents legal challenges to investigators, according to law enforcement officials. And in some cases, it shortens the time period from which a person may adopt extremist views and then...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8chan loses network provider...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/network-provider-cloudflare-drop-8chan-after-el-paso-shooting-n1039151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cloudflare CEO Matthew Prince said the anonymous internet forum's "lawlessness" caused "multiple tragic deaths."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico vows to take legal action against USA after El Paso shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/mexico-vows-take-legal-action-against-u-s-wake-deadly-n1039096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least six of the 20 dead in Saturday's attack, described by Mexico's foreign minister as an "act of barbarism," are Mexican nationals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  DRUDGE critics wrong. Publishing killer manifesto right thing to do...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/08/el-paso-shootings-free-speech-curbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People can decide for themselves what to make of hateful words, whether in Mein Kampf or a murderer’s manifesto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RHETORIC GOT TOO HOT?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/critics-say-trump-foments-white-supremacy-aide-says-dont-blame-him-in-el-paso-shooting/ar-AAFkluq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE:  Anti-immigrant rhetoric looms over El Paso massacre...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/spotlight/how-do-you-stop-these-people-trumps-anti-immigrant-rhetoric-looms-over-el-paso-massacre/ar-AAFkCYL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend of mass killing reflects how violence goes viral... </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Weekend-of-mass-killing-reflects-how-American-14279885.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In El Paso, Dayton and Chicago, a weekend of horrific gun violence seemed on the surface to be another spasm of disconnected mayhem, people taking the lives of others almost at random. But on closer examination, the attacks served to illustrate how America's lone wolf shooters aren't really alone.  Whether the proximate cause was political or personal, whether it grew out of ideological indoctrination, mental illness or some toxic blend of factors that left shooters isolated and damaged, each attack demonstrated a troubling disorder festering in modern America.  The 21-year-old man who allegedly killed 20 people doing their Saturday shopping in El Paso, Texas, appears to have taken pains to post a manifesto that leaned heavily on the virulently anti-immigrant rhetoric that inspired recent mass shootings in New Zealand and California, authorities said - though they were still working to confirm its authenticity.  The suspect, Patrick Crusius, did not appear to be part of any organized group, but the four-page screed posted minutes before he opened fire parroted the extreme white supremacist ideology known as "the great replacement" - the idea that newcomers are taking the jobs of white Christians in America and other Western nations.  The alleged killer of nine people in Dayton, Ohio, Connor Betts, was a 24-year-old Chipotle worker and community college student driven by personal grievance rather than political ideology, authorities said. Betts, who was killed by police, shot his own sister among his victims.  Showing up outside a popular bar around 1 a.m. wearing body armor and carrying a high-capacity rifle and extra magazines, the Dayton shooter instantly joined the ranks of gunmen who have learned online, in video games and in countless movies and TV shows how to escalate personal beefs into community-shattering...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA ROUNDUP...</title>
      <link>https://us11.campaign-archive.com/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=b3f55c7aa3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF ARMS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/04/the-post-says-ban-assault-weapons-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two mass shootings within 24 hours in El Paso and Dayton, days after the Garlic Festival killings. Three months after Virginia Beach, six months after Aurora, nine months after Thousand Oaks, 10 mo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters look to shut down city with strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-protesters-look-shut-211614255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Hong Kong leader Carrie Lam warned of a “very dangerous situation” as protesters moved to shut down the Asian financial hub with a general strike and commute disruptions on Monday, after a ninth straight weekend of unrest in opposition to China’s tightening grip.Demonstrators hampered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAME GAME</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec74c3c86d1f44c0afc40ba2c6c81702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After pair of mass shootings, Trump remains out of sight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d324c661d5f4a748c0990c8444efdb3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life in public-shooting-era America: 'You can't just not go'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c485bb8f6124280821ce0c9ee5adb7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian gang leader dresses as teen daughter in bizarre prison-break...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9654376/brazil-gang-leader-caught-dressed-daughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the bizarre moment a Brazilian gang leader is caught trying to escape a high-security prison – dressed as his teenage daughter. Clauvino da Silva, 42, tried to bust out of Rio’s Geric…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent mass shootings: A timeline...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/recent-mass-shootings-in-the-us-a-timeline/ar-AAFkzcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gilroy shooter left little impression on classmates, community...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/08/04/gilroy-shooter-left-little-impression-on-classmates-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santino Legan was the youngest member of a well-known Gilroy family. Why he carried out a massacre at his hometown’s famed festival remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Star Quits Hit Show, Claims Race and Sex Discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/rookie-star-quits-claims-she-faced-sexual-harassment-racial-discrimination-1229109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afton Williamson announced she would not be returning to the ABC drama starring Nathan Fillion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitch McConnell breaks shoulder...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mitch-mcconnell-fractures-shoulder-kentucky-f22f5892-8a00-4158-93f5-c1aa1c4dfc21.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The injury comes as lawmakers are urging McConnell to cancel the Senate recess to address gun control legilsation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
