<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Police arrest man on suspicion of opening fire outside Mayor's home...</title>
      <link>https://www.10news.com/news/local-news/san-diego-police-arrest-man-on-suspicion-of-opening-fire-during-protest-outside-mayor-todd-glorias-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.10news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was arrested on suspicion of opening fire as a group of people protested outside of the Mission Hills home of San Diego Mayor Todd Gloria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The cost of war: Lives, money and equipment lost...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/31/the-cost-of-the-afghanistan-war-lives-money-and-equipment-lost/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After nearly 20 years of war, the last of America’s troops made a frantic final exit out of Afghanistan on Monday, capping the US’s deadly and botched withdrawal from the strife-torn country.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious item shuts down street near Trump hotel in Vegas... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news3lv.com/news/local/suspicious-item-shuts-down-street-near-trump-hotel-mall-on-las-vegas-strip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news3lv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov Tells Evacuees Not to Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/31/hurricane-ida-louisiana-evacuees-do-not-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1m homes and businesses in Louisiana and Mississippi without power but restoration could take weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida changed death data just as surge began...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article253796898.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the delta variant spreads through Florida, data published by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention suggest this could be the most serious and deadly surge in COVID-19 infections since the beginning of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator caught admitting election 'not skewed' to woman posing as conservative...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/politics/2021/08/31/ron-johnson-says-wisconsins-presidential-results-not-skewed/5670186001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Republicans widened a review of the election, Sen. Ron Johnson said the only reason Donald Trump lost was because he didn't perform as well as other GOP candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian oil spill spreads across Mediterranean...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/31/middleeast/syria-cyprus-oil-spill-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images show the oil spill was larger than originally thought, now covering around 800 square kilometres -- an area around the same size as New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSUS:  Childless older women better off than older men...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-census-2020-7be40ba7ee3019dd0de992f6b2d7e276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older adults who are childless in the U.S. are more likely to be college educated, working and white than those with children, and their numbers are growing. About 1 in 6 adults age 55 and older are childless, and childless older women appear to be better positioned than men when it comes to health and wealth, according to a first-of-its-kind report released Tuesday by the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fellow Republican rips freshman Rep. over 'insane' threat of 'bloodshed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/08/31/fellow-republican-rips-freshman-gop-rep-madison-cawthorn-over-insane-threat-of-bloodshed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cawthorn also suggested breaking Capitol rioters out of jail and hinted at "plans" to call Trump supporters to D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI:  Man Who Killed LYFT Driver 'Inspired By Foreign Terrorist Organization'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/30/dallas-fbi-man-shot-killed-garland-lyft-driver-inspired-foreign-terrorist-organization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities on Monday identified the Lyft driver and the shooter, who was later shot and killed by Plano Police at police headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skepticism grows in El Salvador over pioneering Bitcoin gamble...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/30/scepticism-grows-in-el-salvador-over-pioneering-bitcoin-gamble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country will be first to adopt cryptocurrency as legal tender next month – but economists are sounding warnings over risks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now comes scorching heat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/31/weather/tropical-depression-ida-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The levees held. The power grid did not. Millions of Gulf Coast residents who survived Ida's devastating winds and deluge of rain face a new danger -- widespread power outages that are expected to last for weeks on end, coupled with a period of excessive heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families ask that Covid NOT be mentioned in obituaries, death notices...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/08/30/1011785899/when-covid-deaths-are-dismissed-or-stigmatized-grief-is-mixed-with-shame-and-ang</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After their brother died, two sisters faced a barrage of misinformation, pandemic denialism and blaming questions. Grief experts say that makes COVID-19 the newest kind of "disenfranchising death."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  INSTAGRAM 'incorrectly' deleted account of gold star mother who criticized president...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/instagram-deletes-account-mother-kareem-nikoui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instagram “incorrectly” and temporarily deleted an account belonging to the mother of Lance Cpl. Kareem Nikoui, one of the 13 U.S. service members killed in Afghanistan last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Post Office's Internet Cops Describe Themselves...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7enk3/us-postal-inspection-service-icop-presentation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Postal Inspection Service says its Analytics Team's mission "is to identify and develop intelligence on targets operating on the clear and dark webs."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Number Turn to Homeschooling...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/homeschooling-pandemic-critical-mass-013e4f01-c962-4e38-8cb7-8079bb597540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The educational exodus has shaken up the U.S. school system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  Shots LESS effective at preventing hospitalization...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/live-updates/coronavirus-delta-variant-latest-news/?id=79720727#79723614</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is facing a COVID-19 surge this summer as the more contagious delta variant spreads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star says sex with 13-year-old boy 'ISN'T rape'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3575170/pornhub-host-sex-13-year-old-boy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SICK interview has emerged of a Pornhub host claiming that sex with a 13-year-old boy wouldn’t be considered rape as he’d be lucky to sleep with her. Adult actress Asa Akira made the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Richards out as executive producer of 'JEOPARDY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/tv/mike-richards-out-executive-producer-jeopardy-wheel-fortune-n1278152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The producer has drawn intense scrutiny for his past comments about women, Jewish people and poor people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida restaurant says Biden supporters not welcome...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/debary-restaurant-owner-says-she-doesnt-want-business-from-biden-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of "Debary Diner" is slamming the Biden administration for its handling of the Afghanistan withdrawal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS Workers Launch Rare Campaign To Form Union...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/starbucks-buffalo-union-representation-national-labor-relations-board/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees at three stores in New York state say they face chronic understaffing and unpredictable scheduling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRET FINAL FLIGHT</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-08-30/the-war-in-afghanistan-ends-where-it-started</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A closely guarded flight out of Kabul’s international airport marked the ‘completion’ of the 20-year U.S. military presence in Afghanistan, leaving behind a country in danger and chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,461 US service members and civilians were killed; More than 20,000  injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/30/pentagon-kabul-drone-strike-islamic-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Americans, including acting ambassador, have now now left, ending near 20-year occupation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V-DAY TALIBAN</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9941147/Pentagon-says-troops-left-Afghanistan-just-midnight-Kabul.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon announced on Monday afternoon that the last American troops as the Army released an image of the last U.S. soldier to step foot off of Afghani soil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True scope of destruction becoming clearer...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/scope-hurricane-ida-destruction-becomes-clearer-in-wake-of-storm/1009805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two days after Hurricane Ida blasted the Louisiana coastline at Category 4 strength, the extent of the destruction was beginning to come into focus on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ida aftermath: No power, no flights, scant drinking water...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hurricane-ida-louisiana-new-orleans-mississippi-f6d6750d736af169ae09fa3142f92a4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Louisiana communities beginning the huge task of clearing debris and repairing the damage inflicted by Hurricane Ida are facing the dispiriting prospect of weeks without electricity in the oppressive, late-summer heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-islamic-state-group-dd43bcc58bd17668b1cf4ae79997142b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Faced with tough questions about leaving Afghanistan, including Americans left behind, President Joe Biden planned to address the nation Tuesday about the way forward after 20 years of U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary 'deplorables' speech shocked five years ago -- but some feel it was prescient...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/article/Hillary-Clinton-s-deplorables-speech-shocked-16425102.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let's start with the obvious:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rapid Progression'...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/31/caldor-fire-update-neighborhood-firefight-in-myers-flames-advancing-toward-south-lake-tahoe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of firefighters battled the advancing flames of the wind-whipped Caldor Fire in the subdivisions surrounding the Sierra Mountain community of Meyers early Tuesday, dousing spot fires in attempt to save homes from the destructive path of the raging wildfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate America launches massive lobbying blitz to kill key parts of 3.5 trillion economic plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/corporate-america-launches-massive-lobbying-blitz-to-kill-key-parts-of-democrats-e2-80-99-2435-trillion-economic-plan/ar-AANWrMg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lobbying groups representing companies such as ExxonMobil, Pfizer and Disney are aiming to ensure they do not have to foot the bill as Democrats look to overhaul federal healthcare, education and safety net programs in reconciliation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go-to Lawyer for Capitol Riot Defendants Disappears...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/31/go-to-lawyer-for-capitol-riot-defendants-disappears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious disappearance of the lawyer John Pierce began last Tuesday, prosecutors say, when he missed a hearing for one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS Release Cam Newton...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/08/31/patriots-release-cam-newton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cam Newton's time in New England is over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man attacked by gator in flooded waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/08/30/hurricane-ida-man-attacked-alligator-flooded-louisiana-waters/5660363001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was attacked by an alligator in some of Louisiana's flood waters after Hurricane Ida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Autonomous Cargo Ship Faces Test With 236-Mile Voyage...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/first-autonomous-cargo-ship-faces-200000190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In just two decades from now, half of all domestic ships plying Japan’s coastal waters may be piloting themselves. That’s the ambitious goal of the Nippon Foundation, a public-interest organization backing the country’s development of ocean-traversing autonomous ships. It aims to see crewless ships make up 50% of Japan’s local fleet by 2040.With the foundation’s backing, a group that includes Japan’s largest shipping company, Nippon Yusen KK, plans to have a container ship pilot i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom has huge cash advantage in recall vote. It may mean nothing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/31/california-governor-recall-election-gavin-newsom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor’s rivals have only a fraction of his funds, but an unorthodox voting process throws the usual rules out the window</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market's record price action mimicking late 1999...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/30/market-is-mimicking-1999-it-could-spark-10percent-to-20percent-correction-btig.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is a time to retain emotional control," BTIG’s Julian Emanuel says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor charged in opioids scheme. Then he tried to hire Hells Angel to silence witness...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-doctor-was-charged-in-an-opioids-scheme-then-he-tried-to-hire-a-hells-angel-to-silence-a-witness-feds-say/ar-AANVUg7 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror movies remain one of most profitable genres at box office...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/30/candyman-proves-how-profitable-horror-movies-are-at-the-box-office.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even during a pandemic, where blockbusters have struggled to haul in 2019-level ticket sales, the horror genre remains a profitable investment for studios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Forever war' may be 'over', but for Biden, perilous new phase looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Forever-war-may-be-over-but-for-Biden-a-16424049.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The withdrawal of the final U.S. troops from Afghanistan on Monday marks the end of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highway collapses, 2 killed, at least 10 injured...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mississippi-fe0eb84245c9f41f5b764b0be47d1602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LUCEDALE, Miss. (AP) — Two people were killed and at least 10 others were injured when their vehicles plunged into a deep hole where a highway collapsed after Hurricane Ida blew through Mississippi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honolulu to Require Shot Or Negative Test At Restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2021/08/30/live-honolulus-mayor-unveil-new-vaccine-pass-program-oahu-businesses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honolulu Mayor Rick Blangiardi announced the program Monday amid a surge in COVID cases that's threatening to overwhelm hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor's orders: 'Nature prescriptions' see rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210831100001-qppwk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growing numbers of doctors are prescribing calibrated doses of time outside to treat ailments including obesity and anxiety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Afghanistan, American general's ghostly image books place in history...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210831053345-p4thk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/USA-RUSSIA (PIX, TV):Leaving Afghanistan, U.S. general's ghostly image books place in history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scramble to get out...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210830184939-9qb1p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dry fuel and up-slope canyon winds helped fan the fire over almost 10,000 more acres since Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No stranger to plagues, Venice opens film fest with caution...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-lifestyle-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-coronavirus-pandemic-7d45247873fe55c7a9a2040dcff8f394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENICE (AP) — Visitors to Venice could be forgiven for not realizing that beyond the majesty of St. Mark’s Square and the romance of gondola rides lies a city that helped provide a baseline of what the world knows today about containing pandemics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon jab push ratchets up, dividing faith's members...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-religion-coronavirus-pandemic-f42772097cf7557086f12b549e03b18a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — After more than a year of attending church virtually, Monique Allen has struggled to explain to her asthmatic daughter why people from their congregation of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints don’t wear masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Qaeda Kingpin Resurfaces Surrounded By Taliban Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42189/al-qaeda-kingpin-resurfaces-in-afghanistan-surrounded-by-taliban-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amin Al Haq's reappearance under Taliban protection highlights concerns about the US government's remote counter-terrorism strategy going forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea becomes first country to curb GOOGLE, APPLE payment dominance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/31/south-korea-first-country-to-curb-google-apples-in-app-billing-policies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's billing system takes a 30% cut for most in-app purchases, similar to what Apple does on its App Store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Kitchens of the Rich, Things Not as They Seem...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/31/in-the-kitchens-of-the-rich-things-are-not-as-they-seem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The kitchens of the wealthy in the United States today are capable of providing a humbling experience to the uninitiated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large chunks of ash fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article253865623.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Northeastern California communities face evacuation orders amid the growing blaze and hazardous air quality levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts analyze mRNA long-term effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/israeli-experts-analyze-if-mrna-covid-vaccines-be-dangerous-in-long-term-678171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts believe there will be no long-term side effects to the mRNA vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST AMERICAN FLIGHT LEAVES KABUL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/last-plane-carrying-americans-afghanistan-departs-nation-s-longest-war-n1278012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final flight capped a bloody and chaotic end to the conflict as fighting and terrorist attacks in the evacuation scramble left hundreds dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONGEST WAR DECLARED OVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/30/afghanistan-update-last-us-troops-leave-kabul-ending-evacuation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's longest war ended when the last U.S. planes flew out of Afghanistan's capital, Kabul, before Tuesday's withdrawal deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUNDREDS LEFT BEHIND...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fewer-250-americans-remain-evacuate-203046351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States believes there are fewer than 250 Americans still in Afghanistan who are seeking to leave, a senior US official said Monday on the eve of the deadline for a full US troop withdrawal from the country.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
