<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Legendary 'TODAY' show weatherman Willard Scott dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/news/willard-scott-dead-t152927</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Willard Scott, who forecast the weather on TODAY for more than three decades and spent 65 years at NBC, died this week, TODAY's Al Roker has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clown Prince of Sun and Showers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/04/willard-scott-tvs-clown-prince-of-sun-and-showers-is-dead-at-87/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Willard Scott, the antic longtime weather forecaster on the “Today” show, whose work, by his own cheerful acknowledgment, made clear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This YOUTUBE star wants to be gov. He's best-known Dem on ballot...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/story/2021-09-03/kevin-paffrath-youtube-star-democrat-recall-candidate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Paffrath's real estate advice has attracted 1.7 million YouTube followers. The Democrat is a potential contender in the recall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Supreme Court Test On Docket...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/09/03/texas-abortion-law-scotus-roe-casey-509490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court case this week wasn’t about Roe or Casey. But that doesn’t mean we can’t learn from it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas ban may spur tele-abortions: Virtual visits, then pills...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/texas-ban-may-spur-tele-abortions-virtual-visits-then-pills/ar-AAO61AH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before the U.S. Supreme Court cleared the way to effectively end abortion in the state, a truck rolled through parts of west Texas bearing a billboard with a message in English and Spanish: “Missed period? There’s a pill for that.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banderas, Cruz poke fun at film biz excesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210904-banderas-cruz-poke-fun-at-film-biz-excesses-at-venice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banderas, Cruz poke fun at film biz excesses at Venice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE COVID CASES THAN LAST LABOR DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/03/us-heads-into-labor-day-with-covid-vaccines-but-substantially-worse-outbreak-than-last-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the outbreak is worse by most measures than 2020, the delta variant, vaccines and open schools make it hard to predict how the pandemic will unfold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  GET SET FOR MU!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-mu-variant-health-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization has dubbed Mu a "variant of interest," but the U.S. says it is not "an immediate threat" for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban Fighters Crush Women's Protest Amid Flickers of Resistance...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/04/taliban-fighters-crush-a-womens-protest-amid-flickers-of-resistance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban fighters violently suppressed a women’s protest Saturday in Kabul, while 70 miles to the north ex-Afghan army and militia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARIZONA 3,000 SICK A DAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arizona-coronavirus-pandemic-a75eab49ce1b259d2095a2a022240345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Arizona on Saturday stayed on its recent pace of reporting more than 3,000 additional COVID-19 cases per day during the current surge. The state's coronavirus dashboard reported 3,424 additional cases and 38 virus-related deaths, increasing the pandemic totals to 1,027,359 cases and 18,997 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New migrant caravan sets off for USA from southern Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/new-migrant-caravan-sets-off-us-southern-mexico-2021-09-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A migrant caravan of around 400 people, including many children, set off from the southern Mexican city of Tapachula for the United States on Saturday, just a couple of days after security and migration officials dispersed another large group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump in Talks to Sell Rights to DC Hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-trump-nears-deal-dc-hotel-5b093f84-b9b9-426b-93be-6b13435be774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historic building became a prop and symbol for both sides in the political wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent calls police after child pulled from class for not wearing mask...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/570858-new-york-parent-calls-police-after-child-pulled-from-class-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parent in New York called the police after their child was pulled from class for not wearing a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin McCarthy and Paul Ryan, divided over Trump, see different futures for Republican Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Kevin-McCarthy-and-Paul-Ryan-divided-over-Trump-16435752.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Just 80 miles separate Simi Valley from Yorba Linda, two cities on opposite...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete and Chasten Buttigieg welcome twins...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/570854-pete-and-chasten-buttigieg-welcome-twins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg announced on Twitter that he and his husband, Chasten Buttigieg, have welcomed twins into their family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Still Grieving His Son, Finds That Not Everyone Wants to Hear About It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/04/biden-still-grieving-his-son-finds-that-not-everyone-wants-to-hear-about-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In the hours before Lance Cpl. Jared Schmitz, 20, was killed by a terrorist’s bomb in Afghanistan, he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ether Briefly Tops $4,000 as Upgrade, NFT Momentum Gathers Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/ether-briefly-tops-244000-as-upgrade-nft-momentum-gathers-pace/ar-AAO5hcP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ether briefly rose above $4,000 late Friday amid a monthlong surge around a major upgrade, and as demand for non-fungible tokens continues to widen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDA: As flood alerts lit up phones, did 'warning fatigue' set in?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-environment-and-nature-floods-12d4138915cabd7a08adcb682aced7ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Cellphones across New York and New Jersey pulsed with urgent warnings of catastrophic flooding as the fury of Hurricane Ida's remnants, carrying torrential rains, approached upper New Jersey and New York City on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dread at 30,000 ft: Inside increasingly violent world of flight attendants...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/flight-attendants-unruly-passengers-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unruly passengers are seemingly on the increase in the United States, leaving some flight attendants bracing themselves for violent encounters in the sky as they try to cope with Covid-19 risks and maintain safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bette Midler calls on women to refuse sex...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/570849-bette-midler-calls-on-women-to-refuse-sex-amid-texas-abortion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Bette Midler called for women to refuse having sex amid Texas’s recently enacted abortion law, and suggested that Congress should guarantee abortion rights for women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former DISNEY Star Spilling Juicy Secrets on YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/former-disney-star-spilling-juicy-040345693.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christy Carlson Romano/YoutubeThis is a preview of our pop culture newsletter The Daily Beast’s Obsessed, written by senior entertainment reporter Kevin Fallon. To receive the full newsletter in your inbox each week, sign up for it here.This week:A full-on spiritual meltdown about Steve Martin’s TV show.An untreatable addiction to a Disney star’s YouTube channel.Diane Keaton singing “Thank U, Next” may have broke me.The new Dancing with the Stars casting definitely broke me.The only Real Housewi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map shows AMAZON rapidly growing air fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/04/map-of-amazon-air-locations-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's air cargo fleet is an increasingly critical component of its logistics machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 7,000 Steps A Day Cuts Risk Of Death By 70%...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/7000-steps-premature-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths among men fell by 58 percent however, that rate jumped to 72 percent among women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK mistakenly labels black men 'primates'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210904-facebook-mistakenly-labels-black-men-primates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook mistakenly labels black men 'primates'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildlife 'Red List' grim tally of extinction threat...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-09-wildlife-red-grim-tally-extinction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world will get an update Saturday of the Red List of Threatened Species, the authoritative catalogue of how many of the planet's animal and plant species are teetering on the brink of extinction due to human activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210904024628-nepjd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-abortion group, Texas Right to Life, was blocked from using the mechanism in the Texas law that enables private citizens to sue anyone who provides or "aids or abets" an abortion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremist was released from New Zealand jail despite fears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-zealand-islamic-state-group-3bd1cbbeec8eeda30caa0797f52ae227</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — New Zealand authorities imprisoned a man inspired by the Islamic State group for three years after catching him with a hunting knife and extremist videos — but at a certain point, despite grave fears he would attack others, they say they could do nothing more to keep him behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tahoe evacuees watching weekend with hope as fire slows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-fires-environment-and-nature-lakes-eb5907b71556a9853b38bf75fa0845b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH LAKE TAHOE, Calif. (AP) — Tens of thousands of South Lake Tahoe residents are watching hopefully this weekend for a chance to return home as firefighters make progress against a threatening California blaze that has turned their thriving resort into a ghost town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA DEATHS AT RECORD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-7ed6d05626848aca4e2827681b315770</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Funeral director Wayne Bright has seen grief piled upon grief during the latest COVID-19 surge. A woman died of the virus, and as her family was planning the funeral, her mother was also struck down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Flying Wing Aircraft Photographed Over Philippines...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42261/mystery-flying-wing-aircraft-photographed-over-the-philippines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The aircraft resembles the one seen in an image taken in California a year ago that is thought to be of the elusive RQ-180 stealth spy aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate boards, consulting, speaking fees: How generals thrive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/corporate-boards-consulting-speaking-fees-how-us-generals-thrived-after-afghanistan/ar-AAO5Iz8 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobs report adds fresh concerns over Monday's unemployment cliff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/570823-jobs-report-adds-fresh-concerns-over-mondays-unemployment-cliff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 9 million Americans are set to lose their unemployment benefits and millions more will see their weekly incomes plummet as a host of federal pandemic jobless aid programs expire next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand supermarkets take knives off shelves after 'extremist' stabbing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210904013457-5nck0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWZEALAND-ATTACK/ (PIX):New Zealand supermarkets take knives off shelves after 'extremist' stabbing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comPLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comPLANNED PARENTHOOD wins restraining order against pro-life group...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MU FOUND IN LA</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/mu-variant-los-angeles-first-cases-new-covid-1234827340/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci on Thursday said U.S. public health officials are “keeping a very close eye” on a new variant of Covid-19 that was first detected in Colombia. Known as B.1.621 or the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA DEATHS AT RECORD</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/florida-deaths-at-record-kids-hit-by-delta-wave-virus-update/ar-AAO4Pox?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida reported 2,345 additional Covid-19 deaths in its latest weekly report, the most ever in a similar period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPREADS AMONG VAXXED</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-spread-among-vaccinated-people-154240146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ubiquity of the Delta variant should be cause for some caution heading into Labor Day weekend, health officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians will pay highest gas prices ever for Labor Day weekend...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/californians-pay-highest-gas-prices-130058084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers in California are expected to pay an average of $4.39 per gallon -- the highest price ever for Labor Day weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas anti-abortion tipster site booted by web host...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-anti-abortion-tipster-booted-214357964.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A webpage seeking tips from the public to enforce Texas's severe new abortion restrictions has been told to find a new company to host its site or go offline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jolie feared for her family's safety during marriage to Pitt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/angelina-jolie-says-she-feared-220437513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Couple were married between 2014 and 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Australia Traded Away Too Much Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/09/pandemic-australia-still-liberal-democracy/619940/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How long can a democracy maintain emergency restrictions and still call itself a free country?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban declare China their closest ally...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3591782/taliban-declare-china-closest-ally-uk-refuses-recognise-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALIBAN officials have declared China as their closest ally in the international community. Militants say Beijing is “ready to invest in and reconstruct” Afghanistan and describe the nation as thei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT FOR HIS LIFE:  Oscar De La Hoya hospitalized with covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/oscar-de-la-hoya-hospitalized-after-contracting-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 48-year-old boxer said he was fully vaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Corona Tracking App!</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2021/09/03/australia-testing-orwellian-facial-recognition-coronavirus-tracking-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia is developing an app that uses facial recognition and geolocation data to track its citizens, in part of the country's draconian efforts to control coronavirus, with even the establishment leftist magazine the Atlantic branding the app "Orwellian."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Eye National Plastic Tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/democrats-eye-national-plastic-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats may impose a national plastic tax to finance their $3.5 trillion ($3,500,000,000,000) tax and spending spree, according to a leaked Senate Finance Committee document.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;The document lists a "Plastics Excise Tax" which will "impose a $.20 per pound fee on the sale of virgin plastic." Virgin plastic is a vital material in medical devices and products, clothing, toys, and thousands of household products.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
