<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Fish May Hold Secret To Limb Regeneration -- In Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-garfish-may-hold-secret-to-limb-regeneration-in-humans-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could a freshwater fish hold the answer to limb regeneration in humans? Garfish are a bit scary looking at first glance, and often compared to dinosaurs, but it appears these fish have been hiding a major genetic secret in their fins for thousands of years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai King anoints mistress as official concubine as Queen looks on...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7313849/Thai-king-anoints-army-nurse-mistress-official-concubine-ceremony-wife.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King Maha Vajiralongkorn made 34-year-old Sineenat Wongvajirapakdi his chao khun phra (royal noble consort) in a ceremony on his 67th birthday, with Queen Suthida sat next to him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magician's Stealth Shark Suit Makes Him Invisible To Great Whites...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/magician-andrew-mayne-stealth-shark-suit-makes-him-invisible-to-great-whites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too bad the cast of Jaws never got to meet Andrew Mayne and his Ghost Diver getup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plastic bottles sales banned at SFO...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/224e08cb2a724e67a1f314498faade89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers scream as bat flies through cabin at 37,000ft!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/9639870/spirit-airlines-bat-cabin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PASSENGERS travelling with Spirit Airlines were left screaming in terror after a bat flew through the cabin mid-flight. The bat was spotted 30 minutes after the flight took off according to one of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Sheeran now has highest-grossing tour of all time...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ed-sheeran-now-has-the-highest-grossing-tour-of-all-time-2019-08-02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheeran’s current tour will pass U2’s record for most lucrative of all time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas officers: Jokes during deadly arrest were 'strategy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/investigations/2019/08/02/watch-live-tony-timpas-family-talks-newly-released-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two of the officers involved in the 2016 death of Tony Timpa told Dallas Police Department leaders that they mocked the handcuffed 32-year-old while he was pinned to the ground as part of a strategy to prompt a response from him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBUS testing plane with flapping wingtips...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/airbus-albatross-wing-tips-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the dawn of aviation, birds have been an inspiration for visionaries of flight. And now, engineers are once again looking to feathered friends to inspire the next generation of aircraft wings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater photo shoots of gender activists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/indepth/can-the-millennials-save-playboy/ar-AAFeAWc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to snoop on encrypted WHATSAPP messages?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7314953/Facebook-soon-snooping-encrypted-WhatsApp-messages-plans-moderate-content.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook revealed its plans to transfer content moderation to on-device, AI-powered systems in a presentation at the firm's F8 conference in San Jose, California on May 1, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Probe Final Cost: $32,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/02/robert-muellers-russia-probe-cost-nearly-32-million-in-total-doj.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cost of the investigation has been a weapon used by both Trump and Mueller's supporters in the ongoing political fight over the Russian election meddling probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly too...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/08/01/philadelphia-declares-public-health-emergency-for-hepatitis-a-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since January, 154 people have been diagnosed with hepatitis A, compared to just 21 cases in all of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Cummings says he scared off intruder at Baltimore home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/976731f8086245229c9469407ff67cae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Arrest Gig in Anaheim Not Sold Out  -- Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/aap-rockys-post-arrest-gig-in-anaheim-is-still-on-next-weekend-and-its-not-sold-out-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A$AP is still set to headline Day 2 of The Real Street Fest at Honda Center -- as of now, tickets are still available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top State Dept official fired over 'abusive' management style...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/02/top-state-department-adviser-fired-1444894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kiron Skinner, the director of the Policy Planning Staff, was told on Thursday that she was being dismissed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs massive two-year budget deal into law...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-signs-massive-two-year-budget-deal-law-n1038786</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The signing comes after the GOP-controlled Senate voted 67-28 on Thursday and the Democratic-controlled House voted 284-149 last week to approve the two-year deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA city bars Confederate flag from Veteran's parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/confederate-group-sues-alpharetta-fly-flag-parade/ZrPi8yH5Hq0TTj8T4Js7CO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local Confederate group is suing Alpharetta because the city has barred them from flying the Confederate battle flag in the city’s parade Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA EXASPERATED...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/cnn-reporter-obama-exasperated-over-left-wing-2020-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN reporter Rebecca Buck on Friday said former President Barack Obama is “expressing exasperation” about how the Democratic Party is moving too far left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran curbs waste with 'poop patrol'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf7275bba3dd425ca79dc4f1af47202a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A$AP Rocky released...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9643933/aap-rocky-allowed-leave-sweden-after-being-released-while-awaiting-verdict-over-street-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A$AP Rocky is allowed to leave Sweden while he awaits the verdict over a street fight in Stockholm, it has been reported. His case hit international headlines after Donald Trump weighted in on the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE claims it will stop listening to users through Siri...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Apple-says-its-contractors-will-stop-listening-to-14275626.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. said on Friday that the company would stop using contractors to listen in on users through Siri to grade the voice assistant's accuracy.  An Apple whistleblower told The Guardian that contractors who were responsible for "grading" the accuracy of Siri regularly heard recordings of doctors' appointments, drug deals and couples having sex. Their job was to determine the trigger to activate Siri - if the user had actually said "Hey, Siri" or if it was something else, such as the sound of a zipper.  Apple announced that it is suspending global analysis of those voice recordings until it can thoroughly review the program. For future software updates and review, users will be able to opt-out.  "We are committed to delivering a great Siri experience while protecting user privacy," Apple said in a statement to The Guardian on Friday.  The data was used "to help Siri and dictation . . . understand you better and recognize what you say," Apple told The Guardian. But this wasn't made clear to users in Apple's terms and conditions.  "There have been countless instances of recordings featuring private discussions between doctors and patients, business deals, seemingly criminal dealings, sexual encounters and so on," the Apple whistleblower told The Guardian, highlighting the Apple Watch and HomePod smart speaker as especially prone to mistakes. "These recordings are accompanied by user data showing location, contact details, and app data."  In response, Apple said the recordings from users weren't matched up with their Apple IDs, and that the recordings only account for 1 percent of Siri activations and last for just a few seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL pre-season ratings worst start ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/nfl-preseason-big-brother-tv-ratings-thursday-aug-1-2019-1228845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other networks are largely steady Thursday, with CBS' 'Big Brother' and Fox's 'Masterchef' leading the non-sports slate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scholar bares breasts in protest at jail sentence...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-49210281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rights campaigners say Stella Nyanzi's 18-month sentence for criticising Uganda's president is "outrageous".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-homeless, non-handicap man making $1,000/weekend panhandling!</title>
      <link>https://local12.com/news/nation-world/police-chief-non-homeless-non-handicap-man-making-1000weekend-panhandling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;local12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABILENE, Texas (KTXS) &amp;mdash; An Abilene man -- who appears to be homeless and handicap -- is making a good living by panhandling on weekends, according to the police chief. Chief Stan Standridge said the man panhandles every Saturday and Sunday at the intersection of Hwy 83/84 and FM 707. He sits in a wheelchair and the police department has gotten calls from people concerned about the man thinking he's homeless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolph Lundgren-Sylvester Stallone Action Drama Series Heats Up!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/dolph-lundgren-sylvester-stallone-action-drama-series-interest-cbs-fox-nbc-netflix-apple-1202659482/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Expendables and Rocky co-stars Sylvester Stallone and Dolph Lundgren have reunited for an action drama series, which is shaping up as the first sought-after hourlong project this bro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy with 526 teeth...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/02/indian-boy-seven-found-with-526-teeth-inside-his-mouth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teeth sized between 0.1mm to 3mm discovered in lower jaw of boy during surgery in Chennai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Seeks Spy Tech for Social Media Feeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/07/fbi-wants-tech-track-social-media-criminals-and-terrorists-they-act/158843/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proposals from interested vendors are due later this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida declares public health emergency over Hepatitis A...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article233419627.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Defends Kim:  May Be UN Violation, But...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-does-backflips-defending-kim-jong-un-over-missile-launches-may-be-a-united-nations-violation-but/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump appeared to bend over backwards to defend recent North Korean missile launches, pointing to his rapport with dictator Kim Jong Un.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Extradition, Roman Polanski Will Skype Into Venice Film Festival Premiere...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/roman-polanski-will-skype-venice-film-festival-premiere-1227913</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director — wanted for a 1978 statutory rape conviction — won't attend the event in person thanks to an extradition treaty between Italy and the U.S.: "If he puts his toe one inch over the line, he'll be in jeopardy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rat-human hybrids planned by scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/795731/rat-human-hybrid-scientists-japan-experiment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Mission To 'Touch The Sun' Exceeds Expectation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/nasas-mission-to-touch-the-sun-surprises-during-first-data-delivery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Parker Solar Probe has swung past the sun twice, downloading more new science data than expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only black Republican congressman retiring...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/455872-texas-gop-lawmaker-will-hurd-retiring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Will Hurd (R-Texas), the only African American Republican in the House of Representatives, announced Thursday night that he will not seek reelection in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists Using 'Historic Preservation' Laws to Stop Restaurant Owner From Selling His Diner...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/08/01/neighborhood-activists-would-rather-preserve-toms-diner-than-let-its-owner-retire-in-peace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denver NIMBYs are using historic preservation laws to stop a restaurant owner from selling his diner to a developer so he can retire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-scooters not as green as thought...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-08-e-scooters-green-options.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People think of electric scooters, or e-scooters, as environmentally friendly ways to get around town. But a new study from North Carolina State University finds it's not that simple: shared e-scooters may be greener than most cars, but they can be less green than several other options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN! RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://granite3.com/advertise/drudge-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;granite3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFFICE DEPOT Selling Bulletproof Backpacks As Back-To-School Shopping Begins...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/08/02/north-texas-stores-selling-bullet-resistant-backpacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may see something new on the shelves this year as you shop for school supplies. Some stores in North Texas have begun selling "bullet-resistant" backpacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog loses 100 pounds!</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/5437562/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pam Heggie does not know much about Kai's past before she started fostering him except that he had been taken to the vet to be put down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER WAR: Cartel enforcers brandish anti-aircraft guns, military body armor in hostage video...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/border-war-cartel-enforcers-brandish-anti-aircraft-guns-military-body-armor-in-shock-hostage-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new video posted to YouTube is offering an eye-opening look at the folks who truly control the U.S.-Mexico border, and they’re some bad hombres. “These sicarios are with Gente Nueva, ‘The New People,’” intelligence consultant Jaeson Jones posted to Twitter. “Focus on the helmets, belt-fed weapons, 50cal. Rifle, &amp; body armor these sicarios are …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan who threw 96 mph at in-stadium radar booth signs contract with A's...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/rockies/2019/08/02/mlb-nathan-patterson-fan-96-mph-signs-athletics/1898405001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baseball fanÂ Nathan Patterson lit up the speed-pitch radar booth while taking in a game with his brother.Â Now he's on an MLB roster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers scream in terror as bat flies through plane at 37,000ft!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/9639870/spirit-airlines-bat-cabin/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PASSENGERS travelling with Spirit Airlines were left screaming in terror after a bat flew through the cabin mid-flight. The bat was spotted 30 minutes after the flight took off according to one of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen urinates on WALMART shelf days after woman sullied potatoes...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/nationworld/os-ne-2nd-walmart-urinator-20190802-uogo4be7mbhivezdystbc2rnvm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the second alleged case of inappropriate Walmart urination in recent days, a teen is accused of relieving himself on a store shelf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cherry Juice Strengthens Memory?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/tart-cherry-juice-may-strengthen-memory-cognition-in-older-adults-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study conducted at the University of Delaware has found evidence that a daily serving of cherry juice may improve cognitive functioning and performance in older adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A$AP Rocky witness withdraws claim she saw rapper hit man with bottle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/09fcf75c38d649279138e00bcaf864ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman Denies Owning Meth In Body Cavity...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/not-my-meth-504329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 1--A Louisiana woman arrested yesterday denied ownership of methamphetamine that was discovered inside a plastic baggie lodged in her vagina, according to a probable cause affidavit. Ashley Be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with assault after punching protester...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcpo.com/news/crime/man-charged-with-assault-after-punching-anti-trump-protester-outside-us-bank-arena</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcpo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Georgetown man was led away from U.S. Bank Arena to chants of “Lock him up!” after assaulting an anti-Trump protester Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: President less popular than 'Squad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/2/donald-trump-less-popular-than-all-four-squad-memb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s approval rating is lower than all four members of “The Squad” he told to “go back” to their home countries in July, according to a recent The Economist/YouGov poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80-year-old hoarder found dead, eaten by her dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/in-depth/news/local/michigan/detroit/2019/08/01/detroit-hoarder-squalor-dead-eaten-dog-sally-honeycheck/1492124001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD 157,288,000 EMPLOYED</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/record-xxxxxxxxx-employed-july</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Andrew Spear) (CNSNews.com) - The number of people employed in the United States hit a record 157,288,000 in July, according to the employment report released today by the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment inquiry has begun...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/455180-an-impeachment-inquiry-has-begun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee has filed a memorandum in federal court stating that it is engaged in such an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Area 51?</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/viral/201908011076430332-alien-hunter-discovers-chinas-own-area-51/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past few weeks, the whole world’s attention has been focused on arguably America's most mysterious military facility, Area 51, whose name frequently invoked in stories about UFO sightings, alien encounters and secret government agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulated explosion rocks Atlanta as Eastwood films 'RICHARD JEWELL'...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5atlanta.com/entertainment/simulated-explosion-rocks-downtown-as-filming-for-the-ballad-of-richard-jewell-continues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5atlanta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is no secret portions of downtown Atlanta look as they did during the 1996 Centennial Olympic Games. It is all to bring authenticity to a movie about the park bombing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll ruling arouses controversy in SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-sexdolls/sex-doll-ruling-arouses-controversy-in-south-korea-idUSKCN1US0YG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A petition calling for a ban on importing life-size sex dolls into South Korea h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron isn't same anymore about winning, NBA exec says...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/sports/lakers/story/2019-08-01/lebron-james-david-griffin-lakers-nba-title-pelicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Cleveland Cavaliers general manager David Griffin says trying to build a roster around LeBron James made him miserable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batters to shatter home run record...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/mlb/story/batters-on-pace-to-shatter-mlb-home-run-record-by-10-080119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major league batters are on pace to hit 600 more home runs than in any previous season, nearly 10% above record set two years ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses take stand in final day of A$AP Rocky assault trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/witnesses-stand-final-day-ap-rocky-assault-trial-044221287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US rapper A$AP Rocky's trial in Sweden entered its expected final day on Friday, with witnesses taking the stand in an assault case that has stirred diplomatic tensions and outraged fans. The 30-year-old rapper, whose real name is Rakim Mayers, was arrested on July 3 along with three other people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Am What I Am, Bolsonaro Says, as Unfiltered Words Rile Allies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/am-am-bolsonaro-says-unfiltered-100000819.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro has a clear message for allies and critics alike after a slew of incendiary comments: I am not going to change.Over the past few weeks Bolsonaro has threatened a journalist with jail, mocked the dead father of Brazil’s Bar Association president and canceled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test predicts Alzheimer's 20 years before onset...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/scientists-say-a-blood-test-can-detect-signs-of-alzheimers-20-years-before-onset-of-symptoms-11775417</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in the US say they hope it will become available to GPs within a few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: TESLA Autopilot steered car under semitruck at 68 mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/delray-beach/fl-ne-tesla-autopilot-lawsuit-20190801-zokyrcqxz5cn7jpjeenaoud6iy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wrongful death lawsuit against Tesla alleges its Autopilot feature failed in a crash that killed a 50-year-old man in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Layoffs pummel news outlets...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2019/08/01/large-u-s-newspapers-layoffs-2018/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mid-market newspapers were the most likely to suffer layoffs in 2018. Digital-native news outlets also faced continued layoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of bees drop dead around '5G towers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/795681/Hundreds-bees-drop-dead-5G-towers-California-Sierra-Madre-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIEL: Good for GOOGLE, Bad for America...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/peter-thiel-new-york-times-op-ed-google-china-2019-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Peter Thiel called Google 'seemingly treasonous' and called for the FBI and the CIA to investigate its workings in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT 2' To Terrorize Theaters With 'Clowns Only' Screenings...</title>
      <link>https://uproxx.com/movies/it-chapter-2-clowns-only-screenings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uproxx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alamo Drafthouse’s infamous "clowns only" screenings are back for ’It Chapter Two,’ in case you needed another excuse to not go outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan district attorney keeps digging...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/manhattan-da-subpoenas-trump-organization-over-stormy-daniels-hush-money/ar-AAFclrS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson suffers first major defeat as UK PM...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/breaking-brecon-election-result-lib-18815091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welsh Lib Dem leader Jane Dodds has beaten disgraced former Tory MP Chris Davies in the Brecon and Radnorshire byelection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I don't want to be controversial. We want no controversy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/At-Ohio-rally-Trump-escalates-attacks-on-liberal-14274817.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI - President Donald Trump on Thursday escalated his attacks on Baltimore and other diverse, liberal cities, telling a crowd in this key swing state that Democrats "deliver poverty for their constituents and privilege for themselves."  "For decades, these communities have been run exclusively by Democrat politicians, and it's been total one-party control of the inner cities," Trump said. He called federal funding sent to these areas "stolen money and it's wasted money, and it's a shame."  Trump steered clear of mentioning lawmakers by name, in a departure from his recent attacks on Rep. Elijah Cummings, D-Md., whose district includes parts of Baltimore, and four minority Democratic congresswomen, including Rep. Ilhan Omar of Minnesota.  On Thursday night, he made only a passing mention to "four left-wing extremists" who he said are now leading the Democratic Party, then told the crowd in the mostly full U.S. Bank Arena: "We can name one after another, but I won't do that, because I don't want to be controversial. We want no controversy."  The president's remarks were in line with his recent denunciations of liberal enclaves as violent, dirty and outside the mainstream. Trump offered no policy proposals for how he plans to address the problems he says plague numerous cities across the country.  Trump won Ohio by eight percentage points over former secretary of state Hillary Clinton in 2016, and the state is key to his 2020 reelection bid.  In recent days, Trump has escalated his attacks on Baltimore and Cummings, the House Oversight Committee chairman who has been spearheading investigations into Trump's administration. Trump began by tweeting Saturday that Cummings represents a "disgusting, rat and rodent infested mess" and that "No human being would want to live there." The president lashed out anew on Tuesday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Renew Amnesty for Thousands of Syrians...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/08/01/dhs-secretary-kevin-mcaleenan-renews-temporary-amnesty-for-7k-syrians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting DHS Secretary Kevin McAleenan renewed a temporary amnesty program for about 7,000 Syrian nationals on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALARM OVER NEGATIVITY</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/455849-democrats-express-alarm-over-debates-negative-tone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic lawmakers were left shaken and worried by Wednesday night’s bruising presidential debate, which left some fearing the fight will hurt the party and result in a damaged nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lock her up' chant breaks out at rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/455874-lock-her-up-chant-breaks-out-at-trump-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After President Trump mentioned 2016 rival Hillary Clinton at a reelection campaign rally in Cincinnati, the crowd broke into a chant of "lock her up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it time to take Marianne Williamson seriously?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/is-it-time-to-take-marianne-williamson-seriously-225000879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-help guru Marianne Williamson made her mark during the second round of presidential debates. Is she a legitimate candidate for the Democratic nomination?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS IN DISARRAY</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/08/01/debates-identify-plenty-of-democratic-divisions-but-not-a-consensus-favorite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The two rounds of Democratic presidential debates, rather than bringing clarity to the primary or culling the field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump escalates attacks on liberal cities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c2048ba0aa24543a943a4c134ae159a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.1 million expected at southern border this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/flood-of-illegal-migrants-to-the-border-outpaces-last-two-years-with-1-1m-expected-in-fy2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal law enforcement based on the U.S.-Mexico border are expected to encounter 1.1 million people trying to cross illegally by the end of the fiscal year Sept. 30, despite Mexico's assistance stopping migrants on their journey north.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia Says Women Can Travel Without Male Guardians...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/01/saudi-women-can-now-travel-without-a-male-guardian-reports-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okaz newspaper reports key step in dismantling strict controls over nation’s women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first human-monkey hybrid grown in lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/795498/human-monkey-hybrid-grown-in-china-organ-transplants-scientists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE's extravagant 'climate change' Camp mocked as party for 'entitled fools'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/01/googles-extravagant-climate-change-camp-mocked-as-party-for-entitled-fools/?_ga=2.145353844.1565578393.1564527849-644250957.1564527849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire creators of Google each year invite a who’s who of A-listers to the event which is meant to be a conference where influential people discuss how to make the world a better pla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea conducts third test launch in 2 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/north-korea-launches-projectile-us-officials/story?id=64715583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea has fired at least one projectile into the Sea of Japan, a U.S. official confirmed to ABC News. President Donald Trump said, "It's very much under control."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
