<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>First covid case inside Olympic Village days before Opening Ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/olympics/first-case-of-coronavirus-infection-inside-olympic-village-confirmed-six-days-before-opening-ceremony/ar-AAMfNa4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first positive coronavirus case has been confirmed inside the Olympics Village just six days before the Opening Ceremony, officials confirmed Saturday, amid growing fears about the spread of the virus during the Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Missing, Scores Dead as Raging Floods Strike Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-floods-954655c9382a9b8c12a230bdd8cd5b3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The death toll from disastrous flooding in Western Europe rose above 150 on Saturday as rescue workers toiled to clear up the devastation revealed by receding water and prevent further damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico new home for many of world's refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/final-destination-many-worlds-refugees-mexico-new-home-rcna1316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years, Mexico has gone from being a transitory country for refugees seeking to go to the U.S. or other places to becoming their final destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney tightens new lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9797037/Harsher-lockdown-looms-Sydney-111-new-cases-crackdown-rules-breakers-launched.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sydney's numbers headed in the wrong direction again with 111 new Covid cases recorded on Saturday after three weeks of lockdown. Gladys Berejiklian's response was dramatic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON asked APPLE to remove app that spots fake reviews, and APPLE agreed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/16/apple-removes-fakespot-from-app-store-after-amazon-complains.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fakespot is a well-known app used to help shoppers detect fraudulent reviews on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears 'went missing for 24 hours and was found on the street by surfers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/15612648/britney-spears-missing-24-hours-found-surfers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears went missing for 24 hours and was found by strangers on the street, one of her former best pals has revealed. The bombshell revelation was made by one of her closest confidantes in a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid 'paranoia' at Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jul/16/team-gb-have-covid-paranoia-at-olympics-admits-bianca-walkden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taekwondo fighter Bianca Walkden says Team GB athletes at the Tokyo Olympics are paranoid about catching Covid and missing competition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pingdemic:  Brit app sent half a million exposure notifications in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/pingdemic-englands-covid-app-sent-half-a-million-exposure-notifications-in-a-week/ar-AAMeOiZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Factories, pubs, restaurants and schools are reporting staff shortages after so many urged to stay home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Florida police officers charged in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/two-fla-police-officers-charged-in-new-proud-boys-indictment-in-capitol-riot/ar-AAMf8YQ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Co-defendant case grows with three arrests, including the husband of a sheriff’s deputy. Indictment spotlights law enforcement ties to accused right-wing group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Guests Find Damp Towels, Trash Piles in Worker Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/hotel-guests-find-damp-towels-trash-piles-amid-worker-shortage/ar-AAMeujG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Busted shower handles. Soiled sheets. Trash piling up in the hallways. James Androuais saw it all during the 100-plus nights he spent on the road last year, as low occupancy rates and Covid-19 precautions pushed hotel operators to let traditional service standards slide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weed supper club coming to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/07/16/luxury-micro-dosing-supper-club-coming-to-tribeca/?_ga=2.257876162.890470292.1626489596-1784295609.1625614900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is a space to celebrate the intersection of fine dining and cannabis … Medly Supper Club is designed to encourage conversation amongst our guests.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Rare monkeypox virus reported in Dallas resident...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/dallas-resident-has-texas-first-ever-case-of-monkeypox-but-it-s-not-a-reason-for-alarm/ar-AAMf1Lw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Updated at 6:30 p.m.: Revised to include comments from Dr. Philip Huang, Dallas County’s public health director. A Dallas resident has been diagnosed with monkeypox, the first case of the virus ever reported in a human in Texas, officials said Friday. But they stressed that the risk posed to the general public was very low. The patient flew to Dallas Love Field from Atlanta on July 9 after ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After conquering Earth, Bezos eyes new frontier in space...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/conquering-earth-bezos-eyes-frontier-013259124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos sets his sights on a new frontier in space in the coming days after building a gargantuan business empire which has in many ways conquered the Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney tightens new lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717005253-91n1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Sydney tightens lockdown as Australia's COVID-19 cases rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand bans public gatherings as deaths hit daily record...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210717004423-fav93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/THAILAND (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Thailand bans public gatherings as coronavirus cases and deaths hit daily records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER TRAVEL HELL:  Lawmaker quizzes airlines on delays, worker shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-6bc47103625a126d4194ae515cc6a7ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A key senator is asking six U.S. airlines to explain the high rates of delayed and canceled flights this summer, and she's asking whether there are labor shortages despite the airlines getting billions in federal aid to keep workers on the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE NIGHTMARE FOR 'DREAMERS'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-immigration-f01fc0f485a8983b5f072e7af324c43f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigrants and advocates are urging Democrats and President Joe Biden to quickly act on legislation to protect young immigrants after a federal judge in Texas on Friday ruled illegal an Obama-era program that prevents the deportation of thousands of them brought into the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Suspends Reporter Who Didn't Disclose Michael Phelps Book Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ny-times-suspends-reporter-karen-crouse-who-failed-to-disclose-her-michael-phelps-book-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her ethical conflict was revealed, Crouse was yanked off the paper’s Olympic coverage team and taken off the swimming beat, multiple sources told The Daily Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare case of monkeypox found in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/rare-case-monkeypox-found-texas-resident-who-had-traveled-internationally-n1274163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials say any threat to the general public is low — mainly because the patient and fellow airline passengers were wearing masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans 'disappointed' with lack of Biden action...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210716-cubans-disappointed-with-lack-of-biden-action</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cubans 'disappointed' with lack of Biden action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERVAIS:  'I Can't Name A Funny Woman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3297788/no-funny-women-teases-ricky-gervais/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OUTSPOKEN comic Ricky Gervais is inviting trouble in a new stand-up routine — by claiming he can’t name one funny woman. The Office creator, 60, pokes fun at sitcom star Miranda Hart and says the o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Crack Down On Brothers Behind 45 Million Illegal Robocalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/robocalls-ftc-crack-down-telemarketing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlawful telemarketing campaign included millions of calls to those on FTC's Do Not Call Registry, agency says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone rattled by swarm of over 140 earthquakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article252835908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t panic. The current alert level at the Yellowstone Volcano Observatory is green, which is normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS BACK IN VEGAS,</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-las-vegas-coronavirus-pandemic-d106142a8c0a2710a770c9687514ed7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Masks are back in Las Vegas, after regional health officials on Friday cited a rising number of coronavirus cases and advised everyone — vaccinated or not — to wear facial coverings in crowded indoor places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON PLAGUED BY WIDESPREAD VACANCIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/16/pentagon-weapons-vacancies-china-499838</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has been slow to announce nominees for the 58 Senate-confirmed positions at the Pentagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House in touch with FACEBOOK to ensure correct 'narratives'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/16/psaki-white-house-in-touch-with-facebook-to-push-true-narratives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki on Friday said the Biden administration is “in regular touch” with Facebook to ensure correct “narratives.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-foot-4 Chinese teen girl dominating on the court...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/16/7-foot-4-chinese-teenager-zhang-ziyu-is-getting-comparisons-to-yao-ming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 7-foot-4 adult is rare. A 7-foot-4 14-year-old is unheard of. Enter Zhang Ziyu, a teenage girl from East China’s Shandong Province, after a video of her notching 42 points, 25 rebounds…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film Producer Charged With Operating Escort Service...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/producer-dillon-jordan-charged-prostitution-service-1234983221/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California movie producer was arrested Thursday on a New York indictment accusing him of using a movie production company to operate an international prostitution business. Dillon Jordan, 49, of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA will spend record amount on homelessness...</title>
      <link>https://tylerpaper.com/ap/national/california-will-spend-a-record-amount-on-homelessness-heres-where-its-going/article_9f5eb79c-2313-5348-8ad9-b596ad95333f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tylerpaper.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California will spend a record $4.8 billion over two years to alleviate homelessness after legislators Thursday unanimously passed key details of a new state budget. The package, once signed into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Can't Resist Using, Abusing Facial Recognition...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/16/federal-agencies-cant-resist-using-and-abusing-facial-recognition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some agencies don't even know ways their employees are using facial recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says socials carrying misinformation 'killing people'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210716181832-3l3m5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FACEBOOK (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Biden says social media carrying COVID misinformation is 'killing people'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Destroy 1,069 Bitcoin Miners With Steamroller...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kv739/police-destroy-1069-bitcoin-miners-with-big-ass-steamroller-in-malaysia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malaysian authorities did not mess around when they broke up a cryptocurrency mining farm and charged the operators with stealing electricity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL accounts for 20% of ALL new infections...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/563402-white-house-florida-accounts-for-20-percent-of-all-new-covid-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 20 percent of the nation's new coronavirus infections are now happening in Florida alone, according to a White House official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planned 'Medicaid' Expansion Would Pay for Abortions...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/07/democrats-plan-for-new-medicaid-like-program-would-pay-for-elective-abortions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will pro-life Senator Joe Manchin insist on an alternative that doesn’t fund abortion as part of the reconciliation bill?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Just 7% of our DNA is unique to modern humans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-4edeb2256900dd182f5cac5f26b8aa66</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — What makes humans unique? Scientists have taken another step toward solving an enduring mystery with a new tool that may allow for more precise comparisons between the DNA of modern humans and that of our extinct ancestors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside LA family's $18-million fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-07-16/covid-fraud-conspiracy-los-angeles-ayvazyan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Fernando Valley family was caught creating fake businesses to get pandemic disaster loans, then spending the money on houses, gold and diamonds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS 'Evening News' head departs...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cbs-evening-news-head-departs-c99c37e9-e849-4ed9-97fd-8a7cd982b948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The program has struggled to compete for ratings with other evening news at ABC and NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK DAILY CASES TOP 50K FOR FIRST TIME SINCE JANUARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3295736/uk-covid-cases-surge-january/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAILY Covid cases have today passed the 50,000 mark for the first time since mid-January – with a further 49 deaths recorded.  Infections rose by 51,870, bringing the total to 5,332,371.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines headed to protect embassy in Haiti, but no troops, says Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2021/07/16/marines-headed-to-protect-embassy-in-haiti-but-no-troops-to-stabilize-nation-says-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden signaled he was not open to the request for U.S. troops, which comes as he is drawing down U.S. forces in Afghanistan this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three doses better than two? Debate over third covid shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3141282/spread-covid-19-variants-heightens-debate-over-extra-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Countries such as Indonesia are offering health workers who have been vaccinated with Sinovac an extra shot from Moderna</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis renews restrictions on old Latin Mass, reversing Benedict...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/pope-francis-renews-restrictions-on-old-latin-mass-reversing-benedict-xvi/ar-AAMefnd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Francis spurred anger from church traditionalists and said he was acting “in defense of the unity of the Body of Christ.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like war zone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/like-a-war-zone-stunned-germans-count-cost-of-floods/ar-AAMewQw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aware that a storm was brewing, Cornelia Schloesser quickly installed a water pump in the cellar of her bakery. "We brought a pump into the cellar, but it was useless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Videos Filter Out Of Cuba Showing Brutal Repression...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/15/cuba-brutal-repression-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New videos surfaced Thursday showing brutal repression on demonstrators by the Cuban regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW H'WOOD SHUTDOWN?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/wme-mask-mandate-covid-delta-variant-agency-1234794313/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Once again one of Hollywood top talent agencies is closing the doors because of the coronavirus. Just hours after Los Angeles County health officials unveiled a new indoor mask mandate t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The space race is back on -- but who will win?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jul/16/the-space-race-is-back-on-but-who-will-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alliances are shifting as states led by China and Russia compete with the US and tech entrepreneurs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We'll soon know more about our bodies than ever before, but are we ready?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/jul/16/well-soon-know-more-about-our-bodies-than-ever-before-but-are-we-ready</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tests could show the probability of illnesses occurring in future years, with huge moral and ethical implications, says immunology professor Daniel M Davis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos and the Gilded Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-most-random-space-crew-ever/ar-AAMcLLt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos and three strangers walk into a spacecraft...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To MAGA's hardcore supporters, rallies weren't politics. They were life...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/opinion/article/To-Trump-s-hardcore-supporters-his-rallies-16318883.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump soaked in the adoration as he commanded a rally stage inside a massive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California approves nation's first state-funded guaranteed income program...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/california-guaranteed-income-legislature-governor-gavin-newsom/10889155/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CA approved the first state-funded guaranteed income plan in the U.S. with monthly cash payments to qualified people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Guests Find Damp Towels, Trash Piles in Worker Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/hotel-guests-find-damp-towels-trash-piles-in-worker-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotel Guests Find Damp Towels, Trash Piles in Worker Shortage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOS ANGELES RE-MASKS</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/los-angeles-county-requiring-masks-indoors-for-everyone-1234794072/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is an all hands on deck moment,” said Los Angeles County Public Health Officer Dr. Muntu Davis. “We’re seeing the rates go up too high. We all need to do our part to t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Sanders, once rivals, now partners in power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-government-and-politics-election-2020-3d446757e4d708bf4193b357997efc08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Talkers both, Joe Biden and Bernie Sanders stayed for an hour in the Oval Office , just two former rivals for the White House now acting as potential partners, negotiating a compromise both could live with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Man Stomps Gator, Tries Throwing Onto Roof To 'Teach It Lesson'...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/alligator/gator-theft-bust-715248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even by Florida's loose standards, a guy swinging a stolen alligator around by its tail at 3:20 AM in an attempt at “teaching it a lesson” is truly bizarre. According to police, William Hodge, a 32-y</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland scraps all future oil exploration on climate concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.leadertelegram.com/news/world/greenland-scraps-all-future-oil-exploration-on-climate-concerns/article_ddc79fb8-0041-5f0b-bc26-3a8926387ee1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.leadertelegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenland dropped all plans for future oil exploration on environmental grounds, saying the price of extraction was “too high.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For first time in history, MLB game will be called by all women...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/16/for-the-first-time-an-mlb-game-will-be-called-by-all-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We also want to make sure that while we are getting all these firsts in there, that we also are not the last."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE: 5-Month Luxury 'World Cruise' Sells Out In Hours...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/16/miami-based-regent-2024-world-cruise-sells-out-under-three-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A five-month luxury cruise, on board a Miami-based Regent Seven Seas Cruise liner, sold out within three hours, setting a new company record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Man Stomps Gator, Tries Throwing Onto Roof Of Lounge To 'Teach It Lesson'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/16/florida-man-william-hodge-accused-throw-live-alligator-roof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Homestead man, accused of trying to throw a live alligator onto the roof of a beach side lounge, reportedly told police he was “teaching it a lesson."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waters breach Dutch defenses...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210716121625-bvnl6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-WEATHER/NETHERLANDS (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Hundreds flee as flood waters breach Dutch defences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: DOW jumps above 35,000 as retail sales top expectations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/15/stock-market-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;June retail and food service sales rose 0.6%, while economists surveyed by the Dow Jones had expected a 0.4% decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two charged in plot to attack Dem HQ in Sacramento...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/two-men-charged-plot-attack-democratic-party-headquarters-sacramento-n1274139</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities allege the two were "specific, detailed and serious" in a plan to carry out an attack on the Democratic headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiji rejects lockdown calls as infections soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210716-fiji-rejects-lockdown-calls-as-virus-cases-soar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fiji rejects lockdown calls as virus cases soar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force sending fighter jets to Pacific amid tensions with China...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/15/asia/us-air-force-f-22-guam-tinian-exercise-intl-hnk-ml/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Air Force is sending more than two dozen F-22 stealth fighters to an exercise in the western Pacific this month, an unusually large deployment of the powerful jets that analysts say sends a strong message to a possible adversary in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst Deluge In 200 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/flooding-in-germany-europe-deaths-record-rainfall-western-europe-2021-07-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entire neighborhoods lay in ruins after the worst deluge to hit the region in more than 200 years sent torrents of floodwater careening through towns and villages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive Interview Directly Implicates Donald in Tax Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/explosive-interview-directly-implicates-trump-085548973.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily BeastA witness in the New York investigation against the Trump Organization has told prosecutors that Donald Trump personally guaranteed he would cover school costs for the family members of two employees in lieu of a raise—directly implicating the former president in an ongoing criminal tax fraud case.The explosive claims come from Jennifer Weisselberg, the ex-wife of a longtime company employee, during a teleconference call with investigators on Friday, June 25,</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
