<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Taliban behead women's volleyball player; Post photos on social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3896327/taliban-behead-womens-volleyball-player-head-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONSTER Taliban militants beheaded a women’s volleyball player and posted photos of her decapitated head on social media. A coach from the all-girls team confirmed that Mahjabin Hakimi w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorsey Mocks Metaverse Plan, Says Dystopian...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/jack-dorsey-mocks-mark-zuckerbergs-metaverse-plan-saying-its-dystopian/ar-AAPJPf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg wants Facebook to be a "metaverse company," and Dorsey responded to a tweet about the metaverse being "a dystopian corporate dictatorship."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*CK Joe Biden' Chant Drowns FOX Postgame Show One Day After They Muted 'F*CK YOU A-Rod'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/fck-joe-biden-chant-drowns-fox-alcs-postgame-show-one-day-after-they-muted-fck-you-a-rod/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After muting as many “F*CK YOU A-ROD” chants as they could on Monday, shouts of “F*CK Joe Biden” drowned the ALCS postgame show on Fox Tuesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghouliani turns Abe Lincoln...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-rudy-giuliani-cosplaying-as-abe-lincoln-is-somehow-more-unsettling-than-that-sounds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani with an Abe Lincoln filter. Exactly what we've all been waiting for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If chickenpox shot lasts 20 years, why not Covid ones?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/if-the-chickenpox-vaccine-lasts-20-years-why-not-the-covid-19-shot-682382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will the third booster shot be our last? Israeli doctors explain the science behind it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Crown Jewel Of American Retail, Rampant Crime Has Taken Luster Out Of Chicago's Magnificent Mile...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/michigan-avenue-magnificent-mile-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Police have issued a formal warning after continued robberies on and around the city’s Magnificent Mile, at a time when stores continue to leave while others fight to stay in business after big pandemic hits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blasts closure of restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article255144327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We refuse to become the vaccination police.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW MANY WILL BE REQUIRED?</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/how-many-boosters-will-we-need-israel-says-too-soon-to-know-1.1653686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Israel told a panel of U.S. vaccine experts weighing a potential Covid-19 booster dose from Pfizer Inc. and BioNTech SE on Friday that it’s unclear how long the benefit of such a shot would last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarasota Named Best Place to Retire...</title>
      <link>https://money.usnews.com/money/retirement/articles/what-makes-sarasota-the-best-place-to-retire </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's why this Florida beach retirement spot is No. 1 for the second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS THREATENS TO BACK RESTRICTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/uk-news/3896631/four-key-restrictions-boris-johnson-could-bring-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAJID Javid will tonight dangle the prospect of a return to restrictions unless Brits get their boosters to tackle the Covid surge. Mandatory masks, working from home and vaccine passports are all …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Accused of Crimes Against Humanity in Covid Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bolsonaro-accused-of-crimes-against-humanity-in-covid-probe/ar-AAPKBqp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil senators said Jair Bolsonaro should be charged for nine crimes, including charlatanism, malfeasance and crimes against humanity in their conclusion of a probe into the government’s handling of the pandemic that’s unlikely to have any short-term impact on the president’s political fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toothpaste Will Fly as GOOGLE Drones Test Delivery in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/toothpaste-will-fly-as-alphabet-s-drones-test-delivery-in-texas/ar-AAPKR69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Alphabet Inc.’s drone-delivery operation is expanding to a Walgreens in suburban Dallas where it will make airborne deliveries of toothpaste and other goods to residents of nearby towns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Draws Late-Night Comedy Crowd With 'GUTFELD!'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/fox-news-gutfeld-greg-late-night-comedy-1235093369/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News has drawn a big crowd for years with shows that skewer liberals and the perceived excesses of the left. Now the cabler is seeing strong returns for its experiment with Greg Gutfeld as host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's still very, very good to be DURAN DURAN...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/still-very-very-good-duran-120037916.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Set to release their 15th album, Duran Duran's Simon Le Bon and John Taylor talk recovering from COVID, their favorite bad review and plastic trousers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX workers stage walk-out over Chappelle trans comments...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211020105832-wwsdb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public figures, trans activists and supporters join 'Team Trans' Netflix employees in protest against "harmful content" after release of comedy special said to ridicule trans experiences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How controversy put streamer on blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/How-the-controversy-over-Dave-Chappelle-s-special-16548080.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Netflix endures another week of the maelstrom created by Dave Chappelle's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Isn't Hitting the Panic Button...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/10/progressives-primary-kyrsten-sinema-arizona/620422/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator from Arizona doesn’t seem rattled by progressives’ threats to primary her—and it’s not clear she should be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary Cancer Treatment 'Wakes Up' Immune System To Destroy Tumors.</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cancer-treatment-destroy-tumors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breakthrough cancer treatment "jump starts" a patient's natural defenses by merging chemotherapy, immunotherapy, and tumor-fighting techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY Loses Bid for Secrecy in Dr. Luke-Kesha Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/music-news/kesha-dr-luke-lawsuit-sony-secrecy-1235034004/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the 7-year-old libel suit over a rape accusation nears trial, a New York judge is opening the books on pop music dealmaking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BITCOIN NEW RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/bitcoin-jumps-to-new-record-high-above-65000-after-landmark-us-etf-launch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin notched a fresh all-time high on Wednesday as investors cheered the successful launch of the first U.S. bitcoin futures exchange-traded fund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX could make Musk first trillionaire, says MORGAN STANLEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/oct/20/spacex-could-make-elon-musk-world-first-trillionaire-says-morgan-stanley</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of world’s richest person’s fortune so far has come from electric car company Tesla</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walkouts and strikes hit hospitals in pandemic hot spots...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/20/hospitals-labor-shortage-covid-delta-516303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been at least 30 strikes of health care workers so far this year, according to a tracker from Cornell University’s School of Industrial and Labor Relations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WANTED: 80,000 truck drivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/19/economy/trucking-short-drivers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trucking industry is short 80,000 drivers, a record high, Chris Spear, President and CEO of the American Trucking Associations, tells CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic ordering making things worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/retailers-manufacturers-over-ordering-amid-supply-chain-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retailers and manufacturers are overordering or placing orders too early as they panic over the supply chain crisis, and that's not helping, experts told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Shortages Next Supply-Chain Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/people-hoarding-food-shortages-next-120000053.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In Denver, public-school children are facing shortages of milk. In Chicago, a local market is running short of canned goods and boxed items.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureA $30 Billion Fortune Is Hiding in China’s Silicon ValleyThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightHate-Speech Case Forces Japan to Confront Workplace RacismBut there’s plenty of food. T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the new NFL, teams scoring on two-minute drives like never before...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/in-the-new-nfl-teams-are-scoring-on-two-minute-drives-like-never-before/ar-AAPKcSD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As NFL games wind down, the improbable has become the expected, and offenses are lighting up the scoreboard with unprecedented frequency,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Predicts Difficult Winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-k-s-boris-johnson-predicts-difficult-winter-as-covid-deaths-rise/ar-AAPHweN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson predicted a difficult winter due to coronavirus and other pressures on the National Health Service, as his government acknowledged worsening data in its pandemic response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IN-N-OUT BURGER clashes with San Fran over shot mandate: 'We refuse to become vaccination police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-n-out-burger-clashes-with-san-francisco-over-vaccine-mandate-e2-80-98we-refuse-to-become-the-vaccination-police-e2-80-99/ar-AAPKeoU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As San Francisco requires proof of vaccination to dine indoors, In-N-Out Burger is refusing to become the "vaccination police."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier with 'Hitler mustache' thrown out of military after Capitol riot charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Soldier-with-Hitler-mustache-thrown-out-of-16547809.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Army reservist charged in the Justice Department's sweeping investigation of the U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Tudor Jones says inflation worse than feared; Biggest threat to society...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/paul-tudor-jones-says-inflation-could-be-worse-than-feared-biggest-threat-to-markets-and-society.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire hedge fund manager Paul Tudor Jones believes that inflation is here to stay, posing a major threat to the markets and the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record out-of-stocks, shipping delays expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/20/holiday-shopping-2021-record-out-of-stocks-shipping-delays-ahead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts warn shoppers can expect to find record out of stocks as they scan retail websites and may face prolonged shipping delays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired pope hopes to soon join friends in afterlife...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pope-francis-religion-pope-benedict-xvi-84fc17d61798b96cb712b432cd4da5e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Retired Pope Benedict XVI has said he hopes to soon join a beloved professor friend in “the afterlife,” in a sign that the 94-year-old pontiff is not only accepting his eventual death but welcoming it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin keeps Russian workers home for week as deaths soar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-russia-europe-vladimir-putin-bcb1c48ff55f0b2276d3696baba2084c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin on Wednesday backed the Cabinet’s proposal to declare a non-working week and keep Russian workers away from their offices as coronavirus deaths surged to another daily record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JABS FOR KIDS IN WEEKS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-coronavirus-vaccine-bf6e5c8725aca6c757b129dad8f96926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Children age 5 to 11 will soon be able to get a COVID-19 shot at their pediatrician's office, local pharmacy and potentially even their school, the White House said Wednesday as it detailed plans for the expected authorization of the Pfizer shot for younger children in a matter of weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems push IRS bank reporting plan amid uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-to-scale-back-treasury-e2-80-99s-irs-bank-reporting-plan-amid-gop-uproar/ar-AAPFE2r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration has faced an uproar over the plan from Republicans and industry groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's COVID outbreak grows as cities race to trace infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211020081849-6h7pu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHINA (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China's COVID-19 outbreak grows as cities race to trace infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can see through you: CEOs' language under machine microscope...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211020045902-qbyf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-INVESTMENT/NLP (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-AI can see through you: CEOs' language under machine microscope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg to Be Added to FACEBOOK Privacy Suit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/20/zuckerberg-to-be-added-to-facebook-privacy-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The attorney general for the District of Columbia plans to add Facebook’s chief executive, Mark Zuckerberg, to a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dem Retirements Pile Up as Party Fears Losing Majority...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/20/house-democratic-retirements-pile-up-as-party-fears-losing-majority/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The quickening pace of Democratic retirements in the House may be the clearest indication yet that the party’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm Emanuel Japan confirmation hearing spotlights Dem tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/10/19/rahm-emanuels-japan-confirmation-hearing-spotlights-democratic-tensions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emanuel faces objections from progressive Democrats and activist groups over actions taken when he was mayor of Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen Elizabeth cancels visit on doctors' advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/queen-elizabeth-told-rest-by-doctors-cancels-visit-palace-2021-10-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Queen Elizabeth, the world's longest-reigning monarch, decided on Wednesday to rest for the next few days on advice from doctors and cancelled a planned visit to Northern Ireland, Buckingham Palace said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ORDER CONFUSION</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-white-house-tries-to-finalize-vaccine-mandate-dozens-of-groups-seek-last-minute-meetings/ar-AAPKbrx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies like Walt Disney and industry groups have sought more clarity, while others have sought to slow the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed chief's financial disclosures fuel political clash over nominees...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Fed-chief-s-financial-disclosures-fuel-political-16546180.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As the White House stays mum about who should run the Federal Reserve,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solid majority believes Supreme Court rulings based more on politics than law...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/577444-solid-majority-believes-supreme-court-rulings-based-more-on-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broad majority of Americans — more than 6 in 10 — believes the Supreme Court bases its decisions more on the justices’ political views than on the Constitution and law, a national survey released Wednesday shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Org, Already Under Indictment, Faces New Criminal Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/20/trump-organization-already-under-indictment-faces-new-criminal-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald J. Trump’s family business, which is already under indictment in Manhattan, is facing a criminal investigation by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, hope and activism: meet 'Uganda's rudest woman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/sex-hope-activism-meet-ugandas-061645199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her sexually explicit protests have been likened to pornography, but Ugandan activist and writer Stella Nyanzi says sex is the most effective -- and entertaining -- way to shake people out of their apathy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Arrested for Unblurring Porn in First Deepfake Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgdq87/deepfakes-japan-arrest-japanese-porn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deepfake technology could practically reverse the pixelation in Japanese adult videos, raising legal and ethical questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds swarm DC home of Russian oligarch...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/fbi-agents-swarm-d-c-home-russian-oligarch-oleg-deripaska-n1281844</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deripaska was among two dozen Russian oligarchs and officials who were sanctioned by the Treasury Department in April 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARANDOS: I SCREWED UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/i-screwed-netflix-s-ted-sarandos-addresses-dave-chappelle-fallout-n1281944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarandos' comments come on the eve of a planned employee walkout at Netflix organized by trans and LGBTQ+ staffers, content creators and allies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In secret contracts with govts, PFIZER took hard line in push for profit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-secret-vaccine-contracts-with-governments-pfizer-took-hard-line-in-push-for-profit-report-says/ar-AAPIlby</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With control over one of the world’s most-sought products comes great power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST CAVES ON UNVAXXED</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/19/southwest-vaccine-mandate-unpaid-leave-exemptions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest and American Airlines are trying to reassure employees about job security ahead of the federal vaccine deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX braces for staff walkout and LGBTQ rally over Chappelle special...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netflix-braces-staff-walkout-lgbtq-093600008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix bosses braced for an employee walkout and rally in Los Angeles on Wednesday as anger swelled over a recent Dave Chappelle comedy special that activists say is harmful to the transgender community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 panel votes to hold Steve Bannon in contempt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/steve-bannon-joe-biden-donald-trump-congress-capitol-siege-159b0ae9d4833641285e1114a441721c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol insurrection voted unanimously to hold former White House aide Steve Bannon in contempt of Congress after the longtime ally of former President Donald Trump defied a subpoena for documents and testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurse convicted of killing 4 with air injections...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Texas-nurse-convicted-of-killing-4-men-with-air-16546360.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TYLER, Texas (AP) — A Texas nurse was convicted Tuesday of capital murder in the deaths...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maker's woes hamper global campaign: 'Rushed process'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/19/novavax-vaccine-rush-process-global-campaign-516298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and the world made a huge bet on Novavax, but manufacturing problems are jeopardizing billions of doses earmarked for poor and middle-income countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Considers Erecting 32-Foot 5G Wireless Towers Throughout City...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/10/19/new-york-city-5g-cell-towers-link-5g-wireless-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city is proposing a design to expand fifth-generation wireless technology -- also known as 5G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff 'vehemently' disagrees with AG's reluctance to pursue Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/schiff-vehemently-disagrees-with-attorney-general-garlands-reluctance-to-pursue-trump-214740391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff says he “vehemently” disagrees with Attorney General Merrick Garland’s failure so far to aggressively investigate former President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists think tuberculosis can spread in aerosols, upending understanding of disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.silive.com/news/2021/10/scientists-think-tuberculosis-can-spread-in-aerosols-upending-understanding-of-disease-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.silive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1.5 million people died from tuberculosis last year, the World Health Organization said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland' chief tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/19/politics/homeland-security-secretary-mayorkas-covid-positive/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas, who is vaccinated against Covid-19, tested positive for the virus on Tuesday morning, according to department spokesperson Marsha Espinosa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Cavuto too...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/19/media/neil-cavuto-covid-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News anchor Neil Cavuto has tested positive for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs Have ADHD Too...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-adhd-just-like-humans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogs which don't get enough attention, stay home alone much of the time, or don't get enough exercise show more behavioral changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers worry could grow worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/john-deere-strike-and-supply-chain-woes-has-farmers-worried-rcna3207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some farmers are concerned that supply chain shortages could grow worse after 10,000 John Deere workers went on strike last week. Farm equipment prices are rising, affecting harvest and planting season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants increasingly entering California through coast...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/migrants-increasingly-dangerous-journeys-enter-133518873.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say the shift is in response to restrictive border policies that put migrants at increasing danger as they are pushed farther out to the high seas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rep. indicted for lying to FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/19/nebraska-gop-rep-fortenberry-indicted-516259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department said that Fortenberry repeatedly lied to and misled authorities during an investigation into illegal contributions to his reelection campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers Thumbs Nose at 'Woke PC Culture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/aaron-rodgers-thumbs-nose-at-woke-pc-culture-for-mischaracterizing-him-after-interaction-with-bears-fans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers has no regrets about his “I own you” rant directed at Chicago Bears fans, but he blames the response on a "woke PC culture."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House weighs tapping National Guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-has-weighed-tapping-national-guard-to-address-mounting-supply-chain-backlog/ar-AAPImgz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea appears unlikely to move forward but shows the extent of internal administration concern over the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi to convert oil rig into 'extreme park', resort...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/saudi-arabia-to-convert-oil-rig-into-a-150000-square-metre-extreme-park-and-resort</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil Leader's Pandemic Handling Draws Explosive Allegation: Homicide...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/19/brazilian-leaders-pandemic-handling-draws-explosive-allegation-homicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASÍLIA, Brazil — A Brazilian congressional panel is set to recommend mass homicide charges against President Jair Bolsonaro, asserting that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil Leader's Pandemic Handling Draws Explosive Allegation: Homicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/19/world/americas/bolsonaro-pandemic-investigation-brazil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long-awaited report from Brazil’s Senate concludes that Jair Bolsonaro purposely let the coronavirus kill Brazilians in a failed bid for herd immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking on 'Air': NYC's newest skyscraper attraction...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211019-walking-on-air-new-york-s-newest-skyscraper-attraction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walking on 'Air': New York's newest skyscraper attraction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bus attacked in clashes at Jerusalem's Damascus Gate...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/clashes-break-out-at-jerusalems-damascus-gate-report-682473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bus driver and teen injured from stones * A video on social media shows an undercover Border Policeman firing a gun at the sky during another arrest at Herod's Gate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rep. expects to be indicted for lying to FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/19/nebraska-rep-jeff-fortenberry-expects-to-be-arrested-by-fbi-for-lying.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Jeff Fortenberry, a Nebraska Republican, said he is shocked to be accused of lying to FBI agents when asked about campaign contributions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan 6 panel lays out criminal contempt case against Bannon...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/577322-jan-6-panel-pushes-back-on-bannons-claim-of-executive-privilege</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A criminal contempt report released by the House committee investigating the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More meds coming to vending machines...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/maryland/2021/10/more-non-prescription-meds-are-coming-to-md-vending-machines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vending machines in Maryland can now stock everything from allergy relief to some contraception along with candy or chips under a new state law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA's Last KMART To Close...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/10/19/kmart-grass-valley-closing-december/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California’s last remaining Kmart is closing before Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of 911 callers in Denver being placed on hold...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/10/18/911-denver-on-hold-caller/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denver's 911 system is out of compliance with nationally recognized standards for answering calls as thousands of callers are finding themselves on hold when they call in to report an emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Airplane passenger uses microphone for midflight pandemic rant...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/airplane-passenger-uses-microphone-to-rant-about-pandemic-midflight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unruly woman was captured on video ranting into a microphone about the COVID-19 pandemic during a commercial flight – much to the annoyance of her fellow passengers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN's John King reveals on the air that he has MS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/cnns-john-king-reveals-that-he-has-multiple-sclerosis-in-discussion-about-covid-19-vaccines-1234858329/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN’s John King revealed on Tuesday that he has multiple sclerosis during a segment of Inside Politics in which the discussion turned to Covid-19 vaccine mandates. “I’m going to s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn broadcast on TV station sparks investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/nation-world/national/article255119212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television station KREM has apologized for the Sunday night incident.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
