<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Female Fort Bragg soldier charged in another's killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2021/05/08/one-female-fort-bragg-soldier-charged-in-anothers-killing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sergeant is charged in the death of 22-year-old Spc. Kelia Horton, who police said was found shot outside a Fayetteville home Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRICES RISING EVERYWHERE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/09/investing/stocks-week-ahead/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everywhere you look, there are headlines about higher prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Sniper Boasts of Post-Shooting Sex With Accomplice in New Doc...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/horrific-d-c-sniper-boasts-090258634.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ViceIn I, Sniper, Lee Boyd Malvo speaks at length about the 2002 reign of terror he and partner John Allen Muhammad carried out in the Washington, D.C., area, resulting in ten deaths. Yet despite using audio clips from his phone calls as narration, Vice’s eight-part docuseries (premiering May 10) is most notable for putting its prime emphasis on the pair’s innocent victims, and the countless friends, family members and loved ones left to cope with unthinkable tragedy. To its admirable credit, it’s a true-crime affair that seeks to understand its “monsters” while simultaneously recognizing—and highlighting—the fact that such comprehension doesn’t necessitate empathy, especially when the atrocities in question are as inexcusably heinous as these.Spearheaded by director Ursula Macfarlane, I, Sniper’s calling card is those phone conversations with Malvo from Virginia’s Red Onion State Prison, where he’s currently serving multiple life sentences. In them, the killer recounts, in exacting and chilling detail, both the sniper attacks he perpetrated as a 17-year-old, and the troubled upbringing in Jamaica that led him into the welcoming arms of Muhammad, a Gulf War veteran with a surplus of rage and a desire to unleash it on his homeland. Abandoned by his dad, abused by his mom, and eventually left to fend for himself, Malvo found in Muhammad a father figure who promised to love him as he did his own biological offspring. From the outset, though, theirs was a bond built on exploitation, with Muhammad becoming not only Malvo’s surrogate parent, but also his lover—as well as his mentor, pouring all of his long-simmering hate and resentment into the impressionable, desperate-for-acceptance teen.The Tragic End to Wrestling’s First Great ‘Madman’Muhammad’s gripes were many—he despised the military, white people, and just about every American institutional structure. However, he reserved his greatest enmity for second ex-wife Mildred, who dared to take back her kids after Muhammad had kidnapped them. The loss of his (abducted) brood seems to have been the proverbial match that lit Muhammad’s homicidal spark, and he soon began molding Malvo into his instrument of destruction. Friends and relatives suspected that something was up with their relationship, but no one foresaw what was to come: the cold-blooded murder of Keenya Cook, the niece of Mildred’s friend in Tacoma, Washington, followed by violent robberies, shootings and slayings in Arizona, Louisiana, Alabama, and Georgia. All of those initial acts were merely a test run for Malvo and Muhammad’s grand scheme in Washington, D.C., the epicenter of American power, and thus Muhammad’s venue of choice to strike fear into the heart of the republic by proving that everyone was vulnerable—even children.What transpired was a 22-day nightmare in which 13 individuals (white and Black, young and old, well-off and working-class) were shot, 10 of them fatally, in D.C., Maryland, and Virginia. Because Malvo and Muhammad’s intention was to terrorize in increasingly escalating fashion, each victim was chosen at random at gas stations, on street corners, and in parking lots that afforded the killers ideal vantage points and easy escape routes. They committed these crimes in a customized 1990 blue Chevy Caprice, with Malvo lying in the trunk and firing through the rear keyhole. It was a stealthy plot, and the two benefited from the fact that an early eyewitness said they’d seen a white box truck near the scene—thereby sending police, for the better part of the next three weeks, on a wild goose chase for the wrong vehicle. With no other ballistics-related leads, law enforcement was stymied, which proved to Malvo that Muhammad was right: no one could stop them from exacting their revenge.The question, of course, is revenge against what? I, Sniper connects the dots of Malvo and Muhammad’s troubled pasts and despicable 2002 presents, but no convincing argument is made that Muhammad—the mastermind behind this madness—had suffered losses that weren’t of his own making. Be it his unhinged military tenure, his marital craziness, or his transformation of Malvo into an assassin, Muhammad comes across as a man righteously angry over things that were his own fault. As for Malvo, his cold, clinical recitation of his murderous conduct (and claims of remorse) neuters any sorrow one might feel for his adolescent travails. His present-day compunction is far too little, too late, just as the case he makes for his own victimhood vis-à-vis Muhammad sounds like an accurate and yet insufficient explanation. He knew that gunning down men, women and children was dreadfully wrong, and yet in order to maintain Muhammad’s affection, he actively, and enthusiastically, chose to do it—and even got a thrilling kick from it, as he explains that post-shooting sex with Muhammad was exceptionally exciting.Malvo and Muhammad’s rampage of “retribution and punishment” was unforgivable; as Montgomery County Police Chief Charles A. Moose says, “There’s just no excuse for their behavior. None whatsoever.” To hammer home that point, I, Sniper consistently juxtaposes Malvo’s recollections with prolonged, heartrending interviews with the wives, brothers, aunts and friends of the duo’s victims, as well as some of those who survived their encounters. Those accounts turn out to be vital, providing an up-close-and-personal view of the anguish and trauma that Malvo and Muhammad brought about, and the lingering scars left by this ordeal. They’re the human face of this awful tale, stricken with grief, regret, guilt and fury over senseless crimes that robbed them of loved ones who were simply at the wrong place at the wrong time.Comprised of news reports, crime scene footage, 911 calls, Malvo-penned illustrations, maps and chats with patrolmen, detectives, reporters and doctors, I, Sniper is comprehensive enough to earn the description “definitive.” Yet more than its insight into the mind of its young subject—and, by extension, Muhammad, who was executed in 2009 by lethal injection—what separates it from much of the true-crime pack is its dogged refusal to forget the real, incalculable horror at the center of its story. Malvo is frequently heard but never seen, while the countenances of his and Muhammad’s victims (and those close to them) remain front-and-center throughout. That directorial decision is critical and commendable, allowing the series to pay fitting tribute to the individuals who deserve to be remembered, while keeping its central villain largely faceless, in the dark and out of sight, where he chose to live and kill with his murderous mentor, and where he’ll now remain for the remainder of his days.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Stolen Ahead of Shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/colonial-hackers-stole-data-thursday-035900243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The hackers who caused Colonial Pipeline to shut down the biggest U.S. gasoline pipeline on Friday began their blitz against the company a day earlier, stealing a large amount of data before locking computers with ransomware and demanding payment, according to people familiar with the matter.The intruders, who are part of a cybercrime gang called DarkSide, took nearly 100 gigabytes of data out of the Alpharetta, Georgia-based company’s network in just two hours on Thursday, two people involved in Colonial’s investigation said.The move was part of a double-extortion scheme that is one of the group’s hallmarks. Colonial was threatened that the stolen data would be leaked to the internet while the information that was encrypted by the hackers on computers inside the network would remain locked unless it paid a ransom, said the people, who asked not to be identified because the information isn’t public.The company didn’t immediately respond to requests to comment on the investigation. It said earlier that it “proactively took certain systems offline to contain the threat, which has temporarily halted all pipeline operations, and affected some of our IT systems.”Colonial’s decision late Friday to shut down a pipeline that is the main source of gasoline, diesel and jet fuel for the East Coast, without saying when it would reopen, represents a dangerous new escalation in the fight against ransomware, which President Joe Biden’s administration has identified as a priority.It’s not clear how much money the attackers demanded or whether Colonial has paid. Ransomware demands can range from several hundred dollars to millions of dollars in cryptocurrency. Many companies pay, often facilitated by their insurers.AXA SA, one of Europe’s top insurance companies, said this week that it would break with that trend and stop offering policies in France that reimburse customers for payments made to ransomware hackers, which could be the first in the industry, the Associated Press reported.Cyber-attacks have disrupted the operations of other energy assets in the U.S. in recent years. Last year, the Department of Homeland Security revealed that an attack brought down an unnamed natural gas compressor facility for two days. In April 2018, several natural gas pipeline operators had service interruptions because of the hack of a third-party provider whose technology enables electronic communications between the entities.The theft of Colonial’s data, coupled with the detonation of ransomware on the company’s computers, highlights the leverage that hackers often have over their victims in these kinds of cases. The company said FireEye Inc.’s Mandiant digital forensics division is assisting with the investigation.The White House said that Biden was briefed on the incident Saturday morning.A series of major cyber-attacks in recent weeks also underscored the brazenness of the attackers and the challenges of tackling the problem of ransomware.In a matter of days, attacks were revealed against the police department in Washington, D.C. , where the hackers threatened to release information about police informants to criminal gangs; the Illinois Attorney General’s office, which had been warned about weak cybersecurity practices in a recent state audit; and San Diego-based Scripps Health, where medical procedures were canceled and emergency patients diverted to other hospitals.Ransomware Attackers Up Ante as White House Vows Crack Down(Adds reference to recent attacks starting in 11th paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. 5th Fleet seizes weapons shipment from stateless dhow in Arabian Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-5th-fleet-seizes-weapons-shipment-stateless-dhow-arabian-sea-2021-05-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy’s Fifth Fleet said on Saturday that the guided-missile cruiser USS Monterey (CG 61) seized an illicit shipment of weapons from a stateless dhow in international water of the North Arabian Sea on May 6-7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools Open, but Many Families Hesitant to Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/schools-are-open-but-many-families-remain-hesitant-to-return/ar-BB1gwVLI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pauline Rojas’s high school in San Antonio is open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80% Who Refuse Vaccine Say NOTHING Can Change Their Minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/whopping-80-percent-who-refuse-covid-vaccine-say-nothing-can-change-their-minds-but-theres-good-news-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A whopping 80 percent of people who say they won’t get vaccinated also say that there is nothing that can change their minds in a new poll — but there’s some potentially good news in the poll, as well. In a new The Economist/YouGov poll, respondents who said they don’t intend to get the Covid […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden faces struggle to hold Senate, Dem divisions resurface...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-biden-faces-a-struggle-to-hold-the-senate-democrats-e2-80-99-divisions-resurface/ar-BB1gvMd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In crucial Senate races in Pennsylvania, North Carolina and elsewhere, the Democratic coalition that came together to elect Biden is fracturing again — with big implications for his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abbas voices full support for rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.i24news.tv/en/news/israel/diplomacy-defense/1620420142-abbas-voices-full-support-for-palestinians-rioting-in-jerusalem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.i24news.tv&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OF GAS PRICE SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9558509/Fears-gas-price-surge-ransomware-attack-shuts-Americas-key-fuel-pipeline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack on Colonial Pipeline took place Friday, and affected some of its information technology systems. Operations remain shutdown as of early Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Study Mysterious Behavior of Cats Sitting on Squares...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7eexj/scientists-have-studied-the-mysterious-behavior-of-cats-sitting-on-squares</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cats love sitting on any square object, as if drawn by some primordial instinct. A new study shows that the square can even be an optical illusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive fire breaks out near Iran nuke power plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/massive-fire-breaks-out-near-irans-bushehr-nuclear-power-plant-report-667581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cause of the fire is still unknown, according to Iranian media reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British royal offers to sell access...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210509-british-royal-offers-to-sell-access-to-putin-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British royal offers to sell access to Putin: report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to 'firmly' defend Russian interests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210509-putin-on-wwii-victory-day-vows-to-firmly-defend-russian-interests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin on WWII Victory Day vows to 'firmly' defend Russian interests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC teacher caught sucking topless man's nipple during ZOOM class...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/08/nyc-teacher-caught-sucking-topless-mans-nipple-during-zoom-class/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teacher Amanda K. Fletcher allegedly performed an “inappropriate sexual act” on a Zoom class at Columbia Secondary School for Math, Science, and Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Mediocre...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/09/billionaire-elon-a-musk-see-on-mediocre-episode-of-snl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even if it was an average episode of “Saturday Night Live,” the host was a Musk see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Humility and hubris...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-elon-musk-business-technology-arts-and-entertainment-0563502b7b60d00bd65158031697444c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk showed a combination of humility and hubris as he opened his highly anticipated hosting gig on “Saturday Night Live.” The 49-year-old Tesla CEO, SpaceX founder and one of the world’s richest men opened his monologue by mocking his monotonal speaking style, saying no one can tell when he's joking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin tells Red Square parade that Nazi ideas persist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-government-and-politics-24387d1bd5aa5a7a90896529ef6a0cfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin marked the anniversary of the end of World War II in Europe with a speech warning that Nazi beliefs remain strong. Speaking to the annual military parade on Moscow's Red Square, Putin on Sunday decried “attempts to rewrite history, to justify traitors and criminals, on whose hands lies the blood of hundreds of thousands of peaceful people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson's phone number breach fails to prompt tighter security...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/boris-johnson-phone-number-breach-sparks-no-uk-rethink/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Solutions are out there, but ministers have not been keen to embrace them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Age of Scandals Weakens American Christianity...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/how-american-christendom-weakens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An age of scandals reveals how institutions of the faith can fundamentally oppose the faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street parties celebrate end of Spain's state of emergency...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-spain-lifestyle-coronavirus-pandemic-health-e0ee913b5dd19d3dac5310eac1a512d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARCELONA, Spain (AP) — Impromptu street celebrations erupted across Spain as the clock struck midnight on Saturday, when a six-month-long national state of emergency to contain the spread of coronavirus ended and many nighttime curfews were lifted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Delivers Self-Deprecating 'SNL' Opening Monologue...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/ok-that-was-actually-funny-elon-musk-joined-by-his-mom-delivers-self-deprecating-snl-opening-monologue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk delivered a self-deprecating opening monologue on Saturday Night Live, making fun of many aspects of his persona and getting plenty of laughs from the audience. Musk’s selection as the night’s host was controversial, with even several SNL cast members publicly voicing their disapproval. Musk’s seeming attempt to crowdsource ideas […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogecoin plunges nearly 30% during appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/08/dogecoin-price-plummets-as-elon-musk-hosts-saturday-night-live-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Elon Musk hosted SNL, the price of dogecoin fell off a cliff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama dog Bo dies from cancer...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2021/05/obama-dog-bo-once-a-white-house-celebrity-dies-from-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama’s dog Bo died Saturday after a battle with cancer, the Obamas said on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-year-old, 2 women shot in Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/toddler-woman-shot-new-york-s-times-square-police-say-n1266765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The girl was toy shopping when she was struck, New York police Commissioner Dermot Shea said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists train bees to identify infection...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/552486-scientists-train-bees-to-identify-coronavirus-infection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Dutch scientists are enlisting the help of an unusual group of participants for a new kind of rapid COVID-19 test: bees that have been specially trained to detect the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBERATTACK SHUTS TOP U.S. PIPELINE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210508152642-o9z7n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PRODUCTS/COLONIAL PIPELINE (UPDATE 6, PIX):UPDATE 6-Cyber attack shuts down top U.S. fuel pipeline network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Neanderthals Weren't Cannibals, So Who Ate Them?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/these-neanderthals-werent-cannibals-so-who-ate-them-stone-age-hyenas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME — When a Neanderthal skull was discovered in a cave on the property of a beachfront hotel south of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Separate Worlds of Bill and Melinda Gates...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/the-separate-worlds-of-bill-and-melinda-gates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates and Melinda French Gates were stuck at home. When the pandemic hit last March, the couple retreated to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson Urges 'Step Back' From 'Sexist' HFPA...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/scarlett-johansson-hfpa-statement-criticism-diversity-inclusion-reform-1234752398/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scarlett Johansson has joined the outcry against the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, adding her voice to fellow Avenger Mark Ruffalo, who spoke out on Friday. They unite with numerous publicis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walls closing in on Gaetz?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/may/08/matt-gaetz-florida-sleazy-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigation into Florida congressman is reported to have grown beyond sex trafficking allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W Virginia factory center stage in supply chain crisis, showing economy's strains...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/west-virginia-factory-is-center-stage-in-supply-chain-crisis-as-u-s-economy-seeks-to-rebound-from-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scene inside one plant illustrates the deepening production challenges roiling American industry as it shakes off the pandemic. Parts shortages, price spikes, port delays, labor trouble - all are complicating the economy's rebound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In small NH town, 2020 election still rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-new-hampshire-campaign-2016-election-2020-house-elections-e50dfae66446197767bd255882d19439</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDHAM, N.H. (AP) — Meetings of the Windham Board of Selectmen are usually as sleepy as they sound — a handful of residents from the New Hampshire town, a discussion of ambulance fees, maybe a drainage study...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLDPLAY Chris Martin says lockdowns forced him to re-evaluate fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/may/07/coldplay-chris-martin-lockdowns-forced-re-evaluate-fame</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frontman says Covid pandemic means he has tried ‘to not attach too much to being a pop star’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Suspended Over Photos Showing Them Not Wearing Masks Off-Campus...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/07/umass-amherst-students-suspended-masks-outside-off-campus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three UMass Amherst students said they are not being treated fairly after they were suspended for not wearing masks at an off-campus outdoor event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild VIP Group-Sex Party About to Invade NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-wild-vip-group-sex-party-is-about-to-invade-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On May 15, SNCTM—an exclusive sex club—is set to host an 80-person bash in Downtown Manhattan. Masks are not optional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Internet Turned on Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/05/08/elon-musk-snl-saturday-night-live-host-internet-controversy-485781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unlikely, polarizing SNL hosting stint for the mogul reveals the boundaries and tensions of our ever-present culture wars.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
