<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented show of force...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/19/virginia-gun-rights-rally-activists-plan-unprecede/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are scouring the internet for clues about plans for mayhem, workers are putting up chain link holding pens around Virginia’s picturesque Capitol Square, and one lawmaker even plans to hide in a safe house in advance of what’s expected to be an unprecedented show of force by gun-rights activists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'New Light of God' cult sacrifices 7 in jungle...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/19/new-light-god-cult-kills-7-el-terron-panama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bibles rest on a wooden altar next to percussion instruments - a guiro and a drum - in the room where a religious sect allegedly forced a pregnant woman and five of her children to walk through fire in this remote hamlet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOWA: Pete gets ovation in most conservative county...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jan/18/pete-buttigieg-iowa-conservative-election-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His campaign feared hostility in Iowa’s most conservative county. But the local response told a different story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre Fight Over Wealthy Biochemist's Frozen Head...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/heirs-battle-with-alcor-life-extension-over-dads-frozen-head-keeps-getting-weirder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast riches and a lifelong obsession with fringe technology are threatening to tear a family apart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Team calling charges 'brazen, unlawful'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/277205/donald-trump-legal-time-response-impeachment-brazen-unlawful/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s legal team fired off a defiant response to impeachment, calling the two charges against him “brazen &amp; unlawful.” The first formal response was filed Saturday ev…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Entertainment, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother and daughter 'psychics' get prison time in fraud case...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/crime/fl-ne-broward-pysching-sentenced-for-million-dollar-fraud-20200117-zj7edl5yoveotog5qmigyxcgee-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They claimed they were “white squaw Cherokee Indian” spiritual healers, and used eggs filled with snake embryos to convince their victims that they were cursed, authorities say. But on Friday, the mother and daughter pair of Annie Marie Vwanawick, 74, and April Miller, 44, both of Broward, were sentenced to prison for defrauding two victims with their spiritual scams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UTAH HORROR:  Boy in custody for fatally shooting 4 members of family...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2020/01/18/police-investigating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grantsville • Four members of a Utah family, including three children, are dead and a fifth is in the hospital after a family member opened fire Friday evening inside a Grantsville residence, according to local police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump impeachment, starring Bill Clinton...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/18/trump-clinton-impeachment-100691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is the one fighting to keep his job, but it can feel like the entire country is reliving the last presidential impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it.&amp;#160;He has written about the investigation into Russia&amp;#8217;s election interference, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts, decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea and the impeachment of the president. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post&amp;#8217;s original story breaking the Ken Starr investigation of the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper&amp;#8217;s lead writer on the subsequent impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton.&amp;#160;During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush&amp;#8217;s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama&amp;#8217;s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five&amp;#160;books, most recently&amp;#160;"Impeachment: An American History" (Modern Library, 2018) with Jon Meacham, Timothy Naftali and Jeffrey A. Engel. He also wrote&amp;#160;&amp;#8220;Obama: The Call of History&amp;#8221; (New York Times/Callaway, 2017), a finalist for an NAACP Image Award for Outstanding Literary Work;&amp;#160;&amp;#8220;Days of Fire: Bush and Cheney in the White House&amp;#8221; (Doubleday, 2013), which was named one of the five Best Non-Fiction Books of 2013 by The New York Times Book Review; &amp;#8220;The Breach: Inside the Impeachment and Trial of William Jefferson Clinton&amp;#8221; (Scribner, 2000), a New York Times bestseller; and, with Ms. Glasser, &amp;#8220;Kremlin Rising: Vladimir Putin&amp;#8217;s Russia and the End of Revolution&amp;#8221; (Scribner, 2005), named one of the Best Books of 2005 by The Washington Post Book World.&amp;#160;He will publish his sixth book in May 2020, &amp;#8220;The Man Who Ran Washington: The Life and Times of James A. Baker III,&amp;#8221; co-authored with Ms. Glasser and published by Doubleday. Mr. Baker has won all three major awards devoted to White House reporting: the Gerald R. Ford Prize for Distinguished Coverage of the Presidency (twice), the Aldo Beckman Memorial Award (twice) and the Merriman Smith Memorial Award. Mr. Baker is also a political analyst for MSNBC and a regular panelist on PBS&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;Washington Week.&amp;#8221; A native of the Washington area, Mr. Baker attended Oberlin College and worked for The Washington Times for two years before joining The Post in 1988 as a Virginia reporter. Ms. Glasser is now a staff writer for The New Yorker and the two live in Washington with their son Theodore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump&amp;#8217;s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile "What Is Hillary Clinton Afraid Of?" Her hobbies include singing, and she is married with three children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Policing of the American Porch...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/19/style/ring-video-doorbell-home-security.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ring offers a front-door view of a country where millions of Amazon customers use Amazon cameras to watch Amazon contractors deliver Amazon packages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even C-SPAN Piqued: Senate Puts Limits on Coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/19/business/media/senate-impeachment-trial-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate will control the cameras during the impeachment trial, limiting what viewers see, and reporters will be confined to roped-off areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House managers cite 'overwhelming' evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/house-managers-cite-overwhelming-evidence-against-trump-their-brief-senate-n1118436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House called the impeachment a "dangerous attack on the right of the American people to freely choose their President."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoverboarding dentist found guilty of 'unlawful dental acts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/hoverboarding-dentist-found-guilty-unlawful-dental-acts-n1118431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video captured Seth Lookhart extracting the tooth of a sedated patient as he rode a hoverboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSN:  Daily presidential tracking poll...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/daily-presidential-tracking-poll/ar-AADKLI1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GOOD NEWS FILE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>