<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Hill staff say fear of political violence feels like part of job...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/08/23/hill-staff-fear-political-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bomb threat near the Capitol last week has staffers wondering what’s next. “At this point, you get used to it,” said one Republican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It all happened in six minutes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/survivors-recount-living-nightmare-as-tennessee-s-deadly-floodwaters-swept-them-up-in-moments/ar-AANEa6K?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 21 people were killed, and local officials said Monday afternoon that they believe fewer than 10 people are still missing. The search for victims could last for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys leader sentenced to five months...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/proud-boys-leader-henry-enrique-tarrio-sentenced-to-five-months-in-jail/ar-AANDYch?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tarrio admitted to two crimes, including setting fire to a Black Lives Matter banner stolen from a historic Black church in the District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis covid gamble: Schools, vaccinations, masks --  and his political future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ron-desantis-colossal-covid-19-gamble-schools-vaccinations-masks-and-his-political-future/ar-AANEcNL?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election season is far off, but Gov. Ron DeSantis has been in full-blown campaign mode, crisscrossing the state almost every day in the past week, touting monoclonal antibody treatments for people infected with COVID-19, defending his handling of the pandemic, and excoriating anyone who disagrees with his approach. Delta-variant-fueled COVID infections have surged across Florida for two ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman films rising water before death...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article253693223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The one-minute video was the last time friends and family heard from Linda Almond before she was swept away by floodwaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought worsens in Southern Cal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/drought-worsens-southern-california-ventura-185118065.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Northwest L.A. County, Ventura County, parts of San Bernardino County and others fall into a federal report's highest range — 'exceptional drought.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer of Extremes...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/western-u-bakes-east-deluged-195348687.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the western U.S. bakes and burns under an unprecedented heat dome, Henri leaves a deluged East Coast staggering after a summer of deadly floods and record-setting tropical storms. Climate scientists say one is due to the other and both come against the backdrop of a warming planet. The high pressure that got stuck across the West causing drought and fire actually created the conditions for low-pressure-driven storms in the East. So while July was the hottest month ever recorded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#APPLETOO: Employees organizing to expose workplace harassment at company...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/8/23/22638150/apple-appletoo-employee-harassment-discord</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort launched August 23rd with a website and Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Disasters Messing With Our Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/all-these-simultaneous-disasters-are-messing-with-our-brains/ar-AANB1Lv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquakes and wildfires and wars keep piling up. When does our empathy run out?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Struggling News Industry Steps Up Recruitment of Diverse Leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/struggling-news-industry-steps-up-recruitment-of-diverse-leaders/ar-AANE7Vn?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With much of corporate America targeting greater diversity in its management ranks, news companies are taking steps to close the gap, offering a glimpse at what more representative leadership might bring in an industry that has lagged behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sao Paulo to Require Vaccine for Entry Into Restaurants and Events...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/sao-paulo-to-require-vaccine-for-entry-into-restaurants-and-events/ar-AANE7YY?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most populous city in Latin America will begin requiring residents to have received at least one dose of a Covid-19 vaccine in order to enter restaurants, bars and public events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIACOM LISTS MORE REAL ESTATE:  CBS Studio Center Up For Sale;  Follows Black Rock...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/viacomcbs-eyes-sale-of-la-studio-as-demand-surges-for-stages/ar-AANEsi4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ViacomCBS Inc. is looking to sell a historic Los Angeles movie and television lot as the entertainment company tries to capitalize on the demand for production space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KENTUCKY NEW HOTSPOT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-kentucky-laws-cb3c6191208fe4bd8a8431d8ec0d010a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFORT, Ky. (AP) — Kentucky was hit with record numbers of COVID-19 patients in hospitals and intensive care units Monday as cases were driven up by the fast-spreading delta variant, Gov. Andy Beshear said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors grapple with aftermath of deadly Tennessee flood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/floods-tennessee-c7c876734f3ddbafd61fd98989a647f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAVERLY, Tenn. (AP) — Anna Mays woke up in a panic attack Monday, thinking she was back in the rising floodwater. Two days ago, she had been clinging for her life to the front door of her duplex in rural Tennessee as the water inched up to her neck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POT BELLY:  Man denied owning 'very large bag of marijuana' that fell from his shirt...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/iowa/iowa-pot-belly-824593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a “very large bag of marijuana” tumbles out of your shirt after the handcuffs have been applied, do not be surprised when the cops ignore your disavowal of ownership of said weed. Police respond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC court grants voting rights to felons on probation or parole...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/north-carolina-voting-rights-felons-13e93845-bd27-44e5-a585-13e53aa8bc18.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling restores voting rights to more than 55,000 people who have left prison but are still being supervised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths of newlywed women found shot at campsite investigated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/utah-94ccfda803a0c3fec1c76b1ad8d9e4d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOAB, Utah (AP) — Residents of a Utah tourist town near the campsite where a newlywed couple was recently gunned down say they’re puzzled and concerned as the police investigation unfolds. Crystal Turner and Kylen Schulte were found dead last week at a campsite near Moab, a desert town where they were living that draws visitors from around the world to its sweeping red-rock vistas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough infections rise in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/breakthrough-infections-rise-in-la-county-young-adults-most-infected-with-coronavirus/ar-AANDqVU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By far, the age group now most likely to get infected with the coronavirus in Los Angeles County is younger adults — those 18 to 49.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore PM Questions US Image in Press Conference With Kamala Harris...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/singapore-pm-says-us-image-in-question-during-press-conference-with-kamala-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong said he believed global perceptions of America's image after Afghanistan's fall would be determined in the days ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS DEPLOY INTO KABUL FOR EVACUATIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/23/pentagon-confirms-latest-mission-to-rescue-americans-stranded-in-kabul-506594</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Department’s top spokesperson also suggested a variety of other extraction efforts were taking place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN SETS 'RED LINE'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/23/taliban-warns-aug-31-is-a-red-line-for-withdrawing-us-forces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban is warning President Biden that extending the Aug. 31 deadline to withdraw US forces from Afghanistan as the administration struggles to evacuate American citizens and Afghan allies fro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader sentenced to 5+ months for burning BLM flag, bringing ammo to DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/proud-boys-leader-enrique-tarrio-sentenced-to-over-5-months-for-burning-black-lives-matter-flag-and-bringing-ammo-to-d-c/ar-AANEiuC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge ruled the right-wing organization's frontman 'betrayed' democratic values</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Eating 1 hot dog takes 35 minutes off life...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/23/eating-1-hot-dog-takes-35-minutes-off-life-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers released a nutritional index this week aiming to inform guidelines and help Americans achieve healthier and more environmentally stable diets. The index ranked foods by minutes gained o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll mistaken for body in canal as police invite owner to collect it...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/08/23/sex-doll-mistaken-for-body-in-canal-as-police-invite-owner-to-collect-it-15135790/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'corpse' was floating next to a bunch of reeds in the water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emboldened Iran To Hold War Drills With Russia, China...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/emboldened-iran-to-hold-war-drills-with-russia-and-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran is set to hold a series of war drills with Russia and China, as the hardline regime celebrates the United States' bungled evacuation in Afghanistan and boosts its enrichment of nuclear weapons-grade uranium to historically high levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan, Again, Becomes Cradle for Jihadism -- and Al Qaeda...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/daily-comment/afghanistan-again-becomes-a-cradle-for-jihadism-and-al-qaeda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terrorist group has outlasted the trillion-dollar U.S. investment in Afghanistan since 9/11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland to build fence on border to stop migrants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-poland-migration-belarus-09e740771deed848a6b294628de96322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Poland plans to build a fence along its border with Belarus and deploy more soldiers there to stop migrants seeking to enter the European Union nation. The government on Monday also offered to send humanitarian aid to a migrant group stuck at the border for more than two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS DEPLOY INTO KABUL FOR EVACUATIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2021/08/23/world/taliban-afghanistan-biden-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deployment beyond Kabul’s airport comes as President Biden considers pushing back his Aug. 31 deadline for U.S. troop withdrawal. Violent clashes continued at Kabul’s airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tallest man in USA, 7ft 8 inches, dead at 38 from heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3526483/tallest-man-in-america-igor-vovkovinskiy-dead-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE tallest man in America who stood at 7ft 8 inches died on Friday aged 38 of heart disease, his family confirmed. Igor Oleksandrovych Vovkovinskiy, originally from Ukraine, passed away at the May…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Employers must require...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/23/covid-vaccine-mandate-biden-506609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s call for schools and business to require vaccination comes amid stiff resistance by some Republican governors and lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN pastor giving boot to members wearing masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/tennessee-pastor-giving-boot-to-members-of-congregation-in-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a Sunday sermon, Pastor Greg Locke at Global Vision Bible Church — located in Nashville, TN — delivered some fiery warnings to pro-PPE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person on no-fly list flown into UK...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/afghanistan-person-on-no-fly-watchlist-flown-into-uk-during-evacuation-operation-12389001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The individual, who is not being identified by the government, is understood to have reached UK soil on a British military plane, with officials being alerted "overnight".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rape gangs having sex with DEAD bodies' after going door-to-door for sex slaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15944502/woman-taliban-rape-sex-dead-bodies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN who fled to India as the Taliban seized Afghanistan claims that insurgents rape dead bodies after going door-to-door to find sex slaves. The former Afghan police force member – identi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive MICROSOFT data breach leaves 38 million records exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3525714/microsoft-power-apps-exposed-data-leaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE personal records of 38million people were accidentally leaked on the open internet due to a flaw in more than a thousand Microsoft web apps, according to reports. American Airlines, Ford, J.B. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney's dad says 'star's addiction, mental health problems far worse than public realized'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3525166/britney-spears-dad-addiction-mental-health-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears’ father has kept the true depths of his superstar daughter’s mental health and drug addiction problems secret, court documents have revealed. Jaime Spears has claimed that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal church gathering shut down by police...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com.au/national/coronavirus-nsw-update-police-break-up-blacktown-church-gathering/55e27187-190b-4a1d-8ce0-8a193875ce1a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Daily Deaths Top 1,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-s-daily-deaths-top-1-000-nyc-teacher-vaccines-virus-update/ar-AANBCqT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vaccine made by Pfizer Inc. and BioNTech SE was granted a full approval by U.S. regulators. The Pentagon is now set to require all service members to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Has Most Americans Paying No Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/08/23/the-pandemic-has-most-americans-paying-no-federal-income-taxes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A minority of the population picking up the tab would be dangerous if the situation were to last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO chief calling for two-month halt on boosters...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/568988-who-chief-calling-for-two-month-halt-on-vaccine-boosters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Health Organization (WHO) Director-General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus on Monday called for a two-month moratorium on COVID-19 booster shots as many low and middle-income countries still struggle to provide enough vaccine doses for their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of household wells go dry amid California drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/thousands-of-household-wells-go-dry-amid-california-drought-without-water-youre-nothing/article_61b74be2-0bab-57ba-a52b-8a1f5aa99cbf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADERA COUNTY, Calif. — Fourteen years ago, Heriberto Sevilla came across a ranch on the outskirts of Madera set among fields of stalk grass and bright wildflowers. Pepper trees dotted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A couple, their baby and their dog died on CA hiking trail -- and officials don't know why...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-couple-their-baby-and-their-dog-died-on-a-california-hiking-trail-e2-80-94-and-officials-don-e2-80-99t-know-why/ar-AANDeIX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A family of three was found dead on a California hiking trail, and investigators are short on clues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden considers his pick to run Fed, major role overseeing Wall St slips under radar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-biden-considers-his-pick-to-run-the-fed-a-major-role-overseeing-wall-street-slips-under-the-radar/ar-AANDrhQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no consensus among Democrats about who would be right to be the Fed’s top banking cop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant, Unvaccinated, Intubated: Doctors Alarmed by Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/pregnant-unvaccinated-and-intubated-doctors-alarmed-by-rise/ar-AANDmL0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More young and healthy pregnant people are ending up hospitalized on ventilators, delivering babies prematurely and sometimes dying from Covid-19 during the delta-fueled spike in cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin launches construction of new warships amid tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-fd8c3cad9c4b1c91dda13a4ca4b49555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin on Monday launched the construction of new nuclear submarines and other warships, part of a sweeping military modernization effort amid tensions with the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Cuomo abandons dog at gov mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/state/article/Cuomo-s-dog-Captain-left-at-mansion-after-16402902.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo, who has been staying with one of his sisters in Westchester County...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Disasters Messing With Our Brains?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2021/08/will-pandemic-fatigue-change-how-we-process-disasters/619858/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquakes and wildfires and wars keep piling up. When does our empathy run out?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army fires first 'Iron Dome missile interceptor' in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3524780/us-army-iron-dome-missile-interceptor-fired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Army successfully fired its first Iron Dome missile interceptor on Monday as fears of World War Three build across the world. The troops this morning completed the first test of the missile …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Couch Potatoes 7 Times More Likely To Suffer Stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/couch-potatoes-stroke-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers add that nearly nine in 10 strokes could be attributed to "modifiable" risk factors such as sitting too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Boasts $30 Billion in Payments as Creator Wars Heat Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-23/youtube-boasts-30-billion-in-payments-as-creator-wars-heat-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media companies have thrown considerable resources and money at online creators in recent years. YouTube would like to remind everyone that it throws the most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam deploys troops to enforce rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210823131541-rgvz9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VIETNAM (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Vietnam deploys troops to enforce COVID lockdown in largest city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand extending stay-at-home as outbreak grows...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/568971-new-zealand-extending-lockdown-as-covid-19-outbreak-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand’s government has extended its nationwide lockdown as COVID-19 cases grow around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground arm-wrestling mania slamming NYC streets...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/23/underground-arm-wrestling-mania-takes-nyc-by-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“So much of the world is being taught to shy away from people, that people are dangerous. But we are pack animals — people belong together — and the sport of arm-wrestling teaches you that together…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health worker crunch pressures states battling Delta...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/23/health-worker-crunch-delta-variant-506484</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alarming spread of new cases is draining the pool of available health workers in ways not seen since the pandemic’s winter peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked footage shows grim conditions in Iran's Evin prison...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-health-religion-iran-prisons-01dfade61d7a706d630bf83d30d8cb02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The guard in a control room at Iran's notorious Evin prison springs to attention as one by one, monitors in front of him suddenly blink off and display something very different from the surveillance footage he had been watching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget clash pits moderate Dems against President, Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-c2c1cfd80e7850d32d3387a9e1c05087</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Outnumbered and with their party's most powerful leaders arrayed against them, nine moderate Democrats trying to upend plans for enacting President Joe Biden's multitrillion-dollar domestic program face a House showdown .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborations between Black women sparking golden age for hip-hop...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Collaborations-between-Black-women-are-sparking-a-16404913.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turn on your car stereo. Or open one of Spotify's top hits playlists. Or peruse your...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban warn of 'consequences' if USA extends military presence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taliban-warned-consequences-us-extends-100037785.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The warning came hours after Biden said the US could extend the withdrawal deadline to help evacuation efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental health online: Police posts of crises may traumatize...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-police-mental-health-41883ccc67210e505e13bdd7aaf4713a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE — This story includes discussion of suicide. If you or someone you know needs help, please call the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 1-800-273-8255. The videos are difficult to watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan team says it was told to remove flag before Le Mans race...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210823-taiwan-team-says-it-was-told-to-remove-flag-before-le-mans-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan team says it was told to remove flag before Le Mans race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns of influx of militants disguised as refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/08/23/putin-warns-of-influx-of-afghan-militants-disguised-as-refugees-a74865</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Who is among these refugees? How can we know?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces crucial moment on Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/568963-this-week-biden-faces-crucial-moment-on-capitol-hill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is facing a critical week on Capitol Hill amid Democratic divisions on infrastructure strategy and high-profile criticism over a messy exit in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Topping $50,000 Stirs Forecast of Run Toward Record High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-nears-50-000-level-015607040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin topped $50,000 for the first time since May as crypto prices continued an ongoing recovery from a disorderly rout just three months ago.The largest virtual coin advanced 3.8% to $50,272 as of 6:53 a.m. in New York, with other tokens including Ether and Cardano’s ADA also rising. The revival in virtual currencies has excited the animal spirits of the crypto faithful, putting predictions of $100,000 or more for Bitcoin back in vogue. Others see the volatile asset carving out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Judges Order Defendants to Get Jab. Can They Do That?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/23/2-new-york-judges-ordered-defendants-to-get-vaccinated-can-they-do-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defendant was charged with a number of minor crimes, including drug possession and shoplifting. He was prepared to plead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly firefight erupts at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/23/deadly-firefight-erupts-at-kabul-airport-as-evacuation-chaos-continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is considering extending the deadline for the complete troop withdrawal beyond its original Aug. 31 date, Biden said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds clash in Portland as Proud Boys rally descends into violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hundreds-clash-portland-proud-boys-055220944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Colorado River Dries Up, Phoenix Will Have to Survive on Less Water...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2021/08/us/colorado-river-water-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado River irrigates farms, powers electric grids and provides drinking water to 40 million people. But as its supply dwindles, a crisis looms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida's peak of delta wave could be days away...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2021/08/22/floridas-peak-of-the-delta-wave-could-be-days-away-university-models-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Florida is rapidly approaching the peak of new infections of the delta wave, when the highest single-day counts could come, according to two models created by researchers at Florida…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Jesse Jackson hospitalized with covid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-religion-coronavirus-pandemic-voting-rights-fb8ce99277e00e21189f948b98d15d55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The Rev. Jesse Jackson, and his wife, Jacqueline, remained under doctors' observation Sunday at a Chicago hospital and were “responding positively to treatments” for COVID-19, their son told The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
