<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How Mafia Pivoting to Cybercrime...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epne4j/how-the-mafia-is-pivoting-to-cybercrime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators from Spanish and Italian police explain how organized crime is going online and expanding into cybercrime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO BITE BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/haitian-migrants-bite-ice-officers-deportation-flight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas — Federal assault charges will be brought against two Haitian migrants after they bit federal law enforcement officials on board a deportation flight when the plane was taxiing to the runway, the Washington Examiner has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD CALLING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10016997/Billy-Eichner-Matt-Drudges-double-Impeachment-American-Crime-Story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday night's episode of Impeachment: American Crime Story opened with a scene portraying Drudge's real-life 'origin story' as a clerk in a gift shop at CBS Studios in Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUG COMPANIE$ HYPE VAX 'RESULTS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/sep/21/experts-bemoan-science-press-release-covid-19-era/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drugmakers are hailing great results with COVID-19 boosters and shots for school-age children, enthusing a pandemic-weary public and markets but flustering scientists who say it is important to look at real data before getting too optimistic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former treasury secretaries tried defusing debt ceiling bomb with McConnell, Yellen...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Former-GOP-treasury-secretaries-tried-defusing-16478519.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Two former GOP treasury secretaries held private discussions this month with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX launches autonomous truck routes...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fedex-aurora-to-launch-autonomous-truck-routes-in-texas-11632322936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FedEx Corp. and self-driving vehicle startup Aurora Innovation Inc. are launching a pilot of autonomous truck shipments between Dallas and Houston in an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief slams space joy rides...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/un-chief-tells-musk-bezos-25045505</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The likes of spacefaring billionaires Jeff Bezos, Richard Branson and Elon Musk were heavily criticised by the U.N. Secretary-General, who emphasised the major problems here on Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID REVOLT GROWS IN OZ</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10016021/Police-fire-rubber-bullets-anti-vaxxer-tradies-took-Melbournes-war-memorial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have fired rubber bullets at anti-vaccination protesters who set up camp atop Melbourne's war memorial in the hopes police wouldn't fire on them out of respect for fallen Anzacs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson taking aim at his own book publisher...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Tucker-Carlson-is-taking-aim-at-his-own-book-16478536.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acknowledgment section at the beginning of a book is an opportunity for the author to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas border patrol round up Haitians with whips...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/opinion/op-ed/elviadiaz/2021/09/20/border-patrol-using-whips-del-rio-round-up-haitian-immigrants/5789596001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Border Patrol agents are using reins like whips to round up Haitian immigrants in Del Rio, Texas. What happened to Biden's more humane approach?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Sues NYT, Niece Over Tax Story...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-courts-lawsuits-business-newspapers-da4689bcce1e58c15fc909377fa3a450</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Former President Donald Trump on Tuesday sued his estranged niece and The New York Times over a 2018 story about his family’s wealth and tax practices that was partly based on confidential documents she provided to the newspaper’s reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stalkerware Firm Leaking Real-Time Screenshots of Phones Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7ezj8/stalkerware-leaking-phone-screenshots-pctattletale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;pcTattleTale, which markets itself for monitoring spouses without their consent, lets anyone view screenshots of infected devices by just visiting specific URLs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge mysterious 'void' in space spotted by astronomers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/huge-mysterious-void-space-spotted-25046162</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The huge 'bubble' in space some three thousand trillion miles across should be home to billions of stars, but it's virtually empty, and scientists are struggling to find an explanation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio high school locked down after 100-person brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10017253/Multiple-people-stabbed-massive-brawl-breaks-Ohio-high-school.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 100 people are believed to have been involved in several brawls inside a Columbus, Ohio high school that required pepper spray to be used and led to the fire alarm being pulled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: BIDEN APPROVAL RECORD LOW</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/354872/biden-approval-rating-hits-new-low-harris.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's job approval rating has reached another low point in his presidency. The overall drop in approval is driven largely by political independents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clowns lurked outside schools to promote speech academy. Horrified parents called police...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Clowns-lurked-outside-schools-to-promote-a-speech-16478765.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple clowns have been spotted loitering outside schools in Singapore - staring...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel in Canada is prize for vaxxed and vigilant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-canada-environment-and-nature-coronavirus-pandemic-d00a3ac04df825881223c372899ffd58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KAMOURASKA, Quebec (AP) — When the pandemic descended, the boundless vistas and insane sunsets of Kamouraska became a distant, unattainable dream for this bicyclist from Virginia. This is one of Quebec's most beautiful places and, for me, a yearly touchstone I could no longer touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Sanctions First Exchange...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cybersecurity/2021/09/treasury-sanctions-first-cryptocurrency-exchange-combat-ransomware/185512/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The department also emphasized guidance for victim organizations who risk running afoul of enforcers by paying attackers and failing to report incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Pins Hopes on 'BOND' Director...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/bond-director-cary-fukunaga-no-time-to-die-1235017724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'No Time to Die' helmer on the last-minute decision to move the film, being the first American to steer the franchise and ushering 007 into a post-MeToo era: "You can’t change Bond overnight, but you can change the world around him."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former treasury secretaries tried defusing debt ceiling bomb with McConnell, Yellen...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/09/22/debt-ceiling-yellen-mnuchin-paulson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet freedom on decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/sep/21/internet-freedom-decline-free-speech-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study cited a lack of regulation in the domestic tech industry, and the rise of authoritarian agencies abroad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Woman with no memory found alone on island inhabited by bears...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-with-memory-loss-found-alone-on-island-inhabited-by-bears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Croatian police said Wednesday they have established the identity of a woman who was found in a remote area on a northern Adriatic island with no recollection of who she was or where she came from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man murdered while feeding homeless in Oakland...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/victim-of-east-oakland-homicide-killed-while-feeding-the-homeless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lisa Chavez says Robert Herron found a way to help others despite his own struggles. In her words, he was a success story with a sad ending. He was one of 100 people killed in Oakland this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of organic food market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/22/organic-food-sales-surged-in-2020-higher-demand-and-cheaper-costs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organic food industry is a booming business. U.S. organic sales surged in 2020 by 12.4% to $61.9 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health director says woman tried to run him off road after backed mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/county-health-director-says-woman-tried-to-run-him-off-the-road-after-he-backed-mask-mandate/ar-AAOGdGL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan’s Kent County Health Department Adam London is one of the many health officials who has reported threats and abuse since the start of the covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you 'own' goal? Collectible NFTs rolling into elite soccer...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210922125917-4kjfl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FINTECH-NFT/DAPPERLABS:Can you 'own' a goal? Collectible NFTs rolling into elite soccer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided Swiss to vote on same-sex marriage...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210922125616-a1aw7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SWISS-LGBT/MARRIAGE (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Divided Swiss to vote on same-sex marriage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Man Fed Up With Speed Bump Smashes It To Pieces!</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/09/21/brighton-park-speed-bump-smashed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We've all grown frustrated with speed bumps at one time or another, but a Brighton Park man was so fed up with the one behind his house that he removed it piece by piece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRE MOOD AT UN MEETING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-general-assembly-health-china-climate-business-ce8a39b4001eb05e572093cd3b6459a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Racism, the climate crisis and the world’s worsening divisions will take center stage at the United Nations on Wednesday, a day after the U.N. chief issued a grim warning that “we are on the edge of an abyss.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra Butter? Consuming More Dairy Fat May PREVENT Heart Attack, Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dairy-fat-prevent-heart-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An international team finds people who consume higher levels of these fats are less likely to develop cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen target Ukraine president aide in 'assassination attempt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210922-gunmen-target-ukraine-president-aide-in-assassination-attempt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunmen target Ukraine president aide in 'assassination attempt'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain tells food industry to prepare for CO2 price shock...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210922080748-6vlvb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWER-PRICES/BRITAIN-CARBONDIOXIDE (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Britain tells its food industry to prepare for CO2 price shock</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My whole life in van': Islanders flee Spanish volcano...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-africa-environment-and-nature-canary-islands-acid-rain-d60ce64a9d3df03aefa358013415f728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TODOQUE, Canary Islands (AP) — A wall of lava up to 12 meters (40 feet) high bore down on a Spanish village Wednesday as islanders scrambled to save what they could before the molten rock swallowed up their homes following a volcanic eruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS AT WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/22/biden-warring-democratic-factions-513564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many party lawmakers have waited weeks for their president, after a summer largely focused on off-Hill crises, to turn his attention to the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden slips into political quicksand...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/22/biden-haitian-migrant-513561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is bucking calls to stop deportations of Haitians even as his team expresses outrage over images or aggressive treatment by border agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Bush to hold fundraiser for Cheney...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/573331-bush-to-hold-fundraiser-for-cheney</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President George W. Bush is reportedly scheduled to hold a fundraiser for Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Online Betting Boom Carving Up Century-Old U.K. Bookies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/u-s-online-betting-boom-is-carving-up-century-old-u-k-bookies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Online Betting Boom Is Carving Up Century-Old U.K. Bookies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The press ever-so-politely turns on Biden, as troubles mount...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/573322-the-press-ever-so-politely-turns-on-biden-a-troubles-mount</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden is finally getting criticism from the political press, at least as it pertains to the stories they actually cover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States, cities grapple with critical school bus driver shortage...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/573288-states-cities-grapple-with-critical-school-bus-driver-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;School districts around the country are struggling to fill thousands of bus driver positions as students return to in-person classes this fall while worker shortages lead to late arrivals and last-minute scrambles to bring retired workers back onto payrolls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Gandolfini and Riddle of Tony Soprano...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/22/michael-gandolfini-and-the-riddle-of-tony-soprano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Michael Gandolfini was filming his role in “The Many Saints of Newark,” a period crime drama that casts him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERGRANDE veers toward default -- and $300 billion global shock...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/china-evergrande-debt-markets/2021/09/22/eeb80fd4-19cc-11ec-bea8-308ea134594f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a pledge to pay some debts due this week, the massive property developer is teetering on the brink of collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel makes late push to secure legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/germany-e2-80-99s-merkel-makes-final-campaign-push-for-stumbling-political-heir/ar-AAOGZBA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armin Laschet has campaigned poorly, threatening Merkel’s legacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil health minister tests positive at UN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-health-minister-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-at-un-general-assembly/ar-AAOGB0w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marcelo Queiroga was accompanying a defiantly unvaccinated President Jair Bolsonaro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Abbott sends miles of cars to deter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/21/us/del-rio-texas-border-crisis/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 8,600 migrants remaining under the Del Rio International Bridge, Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said Tuesday officials are using "unprecedented" methods to deter migrants from crossing into the state, including parking Texas National Guard and Texas Department of Public Safety vehicles for miles along the border to create a "steel barrier."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: Stronger mortgage demand points to surge in home sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/22/stronger-mortgage-demand-points-to-september-surge-in-home-sales.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage demand rose last week as more buyers came into the housing market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, GOOGLE raise new concerns by yanking Russian app...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-europe-business-russia-vladimir-putin-b811d32132c41840e1eb32c024235452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERKELEY, Calif. (AP) — Big Tech companies that operate around the globe have long promised to obey local laws and to protect civil rights while doing business. But when Apple and Google capitulated to Russian demands and removed a political-opposition app from their local app stores, it raised worries that two of the world's most successful companies are more comfortable bowing to undemocratic edicts — and maintaining a steady flow of profits — than upholding the rights of their users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Haitian migrants being released in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-united-states-texas-el-paso-del-rio-3a8146cbcb47b9df7a31a19594df3ec6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas (AP) — Many Haitian migrants camped in a small Texas border town are being released in the United States, two U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S HIS 'IMPEACHMENT' NOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2021/09/impeachment-american-crime-story-drudge-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After fleshing out Monica Lewinsky and Linda Tripp’s story lines, the series switches focus to Matt Drudge, the controversial figure who outed Bill Clinton’s affair to the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLINTON VICTIMS:  MATT WAS OUR HERO!</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2016/11/02/exclusive-video-broaddrick-willey-jones-praise-hero-drudge-breitbart-slam-mainstream-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victims of Bill Clinton’s alleged sexual assault - Juanita Broaddrick, Kathleen Willey, and Paula Jones - have blasted mainstream news media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insidious new Covid variant found in Kentucky nursing home... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3707195/new-covid-variant-kentucky-nursing-home-mutations-virus-antibodies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW variant of COVID-19 with deadly mutations that give it “increased resistance to antibodies” was discovered in a Kentucky nursing home. The variant, called R.1, infected 45 residen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Sues NEW YORK TIMES and His Niece Over Tax Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/donald-trump-sues-new-york-times-and-his-niece-mary-trump-over-tax-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president claims there was an “insidious plot to obtain confidential and highly-sensitive records.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE HEALTH DRAMA STRIKES WENDY WILLIAMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3705485/wendy-williams-hospitalized-evaluation-weeks-premiere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WENDY Williams is expected to remain under medical evaluation for weeks and her show’s premiere will likely be pushed back yet again after she was hospitalized for psychiatric issues ear…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates Awkwardly Addresses Ties to Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/bill-gates-gives-a-super-cringe-answer-when-confronted-about-his-ties-to-jeffrey-epstein-well-hes-dead-so/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a Tuesday with Judy Woodruff on PBS, Gates appeared to be caught off-guard by a series of questions relating to Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN AVOIDS CHINA</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-09-21/biden-xi-avoid-referencing-one-another-at-un-as-us-leader-softens-tone-on-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neither leader directly mentioned the other in their remarks at the U.N. General Assembly, though some references were unmistakable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THISCLOSE: VIRGINIA GOV RACE TIGHTENING...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/21/poll-mcauliffe-lead-virginia-513426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results are similar to other recent polls showing McAuliffe with a slight advantage in a tight race for governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES AT UN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-general-assembly-health-china-coronavirus-pandemic-africa-3284c8ff8739dd7cfaf78db214098403</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — In person and on screen, world leaders returned to the United Nations' foremost gathering for the first time in the pandemic era on Tuesday with a formidable, diplomacy-packed agenda and a sharply worded warning from the international organization's leader: “We face the greatest cascade of crises in our lifetime.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEMORIES:  HOW DRUDGE CHANGED IT ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.townandcountrymag.com/leisure/arts-and-culture/a37619535/who-was-matt-drudge-american-crime-story-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.townandcountrymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The influential reporter is back in the spotlight thanks to a pivotal role in Impeachment: American Crime Story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Cards The New Fake IDs?</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/09/20/covid-19-fake-vaccine-card-fraud-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From concerts to college campuses, from the office to the bar, proof of vaccination is quickly becoming common. There’s now concern that fake vaccine cards could become the new fake ID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deported Haitians try to rush back into plane amid anger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/port-au-prince-haiti-c01b09afb49c4586fdd718031d32402a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti (AP) — Dozens of migrants upset about being deported to Haiti from the U.S. clashed with authorities while trying to rush back into a plane that landed Tuesday afternoon in Port-au-Prince.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARA LOGAN:  Migrant Surge Way To Launch 'Virus Attack in Country'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/lara-logan-says-bioweapons-specialists-told-her-migrant-surge-is-a-way-to-launch-a-virus-attack-in-your-own-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Those are questions that we don't even get a chance to ask."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Storm Drain To Enter Illegally...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/09/20/border-patrol-agents-find-migrants-using-storm-drain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio Grande Valley Sector Border Patrol agents responding to a hotel used for human smuggling discovered migrants using a storm drain to illegally enter the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC study says virus can spread in dosed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-education-florida-pandemics-9aa03a247c10215079cafff898b60ab7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK — Health officials in Bangkok have made headway in their effort to vaccinate children against the coronavirus, giving shots of the Pfizer vaccine to students ages 12 to 18 with underlying diseases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Meals Going Green...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mcdonalds-happy-meal-toys-plastic-phase-out-ab165f1c-1b00-4abe-9c6c-5ca154ce4878.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It will instead offer toys made from recycled or bio-based and plant-derived materials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN WANTS TO SPEAK</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210921201715-1njar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/UN-TALIBAN (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Taliban names Afghan U.N. envoy, asks to speak to world leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German police detain suspect in hostage drama on bus...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210921201114-1di25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-CRIME/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-German police detain suspect in hostage drama on bus -Focus Online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge hack reveals embarrassing details of who's behind Proud Boys website...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/huge-hack-reveals-embarrassing-details-of-who-e2-80-99s-behind-proud-boys-and-other-far-right-websites/ar-AAOFRQk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epik long has been the favorite Internet company of the far-right, providing domain services to QAnon theorists, Proud Boys and other instigators of the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans' Superdome catches fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10014045/Massive-fire-breaks-roof-New-Orleans-Superdome-Stadium.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early reports said the fire broke out while the roof of the New Orleans Superdome was being water pressured in preparation to be painted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Quits Over Vax Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/09/21/craig-greeno-denver-sheriff-deputy-quits-covid-vaccine-mandate-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deputy for the Denver Sheriff Department has left the job he held for 9 years, saying the City of Denver's mandatory COVID-19 vaccination order "put him over the edge."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside mutant 'double muscle' pigs, cows...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3702825/inside-the-mutant-double-muscle-pigs-and-cows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUTANT “double muscle” pigs and cows are being bred to potentially help ward off beef and pork shortages. Shocking images of the super-sized farm animals have emerged as scientists reve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Craig slammed for saying Bond 'shouldn't be played by woman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/3704656/daniel-craig-says-james-bond-played-by-a-woman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANIEL Craig has said that James Bond should not be played by a woman – but instead female actors should be written “better parts”. The 007 actor, 53, believes that women can do b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Ex-Spy Chief Caught After Years Disguised in Wigs, Fake Mustaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7ey88/venezuelas-ex-spy-chief-caught-after-years-disguised-in-wigs-and-fake-mustaches</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DEA finally caught up with Hugo Carvajal, the former military intelligence chief of the regime of President Hugo Chávez, in Spain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three-alarm fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/article_33fc9b50-1b03-11ec-8cf4-0735a61cb2d6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Caesars Superdome caught fire Tuesday afternoon, with open flames and smoke billowing from the edge of its iconic roof as New Orleans firefighters rushed to respond to the blaze.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flames pour from Superdome roof in New Orleans... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-fires-new-orleans-4436f19fe1499ed72f62fd9265f2ed8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Smoke and flames shot through the side of the Superdome's roof on Tuesday as crews worked to clean and prepare the New Orleans sports and entertainment arena for painting. The New Orleans Fire Department confirmed firefighters responded to flames on the building's roof shortly before 1 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allegations first 'superspreader' event occurred in Wuhan Military Games in Oct '19...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/coronavirus/global/allegations-first-superspreader-covid-event-occurred-in-wuhan-military-games-in-october-2019/news-story/d7a612421bc888367020b7e3b8f5f072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese whistleblower has made the bombshell claim that the Covid pandemic could have emerged in Wuhan months before the first outbreak was officially reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Songwriting Star Who Won't Let America Forget Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/the-morning-jolt/the-songwriting-star-who-wont-let-america-forget-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singer-songwriter John Ondrasik is on a one-man cultural crusade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Begin Effort to Curb Post-Trump Presidential Powers...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210921151047-7178k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTIONS/CONGRESS (PIX):Post Trump, U.S. Democrats offer bill to rein in presidential powers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson admits he has 6 children...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/21/uk/boris-johnson-admits-he-has-six-children-intl-gbr/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson has finally admitted that he has six children, a question he has previously dodged in numerous interviews and press conferences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emmys granted exemption to mask rules...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/21/emmys-granted-exemption-to-covid-19-mask-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles health officials are defending the 2021 Emmy Awards as a justified “exception” to the local mask mandate after the show faced backlash for its maskless A-list guests.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
