<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers worry '20 will be blueprint for stealing future election...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/lawmakers-worry-2020-will-blueprint-stealing-future-election-rcna24568</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials fear that unless Congress changes the 19th century law controlling presidential elections, a future election could also be overturned. Legally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as 'dead' captain filmed at 'survivors' parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5140378/mystery-dead-captain-sunk-russian-moskva-survivors-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MYSTERY has surrounded the sunk Russian warship Moskva as Kremlin has released a video appearing to show survivors including the captain who was reported dead after the hit. Two days after the atta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unseen scars of those who kill via remote control...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/uw-grads-story-reveals-the-unseen-scars-of-those-who-kill-via-remote-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air Force Capt. Kevin Larson was one of the best drone pilots in the Air Force. The military failed to recognize the toll the job was taking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ordinary couple pulled off $150 million art heist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/16/ordinary-new-mexico-couple-pulled-off-150-million-art-heist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How an unassuming married couple pulled off a $150 million heist and got away with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB party attack leaves 2 dead, 9 injured in Pittsburgh...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/shooting-at-party-in-airbnb-leaves-2-dead-9-injured-in-pittsburgh-city-says/ar-AAWiYEb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes erupt again near flashpoint Jerusalem holy site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-jerusalem-israel-arrests-03ebd01a1e69b177941165c1f3db7d75</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli police on Sunday entered the Al-Aqsa Mosque compound in Jerusalem's Old City to secure the way for Jewish visitors to the flashpoint holy site, fueling clashes that left 17 Palestinians wounded, according to Palestinian medical workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mariupol on the brink as surrender deadline passes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/live-blog/russia-ukraine-war-live-updates-mariupol-brink-surrender-deadline-pass-rcna24716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia offered to spare the lives of Ukrainian soldiers fighting in Mariupol if they laid down their arms Sunday, as the weeks-long resistance in the besieged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt agency accidentally kills 3,000 animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/article/us-government-agency-accidentally-killed-almost-3000-animals-in-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indiscriminate traps, used to reduce crop and safety threats, also snare federally protected species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA stuck going 83 mph on highway, driver alleges...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Tesla-stuck-going-83-mph-17084202.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The turn signals, hazard lights and accelerator all reportedly went haywire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male model testing gender norms in changing Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220417-the-male-model-testing-gender-norms-in-a-changing-saudi-arabia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his hot pink hair extensions and leopard print pantsuit, model Ziad al-Mesfer was bound to turn heads during his recent public photo shoot in deeply conservative Saudi Arabia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea tests new tactical guided weapon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-south-korea-north-d528bd391034f565d9d80a4a09cd8fed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea has test-fired a new type of tactical guided weapon designed to boost its nuclear fighting capability, state media reported Sunday, a day before its chief rivals the United States and South Korea begin annual military drills that the North views as an invasion rehearsal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky urges Ukrainians to buy anti-radiation pills...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/zelensky-warns-russian-nuclear-attack-26730111</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volodymyr Zelensky has urged his country to be ready for the worst case scenario, warning that Russia's potential use of nuclear weapons in future cannot be ruled out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  12 injured, 3 detained in SC mall shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article260484432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the latest details on the Columbiana Centre mall shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portable nuke device missing from stolen vehicle in PA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/portable-nuclear-device-missing-stolen-vehicle-pennsylvania-rcna24686</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“As long as the device is not tampered with or damaged, it presents no hazard to public safety,” David Allard, director of the Bureau of Radiation Protection, said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another wild protest breaks out during NBA game...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/16/protestor-chains-herself-to-basket-during-timberwolves-grizzlies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Timberwolves aren’t done with protesters delaying their games. An animal rights activist chained herself to the basket stanchion Saturday during Game 1 of the Timberolves-Grizzlies playoff seri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art Rupe, pioneering record executive, dead at 104...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/16/art-rupe-pioneering-record-executive-dead-at-104/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Music executive Art Rupe, whose Specialty Records was a premier label during the formative years of rock ’n roll and helped launch the careers of Little Richard, Sam Cooke and many …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crew of sunken warship 'shown for first time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-61129151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's defence ministry releases a video purportedly showing the crew of the Moskva in Sevastopol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Romance With Robots Already Here...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uncanny-future-romance-robots-already-013111368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyIn the late 2000s, a lifestyle reporter in Moscow named Eugenia Kuyda, then in her early twenties, decided to produce a cover story on Roman Mazurenko, the person at the center of Moscow’s creative hipster scene at the time. Right from the start, Eugenia and Roman both felt they had a profound connection, and soon became close friends.A few years later, Kuyda moved to San Francisco to start a chatbot-based virtual assistant company. Shortly after, Mazur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opponents of far-right protest as campaign enters final week...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-04-16/opponents-of-french-far-right-plan-protests-as-election-campaign-enters-final-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avian flu has spread to 27 states, sharply driving up egg prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/avian-flu-has-spread-to-27-states-sharply-driving-up-egg-prices/ar-AAWgZBQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly gun violence surges with at least 24 people shot in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/shooting-philadelphia-kensington-mantua-strawberry-mansion-20220415.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shootings happened in neighborhoods across the city and at all hours of the day, police said, with bullets striking people who ranged in age from 18 to 65.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
