<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>
Vietnam 'totalitarian' law bans online criticism of govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/02/vietnam-criticised-for-totalitarian-law-banning-online-criticism-of-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law forces internet providers to censor content deemed ‘toxic’ by the ruling communist government and hand over user data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers threaten to expose secret 9/11 documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/hackers-threaten-expose-911-documents-13802700</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hackers say that the documents will be released unless a hefty, yet undisclosed, ransom is paid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP-FREE SHOW?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/golden-globes-hosts-sandra-andy-samberg-preview-crazy-pants-show-1172092 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first-time Golden Globes MCs interview each other (with The Hollywood Reporter's help) about their "five days" of prep, taking advantage of the "looser atmosphere," why they will avoid Trump and whether they might get, uh, naked during NBC's live telecast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron govt on tenterhooks as new tax regime takes effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190102-macron-govt-tenterhooks-new-tax-regime-takes-effect</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macron govt on tenterhooks as new tax regime takes effect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at CDC for failing to act on mystery polio-like virus; 'Disease is monster'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6545673/Furious-parents-blast-CDC-failing-act-virus-left-hundreds-kids-paralyzed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furious mothers of children, who have been left partially disabled and fully paralyzed by the polio-like illness of Acute Flaccid Myelitis (AFM) have blasted the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT RESPONDS:  BE TEAM PLAYER AND WIN...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/423455-trump-to-romney-after-op-ed-be-a-team-player-win </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Wednesday responded to an op-ed written by Sen.-elect Mitt Romney (R-Utah), suggesting the incoming senator should be more supportive of his policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying Harry Reid on Trump: He's Amoral, Has No Conscience...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dying-harry-reid-on-trump-hes-amoral-has-no-conscience</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Senate Majority Leader says Trump lacks the discipline of a mob boss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NYT editor rips paper's anti-Trump bias; Eroding credibility...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-n-y-times-editor-rips-trump-coverage-as-biased</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former executive editor of the New York Times says the paper’s news pages, the home of its straight-news coverage, have become “unmistakably anti-Trump.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clever AI hid data from its creators to cheat at appointed task...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/31/this-clever-ai-hid-data-from-its-creators-to-cheat-at-its-appointed-task/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depending on how paranoid you are, this research from Stanford and Google will be either terrifying or fascinating. A machine learning agent intended to transform aerial images into street maps and back was found to be cheating by hiding information it would need later in "a nearly imperceptible, h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California inmate takes unlikely path to freedom: Podcasting...</title>
      <link>http://www.therepublic.com/2019/01/02/us-podcasting-inmate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.therepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California inmate will continue working on a popular podcast after his recent release from San Quentin State Prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Year, Oscar More Likely to Go to Film You've Actually Seen...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2019/01/02/oscars-2019-best-picture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race is already heated with big studio blockbusters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular Weather App Collects Too Much User Data, Security Experts Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/popular-weather-app-collects-too-much-user-data-security-experts-say-11546428914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A weather-forecasting app from TCL Communication Technology Holdings—maker of Alcatel smartphones—asks for data beyond what’s normal for a weather program, a security firm says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$73 MILLION: 20-year-old most expensive American soccer player ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/christian-pulisic-becomes-most-expensive-u-s-soccer-star-after-record-transfer-11546427455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian Pulisic agreed a $73 million move to English side Chelsea from Borussia Dortmund of Germany that should see him playing in the English Premier League from the start of next season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Warns Taiwan Unification Is Goal and Military Force Is Option...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/world/article-a-more-confident-china-threatens-military-force-in-taiwan-holds-up/?cmpid=rss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing intensifies efforts for unification with self-governing democratic region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests in India after women defy ancient ban on visiting Hindu temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-temple/protests-in-india-after-women-defy-ancient-ban-on-visiting-hindu-temple-idUSKCN1OW07Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women defied a centuries-old ban on entering a Hindu temple in the Indian st...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army, in Need of Recruits, Turns Focus to Liberal-Leaning Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/02/us/army-recruiting-tech-industry-seattle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too few recruits are signing up from cities like Chicago and Seattle, so the Army is trying to frame enlistment as a patriotic detour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks Open 2019 With Tumble... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/02/stock-markets-dow-futures-fall-after-weak-economic-data-in-china.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street is set for a weak start to 2019, as more disappointing data from China weighed on global markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Worst Start Since 1995...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hong-kong-stocks-kick-off-075113201.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hang Seng Index closed down 2.8 percent, its biggest loss since Oct. 23. Cnooc Ltd. was the worst performer, suffering its largest drop in nearly three years. The Hang Seng China Enterprises Index retreated below the 10,000 level, closing at its lowest since February 2017, while the Shanghai Composite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haddish Admits She Bombed at Gig...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tiffany-haddish-admits-she-bombed-in-new-years-eve-gig-i-wish-it-was-better/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I have a strong feeling this will never happened [sic] again," comedian Tiffany Haddish tweets after botched performance in Miami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope bemoans disjointed world...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-peace/pope-bemoans-disjointed-world-praises-unity-over-diversity-idUSKCN1OV1I6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis, in his first message of the new year on Tuesday, bemoaned a lack o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Vows New York Will Lead Nation With Progressive Agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Governor-Andrew-Cuomo-Inaugural-Ellis-Island-Speech-Third-Term-NY-503773581.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo is beginning 2019 and his third term with an inaugural address on Ellis Island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTuber who stabbed Tinder date dies in police custody...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/bodybuilder-who-stabbed-tinder-date-dying-police-custody-was-getting-n953356</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney for Erich Stelzer's family said the 25-year-old had been suffering from delusions, erratic behavior and extreme paranoia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big IPOs eyeing brittle Wall Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190102-big-ipos-eyeing-brittle-wall-street-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big IPOs eyeing a brittle Wall Street in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba celebrates 60 years of revolution amid challenges and change... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/cuba-celebrates-60-years-revolution-amid-challenges-change-193231301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba, long a source of inspiration for leftist Latin American governments, celebrated the 60th anniversary of its revolution on Tuesday facing increasing isolation in a region dominated by a resurgent right. The first such anniversary of the post-Castro era coincided with the inauguration in Brazil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong leads Asia markets down as 2019 starts on sour note... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-leads-asia-markets-down-2019-starts-031638926--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian markets sank Wednesday, starting the new year by extending a slide that made 2018 the worst in a decade, with investors jolted by data reinforcing weakness in China's economy. Hong Kong led the losses, tumbling more than two percent, while Shanghai shed one percent after two indicators showed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX BOWS TO KINGDOM</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/netflix-drops-satire-episode-critical-saudi-arabia-164703467.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix confirmed Tuesday that it removed an episode of a satirical comedy show that criticizes Saudi Arabia, after officials in the kingdom reportedly complained. In the episode of "Patriot Act with Hasan Minhaj," the American-born Muslim lashed Saudi Arabia after the killing of Washington</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas tech show to celebrate innovation amid mounting concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/a/global-tech-show-to-celebrate-innovation-amid-mounting-concerns/4725243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jan. 8-11 Las Vegas trade event offers a glimpse into new products and services designed to make people's lives easier, fun and more productive, though talk of security is expected to grow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY DOWNLOADS ON TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/How-a-president-shapes-the-public-character-13502232.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump presidency made a deep descent in December. The departures of Defense Secretary Jim Mattis and White House Chief of Staff John Kelly, the appointment of senior persons of lesser experience, the abandonment of allies who fight beside us, and the president's thoughtless claim that America has long been a "sucker" in world affairs all defined his presidency down. It is well known that Donald Trump was not my choice for the Republican presidential nomination. After he became the nominee, I hoped his campaign would refrain from resentment and name-calling. It did not. When he won the election, I hoped he would rise to the occasion. His early appointments of Rex Tillerson, Jeff Sessions, Nikki Haley, Gary Cohn, H.R.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Ratings Fall Double Digits...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/new-years-eve-tv-ratings-monday-dec-31-2018-1172083</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC leads the way per usual but is down by double digits from a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation so divided, resentful and angry...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/423435-romney-slams-trumps-character-in-new-op-ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incoming Utah Senator and former GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney slammed President Trump's character on Tuesday, writing in a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's magazines dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Womens-magazines-are-dying-will-we-miss-them-13501865.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In late November, Glamour came to the same conclusion reached by so many other women's magazines these days: After 80 years in mailboxes and grocery store checkouts, it will stop publishing its glossy monthly, ending with the January issue. For Glamour, print is officially dead, the inexorable "pivot to digital" now complete. Teen Vogue, a junior version of the fashion bible, was already there. Self, purveyor of 1,000 ways to say goodbye to your back fat, disappeared from the racks in 2017. Seventeen, once a lifestyle primer for high school girls everywhere, now will publish only special issues, and Redbook, one of the "seven sisters" of magazines for suburban housewives, is high-tailing it to the web as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21-year-old QB youngest ever to start NFL playoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/sports/ravens/bs-sp-ravens-lamar-jackson-youngest-qb-20181231-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While fresh-faced quarterbacks have struggled in postseason play, it hasn’t exactly been a case of the young and the feckless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican mayor gunned down after being sworn in...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/mexican-mayor-gunned-down-after-being-sworn-n953601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Alejandro Murat confirmed the killing of Tlaxiaco Mayor Alejandro Aparicio Santiago via his Twitter account Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady overestimated himself and lost $5 million...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/01/tom-brady-overestimated-himself-and-lost-5-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady bet on himself this season and lost big. As part of a series of team-friendly deals the three-time MVP has taken from the Patriots, Brady had $5 million in performance bonuses built into …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banks pull back as rewards cards gain fanatic following...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/rewards-credit-cards-gained-a-fanatic-followingnow-banks-are-pulling-back-11546365926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major perks like airfare and cash back were meant to lead to higher returns. But consumers figured out how to game the system. Now banks are trying to figure out how to keep customers happy while cutting extras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BRIEF INVITATION</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-tells-America-to-chill-out-and-ENJOY-THE-13501836.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump has invited congressional leaders to the White House for a briefing on border security, the first face-to-face session involving Republicans and Democrats as the partial government shutdown entered its second week. The briefing will occur one day before Democrats take control of the House and Trump gets his first taste of divided government. It was unclear whether the Wednesday session would break the budget impasse - now in its 11th day - as Trump had demanded billions of dollars for a U.S.-Mexico border wall and Democrats have rejected his request. Trump had campaigned on a pledge to build the wall at Mexico's expense, a proposition Mexican officials called ludicrous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LET'S MAKE A DEAL?'</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-to-pelosi-on-shutdown-border-wall-lets-make-a-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the fight over the federal government shutdown entered the new year, President Trump on Tuesday expressed his desire to “make a deal” with House Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi over funding for his border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targets crime, leftwing 'ideology'...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/3954/new-brazil-leader-bolsonaro-targets-crime-leftwing-ideology-doc-1bx3qe2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falwell Jr. Argues 'Immoral' For Evangelicals Not to Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/jerry-falwell-jr-argues-its-immoral-for-evangelicals-not-to-support-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack racing league poised to take off...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/jetpack-aviation-racing-test-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitaltrends.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are you ready to enter the world of jetpack racing as a spectator sport? Jetpack Aviation recently tested the concept by carrying out some test flights in which two jetpack pilots flew within close proximity of one another. The next step is to put together a racing league.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian women form '385-mile human chain' for equality...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-46728521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women in Kerala form a huge "women's wall" after protesters stopped them entering a Hindu temple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA fires tear gas to stop migrants from breaching border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/1/us-fires-tear-gas-stop-migrants-breaching-tijuana-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. authorities fired tear gas into Mexico during the first hours of the new year to repel about 150 migrants who were trying to breach the border fence in Tijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sink US aircraft carriers': China chilling recipe to dominate sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/military/sink-two-aircraft-carriers-chinese-admirals-chilling-recipie-to-dominate-the-south-china-sea/news-story/aaa8c33d57da62e7d5e28e791aa26e0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re the pride of the US fleet: enormous 100,000 tonne, 333m long nuclear-powered aircraft carriers. But Beijing thinks they’re Washington’s achilles heel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC, Baltimore defy big city killing downward trend...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/homicides-spike-in-dc-and-baltimore-defying-downward-trend-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homicides surged about 40 percent last year in the nation's capital while nearby Baltimore continued to notch almost one killing per day — defying the downward trend in other big U.S. cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Trump All Day' -- Kanye Reaffirms Support Via Tweetstorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/columns/hip-hop/8491999/kanye-west-trump-support-twitter-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West took to Twitter on New Year's Day to make it clear where he stands politically in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMICIDE SURGE IN NATION'S CAPITAL...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2019/01/2018-homicides-in-the-district-increased-while-the-murder-rate-in-other-parts-of-our-region-went-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Washington, D.C., 160 people died by homicide in 2018, up from 116 in 2017 — a spike of about 40 percent. City officials say more gun violence has contributed to the rising number of murders, and D.C. saw one of the biggest increases in fatal shootings nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year in numbers: 2,860 tweets, 66 judges...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/423327-tweets-confirmations-and-rallies-trumps-year-in-number</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s second year in office was highlighted by controversial tweets, clashes over immigration policies and federal judges, a return to the campaign trail and much of the same internal chaos that shadowed his first year in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazmat Crews Respond To BWI Airport After Passengers Feel Ill...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/01/01/hazmat-crews-respond-to-bwi-airport-after-passengers-report-feeling-ill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hazmat crews and police responded to BWI airport Tuesday afternoon after several passengers reported feeling ill in the baggage area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revelers firing guns shoot kids, celebrants -- and themselves...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/article223802775.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In at least two cases, men celebrating New Year’s Eve with gunfire accidentally shot themselves, police in Kansas and Ohio say. Children and others also were injured by stray bullets across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1-year-old falls into rhino exhibit at zoo...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/child-falls-rhino-exhibit-florida-zoo/story?id=60107410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The child was rushed to a local pediatric hospital in Orlando, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car carrier on fire in Pacific, some crew abandon ship...</title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2018/12/31/coast-guard-commercial-vessels-responding-large-fire-aboard-car-carrier-off-oahu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The distance involved here requires any and all available support."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump invites congressional leaders to White House for wall briefing...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/01/government-shutdown-update-trump-congress-1077368</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting would be the first time the president has sat down with Democrats since the shutdown started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Biden Paved Way...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/01/us/politics/joe-biden-presidential-campaign-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of careful financial decisions, and the creation of nonprofits and academic centers staffed by close advisers, would help a campaign-in-waiting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN hosts blast NYPD...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6543057/New-Yorks-Times-Square-bundles-soggy-New-Years-Eve.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hosts of CNN's New Year's Eve celebration in New York City Andy Cohen and Anderson Cooper butted heads with Times Square security over their use of umbrellas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rose Parade Float Catches Fire...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/01/01/chinese-american-heritage-foundation-float-disabled-by-small-fire-disrupting-rose-parade-route/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A float malfunction caused a traffic jam at the Rose Parade on Tuesday morning. The Chinese American Heritage Foundation’s train float was disabled by a small fire and was towed for the rest of the Rose Parade route, according to Cheryl Moody, a commander for the Pasadena Police Department. The float, which depicted the moment when two locomotives met face to face upon completion of the Transcontinental Railroad, was wreathed in smoke near where the parade began on Orange Grove Boulevard. A tow truck tried, and failed, to pull the 95-foot float onto a side street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine killed on duty in DC...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/local-news/marine-barracks-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials report that a Marine is dead after a shooting at the Marine Barracks in Southeast, D.C. The shooting was reported around 5 a.m. Officials say the Marine was shot and hospitalized but later died from a gunshot wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterdrone Technologies Face Slow Ramp-Up at Airports Globally...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/counterdrone-technologies-face-slow-ramp-up-at-airports-globally-11546283774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite world-wide concerns about unmanned aircraft buzzing around airports, suppliers of commercial drone-detection equipment generally have been looking elsewhere for sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants hide INSIDE mattresses to reach Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8095098/video-migrants-hidden-bed-mattress-van-europe-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the astonishing moment migrants were discovered hidden inside bed mattresses strapped to a van in a desperate bid to reach Europe. Shocking footage shows border officers slashing open plast…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Virus named for anime demon likely culprit in newspaper attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/business/technology/sd-virus-named-for-anime-demon-ryuk-is-likely-culprit-in-attack-on-union-tribune-other-newspapers-20190101-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryuk, a malware program that hobbled newspapers nationwide this weekend, is a sophisticated twist on an extortionate classic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA spacecraft signals from most distant object EVER visited...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/space/nasa-s-new-horizons-spacecraft-signals-most-distant-object-ever-n953546</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The full scope of observations made by New Horizons will take nearly 2 years to beam back to Earth because it traveled so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing taco sauce sparks gunfire at TACO BELL drive-thru...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article223797740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Taco Bell customer angry about not getting any taco sauce shot out a drive-thru window early Monday at an Oklahoma City restaurant, police say. He also entered the eatery as employees hid in a bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Pulls Show Critical Of Saudi Government...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90286962/netflix-pulls-episode-of-hasan-minhajs-show-that-criticizes-the-saudi-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian called out America’s and Silicon Valley’s relationships with the regime after journalist Jamal Khashoggi’s murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Philly homicide of 2019 just 12 MINUTES into new year...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6544857/Philadelphia-sees-homicide-2019-just-12-MINUTES-new-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was shot in the head at 00.12am on New Years Day in Kensington in Philadelphia. The murder follows the PA city's bloodiest year in 11 years. The man in his twenties was found on the sidewalk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican blocked U.S. bishops from addressing sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bc645408ad404df3bc9797c26cfde6d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — The Vatican blocked U.S. bishops from taking measures to address the clergy sex abuse scandal because U.S. church leaders failed to sufficiently consult with the Holy See beforehand about legally problematic proposals, according to a letter obtained by The Associated Press. The Nov. 11 letter from the Vatican's Cardinal Marc Ouellet provides the primary reason that Rome balked at the measures that were to be voted on by the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops at its Nov. 12-14 assembly. The blocked vote stunned abuse survivors and other Catholics who were demanding action from U.S. bishops to address clergy sex abuse and cover-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC WARNS TOUGH FLU SEASON UNDERWAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/living/index.ssf/2019/01/cdc_could_be_a_tough_flu_season_based_on_early_viruses_hospitalizations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;H1N1 viruses, the cause of the 2009 global pandemic, predominate so far this season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSM: HE. WILL. STEP. DOWN...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/423132-predictions-trump-goes-unexpected-candidate-emerges-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the coming year, Trump will alienate even GOP senators and Fox News, and a surprising Democratic presidential candidate will step forth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YEAR END POLL:  APPROVAL 47%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/political_updates/prez_track_dec28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: What NETFLIX Means When Says 45 Million Watched Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bird-box-45-million-viewers-netflix-bandersnatch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix said "Bird Box" was viewed by more than 45 million different accounts during its first 7 days, which drew both cheers and snickers from onlookers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Workers Using TWITTER for BDSM Meetups...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-sex-workers-using-twitter-for-bdsm-meetups-you-have-to-trust-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Goddesses’ have turned to social media to arrange covert rendezvous with those—usually men—interested in financial domination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: CALM DOWN AND ENJOY THE RIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-ushers-in-2019-saying-calm-down-and-enjoy-the-ride-amid-new-year-challenges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump ushered in 2019 in characteristic fashion -- with a tweet expressing supreme confidence in himself, contempt for the “fake news media” and optimism for the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami prostitutes, drug addicts reveal harrowing tales from streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6542633/Brian-Gilden-features-Miami-prostitutes-new-photography-collection.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Gilden captured striking and harrowing portraits of prostitutes for his new collection Only God Can Judge Me. They told him stories of being set on fire and getting hooked on drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon law takes effect allowing roadkill for food...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/423391-oregon-law-takes-effect-allowing-roadkill-for-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new law took effect in Oregon on Tuesday allowing meat from animals killed by vehicles to be harvested and eaten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychic To The Stars Reveals Predictions For Year Ahead...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/12/31/2019-predictions-psychic-nikki-weather-celebrities-health-lottery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychic Nikki makes her 2019 predictions for weather, celebrities, health and the lottery. How do fortunes look for the new year?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver rams into Tokyo crowd in anger over 'death penalty'...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/crime/8-injured-as-man-rams-car-into-pedestrians-in-Harajuku-in-%27retaliation-for-execution%27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people were injured after a man rammed his car into pedestrians on a shopping street in central Tokyo in the early hours of Tuesday, police said. The police arrested Kazuhiro Kusakabe, 21, on suspicion of attempted murder. A 19-year-old university student remains unconscious after being hit by the minicar…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
