<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Want organic meat? Kill it yourself: Hipsters the New Hunters...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/put-down-the-kombucha-and-pick-up-a-crossbow-hipsters-are-the-new-hunters-11547052935</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want organic, sustainable meat? Kill it yourself, say veteran hunters trying to appeal to the next generation of recruits in order to keep the sport alive. ‘Earthy crunchy aligns very well with deer hunting.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record number of migrant families crossing border...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/09/migrant-caravan-trump-crackdown-has-not-slowed-flow-families-us/2523034002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is trying to stop Central American migrants from entering the USA, but new figures show they continue to stream toward the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STORMS OUT OF MEETING WITH DEMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/shutdown-showdown-pelosi-says-no-trump-says-bye-bye-n956836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump abruptly walked out of a closed-door meeting with congressional leaders Wednesday in the White House Situation Room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON DIME!</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalenquirer.com/celebrity/jeff-bezos-divorce-lauren-sanchez-cheating-affair-photos-exclusive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalenquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The marriage of the world’s richest couple is set to explode in all-out war — after billionaire Jeff Bezos was caught cheating on his wife of 25 years with the spouse of a Hollywood mogul! The Nati...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE $140 BILLION DIVORCE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6573485/Amazon-CEO-Jeff-Bezos-novelist-MacKenzie-Bezos-getting-divorce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos, who is worth $140 billion, and novelist MacKenzie Bezos have announced they are divorcing, through a joint statement on Wednesday posted to the Jeff's Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beefed-up WH legal team preps aggressive exec privilege defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Amid-probes-White-House-lawyers-prepare-defense-13522048.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A beefed-up White House legal team is gearing up to prevent President Donald Trump's confidential discussions with top advisers from being disclosed to House Democratic investigators and from being revealed in the special counsel's long-awaited report, setting the stage for a potential clash between the branches of government. The strategy to strongly assert the president's executive privilege on both fronts is being developed under newly arrived White House counsel Pat Cipollone, who has hired 17 lawyers in recent weeks to help in the effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOTAL WASTE OF TIME'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/donald-trump-border-wall-negotiations-nancy-pelosi-chuck-schumer-government-shutdown-today-2019-01-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats and Republicans are digging in on funding the president's border wall as hundreds of thousands of federal workers won't get paid Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico fuel shortage worries industry as lines in capital grow...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190110015846-p34zi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-OIL/THEFT (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Mexico fuel shortage worries industry as lines in capital grow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chocolates recalled over Hepatitis concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.whas11.com/article/news/local/bauers-candies-releases-statement-on-fda-alert-for-possible-hepatitis-a-contamination/417-81795374-10f2-48f3-81c6-4a090ba94810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whas11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA said any Bauer’s Candies Chocolate or Caramel Modjeskas purchased after November 14 should be thrown away because a worker in the facility tested positive for hepatitis A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blades spin inches from mountain during extraordinary rescue...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2019/01/09/watch-extraordinary-helicopter-rescue-in-the-french-alps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pilot showed incredible helicopter skills during a rescue mission in the French Alps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China accuses Canada of 'white supremacy' for demanding release of alleged spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/china-canada-huawei-meng-white-supremacy-11104512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese envoy on Wednesday accused Canada and its allies of "Western egotism and white supremacy" for demanding the immediate release of two ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Roommate busted trying to cash stolen $10M lottery ticket...</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/2019/01/08/vacaville-man-accused-of-stealing-lotto-ticket-worth-10m-from-roommate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VACAVILLE -- Police in Vacaville say a man stole a lottery scratcher worth $10 million from his roommate. The ticket was purchased at the Lucky grocery store on Dec. 20. Police say the man said he bought the $30 ticket in the hope of winning some extra cash for the holidays. The man won and thought at first that the ticket was worth $10,000, according to police. He then told his two roommates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS CRACKING?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/85c7ee1b903841838f620169f14110b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump stalked out of his negotiating meeting with congressional leaders Wednesday — "I said bye-bye," he tweeted soon after — as efforts to end the 19-day partial government shutdown fell into deeper disarray over his demand for billions of dollars to build a wall on the U.S.-Mexico border. Hundreds of thousands of federal workers now face lost paychecks on Friday. The president is to visit the border in person on Thursday, but he has expressed his own doubts that his appearance and remarks will change any minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Aims to Make Big Apple First to Require Paid Vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mayor-de-blasio-aims-to-make-new-york-first-u-s-city-to-require-paid-vacation-11547056738</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio proposed legislation that would require city businesses with more than five employees to provide paid time off. Should it pass, the measure would be the first law of its kind in a U.S. city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poacher gets court date after flirting with game warden on dating app...</title>
      <link>https://www.tulsaworld.com/news/local/cuffing-season-dating-app-chat-leads-to-bust-for-mcintosh/article_76d62c90-d21a-5038-9ba7-d8459c07809c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tulsaworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuffing season took on a whole new meaning for a McIntosh County woman who shared too much information with the wrong man on her dating app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split poised to bump Bezos down wealthy list...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-jeff-bezos-divorce-impact-20190109-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos' split from his long-time wife has the potential to be the world’s most expensive divorce — and drop the most wealthy person on the planet down to the fourth richest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Braces for Highway Closure, Historic Traffic Squeeze...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/seattle-braces-highway-closure-historic-traffic-squeeze-062259074.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — A major thoroughfare for commuters along downtown Seattle's waterfront is set to shut down for good Friday, ushering in what officials say will be one of the most painful traffic periods in the history of the booming Pacific Northwest city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coast Guard families told to hold garage sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2019/01/09/coast-guard-families-told-to-hold-garage-sales-to-cope-with-shutdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 5-page tip sheet published by the Coast Guard Support Program also suggests families babysit for extra money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Gabbard Blasts Dems for 'Religious Bigotry'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/democratic-congresswoman-calls-out-fellow-democrats-for-religious-bigotry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tulsi Gabbard implicitly criticized Democratic senators for subjecting a Catholic judicial nominee to a religious test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHRYSLER Building, Famed Slice of Manhattan Skyline, Up for Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chrysler-building-a-famed-slice-of-manhattan-skyline-is-on-the-block-11547035200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City’s famed Chrysler Building is up for sale, as the art deco landmark’s owners face high costs and stiff competition from new towers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women arrested for alleged assault of trans in bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/two-women-charged-with-assault-on-transgender-person-at-glenwood-south-bar/18110722/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women have been charged with assaulting a 29-year-old transgender person in a bathroom at Milk Bar on Glenwood South in Raleigh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuberculosis, flu, infections rampant... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/31/number-sick-kids-soars-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border authorities are referring 50 people a day for urgent medical care, including tuberculosis, flu and even pregnant women about to give birth, a top official said Monday, saying it’s unlike anything they’ve ever seen before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems to subpoena Don Jr. first...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/house-dems-to-subpoena-donald-trump-jr-first-in-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats probing allegations that the Trump presidential campaign worked with Russian operatives to win the 2016 election plan to issue their first subpoena to Donald Trump Jr., according to a top lawmaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals Ban Visitors as Deadly Flu Spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-01-09/hospitals-restrict-visitors-to-curb-spread-of-flu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA screeners quitting...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/01/09/tsa-union-officers-quitting-over-shutdown-posing-security-threat/2522906002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TSA union official warned that the situation poses a "massive security risk for American travelers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown impacting everyday Americans in unexpected ways...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/01/09/federal-shutdown-impacting-everyday-american-life-jobs-vacations/2519465002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Americans are increasingly feeling the impact of the federal shutdown impasse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theresa May humiliated AGAIN; 2nd time in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8156215/brexit-latest-theresa-may-loses-vote-no-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May has been defeated on Brexit for the second time in 24 hours today as rebels wrestled back power from the Government. Hopes that she can get next week’s deal passed by MPs are now …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  CNN TOPS FOX; DRUDGE OVER GOOGLE NEWS; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GREEN BOOK' Won Big At GLOBES; Hold Up Under Scrutiny?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/Green-Book-won-big-at-the-Golden-Globes-will-13518376.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES - When "Green Book" won three Golden Globes on Sunday, a number of narratives began to take shape: The awards - for best comedy or musical, best screenplay and Mahershala Ali's supporting performance - were among the biggest surprises of the night, upsetting such supposed front-runners as the multi-nominated "Vice" or "Mary Poppins Returns." What's more, "Green Book" arrived at the ceremony dogged by on-screen and off-screen controversies, including criticism from the family of Ali's character, the pianist Don Shirley, as well as accusations that the film is "divisive," perpetuating racist stereotypes of white saviors and "magical Negroes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUTDOWN BITES</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-shutdown-departments-factbox/factbox-impact-on-us-government-widens-on-18th-day-of-shutdown-idUSKCN1P22AB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shutdown of about a quarter of the U.S. government reached its 18th day on Tue...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cars collecting data on everything from weight to music tastes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tech-ces-monitoring/move-aside-backseat-driver-new-tech-at-ces-monitors-you-inside-car-idUSKCN1P219H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As vehicles get smarter, your car will be keeping eyes on you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto hits streets to rebut: 'Sh*t. F*ck yeah'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/09/beto-orourke-border-wall-trump-1089194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O’Rourke filmed himself on Facebook Live for about 75 minutes, visiting friends’ homes and sharing scenic views of the El Paso and Ju&amp;aacute;rez, Mexico, skylines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEFT TURN:  NYC GUARANTEES HEALTHCARE FOR ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/NYC-Health-Care-Guarantee-Mayor-de-Blasio-504046171.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will begin guaranteeing comprehensive health care to every single resident regardless of someone's ability to pay or immigration status, an unprecedented plan that will protect the more than half a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug to clear 'zombie cells' from body in first anti-aging treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/techandscience/drug-to-clear-zombie-cells-from-body-could-be-first-anti-ageing-treatment-after-%E2%80%98impressive%E2%80%99-human-trial/ar-BBRZpiV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela military personnel increasingly jailed, tortured amid coup fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article224089810.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report by Human Rights Watch and Foro Penal says Venezuelan military officials, and their families, are increasingly being detained and tortured amid coup fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Makes Major Correction to Manafort Bombshell...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/new-york-times-makes-major-correction-to-report-on-manafort-and-russian-oligarch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did CIA Director Gina Haspel run black site at Guantanamo?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/guantanamo/article223835570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A declassified argument by a lawyer with top secret clearance appears to disclose an unknown chapter of CIA Director Gina Haspel’s covert career: that she served at Guantánamo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After guilty verdict, prosecutors seek to strip biker gang of trademarked logo...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-mongol-trademark-20190109-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors asked a jury to strip the Mongol biker gang of trademarks it holds over its insignia in a novel legal fight to dismantle the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microbes on Space Station mutating to survive...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/space-bacteria-earth-alien-mutating-survive-disease-international-station-a8717976.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey Manager May Be Key Witness in Sexual Assault Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-spaceys-manager-may-be-key-witness-sexual-assault-case-1174686 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evan Lowenstein — who is said to have spearheaded the "Let Me Be Frank" Christmas Eve video by the actor — was also present at the Nantucket restaurant the night of the alleged assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Samuel L. Jackson Became Hollywood's Most Bankable Star...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/how-samuel-l-jackson-became-hollywoods-bankable-star-1174613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The box office king and Trump golf antagonist beat a crack addiction to build a film career unrivaled in modern stardom, and the 70-year-old 'Glass' actor aims to work well into his 80s — if Marvel and the rest of Hollywood can afford him: "I'm a gunslinger now."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex toys all the buzz at Vegas tech show...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190109-sex-toys-all-buzz-vegas-tech-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex toys all the buzz at Vegas tech show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says Israel ready to thwart election cyber meddling...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190109-netanyahu-says-israel-ready-thwart-election-cyber-meddling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu says Israel ready to thwart election cyber meddling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech wall plan on display at CES...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190108-high-tech-border-wall-plan-display-ces</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-tech border wall plan on display at CES</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire's kidnapped wife held for months amid massive ransom demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/norwegian-billionaires-wife-abducted-kidnappers-demand-10m-ransom-for-her-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are racing to save the life of a Norwegian billionaire’s abducted wife, with the kidnappers demanding $10 million ransom money in exchange for her life and freedom, a sum the police asked the family not to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Traditional masculinity' deemed harmful by medical group...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/american-psychological-association-deems-traditional-masculinity-harmful-could-lead-to-sexual-harassment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Psychological Association for the first time in its history released guidelines concerning men and boys, saying that the so-called “traditional masculinity” not only is “harmful” but also could lead to homophobia and sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: City living giving animals cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6569765/City-life-giving-animals-CANCER.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big polluted cities such as New York and London increase the likelihood that animals will get cancer. Birds, squirrels, rats, mice and hedgehogs are some of the affected wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem donor's THIRD drug victim: 'Thought I was going to die'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6573905/I-thought-going-person-die-Ed-Bucks-house-Man-reveals-Democratic-donor-injected-meth-GHB.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: SEXUALLY EXPLICIT CONTENT. Jermaine Gagnon, 28, spent several nights with Ed Buck at his apartment in L.A. in 2018, where they had oral sex and took drugs together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE $140 BILLION DIVORCE: BEZOS, WIFE ANNOUNCE SPLIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6573485/Amazon-CEO-Jeff-Bezos-novelist-MacKenzie-Bezos-getting-divorce.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos, who is worth $140 billion, and novelist MacKenzie Bezos have announced they are divorcing, through a joint statement on Wednesday posted to the Jeff's Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst measles outbreak in decades sweeps nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6569129/Worst-measles-outbreak-decades-sweeps-New-York-cases-surge-Oregon-Washington-abroad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 160 cases of measles have been reported in New York with most spreading among unvaccinated religious communities. Measles outbreaks have cropped up in over 20 US states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican House Increased Debt $7.9 Trillion in 8 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/republican-house-increased-debt-79-trillion-8-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Paul Ryan and House Speaker John Boehner, March 19, 2013. (Getty Images/T.J. Kirkpatrick) The recently deposed Republican majority increased the federal debt by $7.9 trillion in the eight years it controlled the House of Representatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake beef tartare so real it made vegetarian sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/impossible-burger-2-0-tasted-so-real-it-made-this-vegetarians-stomach-turn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commentary: I haven't eaten beef in a decade, and the new fake meat at CES comes close enough to cow to gross me out. That's a compliment, I think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOTAL WASTE OF TIME'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/09/trump-calls-meeting-with-democratic-leaders-on-shutdown-total-waste-of-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breakdown in negotiations over border wall funding appeared to heighten the possibility that Trump might declare a national emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>78% of workers live paycheck to paycheck...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/09/shutdown-highlights-that-4-in-5-us-workers-live-paycheck-to-paycheck.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the shutdown drags on, 420,000 federal workers are working without pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I may go homeless'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/09/govenrment-shutdown-brings-headaches-to-prospective-homebuyers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stalemate in Washington, one of the longest in history, is throwing a wrench into some people's plans to buy houses, according to real estate experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 millennials with debt expect to die without ever paying it off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/08/1-in-5-millennials-with-debt-expect-to-die-without-ever-paying-it-off.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 60 percent of millennials with debt don't know when, or if, they'll ever be able to pay what they owe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert: A.I. to replace 40% of global jobs soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/venture-capitalist-kai-fu-lee-ai-will-displace-40-percent-of-worlds-jobs-in-as-soon-as-15-years-60-minutes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kai Fu Lee, a pioneer in artificial intelligence and venture capitalist based in China, tells 60 Minutes it won't just be blue collar jobs that are displaced by AI. See the full story, Sunday at 7 p.m. ET/PT on CBS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS installing needle-disposal boxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/starbucks-workers-petition-bathroom-needle-disposal-boxes-2019-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is installing needle-disposal boxes in some bathrooms as it explores solutions to workers' concerns over improperly discarded syringes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: President Losing Argument?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/view/trump-speech-president-is-losing-the-shutdown-argument</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longer the shutdown drags on, the more impressed voters will be with politicians who seem most interested in ending it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Clash Over Global Right to Be Forgotten Returns to Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/google-clash-over-global-right-to-be-forgotten-returns-to-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Clash Over Global Right to Be Forgotten Returns to Court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious deep space radio signals detected from second repeater...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-46811618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A telescope picks up bursts of radio waves from a distant galaxy, shedding light on an astrophysical puzzle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-gonorrhoea spread causes 'deep concern'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-46809526</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two women pick up the hard-to-treat infection, and a European party destination is one line of inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Vest Protesters Call for Huge Run on French Banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c8646ad291c440978c5d8a260a11d454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Activists from a French protest movement encouraged supporters Wednesday to set off a bank run by emptying their accounts, while the government urged citizens to express their discontent in a national debate instead of weekly demonstrations disrupting the streets of Paris. Activists from the yellow vest movement, which started with protests over fuel tax increases, recommended the massive cash withdrawals on social media. One protester, Maxime Nicolle called it the "tax collector's referendum." "We are going to get our bread back ... You're making money with our dough, and we're fed up," Nicolle said in a video message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Iran says holding US Navy veteran, 1st arrest of Trump era...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0db0548912424cbb8f63a6d2bc6e5160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran confirmed Wednesday it is holding U.S. Navy veteran Michael R. White at a prison in the country, making him the first American known to be detained under President Donald Trump's administration. White's detention adds new pressure to the rising tension between Iran and the U.S., which under Trump has pursued a maximalist campaign against Tehran that includes pulling out of its nuclear deal with world powers. Although the circumstances of White's detention remain unclear, Iran in the past has used its detention of Westerners and dual nationals as leverage in negotiations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA says most food inspections halted...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/424562-fda-says-most-food-inspections-have-been-halted-amid-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) says it has suspended all routine domestic food facility inspections amid the partial government shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Emergency declaration coming IF no deal...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/424551-trump-says-emergency-declaration-coming-without-border-deal-with-dems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump argues that he did not shut down the government for political reasons: "I didn’t want this fight."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Using 'Gag Order' To Censor Critique of Prosecutions...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2019/01/09/the-feds-use-gag-orders-to-censor-critiq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cato Institute and Institute for Justice team up to fight for the right to publish a book attacking behavior by the SEC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China orders video apps to censor ALL content...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/china-orders-short-video-apps-101829134.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities have introduced detailed regulations covering the country’s thriving short video industry, singling out 100 categories of banned content, from smearing the image of Communist Party leaders to sexual moaning, in the latest ongoing effort to clean up its cyberspace that has more than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOS ANGELES TEACHERS SET TO STRIKE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/los-angeles-teachers-ready-first-strike-30-years-061352764.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The union representing teachers in Los Angeles, whose 640,000 students make it the nation's second-largest school district, postponed the start of a strike until Monday because of the possibility of a court-ordered delay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Dems identify as liberals for first time...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/245813/leans-conservative-liberals-keep-recent-gains.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's ideological balance held steady in 2018, with conservatives and moderates each at 35% and liberals remaining at last year's record high, 26%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California promises total 'sanctuary'... </title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/07/gavin-newsom-california-governor-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Gov. Jerry Brown is passing his title to fellow Democrat Gavin Newsom, who was sworn in Monday as California's 40th governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon: Military Not Ready for War With China or Russia...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/pentagon-military-logistics-system-not-ready-for-war-with-china-or-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strategic American military system for moving troops, weapons, and supplies over long distances has decayed significantly and needs rapid upgrading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>86-year-old trapeze artist flies through air with ease...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/2019/01/08/la-jolla-woman-earns-guinness-world-record-for-oldest-trapeze-artist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Betty Goedhart isn't letting her age slow her down from things she loves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Jerry Jones $250M Yacht Size Of Football Field...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/01/08/cowboys-owner-jones-reportedly-buys-250-yacht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the yacht's manufacturer, Oceanco, the vessel features a garage for smaller boats or jet skis, a full gym and a spa complete with a sauna and massage room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline Now Want Passengers To Tip Flight Attendants...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/01/08/tip-flight-attendant-frontier-airlines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They take your order, serve up food and drinks, and come back to clean up. But should you tip your flight attendant?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking Toll On Farmers...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/01/08/government-shutdown-taking-a-toll-on-illinois-farmers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many farmers count on government help, especially this time of year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General pick expresses confidence in Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eef75ab2d45547f2ae0f4af9cea84f16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The incoming chairman of the Senate Judiciary Committee said Wednesday that Attorney General nominee William Barr has confidence in special counsel Robert Mueller and will let him complete his Russia investigation. Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., said after meeting with Barr, who led the Justice Department under President George H.W. Bush, that Barr has a "high opinion" of Mueller. Barr was spending most of Wednesday on Capitol Hill, meeting senators on the committee before his confirmation hearing next week. "He had absolutely no indication he was going to tell Bob Mueller what to do or how to do it," Graham said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental app measures breathing -- to spot drug overdoses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0ddb7da1c98b4281b7e939ad7911671f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Too often people die of an opioid overdose because no one's around to notice they're in trouble. Now scientists are creating a smartphone app that beams sound waves to measure breathing — and summon help if it stops. The app is still experimental. But in a novel test, the "Second Chance" app detected early signs of overdose in the critical minutes after people injected heroin or other illegal drugs, researchers reported Wednesday. One question is whether most drug users would pull out their phone and switch on an app before shooting up. The University of Washington research team contends it could offer a much-needed tool for people who haven't yet found addiction treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Showbiz, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheBlaze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein plans an exit from DOJ, ABC reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain — and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official Website of The Sean Hannity Show. Sean Hannity is a multimedia superstar, spending four hours a day every day reaching out to millions of Americans on radio, television and the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-year-old cyclist accused of doping...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/90-year-old-rider-doping-claim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With each pedal-stroke of his 80- and now 90-year-old legs, Carl Grove sought to show his fellow Americans that old age can be rich and rewarding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch CBSN the live news stream from CBS News and get the latest, breaking news headlines of the day for national news and world news today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News was the most-watched cable network for coverage of Pres. Trump's address and the response. MSNBC topped CNN in total viewers during the address and response, while CNN topped MSNBC in the key A25-54 demo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, womenâ€™s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stonezone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Magazine energizes people around shared interests, igniting important conversations on the news, politics, style, and culture that drive the world forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Teen Locked Out Of Apt Falls To DeathTrying To Scale Building...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/01/09/teen-falls-to-his-death-from-9th-floor-of-collins-ave-condo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami Beach police are looking into how a 16-year-old boy fell to his death from the 9th floor of his apartment building on Collins Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston news, sports, politics, opinion, entertainment, weather and obituaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
