<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WARREN PACKS CROWDS IN NH</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/warren-speaks-to-crowd-of-hundreds-in-franconia/28704327</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren campaigned Wednesday in Franconia as she continues to climb in the New Hampshire polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pull of Yang's Pessimism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/08/andrew-yang-2020-message/596122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once derided as a “novelty candidate,” the outsider Democrat is poised to hang on longer than many senators and governors in the 2020 primary race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFENSE: Jay-Z Faces Backlash For NFL Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/08/jay-z-helps-nfl-banish-colin-kaepernick/596146/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former quarterback caused a problem for the league—which turned to the celebrated rapper for assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind Nate Silver's war with NYT...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/15/nate-silver-new-york-times-1461666</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The paper’s onetime data guru can’t stop kicking his ex-employer for its 2020 polling analysis and supposed capitulation to Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPY?  Jeffrey Epstein traveled to Cuba at Fidel Castro's invitation...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article234009227.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake shook LA skyscrapers so hard some got vertigo...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-14/ridgecrest-earthquake-produced-minutes-of-shaking-new-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from seismic sensors in buildings across Southern California show how the 7.1 Ridgecrest earthquake produced surprisingly long periods of shaking in some areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian tanker 'released by Gibraltar' despite US bid to seize ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/us-iran-oil-tanker-gibraltar-released-gulf-latest-vessel-seized-a9061071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Amendment Advocates Warn Over 'Red Flag' Laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/red-flag-laws-second-amendment-advocates-warn-trump-about-support-for-gun-reform-measure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If he basically tries to dismantle the Second Amendment community, he's going to be a one-termer. I firmly believe that," one activist said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film claims group plotted to infect black Africans with HIV...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/film-claims-group-plotted-infect-black-africans-hiv-020555865.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plot by white mercenaries to spread HIV through black South Africa via a phony vaccination program: it sounds like the stuff of pulp spy novels, but documentary-maker Mads Brugger is clear that this is one sensational conspiracy that actually happened. Jones tells the filmmaker that the group undertook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hepatitis A Races Across Country...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/hepatitis-a-spreads-across-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the opioid crisis, the highly communicable hepatitis A virus is spreading in more than half the states and making its way into the general public. Underfunded health officials are va…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodyguard on Lifestyle, Cruelty, Suicide...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/08/jeffrey-epsteins-bodyguard-igor-zinoviev-on-his-old-boss.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former UFC fighter Igor Zinoviev went everywhere with Epstein. In his first interview, he says he thinks Epstein had help ending his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unearthed Recordings...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-08-14/epstein-tapes-emerge-jeffrey-epstein-describes-his-lifestyle-unearthed-recordings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans fear Trump will lose Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/republicans-concerned-over-trumps-strength-in-arizona-heading-into-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democrats are eyeing Texas as a longshot pickup in the 2020 presidential race. But Republicans who are keeping an eye on the national electoral landscape say the party should be more concerned that Arizona could go from red to blue this time around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My night with a male sex doll'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/9721275/two-bendy-willies-and-a-brief-moment-of-passion-my-night-with-a-male-sex-doll/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HENRY is tall, dark and handsome, doesn’t answer back and is always up for sex. Only thing is he isn’t real, he’s a male sex doll. Increasing numbers of British men – and women – are se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of Inconsistencies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/08/here-it-is-complete-list-of-inconsistencies-in-prison-policy-surrounding-jeffrey-epsteins-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Veterinarians At High Risk Of Depression, Anxiety, Suicidal Thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-veterinarians-people-who-treat-animals-face-higher-risk-of-mental-health-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that veterinarians and others who work with animals on a daily basis deal with stressful and emotional events that put them at a higher risk of developing mental health conditions such as depression, anxiety, and, in some cases, suicidal thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast, low, hard to stop: NKorea missile tests crank up threat level...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/North-Korea-s-missile-tests-crank-up-the-threat-14305847.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - President Donald Trump has brushed off North Korea's resumption of missile launches, but the volley of tests in the past four months has significantly raised the country's military capabilities and the threat they pose to South Korea and U.S. forces on the peninsula, experts say.  The launches have included at least two new types of short-range ballistic missiles and a mobile multiple-rocket launcher. Pyongyang has also seen fit to show off a submarine that may be intended to carry nuclear warheads.  Trump says he's been told that Kim Jong Un, the North Korean leader, "only smiles when he sees me." But photos released by North Korean state media show the dictator beaming from cheek to cheek at the successful tests.  "There's no question that the 2019 testing campaign that began in April has showcased some quite serious qualitative advancement in North Korean missile capabilities," said Ankit Panda, an adjunct senior fellow in the Defense Posture Project at the Federation of American Scientists. "The core theme across all of the new weapons seems to be survivability, responsiveness, and missile-defense defeat."  The weapons that North Korea has showcased, including a road-mobile short-range ballistic missile known as the KN-23, with a range of at least 280 miles, appear specifically designed to confound South Korea's missile-defense system.  "The three missiles have several things in common: they are solid fuel, they are mobile, they are fast, they fly low, and at least the KN-23 can maneuver in-flight, which is very impressive," said Vipin Narang, an associate professor of political science at MIT.  "Any one of the missiles would pose a challenge to regional and [South Korean] missile defenses given these characteristics. Together, they pose a nightmare."  On...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More common in strangulation...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/jeffrey-epsteins-injuries-more-common-in-victims-of-strangulation-than-hanging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials refuse to comment on autopsy results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal Justices Still Notching Victories Despite Conservative Court...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/08/14/scotus-conservative-crossovers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court's liberal minority forged winning alliances in unexpected rulings, suggesting the new conservative majority is hardly a cohesive unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi assaulted in Berlin -- second attack in 2 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/rabbi-assaulted-in-berlin-second-such-attack-in-as-many-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incidents are the latest in a wave of racially and religiously motivated crimes against Jews in Germany</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YIELDS FLASH RECESSION WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-us-treasuries-yield/u-s-yield-curve-remains-inverted-for-second-day-idUSKCN1V50KM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. yield curve was inverted for the second straight trading session on Thu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodstock glorified them. Tarantino barbecued them. In 2019, whither the hippie?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/story/2019-08-14/hippie-woodstock-1969-tarantino-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hippiedom's place in history is still unsettled, 50 years after the original Woodstock and as hippie-hating "Once Upon a Time ... in Hollywood" is in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US moves to seize Iranian tanker detained off Gibraltar...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190815-usa-moves-seize-iran-oil-tanker-gibraltar-tehran-london-standoff-persian-gulf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US on Thursday applied for the seizure of an Iranian oil tanker detained near the British overseas territory of Gibraltar, now the centre of a stand-off between Tehran and London, the public prosecutor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC unveiling mission control for space tourism...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-08-virgin-galactic-unveiling-mission-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spaceport America is no longer just a shiny shell of hope that space tourism would one day launch from this remote spot in the New Mexico desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN PACKS CROWDS IN NH</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/warren-matches-sanders-n-h-101516732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren drew almost as many supporters as Bernie Sanders during half as many campaign events in New Hampshire this week, as the two New England senators made their pitch to Granite State voters.About 700 people gathered at a Warren town hall in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu appears poised to block Omar, Tlaib from entering Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Netanyahu-appears-poised-to-block-Omar-Tlaib-14305839.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM - A forthcoming trip to Israel and the Palestinian territories by Reps. Ilhan Omar, D-Minn., and Rashida Tlaib, D-Mich., will possibly be blocked by Israel in its current proposed format, a senior Israeli government official told The Washington Post on Thursday.  Speaking on condition of anonymity because of the sensitivity of the matter, the official said that if Tlaib, an American of Palestinian heritage, made a special humanitarian request to visit her family in the occupied West Bank, then "it would be considered favorably."  Omar and Tlaib, who have both been outspoken critics of Israel and support a boycott movement against the country, are slated to arrive Sunday. Their trip is being planned by Miftah, a nonprofit organization headed by Palestinian lawmaker and longtime peace negotiator Hanan Ashrawi.  Denying entry for Omar and Tlaib would likely deepen the divide between the government of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and Democrats, who have privately said such moves are not emblematic of a country that prides itself as a democracy tolerant of political expression.  Informed Wednesday that Israel would formally deny entry for Omar and Tlaib, Democrats in Congress quietly braced for a new public fight with the long-serving Israeli leader, said several congressional aides familiar with the discussions.  It is still unclear whether Netanyahu will follow through on that decision, however, after a private backlash from the Democratic leadership and some U.S.-based pro-Israel groups, who warned against barring sitting members of Congress from entering Israel because of their political beliefs, said the aides, who spoke on condition of anonymity to describe sensitive discussions.  With three weeks to go before a repeat election on Sept.17,Netanyahu is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway detects radioactive iodine by Russian border days after blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-blast-norway/norway-detects-radioactive-iodine-by-russian-border-days-after-blast-idUSKCN1V510N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norway's nuclear safety authority is analyzing tiny amounts of radioactive ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She's 63 and living by beach in Mexico on $1,000 a month: 'Can't imagine living in U.S. again'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/shes-63-and-living-by-the-beach-in-mexico-on-1000-a-month-i-cant-imagine-living-in-the-us-again-2019-08-15 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After losing her job as a journalist, Janet Blaser left Santa Cruz for Mazatlán, where she started her own magazine. Here are the pros and cons of her life...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-year U.S. Treasury yield breaks below 2%...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/30-year-us-treasury-yield-breaks-below-2-2019-08-15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury yields extend their decline on Thursday as the whole U.S. government bond yield curve slipped below 2% level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sextortion' Via 'FORTNITE': Video Games Open Doors for Predators...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sextortion-fortnite-are-video-games-opening-doors-predators-1230978 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 28 percent of all U.S. gamers under the age of 18, platforms like 'Roblox' and 'Minecraft' are taking measures to protect children as online offenders "go where the kids are."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Is 'Lady of the House'? </title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/where-is-epstein-s-lady-of-the-house-ghislaine-maxwell-mystery-deepens-1.1301957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her townhouse in Manhattan has been sold. Her home in London sits dark. And along the rocky north shore of Boston, past signs marked “No Trespassing,” the latest trail has gone cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONTANA: State With Highest Suicide Rate Desperately Needs Shrinks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-state-with-the-highest-suicide-rate-desperately-needs-shrinks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State With the Highest Suicide Rate Desperately Needs Shrinks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Detect New Repeating Signals From Depths of Outer Space...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201908141076551808-scientists-detect-new-repeating-signals-coming-from-the-depths-of-outer-space/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the astronomers involved in the signal search effort expressed hope that this discovery might encourage other astronomers to “point their telescopes” at the sources of the newly discovered signals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck drove into ICE protesters outside prison. Guard was at wheel...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/ice-guard-allegedly-drove-pickup-truck-group-peaceful-protesters-he-ran-us-over-1454442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden allies float scaling back events to limit gaffes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/457486-biden-allies-float-scaling-back-events-to-limit-gaffes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allies to Joe Biden have been floating the idea of altering the former vice president's schedule in an effort to reduce the gaffes he has made in recent days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machines Replace Third of Workforce at Giant Copper Mine...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/machines-replace-third-workforce-giant-201022081.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Machines are taking over a giant Chilean copper mine, replacing about a third of the workforce as owner Codelco struggles to keep its title as the world’s largest producer of the metal.Codelco officially inaugurated underground operations at its century-old Chuquicamata mine on Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autopsy finds broken bones in Epstein's neck...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Autopsy-finds-broken-bones-in-Epstein-s-neck-14305473.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An autopsy found that financier Jeffrey Epstein sustained multiple breaks in his neck bones, according to two people familiar with the findings, deepening the mystery about the circumstances around his death.  Among the bones broken in Epstein's neck was the hyoid bone, which in men is near the Adam's apple. Such breaks can occur in those who hang themselves, particularly if they are older, according to forensics experts and studies on the subject. But they are more common in victims of homicide by strangulation, the experts said.  The details are the first findings to emerge from the autopsy of Epstein, a convicted sex offender and multimillionaire in federal custody on charges of sex trafficking. He died early Saturday morning after guards found him hanging in his cell at the Metropolitan Correctional Center in Manhattan and he could not be revived.  Attorney General William Barr, whose department oversees the Bureau of Prisons facility where Epstein died, has described his death as an "apparent suicide." Justice officials declined to comment on the new information from Epstein's autopsy.  The office of New York City's chief medical examiner, Barbara Sampson, completed an autopsy of Epstein's body Sunday. But Sampson listed the cause of his death as pending.  Sampson's office did not comment on the injuries found in the autopsy.  The details add to the bizarre circumstances surrounding Epstein's death, which have launched a wave of questions and conspiracy theories about how he could have died in federal custody. Even President Donald Trump has egged on speculation, without evidence, that Epstein - whose alleged victims say they were pushed to have sex with his powerful and celebrity friends - might have been killed to keep him from spilling the secrets of others.  The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyme Baffling, Even to Experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/09/life-with-lyme/594736/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But new insights are at last accumulating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous con man: Crime 4,000 times easier today!</title>
      <link>https://www.techrepublic.com/article/famous-con-man-frank-abagnale-crime-is-4000-times-easier-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frank Abagnale, the real-life inspiration behind the Steven Spielberg's hit movie Catch Me If You Can, talks to TechRepublic's Karen Roby about cybersecurity, passwords, and where executives go wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine families facing elder boom and worker shortage in preview of nation's future...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/A-catastrophic-trend-in-Maine-A-shortage-of-14305176.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOVER-FOXCROFT, Maine - Janet Flaherty got an alarming call last October from the agency tasked with coordinating in-home care for her 82-year-old mother. It could no longer send her mom's home caretaker. It knew of no other aides who could care for her mother, either.  Flaherty's mother, Caroline, has for two years qualified for in-home care paid for by the state's Medicaid program. But the agency could not find someone to hire amid a severe shortage of workers that has crippled facilities for seniors across the state.  With private help now bid up to $50 an hour, Janet and her two sisters have been forced to do what millions of families in a rapidly aging America have done: take up second, unpaid jobs caring full time for their mother.  "We do not know what to do. We do not know where to go. We are in such dire need of help," said Flaherty, an insurance saleswoman.  Across Maine, families like the Flahertys are being hammered by two slow-moving demographic forces - the growth of the retirement population and a simultaneous decline in young workers - that have been exacerbated by a national worker shortage pushing up the cost of labor. The unemployment rate in Maine is 3.2 percent, below the national average of 3.7 percent.  The disconnect between Maine's aging population and its need for young workers to care for that population is expected to be mirrored in states throughout the country over the coming decade, demographic experts say. And that's especially true in states with populations with fewer immigrants, who are disproportionately represented in many occupations serving the elderly, statistics show.  "We have added an entire generation since we first put the safety net in place but with no plan whatsoever for how to support them," said Ai-jen Poo, co-director of Caring Across Generations, which advocates for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nightmare scenario': 15 years since Florida was beaten, bruised by 4 hurricanes in 6 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-charley-frances-ivan-jeanne-15th-anniversary-hurricanes-2004-20190813-kioljgjcefggthkwoszuypa2wq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Charley hit Florida on Aug. 13, 2004, beginning the year Florida became the punching bag of the hurricane season as Hurricanes Frances, Ivan and Jeanne came at the state one after the other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman wounds at least 6 Philadelphia police; 2 others freed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/police-fired-upon-philadelphia-they-respond-shooting-incident-n1042436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers took cover behind cars and blocked off surrounding streets as they were fired upon by the unidentified shooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body claimed by unidentified 'associate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/jeffrey-epstein-s-body-claimed-unidentified-associate-n1042551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epstein was found dead by apparent suicide Saturday morning. Multiple sources said he wasn't on suicide watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest pot company loses $1 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/canopy-growth-worlds-largest-pot-company-lost-1-billion-in-three-months-2019-08-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canopy Growth Corp. reported a C$1.28 billion quarterly loss late Wednesday and missed analyst revenue estimates for revenue, sending shares down 10% in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. King  incites furor with abortion, rape and incest remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/politics/2019/08/14/steve-king-abortion-rape-incest-westside-conservative-iowa-representative-birth-iowa-civilization/2007230001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King said some conservatives told him he would get more support on abortion legislation if he allowed certain exemptions. He did not agree to the caveats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins researchers caused harm, death of dogs, animal rights group says...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/health/bs-hs-dogs-harmed-at-hopkins-complaint-20190813-st3vzmggufhbnob2xqnv5huqw4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An animal rights group has filed a complaint against Johns Hopkins University for what it describes as botched surgeries on nine dogs that led to their paralysis and euthanasia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 quakes in 2 days, no warning from ShakeAlertLA. Now app is getting reworked...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/quakes-in-days-no-warning-from-shakealertla-now-the-app/article_a2a9659d-54d1-5d71-93fe-ba22cdbcafc6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A new version of Los Angeles’ earthquake early warning app will now alert users of weaker shaking, Mayor Eric Garcetti announced Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking hailstone falls out of Colorado sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/national-weather-service-investigating-whether-monster-that-hail-fell-in-colorado-broke-a-record/70009074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:   Trump disapproval rises to 56%...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/457480-trump-disapproval-rises-to-near-record-fox-news-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's disapproval rating has jumped to 56 percent in a Fox News survey released Wednesday, just one point shy of the record high in Fox News polling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd Taunts Officers, Laugh At Them...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/08/14/crowd-taunts-philadelphia-police-officers-laugh-at-them-in-midst-of-gunfire-during-standoff-in-nicetown-tioga/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS3's Alexandria Hoff reports a crowd of people laughed and yelled at officers in the midst of gunfire during a standoff on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge overseeing key case dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/25/judge-jeffrey-epstein-case-dies-1292394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan-based U.S. District Court Judge Robert Sweet passed away Sunday at age 96.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Threaten ICE Contractors, Children, Pets...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/08/13/exclusive-watch-leftists-threaten-before-shooting-at-ice-facility-we-know-where-all-your-children-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of open borders activists threatened employees of an ICE contractor the day before a shooting at the contractor's offices in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD cop commits suicide, ninth this year...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/14/off-duty-veteran-nypd-cop-shoots-himself-in-the-head-in-queens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran NYPD cop became the ninth police officer to commit suicide this year when he shot himself in the head in his Queens home Wednesday evening — just a day after another NYPD officer killed h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YIELDS FLASH RECESSION WARNING</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/055c92ef86604f8c9ab06746e6014627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The threat of a recession doesn't seem so remote anymore for investors in financial markets. The yield on the closely watched 10-year Treasury fell so low Wednesday that, for the first time...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dead after taco-eating contest...</title>
      <link>https://abc30.com/man-dies-after-taco-eating-contest-at-fresno-grizzlies-game/5467417/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc30.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fresno County Sheriff's Office has identified the man who died after competing in a taco eating contest at the Fresno Grizzlies game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSPECT LIVESTREAMS STANDOFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/pennsylvania/police-officers-shot-north-philadelphia-20190814.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One officer was struck in the head and another in the arms. Civilians were being evacuated from nearby streets as the confrontation continued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS DIVE; -800</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/us-markets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up to date market data and stock market news is available online. View US market headlines and market charts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEVELOPING NOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nicetown-philadelphia-shooting-today-live-updates-police-officers-shot-standoff-facebook-livestream-2019-08-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said the situation was still "active" and advised people to avoid the area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Philly Cops Shot Near Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/08/14/philadelphia-police-officer-shot-in-philadelphias-nicetown-tioga-section-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say the shooting happened on the 3700 block of North 15th Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenes of urban warfare...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/287328513a6446cda6bdfc9494f53277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — At least one gunman opened fire on police Wednesday as they were serving a warrant in a Philadelphia neighborhood, wounding six officers and triggering a standoff that extended...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How he met Bill Gates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/14/jeffrey-epstein-met-with-bill-gates-years-after-financier-served-jail-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft founder Bill Gates spoke more than once with Jeffrey Epstein, the late financier accused of child sex trafficking, to discuss ways to increase philanthropic spending, according to people with direct knowledge of the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President lashes out at fed for 'CRAZY INVERTED YIELD CURVE!'</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/859058/exacerbating-recession-fears-trump-diverts-blame-fed-crazy-inverted-yield-curve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has weighed in on the possibly, but maybe not actually ominous inverted yield curve. President Trump isn't a fan of the "crazy" inversion, but unlike many of his critics who have placed America's trade war with China front and center when it comes to reasons why a global recession might be looming, he's pointing to a different problem â€” and it's not one of the items on Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Krugman's smorgasbord of economic issues, either. No, Trump's mad at the Federal Reserve, like he has been for a while. The president frequently clamored for the Fed to slash interest rates, and even though Fed Chair Jerome Powell did eventually cut rates in July, Trump has deemed the action far too little, too late. ..Spread is way too much as other countries say THANK YOU to clueless Jay Powell and the Federal Reserve. Germany, and many others, are playing the game! CRAZY INVERTED YIELD CURVE! We should easily be reaping big Rewards &amp; Gains, but the Fed is holding us back. We will Win! â€” Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) August 14, 2019 Many economists don't agree with Trump. Krugman, for instance, doesn't place sole responsibility for the global economy's teetering on the trade war, but he does consider it a factor. Meanwhile, The Washington Post also reports that the trade war, often through indirect effects like a decline in business confidence and investment, has played a major role in the slowdown. Considering markets closed with their biggest point declines of the year soon after his tweet, it's clear Trump didn't do much to mollify spooked investors. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mini Horses Cleared For Takeoff; Now Allowed To Fly...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/08/14/miniature-horses-cleared-for-take-off-service-animals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miniature horses are among the service animals approved to take on flights, according to new guidelines provided Thursday by the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Can't Imagine What Cops Go Through...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/nypd-police-suicides</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent NYPD suicides should remind us to appreciate the trauma associated with police work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau breached conflict of interest law, ethics commissioner rules...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/politics/trudeau-breached-conflict-of-interest-law-in-snc-lavalin-affair-ethics-commissioner-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mario Dion’s report also says he was denied access to sensitive government information during his investigation by Privy Council Clerk Ian Shugart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia flies nuke bombers near Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-russia-flies-nuclear-capable-190652973.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* State media says it shows Moscow can deploy close to U.S. MOSCOW, Aug 14 (Reuters) - Russia said on Wednesday it had flown two nuclear-capable TU-160 bombers to a far eastern Russian region opposite Alaska as part of a training exercise that state media said showed Moscow's ability to park nuclear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police: Motorist was playing POKEMAN GO on 8 phones simultaneously...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/pokemon-go/pokemon-overload-seatac-694201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Sergeant Kyle Smith of the Washington State Patrol last night spotted a car on the shoulder of a road near the Seattle–Tacoma International Airport, he assumed the vehicle was somehow disabled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Popular ADHD Drugs Change Structure Of Kids' Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/adhd-drugs-may-be-changing-structure-of-childrens-brains-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study offers a warning to parents: one of the most popular ADHD meds, Methylphenidate (MPH), may be affecting the development of white matter in children's brains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVERSTOCK CEO spins Russian-spy drama, starring himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/overstock-shares-fall-as-ceo-gets-even-more-nutty-and-unpredictable-2019-08-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of e-commerce company Overstock Inc. tumbled on Tuesday, as more investors learned of the latest bizarre comments from its founder and Chief Executive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball fan dies during taco eating contest on 'taco tuesday'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/article233990877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Cops Mull Return Of Surveillance Plane To City Skies...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/08/13/remember-the-surveillance-plane-that-flew-over-baltimore-it-could-fly-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of Persistent Surveillance Systems said Tuesday he is meeting with Baltimore City Police Commissioner Michael Harrison next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'NULL' License Plate Landed One Hacker in Ticket Hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/null-license-plate-landed-one-hacker-ticket-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security researcher Joseph Tartaro thought NULL would make a fun license plate. He's never been more wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY giving podcasters unprecedented access to listener data...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/8/13/20802018/spotify-for-podcasters-dashboard-live-beta-analytics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spotify for Podcasters comes out of beta today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein had portrait of Bill Clinton wearing Monica's blue dress in Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7353967/Did-Jeffrey-Epstein-portrait-Bill-Clinton-blue-dress-red-heels-NYC-mansion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The painting was snapped inside convicted pedophile Jeffrey Epstein's $56m New York mansion in 2012, seven years before his suicide in the wake of new charges of sex trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Israel's sensitive preparations for visit of Omar, Tlaib...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ilhan-omar-rashida-tlaib-visit-to-israel-temple-mount-a7d2a029-e647-44bc-986e-6b6121711915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of the delegation may be barred from entry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep Hasidic Out': Small-Town Housing Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/08/14/keep-the-hasidic-out-a-small-town-housing-showdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHESTER, N.Y. — In a peaceful corner of the Hudson Valley, a broad expanse of land sits at the ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Burden lifted off of my soul...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g1VeElBAeas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Google insider who anonymously leaked internal documents to Project Veritas made the decision to go public in an on-the-record video interview. The insider...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reverse Aging in Rat Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.eveningexpress.co.uk/news/boost-for-ms-treatment-as-scientists-reverse-ageing-process-in-rat-brain-cells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eveningexpress.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brains get stiff with age just like muscles and joints, scientists have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 2020 Rust Belt Pitch Threatened by Manufacturing Downturn...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-14/trump-2020-rust-belt-pitch-threatened-by-manufacturing-recession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-Year: Record Low...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-30-yield-falls-record-101045742.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. 30-year yields fell to their lowest level ever as investors sought shelter amid a fraught geopolitical backdrop and concern increased about the impact of the escalating global trade war on economic growth.Meanwhile, the stream of investors into the safest parts of the market has triggered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious drawings by da Vinci found hidden beneath painting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9722419/leonardo-da-vinci-secret-hidden-painting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAWINGS made by Leonardo da Vinci underneath one of his most popular paintings have been revealed. Scribbles from the Renaissance master were found buried underneath his 16th Century work The Virg…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Elizabeth Warren Surges to Statistical Tie With Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/just-in-elizabeth-warren-surges-in-new-national-poll-to-statistical-tie-with-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results of a new poll released conducted by YouGov for The Economist shows Sen. Elizabeth Warren surging into a statistical tie with former Vice President Joe Biden. The poll shows Biden earning 21% s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to gobble up more assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/will-a-merged-viacomcbs-boldly-go-media-assets-1231474</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Bakish and Joseph Ianniello will preside over a film and TV empire that brings together 'Star Trek' and 'Mission: Impossible' — but many believe it needs to go on a buying spree to contend with Disney and Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Has TESLA Valet Key Implanted Into Arm!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/roadshow/news/tesla-model-3-key-implant-biohack-cyberpunk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's only a matter of time before Elon tries to offer this as an option when purchasing your Model 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial AMAZON Facial Recognition Software Can Now Spot Fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/amazons-rekognition-software-can-now-detect-fear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rekognition is also getting better at estimating a person's age, the company says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem contenders unload on corporate media...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/457302-democratic-contenders-unload-on-news-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential contenders are letting loose with a barrage of attacks against the news media, ripping national outlets for what they view as biased coverage of their campaigns or unfair double standards in covering President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: It's Gotten Too Hard to Strike It Rich...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gotten-too-hard-strike-rich-113004604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- In a free-market economy everyone is supposed to have the chance to get rich. The dream of making it big motivates people to take risks, start businesses, stay in school and work hard. Unfortunately, in the U.S., that dream seems to be dying.There are still plenty of rich people</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
