<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Attempt To Edit DNA In Human Sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/08/22/746321083/scientists-attempt-controversial-experiment-to-edit-dna-in-human-sperm-using-cri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NPR visited the only lab in the world known to be trying to use the powerful gene-editing tool CRISPR to modify the DNA in human sperm. If successful, it could be used to prevent genetic disorders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pump Prices Could Fall Below $2 in the South!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbc12.com/2019/08/22/cheap-crude-oil-paves-way-cheaper-gas-this-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbc12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AAA forecasts the national average to drop to $2.40 or lower this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man dies by suicide after video goes viral of him defending relationship with trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/maurice-willoughby-died-by-suicide-after-viral-video-defending-transgender-girlfriend-20190822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The investigation into Willoughby’s death is still pending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy hunter turned to mush as 11ft alligator savages him...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/trophy-hunters-bones-turned-mush-18987291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Perchalski had shared pictures of dead animals on Facebook from his hunting sessions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  Raise capital gains tax back to 39.6%...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/biden-capital-gains-tax-we-should-raise-tax-back-396-percent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden calls for doubling of capital gains tax rate&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Democrat presidential candidate Joe Biden said he’d like to raise the capital gains tax rate to 39.6 percent, a near doubling of the current 20 percent. &amp;#13;&amp;#13;Biden made the remarks on Wednesday, August 21 during an interview with Iowa Public Television: &amp;#13;&amp;#13;“I believe we should, in fact, the capital gains tax should be at what the highest minimum tax should be, we should raise the tax back to 39.6 percent instead of 20 percent,” Biden said yesterday.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Raising the capital gains tax would harm Americans’ ability to build a nest egg and h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Macron seeks to be mediator in G-7 hard times...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7cb2611f95aa4e68be00e088ddf893be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French President Emmanuel Macron hosts the G-7 summit this weekend fresh off a meeting with Russia's Vladimir Putin, hoping to maintain his image as a global mediator at a time of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Man crushed by falling elevator in NYC building...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/video-shows-moment-man-crushed-by-elevator-at-manhattan-promenade-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horrifying video obtained by The Post shows the moment a Manhattan man is crushed under the weight of his luxury high-rise’s malfunctioning elevator and dragged to his death into the darkness…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Risks Recession as Second-Quarter GDP May Be Revised Down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-risks-recession-second-quarter-172410979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Economists expect Mexico’s second-quarter gross domestic product to be revised slightly down on Friday, with some going as far as to predict a negative number that would mean Latin America’s second-largest economy slipped into technical recession this year.The median estimate of economists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY MOVES TO BAN SLEEPING NEAR SCHOOLS, PARKS...</title>
      <link>https://laist.com/2019/08/22/los-angeles-homeless-sit-lie-sleep-law.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;laist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposed changes would outlaw sleeping on public space within 500 feet of schools and parks, and within 10 feet of any building entrance or driveway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems less likely to get Trump's tax returns before 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://hamodia.com/2019/08/22/house-democrats-less-likely-get-trumps-tax-returns-2020-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hamodia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats appear increasingly unlikely to secure President Donald Trump's tax returns before the 2020 presidential election, according to interviews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas governor meets with tech officials about quelling extremism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f0c1ce26cf104ba897ac205c9d5b91a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas Gov. Greg Abbott on Thursday met in Austin with officials from some of the world's biggest tech giants to discuss ways of combatting extremism in the wake of a mass...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global worry over Amazon fires escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e1b052a0ffb34217aef47d20e960a410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Amid global concern about raging Amazon fires, Brazil on Thursday said it was the target of a smear campaign by critics who contend President Jair Bolsonaro is not doing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-term mortgage rates near historic lows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a8e2d9164ad4cb5b192d542a2b9abbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. long-term mortgage rates are near historically low levels, with the average on the benchmark 30-year loan falling this week to its lowest level since November...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see opening on economy, risk cheering recession...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4a0e49f91c6043119e8b4ba4c510ae31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROLE, Iowa (AP) — Campaigning under the stifling August sun, Joe Biden assailed President Donald Trump's trade war with China, accusing him of squandering a strong economy and putting Americans'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female backers sell his message...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2f5a348dca974cb79526fd2a7edf5894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — President Donald Trump's campaign is rallying and training a corps of female defenders, mindful that Trump's shaky standing with women could sink his hopes of reelection...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women open fires on LA Skid Row; 4 injured...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190822204643-hm297</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-SHOOTING/SKIDROW:Four people wounded in Los Angeles Skid Row shooting, female suspect at large</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NBC Sports Pro Football Talk' turns into Trump bash-fest...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/22/chris-simms-uses-nbc-sports-pro-football-talk-to-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC Sports Pro Football Talk turned into a venue for bashing President Trump and conservatives when Mike Florio and Chris Simms said they had to expose “hypocritical sports fans” and media personalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor, who went to school with Kavanaugh, sues HUFFPOST...</title>
      <link>https://www.clarionledger.com/story/news/politics/2019/08/22/mississippi-man-sues-huffington-post-over-story-brett-kavanaugh-illegal-drugs-party-david-kennedy/2078341001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clarionledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawsuit says that claims that Mississippi professor, then a student, helped supply illegal drugs were "outrageously false and defamatory."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Kicks Off Massive War Games, Unveils Russian Missile System...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-kicks-off-massive-war-games-unveils-homemade-russian-missile-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iranian Revolutionary Guard Corps' ground forces kicked off a "massive" set of war drills Thursday as the country unveiled its own version of the S-300.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/ci38996632/executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5.0 Mag Quake Shakes Death Valley...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/50-earthquake-strikes-inyo-county-usgs-says/5486495/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A preliminary-magnitude 5.0 earthquake struck Inyo County, centered in the region that experienced two major temblors in early July, the U.S. Geological Survey said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Guitars. Buy Rocker's Childhood Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/forget-guitars-buy-rocker-childhood-202456158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why would you buy Bob Dylan, Kurt Cobain or Tom Petty's childhood homes? The new owners explain how they're trying to keep legacies alive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victims' Lawyer Claims Epstein Was Murdered...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9757129/jeffrey-epstein-did-not-commit-suicide-murdered-lawyer-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAWYER for Jeffrey Epstein’s victims says he has obtained new information that suggests the billionaire paedo did NOT commit suicide but was murdered. Spencer Kuvin, who accurately predicte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Nazi salute video stirs reminders of dark Orange County history...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nazi-salute-video-stirs-reminders-of-dark-history-in-increasingly-diverse-orange-county/ar-AAGbezv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President kills plan to cut billions in foreign aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/22/white-house-backs-off-foreign-aid-cuts-1472130</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers objected to the plan, complaining that it would hurt foreign aid programs while also jeopardizing the massive budget deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein to be arraigned on new charges weeks before trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7384531/Harvey-Weinstein-arraigned-NEW-charges-Manhattan-Criminal-Court-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson for the Manhattan District Attorney's Office said that Weinstein's appearance has been scheduled for Monday, August 26 , and he will be called at 9:30am</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Doing housework could substantially lower risk of 'early death'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/doing-housework-could-substantially-lower-risk-of-early-death-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doing light physical activity such as cooking or washing dishes each day is enough to substantially lower the risk of early death, a study suggests. Researchers say people can raise their chances o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Divided Over More Cuts...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/trump-economy-interest-rates-federal-reserve-split-on-next-move-2019-8-1028467749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giraffes move closer to endangered species protection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8839637123514ace82f80f526f2ff0e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — Nations around the world moved Thursday to protect giraffes as an endangered species for the first time, drawing praise from conservationists and scowls from some sub-Saharan African...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  ESPN International hit with layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/espn-international-hit-with-layoffs-amid-shifting-resources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN is undergoing layoffs in its international division, sources have told The Post. The layoffs and reorganization are expected to impact more than 30 employees, the majority of whom are on-air p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein's Intellectual Enabler...</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/amp/article/154826/jeffrey-epsteins-intellectual-enabler</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVERSTOCK CEO Resigns Amid 'Deep State' Fallout...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/08/22/overstock-ceo-resigns-deep-state-butina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEO of Overstock.com resigned Thursday amid fallout from his remarks last week about taking part in an FBI &amp;quot;deep state&amp;quot; operation against Maria Butina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foot on table: British PM at home in French president palace...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/368ee2316b744bc38576cf2aad0af835</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson apparently wasn't sweating it despite the high stakes subject of his talks with the president of France: Brexit. So relaxed was he during...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World powers increasingly see icy Arctic as hot property...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/20632f3e017741b89a15e0d0927a7ada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TASIILAQ, Greenland (AP) — From a helicopter, Greenland's brilliant white ice and dark mountains make the desolation seem to go on forever. And the few people who live here — its whole population...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addiction Clinics Market Unproven Infusion Treatments To Desperate Patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/08/22/741115178/addiction-clinics-market-unproven-infusion-treatments-to-desperate-patients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some addiction treatment clinics offer IV infusions of a mix of supplements — including something known as NAD. The treatment isn't proven to work and is not FDA-approved for addiction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks Testing Resolve of Cities Across America...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/ransomware-attacks-are-testing-resolve-of-cities-across-america/ar-AAGapHU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China warns foreign news outlets...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/08/22/china-letters-news-hong-kong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China sent a letter to foreign news outlets Thursday urging journalists to be more &amp;quot;objective&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;impartial&amp;quot; in their reporting of the Hong Kong protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight over facial recognition dividing Detroit...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/fight-over-facial-recognition-dividing-detroit-high-stakes-police-privacy-n1045046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detroit’s police chief says facial recognition is making the city safer. Some residents fear it could create a surveillance state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12% of Republicans would be unhappy to see him reelected...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-has-remade-gop-but-poll-finds-its-at-a-price/ar-AAGb3xH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS Player Indicted For Cocaine Possession...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/patriots-safety-patrick-chung-indicted-for-cocaine-possession/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New England Patriots safety Patrick Chung was indicted on Aug. 8 for cocaine possession, according to multiple reports. According to the Boston Herald, the Belknap County Attorney’s Office in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative radio host may run against...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/conservative-radio-host-joe-walsh-may-run-against-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Walsh, a conservative radio host who served one term as an Illinois congressman, is inching toward challenging President Trump in a Republican primary. “I’m strongly, strongly consi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas buying $15M Martha's Vineyard estate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/barack-and-michelle-obama-are-buying-15m-estate-in-marthas-vineyard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack and Michelle Obama are close to buying a massive Martha’s Vineyard estate. TMZ reports that the former president and first lady are in escrow — aka in contract to purchase &amp;#8212…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA SENDS HUMANOID INTO SPACE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-send-fedor-first-humanoid-robot-space-020751065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Thursday launched an unmanned rocket carrying a life-size humanoid robot that will spend 10 days learning to assist astronauts on the International Space Station. Named Fedor, short for Final Experimental Demonstration Object Research, the robot is the first ever sent up by Russia. Fedor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Allies Angry At 'Ungrateful' Rapper A$ASP Rocky...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/full-story-trump-free-asap-rocky-161654472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;the White House and its unconventional allies scrambled to secure Rocky’s freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sound Of Dog Whimpering Makes Humans Feel As Sad As Baby Crying...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-dogs-communicate-distress-to-humans-better-than-cats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study conducted in Denmark concludes that pet owners develop a special sensitivity to all dogs' and cats' whines, whimpers, barks, and meows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing sector contracts for first time in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/22/manufacturing-sector-contracts-for-the-first-time-in-nearly-a-decade-according-to-ihs-markit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. manufacturer growth slowed to the lowest level in almost 10 years in August, the latest sign that the trade war may be exacerbating the economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine Sen. Susan Collins faces bipartisan anger in reelection bid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/susan-collins-faces-bipartisan-anger-080000219.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Republican Susan Collins is caught in the cross-fire of the angry partisan division that’s defining the nation’s politics, turning her from a shoo-in for re-election into one of the most vulnerable senators running in 2020.After spending four terms building a bipartisan brand in her home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microplastics in drinking water 'not a health risk'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/microplastics-drinking-water-not-health-risk-now-000415312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization (WHO) said Thursday the level of microplastics in drinking-water is not yet dangerous for humans but called for more research into potential future risk. In its first report into the effects of microplastics on human health, WHO looked into the specific impact of microplastics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARLEY-DAVIDSON unveils electric bicycles</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/harley-davidson-unveils-upcoming-electric-bicycle-lineup-144247683.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to launching an all-electric motorcycle, Harley-Davidson has a series of battery-powered city bicycles in the works. Over a year ago, Harley-Davidson announced that they had some electric bicycle projects up their sleeve and, until yesterday, the company had only revealed electric micro-transportation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:   TRUMP DISAPPROVAL 62%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ad13f32984a4480a45738ead2b4c0d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — About 6 in 10 Americans disapprove of President Donald Trump's overall job performance, according to a new poll released Thursday by The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers implanting malware in chargers...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/be-careful-whose-charger-you-borrow-phone-charging-cables-can-hack-your-devices-experts-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most people, borrowing a cable from someone else to charge your phone may seem as commonplace as asking for the time. But that ordinary-looking charging cable could actually contain malware intent on stealing your passwords and other sensitive information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Cell Phone Use Causes Brain Depletion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cio-briefing/2019/08/your-brain-doesnt-recharge-if-you-use-your-phone-break/159330/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants who took phone breaks experienced the highest levels of mental depletion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers describe 22-hour DELTA nightmare at JFK --  stuck on tarmac overnight!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Delta-Flight-Stuck-Tarmac-JFK-Airport-Hours-Los-Angeles-557861311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Delta flight that was supposed to leave John F. Kennedy Airport Wednesday afternoon en route to Los Angeles was still stuck on the Queens tarmac the next morning, prompting a flood of angry tweets from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Signs Sarah Huckabee Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/sarah-huckabee-sanders-fox-news-contributor-1203310352/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Huckabee Sanders, one of the more controversial holders of the office of White House Press Secretary in recent memory, will join Fox News Channel as a contributor. The former Trump administra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Man crushed to death by elevator in NYC building...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/22/man-crushed-to-death-when-elevator-in-nyc-building-suddenly-drops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was crushed to death by an elevator at a Manhattan luxury, high-rise rental building Thursday morning, authorities said. The victim became stuck between the elevator car and the shaft wall on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Formula One' secret behind Tom Brady's time-cheating dominance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/aug/22/the-formula-one-secret-behind-tom-bradys-time-cheating-dominance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 42-year-old quarterback is among the NFL’s best and he’s shown little sign of slowing down. How does he do it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python wars: Snake epidemic eating away at Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/aug/22/florida-python-action-team-snake-epidemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are tens of thousands of pythons in the Florida wild, attacking animals and damaging ecosystems – and the quest to stop them has become a collective crusade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Satanic Sex Cult Leader Who Loved Animal Sacrifices, Orgies, and Murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-devil-you-know-the-satanic-cult-leader-who-loved-animal-sacrifices-orgies-and-murder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Devil You Know,” a new docuseries premiering Aug. 27 on Viceland, explores the horrifying life of Pazuzu Algarad, a disturbed Satanist who ran a house of horrors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOB GROWTH REDUCED BY 501,000</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-created-500000-fewer-jobs-since-2018-than-previously-reported-new-figures-show-2019-08-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out hiring wasn’t quite as strong in 2018 and early 2019 as the government initially reported — by about a half-million jobs. The U.S. economy had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence by refugees and far-right extremists darkening political attitudes in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-08-21/violence-by-refugees-and-far-right-extremists-is-darkening-political-attitudes-in-germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mood in Germany has darkened this summer amid grisly killings committed by refugees and shootings by right-wing extremists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gary Busey, Set to Play God, Believes 'There Is No Death'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/gary-busey-accident-trump-playing-god-new-musical-1233086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two decades after a motorcycle crash that "turned his personality up to 11," the Oscar nominee and icon of unhinged aggression (in film and on YouTube) has become a foulmouthed Malibu mystic about to star in a new off-Broadway musical, 'Only Human,' playing "The Boss" in a corporatized version of heaven.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden, Warren tied with Trump -- in Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/458344-poll-shows-biden-warren-tied-with-trump-in-arizona</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden and Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) are statistically tied with President Trump in Arizona, a state that hasn't voted for a Democratic presidential candidate in a quarter century, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surprising Surge of Andrew Yang...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/08/22/andrew-yang-2020-president-profile-227631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out delivering a message of economic doom with a little self-deprecating humor can win over some people. Even a few disenchanted Trump voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated by unpopularity with Jews, thrusts Israel into culture war...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Frustrated-by-unpopularity-with-Jews-Trump-14369952.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump decided long ago that it would be smart politics for him to yoke his administration to Israel and to try to brand the Democratic Party as anti-Semitic.  He set about executing a pro-Israel checklist: Moving the U.S. Embassy to Jerusalem, recognizing the Golan Heights as part of sovereign Israel and taking a hard line against Iran. And he promoted himself as the greatest president ever - a deity even - for Jewish people.  Yet Trump has become flummoxed that Jewish Americans are not in turn lining up to support his reelection, according to people familiar with his thinking, and he has lashed out in predictable fashion.  "If you vote for a Democrat, you're very, very disloyal to Israel and to the Jewish people," Trump said Wednesday on the South Lawn of the White House. He was amplifying a statement he made in the Oval Office a day earlier: "I think any Jewish people that vote for a Democrat, I think it shows either a total lack of knowledge or great disloyalty."  Trump's use of the word "disloyalty" drew immediate criticism from Jewish groups, whose leaders said it echoed anti-Semitic tropes about where American Jews' loyalty lies. The president insisted his comments were not anti-Semitic.  Regardless, this turn in the president's rhetoric about Jews magnifies his transactional approach to politics and his miscalculation that his support for Israel should automatically translate into electoral support from Jewish Americans.  It also reveals a fundamental misunderstanding of the motivations of many Jews, who are not a monolithic voting bloc and but rather prioritize a wide range of issues - not only Israel, but also education, the economy and the environment, as well as civility and morality.  "He is reflecting a concept of Jewish Americans...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storming Area 51 started as joke. But it's mystery as to how many will show up...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-08-21/area-51-storming-nevada-ufo-aliens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will millions arrive at Area 51 in September to storm the gates? Nobody knows for sure, but government agencies are preparing for the worst</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York ranked least friendly state in America, survey claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/travel/new-york-ranked-least-friendly-america-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’re looking to see some friendly faces, you apparently shouldn’t head to The Empire State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco board rebrands 'convicted felon' as 'justice-involved person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/san-francisco-board-adopts-new-language-for-criminals-turning-convicted-felon-into-justice-involved-person</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crime-ridden San Francisco have introduced new sanitized language for criminals, getting rid of words such as “offender,” “addict” while a “convicted felon” will now be known as a “justice-involved person.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There is story to be told in New Mexico,' official says of ranch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jeffrey-epstein-new-mexico-ranch-official-says-there-is-a-story-to-be-told-in-new-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Mexico's commissioner of public lands has turned over 400 pages of Epstein's property records that may contain names of his alleged co-conspirators</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles sheriff's deputy shot by sniper from apartment building; Still on loose...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/los-angeles-sheriffs-deputy-shot-station-sniper-holed/story?id=65114172</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sniper located in an apartment building in Los Angeles County opened fire on a sheriff's deputy just outside his station house on Wednesday afternoon. The deputy, identified as 21-year-old Angel Reinosa, was shot in his bulletproof vest in the parking lot of the Los Angeles County Sheriff's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killings by police divide Brazilian city weary of crime...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/killings-police-divide-brazilian-city-weary-crime-65113291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Groups are raising alarms about the record levels of deaths at police hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Bernie unleashes $16 TRILLION climate plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2019/08/22/bernie-sanders-climate-plan-green-new-deal-follow-costs-16-trillion/2081655001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plan calls for the U.S. to install renewable energy across the economy by 2050 as well as declare climate change a national emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airports with best, worst TSA wait times...</title>
      <link>https://www.nwaonline.com/news/2019/aug/21/these-are-the-airports-with-the-best-an/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nwaonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Huge lines at airport security can be a nuisance or a disaster, depending on what time you show up for your flight. To know what you're up against, Upgraded Points conducted a study that looked at data on Transportation Security Administration (TSA) wait times at America's 25 busiest airports in 2018 to determine the nation's fastest and slowest security checkpoints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soccer star drilled 55-yard field goal. Hall of Famer says she should get NFL tryout...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Carli-Lloyd-drilled-a-55-yard-field-goal-A-Hall-14368449.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As far as Carli Lloyd was concerned, she was on just another field, doing what she does best.  The difference Tuesday was that she was on an NFL field when she pulled back her right leg and sent a ball straight and true for 55 yards, stirring up all sorts of buzz with a viral video. Lloyd, a two-time World Cup winner, twice an Olympic gold medalist and twice FIFA Player of the Year, made football look as easy as futbol as Sam Koch of the Baltimore Ravens held for her field goal attempt after a joint practice with the Philadelphia Eagles at the NovaCare Complex in Philadelphia.  Her kick was money. So much so that it got one veteran NFL observer musing about whether the time was approaching when a woman might kick for an NFL team. "Honestly, I don't think it will be long before we see a woman break through this NFL barrier," Gil Brandt, the Dallas Cowboys' vice president of player personnel from 1960 to 1988, tweeted.  Note that Lloyd, the 37-year-old who plays for the NWSL's Sky Blue franchise in New Jersey, wasn't facing pressure and she was taking too many approach steps. All of which was pointed out to Brandt, who countered, "I heard the same kind of things when I was bringing in track athletes and soccer players back in the '60s."  Brandt wasn't kidding and he offered a reminder of just how problematic kicking was in the NFL last season. Mason Crosby of the Green Bay Packers missed five field goal attempts in one game; Week 11 was a record-setting day for missed extra-point attempts. And perhaps no team had a more ignominious experience than the Chicago Bears, whose "double-doink" disaster occurred when Cody Parkey's potential game-winner from 43 yards out was tipped at the line, then hit the left upright and the crossbar. The Bears lost that wild-card game 16-15 to the Eagles.  The team released Parkey in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Droid nurse helps you dress...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/nurse-named-baxter-that-helps-you-dress-could-aid-staff-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Machine currently being developed by Imperial College London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nervous Retirees Too Scared to Spend...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/nervous-retirees-with-money-to-spare-are-sitting-on-their-wealth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nervous Retirees Are Too Scared to Spend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Babies and diapers replacing sex and drugs at Burning Man?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/21/babies-and-diapers-are-replacing-sex-and-drugs-at-burning-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Bianca Snyder gave birth to her son, Tage, she and her husband, Tad, didn’t think twice about bringing him to Burning Man. “Our son is such an extension of our life, and Burning Man is a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sao Paulo shrouded in darkness as Amazon rainforest continues to burn...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/5789726/sao-paulo-darkness-amazon-wildfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Global News meteorologist Ross Hull, a few factors came together at "just the right moment" to place Sao Paulo under a shroud of darkness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana hailstorm slaughters 11,000 birds!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Montana-hailstorm-slaughters-11-000-birds-14366687.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of birds were killed on Aug. 11 when a destructive hailstorm lashed regions northwest of Billings, Montana. According to Montana Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, the supercell thunderstorm "killed and maimed more than 11,000 waterfowl and wetland birds at the Big Lake Wildlife Management Area west of Molt." Molt is about 20 miles west-northwest of Billings, Montana's largest city.  According to the release, biologist Justin Paugh estimates that roughly a quarter of the birds at the lake were injured or killed. About 5% of surviving ducks and a third of living pelicans/cormorants "show some sign of injury or impaired movement."  The Storm Prediction Center had already been calling for potential large, damaging hail as early as 12 hours in advance, outlining Billings in a narrow corridor of "significant severe" potential. Their morning bulletin advised that volatile atmospheric parameters would "favor supercells initially with large hail and possibly a couple of tornadoes." By late afternoon, storms had developed, quickly becoming severe. Some storms towered to nearly 10 miles high.  The National Weather Service issued a severe thunderstorm warning for Molt at 6:27 p.m., alerting of the potential for golf ball-sized hail and damaging wind gusts in excess of 60 mph. The storm proved to be an overachiever, bringing an unusual August episode of three-inch hail and winds gusting up to 74 mph.  "This isn't uncommon for us, but it normally happens in June," explained Shawn Palmquist, a meteorologist at the National Weather Service in Billings. "June is when we have lower freezing levels and can get hail. August is typically more a wind month."  "We only had a high of 82 degrees at Billings Airport last Sunday," said Palmquist. "That was six degrees below normal, knocking freezing levels down just a bit. We also had above...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENDLESS WAR: Combat Death Toll in Afghanistan Highest in Five Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/patrick-goodenough/2019-us-combat-death-toll-afghanistan-rises-14-highest-annual-figure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Photo by Mark Wilson/Getty Images)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphones leaking more radiation than safety limits?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/smartphones-may-be-leaking-out-more-radiation-than-we-think/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An investigation by the Chicago Tribune suggests iPhones and Galaxy models may exceed radio frequency radiation safety limits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline running 19-hour test flights to see how impacts people's health...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/22/qantas-to-run-19-hour-test-flights-to-see-impact-on-peoples-health.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qantas on Thursday said it's going to run "research" flights from London and New York to Sydney to see how it affects passengers' health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid 'commands' Russian rocket test flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/humanoid-robot-passenger-russians-launch-key-rocket-test-flight-skybot-f-850-fedor/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The humanoid robot is known as Skybot F-850 and as FEDOR; the test flight was needed to clear an upgraded Soyuz booster to launch human crews to the space station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSWEEK: Time to Rethink Taboo on Cannibalism?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/08/22/newsweek-time-to-rethink-taboo-on-cannibalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perhaps it is time for humans to rethink the “ultimate taboo” against eating human flesh, Newsweek proposes in an article Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON, MICROSOFT 'putting world at risk of killer AI'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amazon-microsoft-may-putting-world-risk-killer-ai-224436302.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, Microsoft and Intel are among leading tech companies putting the world at risk through killer robot development, according to a report that surveyed major players from the sector about their stance on lethal autonomous weapons. "Why are companies like Microsoft and Amazon not denying that</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
