<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vaxxer Goes to Homeless Shelter to Pay Someone For Fake Status...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyvn3w/anti-vaxxer-went-to-homeless-shelter-to-try-to-pay-someone-for-fake-vaccine-status</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating the incident at a homeless shelter in northern Alberta. The incident occurred two days after the province announced vaccine passports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going to Make Rich Pay,' Manchin Tells Protesters From His Yacht...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kvgxe/were-going-to-make-the-rich-pay-joe-manchin-tells-protesters-from-his-yacht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists kayaked to Senator Joe Manchin's $700,000 yacht to ask why he wouldn't support the infrastructure bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces fractious Dems with agenda on line...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/01/house-democrats-biden-infrastructure-deal-514878</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi repeated her mantra that Democrats are “on a path” to pass the infrastructure bill Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema Skips Town for 'Medical Appointment', Fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/574941-sinema-in-arizona-as-democrats-try-to-get-spending-infrastructure-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Bezos Being Knocked Back Down to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/jeff-bezos-is-being-knocked-back-down-to-earth/ar-AAP328N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a summer of flying high, the space billionaire is facing a chaotic moment at his rocket company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER antibodies gone by 7 months for many...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001194329-xkwip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SCIENCE (GRAPHIC):COVID SCIENCE-Delta increases COVID-19 risks for pregnant women; Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine antibodies gone by 7 months for many</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV station has 'No News Monday' so staff can attend trauma, stress management seminar...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/entertainment/2021/09/portlands-katu-has-no-news-monday-so-staff-can-attend-trauma-and-stress-management-seminar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an unusual move, Portland's KATU-TV preempted morning and afternoon news shows so the staff could attend a seminar designed to help deal with job-related trauma and stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why this woman becoming world's most dangerous...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/leaders/kim-yojong-the-powerful-sister-of-north-korean-dictator-kim-jongun-on-track-to-become-worlds-most-dangerous-woman/news-story/70bf32c7f581b2ab577227ea84911e4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not too long ago, even the most devoted watchers of North Korean politics knew little to nothing about Kim Yo-jong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN WAR GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001155142-62r2v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-AZERBAIJAN/WARGAMES:Iran holds border war games amid tense relations with Azerbaijan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Union Boss Says 60K Members 'Deserve Respect' As Strike Ballot Voting Begins...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/iatse-srike-authorization-ballots-sent-out-network-studios-labor-1234848042/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The countdown has officially started this morning in what could be one of the largest labor actions in Hollywood history. Tens of thousands of IATSE members woke up early Friday or were …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers stole crypto from 6,000 COINBASE customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/coinbase-says-hackers-stole-cryptocurrency-least-6000-customers-2021-10-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers stole from the accounts of at least 6,000 customers of Coinbase Global Inc , according to a breach notification letter sent by the cryptocurrency exchange to affected customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Steps Up Taiwan Flybys as 38 Warplanes Enter Defense Zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-steps-up-taiwan-flybys-as-38-warplanes-enter-defense-zone/ar-AAP2QT7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese warplanes made multiple incursions close to Taiwan Friday in the second major display of military might in two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly Priest Shot With Paintball Gun In Church Parking Lot Over Funeral Parking Spat...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/09/30/priest-paintball-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baffert's Last Stand:  Horse racing's most successful, embattled trainer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/the-last-stand-of-bob-baffert-horse-racings-most-successful-and-embattled-trainer/ar-AAP28HQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Baffert has cultivated the story of a horse racing dynasty built from humble roots. He now faces scrutiny about short cuts he's alleged to have taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissension among Supremes as justices take anger public...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/01/politics/supreme-court-unhappy-justices/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court justices have revealed a new level of defensiveness and anger in recent weeks, showing irritation with public expectations, the news media and one another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Hosts First Royal Wedding Since Bolshevik Revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-romanov-royal-wedding/31488187.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rferl.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has held its first royal wedding since the 1917 Bolshevik Revolution toppled the Romanov monarchy, with royals from across Europe attending the lavish ceremony in the city of St. Petersburg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private jet rage grows; Record fliers strain system...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/private-jet-rage-grows-as-a-record-number-of-fliers-strain-the-system.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private jet fliers are facing increasing delays and cancellations as the industry struggles to serve a record number of new fliers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Robertson steps down as '700 Club' host after 60 years...</title>
      <link>https://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/2021/september/pat-robertson-steps-down-as-daily-host-of-the-700-club-after-60-years-of-history-making-tv-ministry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBN Founder Pat Robertson, America's longest-running TV host, is stepping down from his role as daily host of The 700 Club. "'Good and faithful' doesn't even begin to describe my father's service to CBN for 60 years," says CBN CEO Gordon Robertson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bible archaeologists find Mount Sinai where 'God handed Moses the Ten Commandments'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3774807/bible-archaeologists-mount-sinai-god-moses-commandments-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIBLICAL archaeologists have claimed to have located the holy mountain where the Bible says God gave Moses two stone tablets inscribed with the Ten Commandments. They believe features and archaeolo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's death pinned on cougar attack; Wildlife experts say no way...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/agriculture/nobody-will-tell-me-the-truth-man-s-death-pinned-on-cougar-attack-wildlife-experts/article_6f30de57-9c05-5bde-99ca-fb2e20582471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS — With a mountain lion skull tucked safely under his arm, Mike Bodenchuk walked more than a mile across downtown Fort Worth to the medical examiner’s office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to Build Specialized Quarantine Hubs for Travelers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-is-building-a-chain-of-giant-covid-quarantine-centers/ar-AAP2sWd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is asking city governments to create specialized quarantine facilities that can house thousands of overseas arrivals, as the country continues to take a zero-tolerance approach to keeping out Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of NEIMAN MARCUS Customers Exposed In Cyber Breach...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/01/neiman-marcus-cybersecurity-4-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Neiman Marcus Group customers are being alerted that their online accounts -- including very sensitive information -- may have been breached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican cartel thugs line up and execute 20 rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3772973/mexico-cartel-line-up-execute-20-rivals-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISTURBING video shows Mexican cartel hitmen lining up 20 rival gangsters in a forest before executing them one by one. It was released as a warning on social media by Los Tlacos, who claimed they …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER MOB TURNS ON ROBINHOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/newsletters/protocol-fintech/robinhood-florida-lawsuits </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Bonkers Revelations in Stephanie Grisham's Tell All...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/7-most-bonkers-revelations-about-the-trump-white-house-in-stephanie-grishams-book-clown-car-on-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Grisham's new book details the behind-the-scenes disarray in the Trump White House, which she reveals in an excerpt published in Politico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For first time ever, ocean drone sent into eye of Cat 4 hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/drone-mission-to-the-eye-of-hurricane-sam/1026104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sea drone traveled "where no research vessel has ever ventured" when it entered the eye of Hurricane Sam, and the groundbreaking mission has the potential to alter scientists' understanding of hurricanes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Stagehands Begin Strike Vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-pressure-hollywood-producers-negotiate-021501920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Adam B. Schiff and Sens. Charles E. Schumer and Bernie Sanders wade into Hollywood's biggest labor fight, telling AMPTP to negotiate with IATSE crews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Backs Down! House Of Mouse Settles Streaming Lawsuit With Johansson...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/09/disney-black-widow-lawsuit-scarlett-johansson-rsettlement-1234847437/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with more details: Just days after the first court hearing in Scarlett Johansson’s Black Widow profits mega-bite lawsuit on Disney was pushed back to March 2022, the Oscar nominee and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion mogul Nygard consents to extradition to USA on sex trafficking charges...</title>
      <link>https://winnipeg.ctvnews.ca/peter-nygard-consents-to-extradition-to-united-states-1.5607086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;winnipeg.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former fashion mogul Peter Nygard has consented to being extradited to the United States to face charges including sex trafficking and racketeering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing historic challenge, Florida Dems stumble against DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facing-a-historic-challenge-Florida-Democrats-16501880.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. - To Kelly Smith, the case against Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Jet Market Grapples With Surge in Get-Me-Away Demand...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/private-jet-market-grapples-with-surge-in-get-me-away-demand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even people who can normally afford to charter a private jet at a moment’s notice are being forced to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphone Sensor Can Detect If High...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smartphone-high-on-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new AI system detects marijuana intoxication by examining smartphone user behavior before and after using cannabis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadband firm sues NETFLIX after traffic surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/skorea-broadband-firm-sues-netflix-after-traffic-surge-squid-game-2021-10-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korean Internet service provider SK Broadband has sued Netflix to pay for costs from increased network traffic and maintenance work because of a surge of viewers to the U.S. firm's content, an SK spokesperson said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority of Trump Voters Now in Favor of Seceding...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/shock-poll-majority-of-trump-voters-now-in-favor-of-seceding-from-the-union/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shocking new poll reveals that over half of Trump voters polled, and 41% of Biden voters, are in favor of blue and/or red states seceding from the union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation Gauge Highest Since '91 as Americans Spend More...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inflation-gauge-hits-highest-since-125743783.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. personal spending growth accelerated by more than forecast in August, driven by goods purchases, while a closely watched measure of inflation exceeded estimates. Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsAn Unapologetic Old Boys’ Network Is Costing Australia BillionsThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtHSBC Bets Big on China as Pressure Mounts in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador mining bitcoin using energy from volcanoes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/01/el-salvador-just-started-mining-bitcoin-with-volcanoes-for-the-first-time-ever-and-theyve-already-made-269.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;El Salvador has mined 0.00599179 bitcoin, or about $269, with power harnessed from a volcano, in a first for the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta's Wealthiest, Whitest District Wants to Secede...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-10-01/buckhead-cityhood-vote-district-wants-to-secede-from-atlanta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some residents are pushing to make Buckhead its own city, the latest in a series of political ruptures by race and class across the metro area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last stand of Bob Baffert, horse racing's most successful and embattled trainer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/last-stand-bob-baffert-horse-103046549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Baffert has cultivated the story of a horse racing dynasty built from humble roots. He now faces scrutiny about short cuts he's alleged to have taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million bolivars become one as Venezuela recalibrates battered currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211001-a-million-bolivars-become-one-as-venezuela-recalibrates-battered-currency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A million bolivars become one as Venezuela recalibrates battered currency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man invited people into motel room. Then sacrificed them and set them on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/A-Texas-man-invited-people-into-his-motel-room-16501500.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside of the Mid City Inn in Euless, Texas, Jason Alan Thornburg was often seen reading...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-food chains close indoor seating as cities mandate jab checks...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211001095910-p0smd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RESTAURANTS/VACCINES (PIX):Fast-food chains close some indoor seating as U.S. cities mandate vaccine checks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's most restrictive abortion law back in Texas court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-austin-texas-courts-lawsuits-a7961b629e913e1008f8e929c99fb310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — A federal judge on Friday will consider whether Texas can leave in place the most restrictive abortion law in the U.S., which since September has banned most abortions and sent women racing to get care beyond the borders of the nation's second-most populous state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can RNA Be Altered? Scientists Could Bend Strands Into Circles to Treat Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-10-01/can-rna-be-altered-scientists-could-bend-strands-into-circles-to-treat-cancer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors flock to biotech startup Orna Therapeutics on the promise of low-cost treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon's 300% Surge Throws Another Price Shock at World...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/silicon-300-surge-throws-another-032657665.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A metal made from the second-most abundant element on Earth has become scarce, threatening everything from car parts to computer chips and throwing up another hurdle for the world economy.Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsAn Unapologetic Old Boys’ Network Is Costing Australia BillionsThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued by Fire, Frost and DroughtHSBC Bets Big on China a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PWC will allow ALL employees to work virtually, live anywhere they want...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/exclusive-pwc-tells-us-employees-they-need-never-return-office-2021-09-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accounting and consulting firm PwC told Reuters on Thursday it will allow all its 40,000 U.S. client services employees to work virtually and live anywhere they want in perpetuity, making it one of the biggest employers to embrace permanent remote work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Wants Greenland's Minerals. Greenlanders Wary...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/the-world-wants-greenlands-minerals-but-greenlanders-are-wary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NARSAQ, Greenland — This huge, remote and barely habited island is known for frozen landscapes, remote fjords and glaciers that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange Allure of Pool-Cleaning Videos...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/the-strange-allure-of-pool-cleaning-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some TikTok creators have become successful on the video platform by dancing, singing or performing everyday tasks. Miles Laflin has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Parisians Are Over FOGO...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/the-parisians-are-over-fogo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — On a recent sunny afternoon, a cluster of young women in short dresses and high boots crowded into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock, Bond, Real Estate Prices All Uncomfortably High...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/stock-bond-and-real-estate-prices-are-all-uncomfortably-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prices of stocks, bonds and real estate, the three major asset classes in the United States, are all extremely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Rape Accusations, Fraternities Face Protests and Growing Anger...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/01/after-rape-accusations-fraternities-face-protests-and-growing-anger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the University of Nebraska-Lincoln, hundreds of students protested outside a fraternity house in August after a student reported a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Month Later, Five Zebras Still on Run in Maryland...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/30/a-month-later-five-zebras-are-still-on-the-run-in-maryland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re still out there, roaming free. A month after they escaped from a farm in Maryland, five zebras have evaded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Afghans leaving U.S. military bases before resettlement...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/exclusive-giant-can-worms-some-afghans-leave-us-military-bases-before-2021-10-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something unexpected is happening at U.S. military bases hosting Afghan evacuees: Many hundreds of them are simply leaving before receiving U.S. resettlement services, two sources familiar with the data told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson, DISNEY Settle Explosive 'BLACK WIDOW' Suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/scarlett-johansson-disney-settle-black-widow-lawsuit-1235022598/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The settlement ends a back-and-forth PR battle pitting the CAA-repped star against the studio that was poised to have dramatic implications for all of Hollywood’s majors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Brazil election run-up, US-style Big Lie not ruled out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-election-run-us-style-012907270.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leftist former president Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva is the favorite in Brazil's elections one year from now but surprises along the way are not ruled out -- not even a dramatic US-style finale with charges of a rigged result.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flag-wearing man throws Molotov cocktail into Austin Dems HQ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-austin-texas-0d88e008e385feb7001be133f19c11c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — An arson investigation was underway after a man wearing an American flag bandanna threw a Molotov cocktail into the headquarters of the county Democratic Party in Austin. The incendiary device did not ignite when it was thrown at the Travis County Democratic Party headquarters at about 2 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne covid cases hit record DESPITE two months of lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australias-victoria-reports-record-new-covid-19-cases-2021-09-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melbourne's COVID-19 cases surged to record levels on Thursday with officials blaming illegal home gatherings to watch a key sporting event for the spike as a hard lockdown to combat the spread of the Delta variant neared two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Uprecedented efforts to intimidate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/justice-alito-says-the-supreme-court-didn-t-nullify-roe-v-wade-in-texas-abortion-decision-this-portrayal-feeds-unprecedented-efforts-to-intimidate-the-court/ar-AAP0PQi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The justice also said that recent claims about the court's decision-making are "false and inflammatory."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIEW TO A CHILL:  WILL AUDIENCES FLOCK TO BOND?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/the-new-james-bond-film-aims-to-steady-a-shaken-industry-but-no-one-seems-to-know-what-will-leave-audiences-stirred/ar-AAP0DRo?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As "No Time to Die" opens, the era of major movies debuting exclusively in theaters is finally back. But which genres can actually entice consumers is vexing Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ridley Scott, 83, Plans 'GLADIATOR' Sequel  After Napoleon!</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/sopranos-fever-sweeps-the-youth-pitt-clooney-reunion-ridley-scotts-new-gladiator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Bond suggestions; the Many Saints of Newark meaning; kids today love The Sopranos; Brad Pitt and George Clooney face off; Ridley Scott is planning a Gladiator sequel. All in today’s Movie News Rundown. But First: This short bonus episode of The Industry podcast looks at one man’s quest to fix Superman IV. It’s on Spotify and Apple and […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California returns land to descendants of original Black owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-09-30/newsom-signs-law-to-return-bruces-beach-black-family</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom authorizes returning the land known as Bruce's Beach to the descendants of a Black couple that had been run out of Manhattan Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major flea infestation shuts 2 Oakland schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/major-flea-infestation-shuts-2-oakland-schools</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two elementary schools in Oakland will be closed for the rest of the week due to an infestation of fleas that may have been caused by raccoons in the area, school officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oldest man who ever lived' dies at 127...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/oldest-man-who-ever-lived-25112382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Natabay Tinsiew, who claimed to have been born in 1894, passed away in his remote village of Azefa on Monday as his family look for him to be officially recognised by the organisation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN PUSHES ELIMINATION OF DEBT CEILING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/30/yellen-lends-support-for-effort-to-remove-the-debt-ceiling-altogether.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said Thursday she would just as soon see the power over debt limits taken away from Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS To Slow Mail Delivery Beginning Friday; 'Will Be Slower Than In 1970s'; 'Disastrous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mail-delivery-slower-usps-october-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Postmaster General Louis DeJoy's 10-year plan is aimed at cutting costs. Critics call it "disastrous."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem civil war hits new heights...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/574814-democratic-civil-war-hits-new-heights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats engaged in a verbal war on Thursday, with progressives and centrists accusing one another of essentially sabotaging President Biden’s agenda and putting the party’s majorities in jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST LOOK: Scheindlin Returns to Courtroom In Trailer for New 'JUDY JUSTICE'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/reality-tv/news/judge-judy-scheindlin-returns-courtroom-trailer-new-show-judy-justice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Judy Scheindlin is back in the courtroom for the first look trailer at her upcoming [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIP-HOP HALFTIME FOR SUPER BOWL 2022...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/30/super-bowl-2022-halftime-performers-announced/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for the most stacked Super Bowl halftime performers lineup of all time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Month for Stocks Ends With Few Signs the Drama Is Over...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bad-month-stocks-ends-few-202428322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The end of the September in the stock market was a time of volatility, accelerated hedging and economic unease. It did not, however, spur an extreme reordering in trader sentiment, and to some of Wall Street’s old guard that’s worrisome.Most Read from BloombergWall Street Titans Warn of the Next Big Risks for InvestorsAn Unapologetic Old Boys’ Network Is Costing Australia BillionsThe Unstoppable Appeal of Highway ExpansionThe Country That Makes Breakfast for the World Is Plagued b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKHEED refuses  comment on video exposing mystery craft on secret testing base...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/09/30/lockheed-martin-skunk-works-chief-skunk-jeff-babione-national-defence-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockheed Martin Senior Executive Refuses To Comment On Odd-Shaped Aircraft That Surfaced In TikTok Video At Apparent Skunk Works Facility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Biden rules would limit arrest, deportation of migrants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-donald-trump-joe-biden-mexico-arrests-af64610730b9c603b592101e4a7ddfa8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing bipartisan criticism over its approach to immigration, the Biden administration on Thursday announced new rules that require authorities to only pursue migrants who recently crossed into the country without permission or are deemed to pose a threat to public safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman arrested for felony grits attack...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/grits-attack-arrest-908572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 30--A Florida Woman is behind bars for allegedly striking her boyfriend in the head with a sauce pan “containing freshly cooked grits,” according to a felony complaint. Investigators say De</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
