<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Construction workers 'lose' sensitive docs during renovations at UK spy HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/27/uk/mi6-headquarters-sensitive-documents-renovations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A source on background has confirmed to CNN that sensitive documents that had been reported missing by The Sun newspaper were not UK government papers, but were a construction firm's documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACHETE WIELDING MAN ATTACKS NY HANUKKAH PARTY</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/12/28/stabbing-monsey-synagogue-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS2’s Tony Aiello has confirmed a man entered Rabbi Rottenburg's Shul in Monsey and stabbed three people Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is 'Dixie Highway' racist? The debate is growing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/hallandale/fl-ne-dixie-highway-rename-effort-20191227-iuj3mdirozbcdnhit5y33medwy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal to rename Dixie Highway — for some a painful reminder of slavery — might be gaining steam in Broward County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Unions Keep Pressure on Macron With New Round of Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/french-unions-keep-pressure-on-macron-with-new-round-of-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French Unions Keep Pressure on Macron With New Round of Protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKOUTS, PURGES...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2019/12/28/un-moves-towards-handing-dictatorships-power-to-control-the-internet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legitimizing web blackouts and free speech censorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop sucker punched, wrestled to ground in Brooklyn...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/28/man-sucker-punches-wrestles-nypd-cop-to-the-ground-in-brooklyn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A deranged man sucker-punched an NYPD officer on a Brooklyn sidewalk, pinning the cop to the ground and refusing to budge, body camera footage obtained by The Post shows. The wild video shows Steve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhino believed to be 'world's oldest' dies aged 57...</title>
      <link>http://www.china.org.cn/world/Off_the_Wire/2019-12/29/content_75558801.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.china.org.cn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing blowback, Biden clarifies stance on impeachment trial testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden-subpoena/facing-blowback-biden-clarifies-stance-on-impeachment-trial-testimony-idUSKBN1YW0BM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Democratic presidential contender Joe Biden on Saturday said there would be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Baltimore needs Lamar Jackson-like figure to save it...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/475839-baltimore-needs-Lamar-Jackson-like-figure-to-save-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ravens quarterback has demonstrated values that could save Baltimore if put into practice by someone with strength, integrity and conviction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUNDAY SHOWDOWN: Garoppolo faces Seattle crowd noise for 1st time...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/garoppolo-must-deal-seattle-crowd-noise-1st-time-000754338--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday’s game against the Seahawks in Seattle will be the biggest test of Jimmy Garoppolo’s career. Since 2010, QBs with 25 or fewer career starts have won just six of 28 games in Seattle. If the 49ers lose on Sunday, they’ll be a wild-card team and start their quest for the Super Bowl on the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nothing Less Than Civil War': These Voters See Doom Without Trump...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/12/28/nothing-less-than-a-civil-war-these-white-voters-on-the-far-right-see-doom-without-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOLDEN VALLEY, Ariz. — Great American Pizza &amp;amp; Subs, on a highway about 100 miles southeast of Las Vegas, was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK publishes celebrity home addresses by mistake...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/166344fbc59238cbe55ca1ad79736bac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British officials have apologized after mistakenly publishing the home addresses of more than 1,000 people who received special honors including singers Elton John and Olivia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO: Man scales 30-foot border wall -- in 23 seconds!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/shock-video-man-scales-30-foot-border-wall-in-23-seconds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A real-life Spiderman lives in Mexico. A migrant scaled a new 30-foot section of the border wall with relative ease recently. Watch: This video is sickening. Democrats have decriminalized illegal immigration and instead reward &amp; incentivize it, This only encourages more… If you give a🐁 a cookie 🍪…#DemocratsAreDestroyingAmerica #NOAmnesty#BuildTheWall @realDonaldTrump pic.twitter.com/8CG56FMSpi — 💄ɳαɳ૮ყ ن🇺🇸#KAG (@LVNancy) …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIACHINA-BACKED INTERNET RESOLUTION ALARMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/united-states-canada/article/3043763/un-approves-russian-sponsored-china-backed-bid-new</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The resolution was approved on Friday by the general assembly by a vote of 79-60, with 33 abstentions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi gets under Trump's skin...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/476068-pelosi-gets-under-trumps-skin-on-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has made attacking House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) a theme of his holiday break at his Mar-a-Lago resort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACE RACE: NASA rover to prepare humans for Red Planet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mars-2020-rover-seek-ancient-life-prepare-human-011711939.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mars 2020 rover, which sets off for the Red Planet next year, will not only search for traces of ancient life, but pave the way for future human missions, NASA scientists said Friday as they unveiled the vehicle. The rover has been constructed in a large, sterile room at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even amid affluence of tech capital, local news struggles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/45daa649c4a54db431635c7fdc640778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — The cities and suburbs on the eastern side of San Francisco Bay are home to 2.7 million people, a world-class University of California campus and bedroom communities for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says he would not comply with subpoena in impeachment trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2019/12/27/joe-biden-would-not-comply-senate-subpoena-trump-impeachment/2759398001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden said any attempt to force his testimony on impeachment would be 'specious' and an attempt to take focus away from President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged abuse victim accused of killing priest by ramming crucifix down his throat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/28/alleged-abuse-victim-accused-of-killing-priest-by-ramming-crucifix-down-his-throat-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teenager in northern France is accused of killing a priest who allegedly abused him — by ramming a crucifix down the cleric’s throat. Roger Matassoli, 91, had been accused of molesting at l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Beaten to Death for $1 -- No One Stops to Help...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/man-seen-on-video-beaten-in-bronx-for-1-and-no-one-stops-to-help/2250599/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was viciously beaten as he left a Bronx McDonald’s in a violent robbery attempt caught on camera over $1 — and no one stopped to help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake-like UFOs seen across eight states...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/snake-like-ufos-seen-across-21135639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The conspiracy world has been sent into a frenzy this year from numerous videos of snake-like UFOs hovering over the US. A researcher has now told this site that more will be seen in 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood producers recruited at sex robot factory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-giant-hires-hollywood-21174152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: RealDoll told Daily Star Online that it is employing people who have previously made movies at the iconic US studios to manufacture human-like dolls powered by artificial intelligence (AI)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Investigating 9th Anti-Semitic Attack This Week...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/12/28/rash-of-anti-semitic-attacks-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is putting up more patrols around Hasidic neighborhoods in response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restrict online freedom?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/un-backs-russia-internet-convention-alarming-rights-advocates-011310327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Nations on Friday approved a Russian-led bid that aims to create a new convention on cybercrime, alarming rights groups and Western powers that fear a bid to restrict online freedom. The General Assembly approved the resolution sponsored by Russia and backed by China, which would set up a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa stock rally slays records...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/recession-everyone-scared-just-got-120000465.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Should American investors, $6 trillion richer after the stock market’s best year in six, take shelter now, convinced a reckoning is at hand and the good times won’t last? As far as earnings, the economy and equities themselves are concerned, the answer is no.Or at least, not necessarily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots and VR: Digitalization changing our sexuality...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesundaily.my/home/sex-robots-and-vr-here-s-how-digitalisation-is-changing-our-sexuality-JB1829649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesundaily.my&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEX as we know it is about to change. We are already living through a new sexual revolution, thanks to technologies that have transformed the way we r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nine people shot, two fatally, in music video 'ambush'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/local/article/2-killed-7-injured-in-drive-by-ambush-14935856.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were shot and killed and seven others injured in a drive-by shooting while they were filming a music video near Houston, Harris County Sheriff Ed Gonzalez said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fleet of 30?</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/2019/12/27/mysterious-drones-spotted-in-4-colorado-counties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON COUNTY, Colo.  --Law enforcement officials in at least 4 Colorado counties are looking for the source of some mysterious drone sightings. Sheriffs in Phillips, Lincoln, Yuma, and Washington Counties all confirm unusual sightings over the past week. In most cases, those drones have been flying in formations, between 6-10 P.M., according to Washington County Sheriff Jon Stivers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
