<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Anti-abortion activist scales 60-floor SALESFORCE tower...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktvu.com/news/video-anti-abortion-activist-scales-60-floor-san-francisco-salesforce-tower</link>
      <description>ktvu.com ― An anti-abortion activist was seen scaling the 60-floor Salesforce tower in San Francisco on Tuesday morning, a wild scene captured on video by some awe-struck admirers. His actions were condemned by police and firefighters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC restates recommendation for masks on planes, trains...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-science-travel-health-business-3b819aa097b4e642a97d39f606924203</link>
      <description>apnews.com ― NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. health officials on Tuesday restated their recommendation that Americans wear masks on planes, trains and buses, despite a court ruling last month that struck down a national mask mandate on public transportation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalization may affect thinking similar to 20 years of aging...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2022/may/03/covid-hospitalisation-thinking-ageing-cognitive-decline-illness</link>
      <description>theguardian.com ― Some people experience lingering cognitive decline, with degree of impairment linked to illness severity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild fox kills 25 flamingos, duck at National Zoo...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2022/05/heartbreaking-wild-fox-kills-25-flamingos-1-duck-at-national-zoo/</link>
      <description>wtop.com ― A wild fox broke into the National Zoo’s flamingo enclosure, killing 25 flamingoes and a duck in D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINTER IN MAY!  15 inches of snow coats Nebraska...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/early-may-snow-makes-spring-look-like-middle-of-winter-in-nebraska/1181510</link>
      <description>accuweather.com ― Portions of interstates were shut down and numerous traffic accidents were reported amid a blast of winter weather on the second day of May in the Nebraska Panhandle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Number Of Americans Quit Jobs; Openings Surpass Unemployed By 5.6 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/record-number-americans-just-quit-their-job-job-openings-surpass-unemployed-workers-0</link>
      <description>zerohedge.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Tracked Millions of Phones to See If Americans Followed Lockdown Orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7vymn/cdc-tracked-phones-location-data-curfews</link>
      <description>vice.com ― Newly released documents showed the CDC planned to use phone location data to monitor schools and churches, and wanted to use the data for many non-COVID-19 purposes too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid  Infection Can Age Brain By 20 Years, Lower IQ Significantly...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/covid-19-infection-could-age-brain-by-20-years-lower-iq-significantly/</link>
      <description>braintomorrow.com ― A severe coronavirus infection could leave patients with the brain of a 70-year-old, lowering someone’s IQ by 10 points, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINTER IN MAY!  15 inches of snow coats Nebraska...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/ en/weather-news/early-may- snow-makes-spring-look-like- middle-of-winter-in-nebraska/ 1181510</link>
      <description>accuweather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study into mRNA vaccine death rates sends 'danger signals'...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/study-into-mrna/</link>
      <description>unherd.com ― Do the covid vaccines save lives? That is the question on many people’s minds, that has led to heated discussions across the world. A bombshell new study by a distinguished team of Danish researchers led by Prof. Christine Stabell-Benn suggests a surprisingly nuanced answer. In the randomized trials of the covid vaccines, the adenovector-based vaccines, [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ways Tuesday's primaries could shake 2022 election...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/05/03/2022-primary-elections-ohio-indiana-00029491</link>
      <description>politico.com ― Voters in Ohio and Indiana will nominate candidates in a key Senate race and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killings in LA on pace to top last year's high...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/killings-l-pace-top-last-120048055.html</link>
      <description>news.yahoo.com ― People are being killed in Los Angeles in 2022 at near the same elevated rate as last year, when homicides hit a 15-year high, according to LAPD data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY Refuses Chinese Demand to Scrub Statue of Liberty From 'SPIDER-MAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/sony-reportedly-refused-chinese-governments-demand-to-scrub-statue-of-liberty-from-latest-spider-man-film/</link>
      <description>mediaite.com ― Sony reportedly refused the Chinese government’s demand to scrub the Statue of Liberty from Spider-Man: No Way Home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America flexes maritime muscles; Tests 2,000-pound 'quicksink' bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10778291/US-Air-Force-successfully-tests-2-000-pound-air-launched-quicksink-bomb-sinks-cargo-ship.html</link>
      <description>dailymail.co.uk ― The US Air Force tested the munitions against a cargo ship in the Gulf of Mexico, breaking it in half and sinking it. An F-15E Strike Eagle fighter launched the modified bomb, striking the target,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Direction Your Bed Faces Could Be Making Sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/direction-bed-making-you-sick/</link>
      <description>studyfinds.org ― Maharishi Vastu architecture is a holistic wellness architectural system which aligns buildings with nature’s intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado River Reservoirs So Low, Govt Delaying Releases...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/05/03/colorado-river-reservoirs-are-so-low-government-is-delaying-releases/</link>
      <description>dnyuz.com ― With long-term severe drought continuing to take a toll on the Colorado River, the federal government is expected to announce</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy City or Theme Park? Israel Plans Zip Line for Ancient Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/05/03/holy-city-or-theme-park-israel-plans-zip-line-for-ancient-jerusalem/</link>
      <description>dnyuz.com ― JERUSALEM — A picturesque ridge in Jerusalem, steeped in ancient history, is a favorite with visitors who come to snap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Energy Price Spike: Electric Bills...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/05/03/get-ready-for-another-energy-price-spike-high-electric-bills/</link>
      <description>dnyuz.com ― Already frustrated and angry about high gasoline prices, many Americans are being hit by rapidly rising electricity bills, compounding inflation’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy City or Theme Park? Israel Plans Zip Line for Ancient Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/05/03/world/middleeast/israel-jerusalem-zip-line.html</link>
      <description>nytimes.com ― A Jewish settler group is promoting projects that opponents say will change the delicate historic, religious and political balance in highly symbolic areas around Jerusalem’s Old City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flawed math behind Musk's TWITTER deal?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/the-flawed-math-behind-elon-musk-e2-80-99s-twitter-deal/ar-AAWPSy9</link>
      <description>msn.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Don't Have Business Plan': Elon Musk Wings It...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/tech-news-technology/i-dont-really-have-a-business-plan-how-elon-musk-wings-it-7899121/</link>
      <description>indianexpress.com ― While Musk has successfully bet on electric cars, space travel and artificial intelligence, he often wings it in the biggest moments, eschews experts and relies almost solely on his own counsel, they said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ready for Another Energy Price Spike: Electric Bills...</title>
      <link>https://globalonlinemony.com/high-electric-bills-get-ready-for-another-energy-price-spike-high-electric-bills/</link>
      <description>globalonlinemony.com ― In Oregon, for instance, electrical charges fell virtually 1.5 % in January and fewer than 1 % in February, although some corporations like Portland Common</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Relieved as China Appears to Heed Warnings...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-05-03/u-s-relieved-as-china-appears-to-heed-warnings-on-russia</link>
      <description>usnews.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Russia accuses Israel of supporting neo-Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10777715/Russia-accuses-ISRAEL-supporting-neo-Nazis-Sergei-Lavrov-claimed-Hitler-Jewish-blood.html</link>
      <description>dailymail.co.uk ― The Russian foreign ministry doubled down today and said Israel's criticism explained 'why the current Israeli government supports the neo-Nazi regime in Kyiv'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GILDED' GALA:  MASKED WORKER TENDS TO MASKLESS HILLARY...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2022/05/02/hillary-clinton-maskless-at-met-gala-as-masked-black-staffer-attends-her-gown/</link>
      <description>breitbart.com ― Former Democratic Party presidential nominee Hillary Clinton went maskless at the Met Gala as a masked black staffer attended her train.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope says he wants to meet Vlad in Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/pope-says-he-wants-to-meet-putin-in-moscow-01651566307</link>
      <description>barrons.com ― Pope Francis said in an interview published Tuesday that he requested a meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin over Ukraine, while comparing the scale of the bloodshed to Rwanda's genocide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST REPORTER FABRICATES 'DRUDGE REPORT' HARASSMENT; APOLOGIZES...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/oliverdarcy/status/1521346779018629125</link>
      <description>twitter.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  W. Bush to appear at fundraiser for Trump nemesis Kemp...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/05/02/george-w-bush-brian-kemp-event-trump-00029476</link>
      <description>politico.com ― Kemp has been sharply criticized by Trump for his resistance to the former president’s efforts to overturn the results of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accusations against Rep. Madison Cawthorn multiply...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/accusations-against-rep-madison-cawthorn-multiply/ar-AAWQh6m?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>msn.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100-year-old man runs 100 meter race!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/100-year-old-n-j-native-and-wwii-veteran-runs-in-penn-relays</link>
      <description>fox5ny.com ― A typical start to race and, just like that, 100-year-old Lester Wright was off to the races, running in the Penn Relays, bringing the 1,000s in attendance to their feet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden officials want Trump 'crazy' back on social...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/biden-officials-want-musk-to-bring-trumps-crazy-back-to-twitter-report</link>
      <description>washingtonexaminer.com ― White House officials are letting it be known that they desire Twitter to invite back former President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE 'GILDED' GALA...</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/slideshow/inside-the-met-gala-2022</link>
      <description>vogue.com ― Photographers Hunter Abrams and Flo Ngala roamed the Metropolitan Museum of Art throughout the night, capturing all the candid moments and iconic fashion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Win Next War, Pentagon Needs Nerds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/to-win-the-next-war-the-pentagon-needs-nerds/</link>
      <description>wired.com ― Data scientists, coders, and other techies could prove decisive in future conflicts—if Uncle Sam can recruit them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Podcast Venture Comes To Abrupt End...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/facebooks-podcast-venture-comes-to-a-abrupt-end-one-year-after-launch/</link>
      <description>mediaite.com ― Just one year after launching their podcasting venture, Facebook will be closing the doors to their audio hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California population falls for 2nd year in row...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-lost-population-in-2021-still-largest-17142047.php</link>
      <description>sfgate.com ― SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California's population shrank for the second year in a row...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHALLENGES ON ALL FRONTS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/six-months-before-crucial-midterms-biden-faces-many-challenges/ar-AAWPdNJ</link>
      <description>msn.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latinos discriminated against by other Latinos just as much as others...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/05/02/us/discrimination-latinos-pew-research-report/index.html</link>
      <description>cnn.com ― Latinos in the United States with darker skin are experiencing discrimination from fellow Latinos and from non-Latinos at nearly the same rate, a new poll from the Pew Research Center says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Naval Boats Sunk?</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/politics/news/ukraine-says-it-sank-two-russian-naval-boats-as-new-blasts-hit-russian-border-city-11651493101955.html</link>
      <description>livemint.com ― Fighting for Eastern Ukraine’s Donbas region rages on as Europe debates the consequences of the war on its energy supplies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  VICE looking to sell...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/05/02/vice-media-hires-financial-advisors-to-seek-buyer-may-sell-itself-in-pieces.html</link>
      <description>cnbc.com ― Vice is considering selling itself outright or in pieces after failing to go public last year, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking to tie up less of his wealth in deal...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-musk-talks-twitter-financing-182716769.html</link>
      <description>finance.yahoo.com ― (Reuters) -Elon Musk is in talks with large investment firms and high net-worth individuals about taking on more financing for his $44 billion acquisition of Twitter Inc and tying up less of his wealth in the deal, people familiar with the matter said. Last week, Musk disclosed he sold $8.5 billion worth of Tesla stock following his agreement to buy Twitter. The new financing, which could come in the form of preferred or common equity, could reduce the $21 billion cash contribution that Musk has committed to the deal as well as a margin loan he secured against his Tesla shares, the sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400 troops dying a day...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-officers-shocked-putins-wild-26850180</link>
      <description>dailystar.co.uk ― Russian officers are reportedly in dismay at Vladimir Putin's wild plan to take the birthplace city of Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy in just over one week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton lunches at White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/former-president-bill-clinton-lunches-with-biden-at-the-white-house/ar-AAWQwf7</link>
      <description>msn.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body found in barrel in Lake Mead may date back to '80s...</title>
      <link>https://www.8newsnow.com/i-team/i-team-body-found-in-barrel-in-lake-mead-may-date-back-to-1980s-more-likely-to-appear-as-water-recedes-las-vegas-police-say/</link>
      <description>8newsnow.com ― The body found in a barrel at Lake Mead on Sunday may have been underwater for as long as four decades and more bodies are likely to appear as the lake recedes due to severe drought, Las Vegas poli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stalker claiming to be priest spends night in Windsor Castle barracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/18438925/queen-shock-security-blunder-windsor-castle/</link>
      <description>thesun.co.uk ― A STALKER claiming to be a priest was allowed into barracks by Royal Guardsman protecting the Queen in an astonishing security blunder, The Sun can reveal. Soldiers at Victoria Barracks, just yards…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thunderous Garth Brooks concert registers as earthquake...</title>
      <link>https://www.sunherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article260983772.html</link>
      <description>sunherald.com ― The crowd at LSU erupted when he sang a beloved song among Baton Rouge locals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey terrorizes D.C. residents, drawing blood and sowing fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-tom-turkey-terrorizes-washington-dc-residents-kenilworth-gardens-20220502-cj54tsp2irgctjp4v76pcbupve-story.html</link>
      <description>nydailynews.com ― A turkey is terrorizing D.C. residents, has crossed state boundaries into Maryland and is eluding five agencies from as many jurisdictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK VIDEO:  Illegal Drowns Attempting to Cross Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/shock-video-illegal-drowns-attempting-to-cross-rio-grande/</link>
      <description>infowars.com ― Graphic footage captured illegal alien from Nicaragua drowning in Rio Grande River while attempting unlawful entry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top general visits war front...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220502-russia-s-top-general-visited-ukraine-front-pentagon</link>
      <description>france24.com ― Russia's top general, Valery Gerasimov, visited the Donbas front in the Ukraine war last week, a Pentagon official said Monday, but reports that he was injured in a Ukrainian attack could not be confirmed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>